One cannot penetrate the labyrinth
by moving in a straight line.
THE OTHERWORLD
Here, in the south of France,
exists a web of
concentrated telluric energies.
A portal in Montségur,
Rennes-m-Chéteau and Bugarach.
Together they form a gateway
to the otherworld.
Seven centuries ago,
crusaders perpetuated a genocide
against the Occitan countries
and the Cathar faith.
In 1244, they besieged Montségur
where 210 martyrs
condemned by
the Church of Rome
died at the stake.
But their faith and occult science
didn't die with them.
MONTSEGUR - SUMMER SOLSTICE - 2012 AD
URANIE - sorcerer
It's that time of the year when
there's a sort of portal...
A gate that might open
onto a spiritual world.
And which allows
some people who so desire
to accomplish
a transmutation. It's alchemical.
And it's part of a system
that was adopted by
the Cathars and the Templars
from ancient prehistoric
and megalithic sites
designed to capture and channel
the different telluric
and cosmic energies.
And here in Montségur,
the castle is built according
to a certain geometric shape
according to siderial geography...
It's a sort of... How can I put this?
Sort of testament they left behind.
It's a tradition that goes
way back in time.
And that's the Cathar heritage.
The Cathar Grail that was
described by Otto Rahn:
is the geometric
form of the castle, the way it's built,
the way you make
your way around it...
It's the geometric symbolism
of the star system,
the pentagram: incarnation of the flesh
the hexagram: the union of
heaven and earth...
It's very symbolic and at the same time,
it's like radionics. Waves that form shapes.
The connection has been established
by people who supposedly had access to
the spiritual dimension
and whose mission it was to transmit that
knowledge over time.
And speaking of
those portals or gates,
they're still very much active.
Science and all that...
That's for trying to understand
how all this works,
so as to gain access
to other worlds, you see?
It's a place where obviously,
things happen to people
who come in search of something,
like all the ones present here tonight...
There was a time about twenty years ago
when a lot more people were present
here for the solstices.
There were Occitans, nazis, hippies...
There were Krishnas,
and even inquisitors
recognizable from
their Dominican clothing
present hereto see
what was going on...
They were intrigued,
they were wondering
what so many people were doing
at Montségur, freezing their butt off
just to look at a ray of sunlight.
There are stories about solar temples
because this ray of light was discovered
but what was it really?
It was just a calendar
because the people who lived here,
they were peasants
and they needed to know
when the solstices ended
so they could plant
their seeds and things.
There's nothing weird about it,
it's a sort of clock.
Everybody's going nuts
over this orange ray of light...
Yeah, it's a phenomenon
but that's not the point.
This is a high place
since prehistoric times.
Every man looks to the heavens
in search of God.
You only have to look at
the starry landscape above.
People have always gathered here
because it's a high point,
it's a place full of energy
and submitted
to telluric forces and that's it.
There's every chance of
meeting outsiders
here whose vision and way of thinking
is similar to that of the inhabitants of Montségur.
We're here to see the sunrise tomorrow morning
and everything has been thought out,
everyone will see it...
The sun aligns,
it lights up...
The ultimate goal is
to release our souls trapped
in our material bodies
living in this world of Satan and
ascend towards the kingdom of our Father
of which we were born.
An old Cathar prophecy announces
that after a period of 700 years,
the laurel will turn green again
and the old ways return.
When we come to Montségur today,
in the 21st century,
we're struck by
the magic of this place.
FABRICE CHAMBON - archeologist
- There's the landscape,
and this mountain dominating
the forests facing the Pyrénées
and where sometimes birds of prey fly over.
The feeling here
is that of being out of time.
RICHARD PIGELET - curator
- The mountain of Montségur
is a very particular place.
Whichever side
you observe it from,
you see this emerging peak
and you feel a strong magnetic pull.
Just from looking at it,
you can feel this strong natural magnetism
coming off of Montségur.
There's the history of this region,
the tragedy that took place
Much can be said about
the treasure or the stake...
But you never leave this place
as you came.
To a lot of people,
Montségur is a solar temple.
To others,
it was a temple of worship to the Cathars.
And others still,
by touching the stones of the castle,
try to communicate
with the memory of the rocks.
Some, in a more mundane way,
come to Montségur to meditate.
And a lot has been said about Montségur
Some even said it had
a relation with extraterrestrials.
This place is a site of pilgrimage
that attracts more and more people,
I think it's because they
wonder about Catharism
and its still remaining mysteries.
It's on a spiritual level.
I think they're looking for understanding.
Montségur is a place of initiation.
TRISTAN BERGEROT - founder espritcathare.org
- People come to Montségur in search of answers
to their past, to their future
and to their present.
They identify with
the history of the Cathars,
a history worthy of
a novel or a movie.
You get the feeling
that everything was predestined.
You can feel people
searching for something
inside themselves,
as if this place called
for instrospection of the self.
The height of the mountain
symbolizes the union
of heaven and earth.
As in all civilizations, it's the
dwelling place of the gods.
It's where man rises up,
where he has the possibility
to rise toward God.
As you can see,
this place is no simple castle.
It's not just an historical site.
We're in a place that holds a lot of depth
and importance to many people.
AIMEE COUQUET - inhabitant of Montségur
Many people hold magical rituals up there.
Sects still come here to
practice magical rites.
SCARLETT AMARIS - author & esoteric researcher
We know that the Cathars
- and this is very innovative -
did not discriminate between women and men.
There's a woman from here
who's very famous,
she was the sister of the Count of Foix
and her name was Esclarmonde
Ever since she was a child,
she was surrounded
by poets, troubadours and musicians
so she was very gifted, very intelligent.
When the troubadours
sang about Esclarmonde,
they praised the beauty of this woman
but not just her physical beauty,
her inner beauty as well.
She allowed the fortification of Montségur
so as to be able to receive the Cathars
fleeing from the Inquisition at the time.
When the Northern Crusaders arrived
in Languedoc, arms in hand,
they were very surprised
by the freedom women had here.
They were astonished to see
women commanding men.
Countesses of Comminges commandeering their
troops.
There were women,
as in Montségur, who took up arms.
They were like Occitan
Joan of Arcs.
Esclarmonde died in 1240
and didn't witness the fall of Montségur.
What's interesting about Catharism
is the great role played by women.
One might say that
without the Cathar women,
catharism wouldn't have scared
the Roman church so much.
One might extrapolate even further.
Maybe the crusades
never would've existed.
It was the women who really shook
the Roman church in its beliefs.
Beyond that,
it's interesting to note
that when prehistoric people depicted
human beings, they were always women.
The most beautiful examples
of ancient findings
were discovered by archaeologists
deep in the caves of the Pyrenees
and they're called
“Mother Goddesses”.
They're small statuettes
and form the first known traces
of art created by humanity.
Today, even in novels, when Cathar women
and Esclarmonde are mentioned,
it's obviously a direct reference
to the worship of womanhood
that still exists
in the Pyrénées today.
Like I said, the castle of Montségur
is the grail itself.
It holds the keys to the architecture
and the network
in place since prehistoric times.
THE DEVIL'S CHAIR - RENNES-LES-BAINS
We don't know why there's a pentacle,
why there's a hexagram...
In fact, nobody really knows.
Those are astronomical markers
for certain periods of time...
that coincide with...
the places built on telluric
and cosmic landmarks.
THE CIRCLES SPRING
It's the heritage.
In that sense, it is the grail.
The Grail isn't hidden somewhere. It's not about
blowing up Montségur in order to find it.
The grail is the castle itself.
So, if you have some time
on your hands
and you don't know what to do,
you can take a map
and trace lines accordingly
and see what turns up.
So, Hook a map
of the surroundings and the castle...
And I thought to myself, if there's
something to be found,
it must be accessible for everyone,
more or less,
by easy means.
Not everybody's a freemason
of the 33rd degree and carries knowledge
of all the arcana of sacred geometry.
And my first thought was Rennes-le-Chéteau,
Rennes-les-Bains.
So I said to myself that I'd
trace a circle, just out of curiosity...
I took the church of Rennes-le-Chéteau
and put my compass here, hop,
The church of Rennes-les-Bains, toc
We try to make it somewhat precise,
since we're going at it...
And I traced the circle, simply enough.
This is when I realized
that the circle...
was connecting
with Campagne-les-Bains
to the ancient Templar fortress
and the church...
I traced the line and...
The first evident line that stuck out was
the radius connecting
Rennes-le-Chéteau / Rennes-les-Bains
And so I traced...
And I thought to myself, well, these things
have stumbled upon themselves nicely.
I then pursued from Rennes-les-Bains, hop...
and kept the same radius...
Without changing it...
And I then traced what they call
the Vesica Pisces shape
in the construction lingo.
And now, we trace
from Rennes-les-Bains...
And I realized that churches of
Rennes-les-Bains and Bézu.
Were connected
on the same radius.
Well, hum, a whole new coincidence...
Four churches that connect
just by making one tracing like that...
Which made in turn, a composite
of two hexagrams...
with a slight offset, which allowed me
to draw a twelve-branch star.
Drawing this shape
led me to discover other points
and little by little,
that's how it developed.
And I realized that
in relation to my place...
URANIE'S PROPERTY
...on my property, there are landmarks
relating to the phases of
the solstice and the equinox...
So, I had my three axis seen from here
which were already included
in a figure because...
That's sort of the shrewdness...
If you begin this personal research
because that's what it is...
Nobody else can make it for you...
Tracing...
You have to do it on your own... to see.
Already, when we trace,
we find things we can't explain!
And we realize that these
shapes are alive.
They're active.
They act on the spirit.
There's always a moment when
something will happen,
that'll lead you to discover a new figure
made by mistake.
And I've made lots of mistakes.
And found lots of things
by making errors in my angles...
I would be tracing one figure
and end up drawing another!
So yeah, some things
happen on their own
because this site remains active.
RENNES-LE-CHATEAU - SUMMER 2012
(Latin) This place is to be feared, this is
the house of God and the Gate to Heaven.
CHURCH OF THE HOLY MARY-MAGDALENE
The church is dedicated to Mary Magdalene
who is another manifestation of the Goddess.
The first ray of sun on the 17th of January
illuminates the edifice.
In the nineteenth century,
Abbé Bérenger Saunière
allegedly uncovered a fabulous treasure
that made him immensely wealthy.
He built this place
following an occult concept
and took the secret to his grave.
This mystery fed
a prosperous commercial industry
ranging from "The Holy Blood and the Holy Grail"
to the "DaVinci Code".
ALAIN X - Stone Mason
-'Rennes-le-Chéteau is a place...
that can be as beneficial
as negative.
ALEX PAINCO - Mayor of Rennes-le-Chateau
-Rennes-le-Chéteau is an old village,
an historical village
and it has changed a lot
since the arrival of
Abbé Saunière in 1885.
Abbé Saunière has built
a lot of edifices here
and that's where the mystery of
Rennes-le-Chéteau springs from.
Rennes-le-Chateau is a place of initiation.
Not everybody
can just go into this.
The elders knew
that Hell had seven gates.
Each one has a guardian
worse than the other.
It's only by passing
through these gates
that we can escape the hell
of the material world.
Or bring heaven
down to earth.
ARTUR SALA - physicist
And the horror movies?
The Fulci films? The Italian horror films?
Yeah. That's what opened the door for me.
The gates of Hell?
Yes.
Rennes-le-Chéteau is...
It's special...
It's a place where you can
either lose your soul or rise.
It's... it's a labyrinth like the ones
that exist in old cathedrals,
built by our ancestors...
With hidden pits and traps...
We get a lot of tourists here,
about 120,000 each year.
For such a small village
with eighteen year-round inhabitants,
ten shops is a lot.
So we can say tourism is what makes
Rennes-le-Chéteau live.
Rennes-le-Chéteau is like a spiderweb
with a spider in the middle.
It's gigantic but invisible
at the same time.
And the people who come here
should know that they're like flies.
If they get caught in the web,
well... They get eaten.
Thanks to Abbé Saunière,
the mystery lives on.
Researchers come here,
several movies have been
made about this place...
...Numerous books have been
written, about 600 until now.
Rennes-le-Chéteau has
become internationally known,
since Abbé Saunière came here.
When you set out in your path of initiation,
when you travel around France...
...It's up to you not to stumble
and keep walking on the right path
to become what is known
as a "companion".
If you're not capable
of being a companion,
if you can't get rid of...
If y0u're just bait and y0u're incapable
of seeing the apprentice side of things,
You can't be a companion.
You're not part of the companionship
in Rennes-le-Chéteau,
it's as simple as that.
For the people to understand.
It comes from ancient times,
it's from a lost world
of gates and...
For the people to understand.
I mean...
For the people who come here,
the ones seeking something,
it's up to them not to get lost.
That's all I have to say.
If some people lose themselves
here in Rennes-le-Chéteau,
others come to seek answers.
That was the case
of François Mitterrand
who came here a few days
before the election
on a very mysterious visit.
As for Mitterand's visit
to Rennes-le-Chéteau,
ANDRE GALLAUD - Journalist
-it didn't go exactly the way it's described
in the books or
the movies made about it.
It happened during
the presidential campaign
that took place in the
month of May, 1981.
Mitterrand was asked
to come to Couiza
to present himself to the people here.
As tradition has it,
a great dinner was held
at the village hall.
After the dinner was over,
president Robert Capdeville
turns to Mitterrand and
asks him if all is well
and Mitterand responds in form...
Capdeville then says
“Listen, if it's all right with you
and in order to properly
digest this excellent meal,
I would like to show you a site
that you’ll remember.
Instead of your usual walk,
I'll take you up
to Rennes-le-Chéteau...
So they went up
to Rennes-le-Chéteau,
They were welcomed by
the departmental councilor and the mayor.
Mitterrand then discovered this site
and was amazed by the view
and What the Abbé had built,
but there was never any question
about a treasure or anything like that.
After walking around a bit, Mitterrand
wanted to see the Magdala Tower.
So we came up here and he
climbed to the top of the Tower
and he was...
He was completely
in awe with the view.
That was that.
That was the way Mitterrand's
visit to the department of Aude,
Couiza and
Rennes-le-Chéteau went.
It all happened very simply,
it was mostly a digestive walk.
As history has it,
something happened here a few years back.
The mirror downstairs
is not the original one.
What happened was
that several youngsters
came up here,
one of which was the owner's daughter.
They looked into the mirror
and saw the Devil.
They were scared
out of their wits.
And they ended up at my place.
The only time they ever came here...!
They told me they'd seen
the Devil in the mirror.
And it reminded me
of what one of the early
researchers told me,
a guy named Jean Pelé.
He said he knew about formulas
to call up the Devil in mirrors.
He had taught this formula
to certain people
and now regretted it because
they'd abused it.
And what probably happened back then,
I think that the people who lived here...
...used those formulas
and opened a gate, toc,
through the mirror...
and saw the Devil.
But they weren't prepared for it.
And I'm the one who broke
that mirror when I came here
in the early nineties...
...to do a sort of purification...
Because it was so loaded that
something had to be done.
And this mirror had
an importance in history.
I don't really know
the bottom of the story,
what happened then...
But point being, I broke it!
And so I closed the door for this devil.
When you dine with the Devil,
you better have a big spoon
otherwise...
you don't eat.
And since this place is a sort
of spider web, you know,
it's like a spider...
This is sort of the center where impulses
are received from various places...
URANIE'S HOUSE
...from as far away as England
or maybe even further...
...it's the whole network that's used...
And over the course of history in
Rennes-le-Chéteau and the area of La Coume...
URANIE'S CAT
I can say that there
have been lots of assaults...
...a lot of things done to destroy...
this place, the community
and the people who live here.
I've made all this over time and it's...
Well, there's no artistic purpose
in exhibiting works with a "vision"...!
The ultimate goal is
to balance the energies
so all this has been
made little by little,
during certain periods,
moments, certain phases...
...over time.
It has a therapeutic purpose.
Magico-therapy.
To balance energies
and avoid taking too much in.
They're like shields.
URANIE'S NEIGHBOR - corporate CEO Jaap
Rameijer
JAAP'S HOUSE
JAAP'S CAT
JAAP'S VIDEO - LES LABADOUS - SUMMER 2012
It's...
To really understand Rennes-le-Chéteau
one must come here,
look around...
And then one must check out a map.
If you have
Rennes-les-Bains here...
Rennes-le-Chéteau there...
And draw the equilateral triangle...
Then you only have to look out
the window and see what there is.
If you look hard enough,
you can see a farm
called Le Carla.
If we divide this in half...
And take the bisector...
Le Carla is at this precise spot.
It's a very particular geometric shape
If you look at the bottom of those rocks...
Just at the edge of the field,
there's a tiny red spot.
All that's needed is a little
bit of phonetic Cabala
to make an anagram of Carla
So, toc, what does Sauniere show us?
The Grail.
It's a nice gift, isn't it?
And then I discovered...
...that a shape appears here...
...of a woman's head...
...right in the axis of
the rising sun and
leading straight
to Le Carla.
Le Carla can be seen
from the Magdala Tower.
Let's see what Saunière
might have wanted to tell us
if it had any such intentions...
It's the alignment of this ramp knob
with the middle of the window, the
church window that has been placed here...
And if we align the two...
We end up on the cave of Mary Magdalene.
It used to be the Fournet Cave but
it has been renamed to Mary Magdalene.
I think it used to be
an ancient celtic or druidic site,
where certain initiations
or rituals took place...
There's all this symbolism
of fecundity,
death and rebirth
related to caves.
And we can see on the church's altar
a painting of Mary Magdalene in the cave...
It's always been a place where
groups of people
come to do rituals... It's always active.
There seems to be a certain
specificity to this place
in that it has this sort
of incubating role...
in the practices of certain occult groups
surrounding the culture of
succubi and incubi and other spirits...
These people are trying to get
women to copulate with the incubi
in order to give birth
to fantastical creatures.
Legend has it that Mérovée,
the first Merovingian king,
was the son of a witch
and a succubus.
Just like Merlin the enchanter.
So there's a persistent underlying
base in Rennes-le-Chéteau
where there's a lot of ceremonials
and sexual rituals that are carried out
in order to incarnate spirits
that are believed to be superior.
I hope the village
will stay as it is, pretty and peaceful,
and keep attracting
tourists, but normal ones.
I've had a lot of
administrative problems
such as obtaining
a building permit...
...of conformity...
Right now, I'm living here
as an outlaw since my house isn't in
accordance with sanitary regulations.
Three years ago, we surprised several
people digging beneath the cemetary.
They were caught in time.
I receive mail from people telling me
that Jesus is no longer buried here,
but is buried in Bayonne.
People who believe that the
body of Jesus is in the church
or that they've uncovered
the treasure...
-- people who believe that Mary Magdalene
is buried beneath the village --...
It took me twelve years,
twelve years and three internments...
...to get the whole property back.
Plus the problems... The worries...
Everything you can imagine...
...all the things that happen
when the powers that be
have decided to
destroy your life.
Things like isolation...
Total isolation, separation
from friends and family...
No more means,
no car, nothing...
Loss of income, the maximum in other words.
We've also had Jesus himself
stop by at the mayor's office,
some guy
claiming to be Jesus.
It's fabulous.
I filed a complaint...
They said I was right.
And then they measured
up the terrain
and to tell me I was right,
they went toc, and reclaimed some of it!
So, yeah. It's that type of
administrative harassment...
But we can't say they did it on purpose.
I don't know.
We can say it's a mistake, at least, that's
what they told me after twelve years.
“We're sorry, we made a mistake”.
They still confined me three times
to a mental hospital
with chemical treatment.
That's not nothing.
It's not an easy situation.
I still have treatments with a psychiatrist.
It's three months in a hospital.
And then it's three months of therapy...
...and injections of psychotropic substances.
In my case it was Aldol.
Generally, I just turn them back nicely
by saying that Rennes-le-Chateau
wants to remain a peaceful place...
So that these types of people
can just go away and not stay here.
Then there were the direct threats
on my life, death threats. Obvious ones.
And several misguided attempts
to eliminate me.
Physically.
There are quite a few people
who are a little “special”,
one might say..
But they're mostly
in Bugarach
To me, Rennes-le-Chéteau
was the precursor
to the Bugarach phenomenon.
BUGARACH - SUMMER 2012
JEAN-PIERRE DELORD - mayor of Bugarach
- We're all a little weird...
People come here
with their own beliefs...
This is a democracy where people are free
to think and believe as they want.
I have no problem with people
coming here on a pilgrimage
or searching for something else.
My problem is if having too many of
them here at once.
36 years as the mayor.
It's a job like any other.
It's like being the chief tribesman.
But it's okay.
Two hundred people to care for...
A superb countryside and...
that!
Fantastic!
That mountain is particular.
We can already see it by its shape
and placement.
It's particular because
geologically speaking,
all the layers are reversed.
If you consult a compass...
there's a definite discrepancy. There must
be a very large mass of iron underneath.
I tell everybody to
"Get up there and you'll see,
you’ll come down different”.
Some never get fully back
down, they stay perched up there!
The truth is that when
I heard about this event,
I notified the prefectoral authorities so
they'd take an interest in the phenomena.
In turn, they notified MIVILUDES, the government
department that monitors cult activity
and which have investigated
the three regional divisions around here.
They indeed thought there was
something going on
and following that discovery, the prefect
decided to put this place under surveillance.
Maybe they'll call in the military.
There's always that possibility.
JEROME VIGUIER - mountain guide
- The mayor's office and the mayor in particular
is very down to earth.
So he's probably afraid
that people are going to climb
the mountain of Bugarach
and throw themselves
into a vortex or portal.
When the month of December is over,
they'll just find another date to hold on to.
They'll all look like idiots.
That's what I believe.
It's all bogus stuff.
It's a complete delirium.
I still have my feet firmly planted
on the ground, I'm not gone yet!
If I'd wanted to set
all this up myself...
Already, with an advertising agency,
it would've cost me a fortune.
It probably wouldn't have
had the same impact.
I'm completely baffled...
by the proportions
this fad has taken.
Of course, these stories about the end
of the world periodically resurface.
We humans are haunted
by the demise of our planet.
I think the real problem
lies therein.
One night, it must've
been around 2 a.m.
I was spending the night
in a cave with friends...
Just near its entrance.
And around 2 a.m.,
I woke up for no reason.
And I saw this huge
white light outside.
It filled up the whole
entrance to the cave
which must've been...
30-50 feet wide.
I didn't have the presence of mind
to get up and check it out.
The next morning,
I talked it over with my friends
and one of them said
he'd seen the same thing.
Like me, he didn't get up
to see what was going on but...
A great white light...
On a moonless night.
We were far from the road
so it couldn't have been car lights.
The mystery remains.
The story stems from a character who lived
- he's passed on, now -
he lived near the "Source Salée" domain
on the edge of the village...
He claimed to hear
humming coming from a cave
and believed the sound was coming from
an underground garage where
they repaired flying saucers, etc...
The myth started from this.
It got in print in UFO magazines
and then the story
came back on the internet, etc, etc.
A trekker took this picture
in Montferrier in 1976...
It shows a flying saucer that
supposedly appeared
in the sky one morning.
The picture has never been
authenticated by professionals
so nobody knows
whether it's fake or not.
The person whose idea it was
to print a postcard
representing a flying saucer
is a photographer
who lives one village over.
He sold it to us.
There's another postcard with a small
blue-green creature next to the peak
who's obviously
an extraterrestrial.
Some people firmly believe that Montségur
is an extraterrestrial landing base.
There was this group who came in
with all sorts of electronic equipment
and who set up antennaes
all over the mountain.
So l went up to them
to ask what was going on...
They told me they were communicating with
extraterrestrials who were living inside the mountain.
I have a lot of friends who are
very much in touch with Nature...
They see faeries, gnomes and goblins
in Bugarach. All sorts of phenomena.
You pass through a gate
where you see
all things material
such as houses, standing stones,
dolmens, trees, hills, mountains, earth...
That's what you see.
And then, there's another gate
where you hear voices,
sounds of horses,
but you can't
communicate with them.
It's as if they don't see you at all.
All the places like that,
like in Montségur, are doors.
There are certain periods of
the year when those energies
are more active than at others...
It's a sort of...
it's a celestial gate...
and at the same time infernal.
Because it's also a gateway to Hell.
If you invoke the Devil
here, no problem,
he'll show up and
ask you what you want.
In general, when
passing through a gate,
there's a mix of the past,
the present and the future.
Let's say that,
a few years back,
I had an intense experience
about Montségur.
I came across a book
about the Cathars
which I'd never
heard about before.
When I looked at the cover picture
of Montségur, I had a revelation.
I think I may have lived
a previous life here.
The first time I went to Montségur,
I remembered who I was...
I don't know...
They say that before you die, all
the important things in your life
flash before your eyes...
I experienced that but
the other way around. In fact...
I was Arpaïx de Péreille,
one of Raymond de Péreille's daughters.
He was co-lord of Montségur.
My role was very important.
But I didn't end up
at the stake with the others.
We ran off... in the direction
of the mountains.
And we were arrested there by our own men.
I don't know the reason why.
It was very hard for me
because I ran away with my husband
and he had our child in his arms.
It was a little boy but I don't know
exactly how old he was.
And we were separated at that point.
I spent the rest of my life
in a prison in Carcassonne.
This is a place I need to
return to regularly
to renew myself.
I feel at home here.
Not so long ago, about
three or fours years back,
I realized that I'd lived
several past lives.
During an akashic lecture,
it was explained to me that
I'd lived a very important one in the
Middle Ages and it had made a mark on me.
Which explains the problems
of my present life.
So I delved into this...
...and I realized that
everybody has had several lives
filled with different experiences
- good and bad -
and that one needs
to find a balance between the two
in order to become
an accomplished soul
and no longer have the need
to reincarnate.
Maybe that's the reason I chose
medieval names for my children.
I didn't yet know
about this past life,
I didn't feel anything towards reincarnation.
I didn't even understand it.
The names I'd chosen
for my children were
Aliénor, Margaux,
Childéric and Alaric
and I know now that it was no coincidence.
I've always been attracted to the Middle Ages.
So evidently, there's a problem with those who mistake
their desires for reality or their dreams for reality.
Still, it's kind of amusing
that during the course
of one year,
four different Raymond de Péreilles
stop by the museum of Montségur
to introduce themselves...
If all the people pretending
to have been reincarnated
were accounted for,
I think the number of Cathars
burned at the stake
would greatly supersede 225. The number
would be closer to the thousands.
I think we're all destined
to find each other.
I've met people in Lavalanet
or in other places who've had
the same experience as me.
- Even on Facebook -
So it's more or less of a coincidence...
JAAP'S VISION OF THE MAGDALENE
I put this clock here
to be sure of what time it is...
Because we're not in the real time.
If you check your watch,
it's probably around 2 p.m.,
maybe a little more?
A little later,
2230 p.m.?
And in fact, there's a two hour gap here
so we live on fake time.
So here's our famous pentagram.
You just have to open
your heart and soul.
The key is the heart.
That's where the grail is.
Since our souls are locked
in this world of flesh
it is our destiny to rise and return
to the Father of all good souls.
That's it. Have a nice journey home...
Subtitle resync by
Lucky Desert Horse