"Thanks to the Studio, Author and others for creating this beautiful masterpiece"
[Previous episodes]
Surrender all of your monstrous essences.
so many people
harassed some students,
Aren't you afraid of being laughed at?
Report.
There's one more chase team.
that Xue Tu killed.
They are interested
to work with me?
¿Fruta Yuling madura?
exploding pearls
even if he could hurt the Ice Monkey King,
but could not kill him.
Add more,
there are still other ice apes.
As long as you can hurt the Ice Monkey King,
the rest leave it to me.
Episode 7
A la Xue Tu.
You...
You can not scape.
¡Argh!
He's been following me for a long time
Aren't you tired?
This place is pretty good.
You guys just rest here.
Xue Tu.
We have reported your track
to the Third Master.
Obey and surrender.
¿Oh?
Then,
I have to be more agile.
You...
Don't be careless.
Attack him!
Base.
I have to find a way
to get away from them.
Although the members of the Liu Territory are like dogs,
they will be controlled by me this time.
This place is not far
from the Valley of Snows.
You must get the Yuling fruit soon
to treat this [ __ ] wound.
So I can go far.
Was it the Ice Monkey King?
Intermediate...
Intermediate level monsters.
Unexpected anesthetic pearl
doesn't work for him
On the contrary, making it even more fierce.
And if
Shall we go back?
We can't run
if he finds out.
Mu Chen.
What do you think?
Are you willing to give up like this?
Of course he is not willing.
I can't go home empty handed.
Report.
There is a sign of pursuit.
The safe villain
fled into the Beiling Plains.
Inland Beiling Plains?
there are many there
high level monsters
that is comparable to the level of Shenpo.
if entered,
most likely to die.
Xue Tu really was quite cunning.
He thought we were going to back off.
if he goes into the interior of Beiling Plains?
Correct.
even the bastard
hide In High Level Monster Cave,
we also have to catch him.
Chase!
GOOD!
If you want to get Yuling Fruit
from this monster's hand,
we have to divide the task.
Leiyin.
Lin Zhong.
MoLing.
You lure him away
from the Yuling fruit tree.
I will look for opportunities to fight him
with explosive pearls.
Hermana Qian's.
You hide.
When the opportunity comes,
immediately pick up Yuling Fruit.
GOOD.
We will do it as soon as possible.
Back off immediately if something goes wrong.
exploding pearl,
I would consider it wasted.
GOOD.
Mover.
Lin Zhong.
Support it.
GOOD.
MoLing.
Return.
GOOD.
Ray.
Stupid creature.
Where are you looking?
Lightning Boomerang!
Hurts?
Stupid creatures, come get us.
this creature
not as stupid as you think.
It doesn't seem like it will disappear even if I die.
Hermana Qian's.
Turn around in silence.
It seems that you can not fish.
Attack together.
I have to break his defense.
it's time
Get out of the way!
It worked.
Don't be careless.
keep an eye on it
Hermana Qian's.
Can you even bear this?
place.
They are almost awake.
Quickly notify the team leader,
back immediately.
Eve of this creature
should have made it to the top
Intermediate level monsters.
It seems to eat a lot of Yuling fruit.
his skills
comparable to Linglun level of late phase.
However,
He's already hurt.
Let's fight again.
Buying time for Sister Qian'er.
GOOD.
Hermana Qian's.
Ey,
stupid monkey.
Here.
Come here.
catch me!
I'm in a hurry.
Finally I got it.
¡ Mu Chen!
I have it!
¡Hermana Qian's!
Hurry!
you beast!
Arrest.
I will fight you!
Art of the Great Pagoda.
Team leader.
The ice monkey outside had woken up
being bullied by the Ice Monkey King.
Go, hurry up.
Otherwise, there will be no time.
¡ Mu Chen!
Hurry back!
The Ice Monkey King is here,
we can't run away
The Ice Monkey King cared the most about
This Yuling Fruit.
I'll get over it.
Leave immediately.
Just me.
- You go.
- Should not.
It's very dangerous!
¡Ey!
Giant creature.
Watch this.
I love you?
Come on, chase me.
Mu Chen.
Leiyin.
Take Sister Qian'er
and Senior Mo Ling back alive.
Otherwise, I won't forgive you!
Go, hurry up.
Let's go.
Mu Chen.
Fast.
Back off.
Apparently,
this creature will stop at nothing
before getting Yuling Fruit.
I have to find a way to get away from it.
Beiling Plains inland is ahead.
There should be a lot of high level monsters.
who could match the Ice Monkey King.
Apparently,
high-level monsters have entered the jurisdiction .
It should be
high level monster cave.
Get in first.
Why are you so quiet?
If you see the frightened look of this creature,
Monster level in this cave
must be very high.