Subtitle by Kingcastillo, thank you for faithfully watching
♪In the mundane world, the blade lies♪
♪The bloodstained funeral♪
♪Wandering among the phantom♪
♪Tears shed on thousand feathers♪
♪As I look back, rain fills my vision♪
♪The thriving youth♪
♪Wandering alone, unsheathing my sword♪
♪Transcend above the cycle and conquer♪
♪My ambition is as huge as
the mountain and the river♪
♪Wandering alone, unsheathing my sword♪
♪Transcend above the cycle and conquer♪
♪My ambition is as huge as
the mountain and the river♪
♪Wandering alone, unsheathing my sword♪
♪Transcend above the cycle and conquer♪
♪My ambition is as huge as
the mountain and the river♪
[The Success of Empyrean Xuan Emperor]
[Crisis of Mortal Realm]
[Episode 170]
How ridiculous!
Let me show you the invincibility
of an Empyrean God!
Taboo martial art,
Reigning Empyrean of the Ninth Heaven!
Clan Martial God's Skill,
Empyrean Fist!
A Double Vital Fire Cosmic Martial God?
However, it's a pity
that you have such a poor foundation.
There are too few Stars
in the Star Manifestation.
I'm good enough as an auxiliary battle force
to stop you.
An auxiliary battle force?
Come on out,
Golden Armor War God!
The Golden Armor War God has no sense of pain.
Even if his arms and legs are cut off,
he'll continue to fight frantically.
Moreover, as Qianjin City's heritage,
he'll be fueled by Qianjin City's power
and battle non-stop.
As for his power level,
he's the same as me.
He's also a Double Vital Fire Cosmic Martial God.
Sea Dragon Seal!
Let's attack!
Fifth Brother,
it's time for you to come back with me.
Li Fei Mang,
you compelled my Fifth Brother
to make the wrong decision.
Hence, you're going to pay for it!
Then, I shall get rid of you first
to clear the way for Wu Tong
to become the duke of the Demons.
Die!
Mighty Golden Form Technique!
Holy Ape Transformation!
Fifth Brother,
if you come back with me,
I'll forgive you.
Never!
Demon Sun Divine Eyes!
The matured Yao Wu Gu
is so scary.
Fire Dance of the Ninth Heaven,
Heaven-Suppressing Hand!
How dare you challenge me!
I suppose you have a death wish!
Martial God's Skill, Ten Thousand-Jin Fist!
Bei!
Moon Flick!
Hmph!
Is that all?
Are you really an auxiliary
for the Golden Armor War God?
Or,
is there someone more dangerous
lurking in this chaotic battlefield?
Golden Armor War God,
attack!
How weak!
God-Killing Spear Technique!
Ha ha ha!
Here comes my chance!
Empyrean's Sword Assassination Technique!
This is impossible!
During the second Curse-breaking Battle,
you were clearly weakened
after practicing this technique!
How are you doing this now?
Are all my opponents this dumb?
I was at 5,000 Stars back then.
But now, I'm at 9,700 Stars.
So, how can my combat effectiveness
remain the same?
I think you'd better worry about whether
your taboo martial art has reached its limit.
Your taboo martial art is almost used up indeed.
Tiger King's Spear Skill!
Vital Fire,
Rainbow-Shocking Slash!
Zap!
Vital Fire,
Empyrean's Decree Kill!
I've only provoked you a little,
but you've put your life's strength
into the attack with all your might.
Although the sword is strong,
it's too bad that your body is weak.
It's so easy for me to break that move.
Snow Demon-freezing Skill!
Boring.
You're still not revealing yourself
at this point.
This is a complete disregard for your life
as a member of  Empyrean Gods.
Who exactly are you working with?
[Advertisement]