Ride along with the heroes
of 9-1-1 Lone Star.
Let's show 'em what we got!
See all-new episodes
Mondays.
And check out
our other Fox programs...
Prodigal Son, 9-1-1
and Deputy.
You need three things
to do this job...
a badge, a gun
and what's in your heart.
ANNOUNCER: Only on Fox.
TODD: But it's all about
what you're putting
in the meat, right?
Let me tell you.
[speaking indistinctly]
Hey!Watch it, you little hellions.
They started it, Uncle Todd.
I don't carewho drew first blood.
Move the Jedi battleaway from the grill
before somebody gets burned.
[easygoing music]
[children giggling]
Man, I ain't never having kids.
All right, everybody,
get out your phones.
It's time for the reveal.
Benny, Charlie, Ricky.
Dang it.
You heard your mom.Get over here.
Come on.
Dear Lord,
please let it be a girl.
Amen.
Okay, here we go!
Can we get a countdown, y'all?
ALL:
Five, four, three...
JAMES:
Dang it, Charlie.
It's a girl.
James, we're finally having
a little girl!
Sweet God, hallelujah.
[laughs]
[Molly gasps]
-[flames roar]
-[Todd screams]
[all screaming]
[mouths word]
[screaming]
-[siren wailing]
-How bad?
Well, you're very lucky
that your brother-in-law
got you into that pool so fast.
Let's push one mil of morphine
to make him comfortable.
Yes, Cap.
Sir, this might sting
a little bit, okay?
I'm just gonna put
this sterilized gauze...
[inhales sharply]
On until you getto the hospital, okay?
The burns lookpretty superficial, actually,
probably nothing morethan a second-degree.
But my face will be okay,
right?
I think so.
And that eyebrow will
grow back in no time.
Wait.
What's wrong with my eyebrow?
[whispers]
Nice one.
What do you say, Captain?
-Hey, Judd.
-Hey.
Hey, y'all, that's good.
That's enough!
Hey, Stollman,
kill the pressure
on the hose, will you?
All right.
Hey, great work, everybody.
Let's pack it up and go.
[indistinct chatter]
Whew.
Man, who knew gender reveal
dust could go out like that?
Yeah, well, you take
any starch-based powder
and put it near an open flame,
watch what happens.
You ask me, the whole idea
of a gender reveal party
is pretty messed up,
people filming
themselves rooting
for a girl or a boy,
it's unseemly.
Yeah, not to mention,
you don't get the gender
from the ultrasound.
You get it from the kid.
Sing it, brother.
126, we're on the move.
Let's go.
-MOLLY: Ohh!
-MAN: Miss Molly!
-Hey, what happened?
-[Molly moaning]
JAMES:
Breathe, breathe, breathe.
-Ma'am, are you okay?
-She's coming!
Sir, how many months is she?
Uh, seven months.
Uh, it's too early.
Probably induced by the stress.
Ma'am, we're gonna get you
-to a hospital right away.
-No time.
-But you just went into labor.
-I've had three of these, kid.
Trust me, she's coming now.
[moans]
-Judd.
-What?
Since Cap's gone,you're in charge.
Oh, right.
Uh...oh, right.
All right, so go inside,
get...get sheets, towels,
anything that's clean.
-PAUL: Yeah.
-Get on the radio,
tell them that we needan RA unit ASAP.
Hey, then grab that med kit offthe truck, come back with it.
You can help Marjanwith anything she needs.
-Me?
-Yeah, you're certified,
-ain't you?
-[Molly moaning]
MARJAN: You can do this.You're almost there.
Take a deep breath and push.
Oh, God!
-MARJAN: Push.
-[Molly moaning]
-MARJAN: I can see it.
-MOLLY: She's coming early.
-Oh, she's coming early.
-You got this.
MOLLY: I'm not ready for this.
She's too early.
Take a deep breath and push.
Oh, God!
[whimpers]
MARJAN: Okay, push,push, push, push.
[moaning]
I can see her!I can see her!
[moans]
[dramatic music]
-JUDD: Ooh.
-PAUL: Ooh.
[laughing]
You did, Mama.
-PAUL: Wow.
-MARJAN: You did it.
MOLLY: Aww.
Congratulations, it's a boy.
That's impossible.
That...that cloud was pink.
It was pink, man.
ALL: Yay!
-JAMES: Pink.
-[baby and Molly crying]
[tense music]
♪
GWENYTH: Who misses
their own son's birthday?
OWEN: One of my guys was
having a hard time.
I just couldn't bail.
GWENYTH: Your son was
having a hard time.
OWEN: TK understands.
Everyone at my station has
lost so many people...
GWENYTH: So help me, Owen,
if you throw 9/11 in my face
one more time...
[machine beeps]
OWEN: They're calling ita level two coma.
He moans a little,chews in his sleep.
-Mm.
-He's probably starving.
[monitor beeping]
And it seems like he's gonnawake up, and he just...
doesn't.
Owen, I'm so sorry.
[inhales deeply]But we were lucky...
that the bullet didn't hithis heart or his spine.
It's a miracle.
It did nick a major vesselin his shoulder,
under the sub...
Subclavian artery.
I had to take a couple
of anatomy surveys
in grad school, so...
-Huh. Good recall.
-Thanks.
And then he went intohypovolemic shock,
and...some of his organsstarted to shut down.
Oh, my God, Owen.
But look at him,He's...he's doing better.
He's breathing on his own.
Everything seems to befunctioning okay now.
[solemn music]
Come on, come meet my boy.
[chuckles softly]
♪
Oh.
He looks like you.
He looks more like his mother,actually.
Does she know yet?
She's travelling on businessin China.
She's desperately trying to geta flight back,
but...I told her by the timethat happens, he'll be awake.
-Yeah.
-And the doctors say
it could be any minute.
So I'm...I'm just waiting here.
♪
I'm glad you're here.
I didn't realize how muchI could use the companionship.
♪
-And a shower.
-Yeah.
-Right?
-Yep. Yeah.
-I'm...I'm guessing.
-You're pretty gamey, yeah.
[whispers]
Dad.
TK.
Hey...hey.[shushes]
-Dad.
-It's all right.
-Where am I?
-What happened?
-It's all right.
It's all right.You're okay.
You're in the hospital,but you're okay.
I'm here.I'm here.
What happened?
[panting]
You were shot.
♪
Is she my doctor?
Who, me?
Oh, no.
No, I'm...I'm his, uh, date.
[curious music]
You brought a date?
♪
[somber music]
Last thing I remember is...
being at the stationthat night,
talking to youand petting Buttercup.
[monitor beeping]
After that,it's...it's all black.
That's probably for the best.
Dad, what happened?
Who...who the hell shot me?
[breathes deeply]
We were responding
to a possible cardiac event
behind a locked door...
[clicks tongue]
Forced our way in,
and a seven-year-old boy withhis grandfather's gun shot you.
He thought we were intruders.
[softly]Oh, that poor kid.
Does anybody knowhow he's holding up?
I hear he's been meeting
with APD counseling.
He's come from a good family,
goes to a nice church.
♪
[chuckles]
It's so like you
to be sitting here
with a hole in your chest
and still thinking about
somebody else.
Right, I'm...I'm gonna go hometomorrow,
but I-I can't evenremember it.
Is that kid gonna be ableto forget it?
[sighs deeply]
Okay, there...there isone more thing
I have to ask you,but you got to promise
to give it to me straight.
Sure, anything.
What's the dealwith that hot babe, Zoe?
First of all,
she is not just a hot babe.
She is the head of the
psychology department at UT.
Oh.
-And she is a really hot babe.
-[laughs] Yeah, she is.
So are you gonna tell me howlong you've been seeing her?
When you tell me how long
you've been seeing the cop.
Oh, God.
[laughs]
[upbeat music]
MARJAN: Wait.
No, no, no.
No, wait.
Wait.
PAUL: You still here?
I'm bonding with Buttercup.
PAUL: Your shift is over.
Wait.
Okay.
[laughs]
You see how good he listens
to Auntie.
That's 'cause you love Auntie
the most.
Okay, it's because you havethe doggy treats.
Wait till TK gets back.
We'll see how much loveyou get then.
When is TK coming back?
-He needs to heal.
-So, like, a couple weeks?
No, sooner than that.
He was shot.
Yeah, I heard thata firefighter in Los Angeles
had a piece of rebargo through his brain,
and then he was back at workwithin a month.
That's impossible.
Well, my buddy swearsit's true.
-[chuckles]
-California, man.
When's Cap coming back?
Soon, I hope.
PAUL: What, you don't likefilling in for him?
I mean, I like
the little bump in pay,
but y'all can keep
the rest of it.
[cell phone ringing]
Hey, Daddy, where you at?
STUART:
I'm at home.
Wait, what are you doing?
You're supposed to be
running errands today,
and plus, Grace is cooking.
STUART:
Well, I hope she didn't go
to a lot of trouble,
'cause I'm...I'm gonna have
to take a rain check.
Wha...oh, you not feeling good?
STUART:
No, I'm fine.
I just had some things
I had to do around the house,
lost track of time.
All right, well,
get in your truck,
and, you know,
we'll keep dinner warm.
I'm just getting
off of work now.
STUART:
Not tonight, Juddy.
Think I'll stay in.
Hey, you sound kind of funny.
STUART:
I am funny.
[laughs]
Life of the party.
Give my apologies to Grace.
We'll talk soon.
All right.
[dramatic music]
♪
[knocking on door]
Hey, Daddy, where are you?
STUART: Lord in Heaven.You drive all the way out here?
JUDD:
Oh, man.
♪
JUDD:
Oh, for Pete's sake.
Why didn't you tell me
you needed help?
Because I don't need
any help.
-JUDD: Yeah.
-[Stuart grunts]
How long you beenlaying here in the dark?
[sighs]
Well...
since the sun went down.
Oh, so you've beenlaying in here all day?
No, just from the middle
of the afternoon,
and now I've got to go
relieve myself.
Thank you very much.
So you were just holding itall day?
You can sniff the rug
if you need to.
-Yeah, yeah.
-[Stuart laughs]
-I'ma pass.
-[door closes]
[quirky music]
-So how'd that happen?
-[urine splashing]
STUART: How did it happen?
I-I just got out
of the shower,
and I tripped over
that damn rug
while I was looking
for my britches.
-[toilet flushes]
-STUART: Oh, here they are.
So how come you didn't call
Mr. Rick or Delores?
♪
What, and have them
come over here
and catch me in my skivvies?
Well, you should have
called me.
Oh, you was at work.
It wasn't an emergency anyway.
Besides that, I was just fixingto get up
when you walked in here.
Yeah, you looked like
you was just fixing to.
[sighs]
You hungry?
Oh, I-I could eat.
Yeah.
Why don't you let me
fix you something?
You got anything in there?
There's some chorizo
in the icebox,
and, uh, I think there's
some eggs in there, too.
I thought Grace was
gonna cook.
Well, I'ma have
to give her call now
'cause she...she...
[sighs]
She was making a chili...
[metallic clang]
Hey, let...let me get rid
of that old rug, will ya?
Oh, no,your mama loved this rug.
It ain't gonna go anywhere.
♪
WOMAN [on TV]:
What are you doing?
Here you go, son.
I'm not even halfway done
with this one.
You heard the doctor.
You can't overhydrate.
If your...
Don't tell me what color
my pee should be again.
-TK: What?
-OWEN: You need a pillow.
-TK: I'm fine.
-No.
No, you look uncomfortable.
Last thing you need isa stiff neck.
I said I'm fine.
Do you really plan to hover
over me like a mother hen
for the next three weeks?
They said you might heal upin ten days, but, yeah.
I talked toDeputy Chief Radford.
He said to take as much timeat home as I need.
Dad, that's crazy.
You should get back to work.
What are you gonna doabout food?
You...you stocked the fridge,
and I got a delivery app
on my phone.
I'll be okay, I promise.
-[sighs] You sure?
-I'm sure.
You could probably make
next shift.
All right.I'll go get changed.
-[TK sighs]
- Listen, Tk.
[dramatic music]
You'll be back in no time...two weeks or less.
Yeah, we'll see.
♪
BENNETT: Devil's Horn.
Now, inside that cave, son,your destiny awaits.
I always kind of pictured
my destiny including
Wi-Fi and sunlight.
And, Dad,I can tell you right now
that caving is not gonna bemy jam.
Okay, how far does this thingeven go?
It's called spelunking,
and whether it'syour jam or not,
it's good to bea little scared sometimes.
Okay, please don't drop
a quote on me.
"Fear defeats more peoplethan any other one thing
in the world."
There's a reason thatpeople climb mountains
or swim with sharks.
It's because when youpush yourself to the limits
and you succeed,then you feel like
there's nothing thatyou can't conquer.
[curious music]
Wait.
Is this about Trent Davis
kicking my ass?
It's not just aboutTrent Davis kicking your ass
or Derek Coburn.
It's about you beingtoo chicken
to turn in your résuméfor the art gallery internship.
Because I'm not like you!
[birds chirping]
I didn't inherit
your confidence.
That's just it, Keithan.
I wasn't born with confidence.I earned it, and you can, too.
♪
By crawling througha pitch-black hole
into the bowels of the Earth?
♪
Yep.
KEITHAN: Ow.
BENNETT: You doing any better
now that
we've been in here
a little bit?
KEITHAN:
No, it still feels like
I'm crawling through
a nightmare factory.
[grunts softly]
Hey, wait.
Don't...don't bats hang out
in caves?
There's no bats in this cave.
Blind salamanders maybe,
spiders for sure.
You know, you could have
just stopped after saying
there weren't bats.
[tense music]
Dad, this seemsa little narrow, no?
[Bennett sighs]
Well, they call it
"the Birth Canal."
Now, it's a tight squeeze,
but just beyond this passage,
the cave opens up
into a beautiful
cathedral of stone.
Every time,
it's like a rebirth,
and I won't let fear...whoa!
Whoa!
Ahh!
-Dad!
-[Bennett grunting]
-KEITHAN: Dad!
-KEITHAN: Are you okay?
-I'm okay.
[grunts]
I'm okay.
Grab my legs...
and I'll try to shimmy
out of here.
[suspenseful music]
[Keithan grunting]
[Bennett grunts]
[panting]
You're stuck.
Hey, Dad,
what are we gonna do?
BENNETT:
I need you to listen to me.
You need to climb out of here
and go get help.
You can do this, son.
I believe in you.
Now go, okay?
♪
[sirens wailing,
horn honks]
[dramatic music]
♪
My dad and I were crawling downthis tunnel when he slipped.
He fell face-first.
Now he's stuck up to his knees.I-I couldn't pull him out.
Do you know what angleyour dad got stuck at?
Were his legs like
this, this, or this?
Uh, like...like that.
♪
So do you rememberhow far in y'all went,
how far down, how many turns,any of that?
KEITHAN:
No.
No, it was dark,
and...and I was scared.
Wait.
Wait!
My dad called it
"the Birth Canal."
-Does that help?
-Yeah, it does, actually.
That's a great jobremembering that.
Please don't let him diedown there.
We're gonna do everything
we can to get him out.
In the meantime,
I want you to go get
those cuts looked at.
Paul, take Keithan down to EMS,have him checked out.
-PAUL: You got it, Cap.
-OWEN: All right.
So?
They got to seal
this thing up.
I've had three calls where
people got stuck down there.
Three calls?
How many saves?
How far down is it?
Uh, to the Birth Canal
is 80 feet.
All right,
let's get geared up!
Cap, Cap.
There's some 90-degree turnsin there
that ain't but two-feet wide.
Well, that excludes everybody
except...
[tense music]
♪
[Marjan groans]
This reminds of
that movie The Descent.
It's where these monsters
just jump out
and rip these spelunker chicks
in half...
-MARJAN: Hey, Mateo.
-MATEO: Yeah?
MARJAN:
Would you please stop?
MATEO:
Copy that.
MARJAN: Bennett!
Can you hear me?
BENNETT:
Oh. Oh, thank God!
Who's there?
My name's Marjan.
I have Mateo with me.
We're from Austin FD,
and we're gonna get you
out of here, okay?
[uneasy music]
Is Keithan okay?
MARJAN:
Yeah, he's doing fine.
He'll be a lot better
once you're up there, too.
MATEO:
I'ma toss this down, Marjan.
MARJAN: We're gonna pull you
out of here, all right?
BENNETT:
Okay.
MARJAN: You're doing good.
Just hang in there.
[grunts]
We're moving as fast as we can.
All right, Mateo, I'm gonna
throw this up to you.
Ready to catch?
MATEO:
Got it.
[suspenseful music]
MARJAN:
And pull!
♪
[Mateo grunts]
Come on.
-BENNETT: Ow! Ow!
-MARJAN: Okay, stop!
-MARJAN: Stop, stop, stop.
-BENNETT: Ow!
He's in there pretty good.
Okay, take that back up
to the surface
and drill in rope anchors
at every corner
so it doesn't snag.
MATEO: Okay.
What about you?
I need
to open this tunnel up.
[sighs]
Okay, Bennett, you're gonna
feel some vibrations,
and I have to warn you,
this may not feel good.
[chisel grinding]
[drill buzzing]
[Bennett groans]
[chisel grinding]
[dramatic music]
♪
Ow! Ow! Ow!
OWEN: We're starting
to lose light up here.
How we looking down there,
Marjan?
[grinding stops]
I just need to add
a little lube,
and we should be good to go.
♪
Okay.
I'm pouring soap solution
on you now
to reduce the friction.
How you holding up?
Eh, I can't...I can't...
I find it hard to breathe.
I don't know why.
My chest hurts.
MARJAN: Well, your lungs
weren't built to hold
the weight of your body.
But we're almost done.
-Okay.
-MARJAN: All right.
Here we go.
Do it, Cap.
Okay!
[tense music]
It's working.
-[yelling]
-MARJAN: Stop!
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
♪
Bennett, what happened?
My chest...there's a rock
protruding.
Can you flex your back
and lift yourself up?
I can't breathe.
Cap, we have a problem.
He's snagged on a rock,
and if he had
any strength left,
he could just lift
himself clear,
but he's about to asphyxiate.
Put the radio next to him.
Here, I want you to talk
to your father.
Ben, you still with me?
Okay, my cap wants you to hear
something.
KEITHAN:
Dad?
[gasps softly]
K-Keithan.
Look, I know
that you're tired...
and scared
and you just want to give up.
But come on,
like you said, right?
"If we face our fears,
there's nothing
we can't conquer," right?
[straining]
Right.
KEITHAN:
So, when they say "now,"
you got to give it
everything you got.
And, Dad...I love you.
[sniffles]
I love you, too.
[whimpers]
[stirring music]
Good job.
On three,
everything you've got.
One, two...
now!
♪
He's clear!
[grunting]
Send down a basket so we can
get him out of here.
[uplifting music]
♪
KEITHAN:
Dad!
I've never been so scared
in my life.
You did it.
You did it, son.
You saved me.
No, they did.
Your dad's right, he wouldn't
have made it without you.
KEITHAN:Thank you.
Keithan, you still scared
of a little internship?
-Hell, no.
-BENNETT: That's my boy.
♪
[bluesy music]
STUART: Oh, man,
I'm about fit to bust.
[chuckles]
Gracey,
this cobbler is one of
the many reasons that
you're my favorite
daughter-in-law.
[both laugh]
Well, thank you, Dad, so much.
Daddy, let me ask you this.
How come you alwaysgo on about her being
your favorite daughter,but you never say anything
about...about where I rankamong your favorite sons.
Oh, you're one
of the top three.
Top three, ah, damn.Wow.
Thank you.You want some coffee?
No, thanks.
It's getting late.
I guess I better be
hitting the road.
So hang on just a...
just a minute here,
'cause...
[exhales deeply]
We wanted to talk to you
just about what happened
the other night
over at your place.
What happened?
With you falling down
and everything.
[chuckles]
Well, shoot, that's nothing.
Well, you know,
we were talking.
That's the third time
you fell this year,
and that ain't including
the automobile accident
you got in last spring.
-JUDD: So...
-Well, I told you
that that's because
that nitwit cut me off.
The insurance company
agrees with me.
What...what's that got to do
with anything?
Well, we're just worried
about you, Dad.
That's all.
There's no reasonto worry about me.
Well...
we kind of see it different
than that, you know.
You...you being in
that big-ass house
all by yourself
is worrisome.
What's worrisome
about me being in my house?
I've been in that house
for 40 years.
I plan to die in that house.
Well, yeah, at this rate,it ain't gonna be long.
What the hell
do you mean by that?
You know exactly what it means.
If I hadn't come over therethe other night,
you'd still be on your keisterright now.
What the hell you say?
And who asked you
to come over anyway?
Oh, my God, you can bea stubborn old goat, man.
Judd...
What is this?
Y'all trying to get me
to move into a nursing home?
Is that it?
What are you talking
about a nursing home?
Hell, no, we're not.
We're saying that
we want you to have
a-a-a more manageable house
with fewer steps
that's closer to us.
I told you that
I want to stay in my house,
in myhouse.
Okay. Fine.
Would you at least
let us get you some help?
Look, I spent 30 years
on the rig, offshore,
in the Gulf of Mexico.
-I-I've worked through heat.
-I know.
I've worked through
hurricanes...
Yeah, I know 'cause you'rea real hard son of a bitch
and everybody knows that.
You know what? But you're not45 years old anymore.
You're 81, and you got goutand you got your arthritis
and God knows what else.
[sighing]
Gracey, that...this was...
a wonderful meal.
You...you really outdid
yourself.
Y'all have a wonderful evening.
♪
[door closes]
A car, sir?
ANDREW:
Harry, come down.
Okay, where is your son now?
-[siren wailing, horn honks]
-ANDREW: Hurry, hurry!
He's gonna get himself
killed up there.
[dramatic music]
♪
Hey, Harry's this way.
He was playing in his room.
I knew something was wrong
when it got quiet.
Too quiet?Yeah, I know that sound.
You must be a dad, too.
He put one of his toy cars
up his nose.
When I told him we needed to goto the emergency room,
he bolted.
Now he's up there.
He's very nimble.
All right, Judd,raise the ladder.
Paul, you're going up.
♪
PAUL: Hey, buddy.
I'm Paul.
I'm here to get you down.
[indistinct radio chatter]
No, I can't.I'm too scared.
It's bad.
Aw, come on, now, little man.
Let me take a look at you.
It's just a toy...
Okay.
I told you.It's bad, huh?
Nah, we, uh...we see stuff
like this all the time.
Mind if I, uh...
How exactly did you get
that in there?
The tires smell like cinnamon,and I really like cinnamon.
Apparently.
All right, well,
the good news, Harry,
is that your airways are clear.
So how about you let me
take you down, and we can...
No, if I go back down,
my dad says I'll have to goto the hospital.
What's wrong with the hospital?
That's where my mommy wentthe day she got the headache.
She never came home.
[somber music]
I see.
Look, I'm really sorry
about that.
Hey, how about
we make a deal?
If you come with me now,
you won't have to go anywhere.
-I won't?
-No, I can get it out for you.
But this is a "limited time,
expires immediately" offer.
Okay.
Okay, Harry, showtime.
Now, on the count of three,
I want you to blow your nose
like you have
the biggest booger
in the world in there, okay?
-Okay.
One, two, three.
Blow.
[Harry's nose squeaks]
-PAUL: Blow, blow.
-[Harry sighs]
HARRY: It didn't work.
It's okay, no worries.
It just means we're gonna have
to go to plan B,
where I use my special
"toy car removal" device.
Promise it won't hurt,though, right?
Uh, yep.
-You swear?
-Do I swear?
[mouths words]
I swear.
♪
Okay, buddy.
Here we go.
-Ow, ow.
-Yeah, okay.
-Ow, ow, ow.
-Yeah.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
-I know.
-Ow!
- [screams] Ow!
-Hey!
-PAUL: Got it!
-Hey.
-[Paul laughs]
- ANDREW: Huh.
Look, there's not even
any blood.
You lied!You promised it wouldn't hurt!
It hurts!
I'm...I'm sorry.
I didn't realize
that it was gonna...
-Wow, you lied to a child?
-You're a monster.
I-I kind of feel likea monster now.
Thank you.
Oh, don't tell me
he did it again, sir.
ANDREW:
Not exactly.
[knocking at door]
[dramatic music]
How?
After you left,
I kept wondering
how Harry got it
so far up there.
So you figured it out.
Tweezers.
[snaps fingers]
[doorbell rings]
[light music]
Hi.
-Hey.
-TK: Thanks for coming by.
-Please, come in.
-Yeah, don't mention it.
I actually teach a, uh...
a grad seminar down the road.
I really love this whole
new look you got going,
without all the tubes
coming out of your face.
-Oh.
-That's a joke.
I do that.
I joke.
Oh, right.Well, good one.
Uh, so you'rea psychology professor.
That must bepretty fascinating,
diving deepinto people's heads,
figuring outwhat motivates them and stuff.
I dig it, yeah.
TK: You know, firefighting's
the complete opposite,
always something new
and unexpected.
We never get to, you know,
really drill down on anything.
Um, can I get you an iced tea?
Sure, yeah,but I have to admit,
no one's ever reached outthrough my dot-EDU email
for iced tea before.
Right.
Um...
-So...
-ZOE: Thanks.
You and my dad...
♪
Sorry, was that a question?
You guys are good, right?
We're having fun.
But do you think it could be
something that turns into...
something?
What's going on here?
I just want my dad
to be happy,
in case, for some reason,
I'm ever...not around.
Are you planning ongoing into another coma?
No, no.
To be fair, this is
the second time this year
that I've almost died.
That's a long story.
What's going on?
What do you mean?
Why am I here?
♪
-Honestly?
-Uh-huh.
I'm not sure.
You know, I feel like
I-I really need
to talk someone, and, well,
you're a psychologist.
-So...
-I...mm...
I'm a professor of psychology
with a focuson human sexuality.
Oh.
But I'm alsoa really good listener.
Well, thank you.
I appreciate
any professional advice.
Okay, so who do younormally talk to
about these things?
Well, like, um,
I guess there is my boyfriend.
-Oh.
-Who I don't even really know
is my boyfriend, boyfriend.
-Uh-huh.
-It's all kind of new.
Um, nota professional diagnosis,
but I-I think I seewhat's happening here.
You do?
What's, um...
what's...what's happening?
Well, it's common when you have
a near-death experience...or two...
-Mm-hmm.
-Um...
you question your life choices.
But all I've ever wanted
was to be a firefighter,
ever since I was a kid.
I didn't mention that,actually.
But interesting you did.
♪
[tense music]
Grace, I got a callerasking for you specifically.
-For me?
-Won't talk to anyone else.
Line nine.
Okay, thank you, Zach.
[computer beeping]
This is Grace Ryder.
What's your emergency?
STUART: Gracey,
I'm...I'm cut up pretty good.
Stuart?
[stammers]
I got a little wobbly
and...and...and fell through
the coffee table.
Are you bleeding?
Yeah, like a stuck hog.
Where?
My arm a little bit,
but the bad one is...
is on my leg.
Okay, are you bleeding
above or below the knee?
-STUART: Below.
-Well, that's better.
Listen, um, the cabinet
that's behind you
in the dining room,
can you get to it?
-I'm...I'm right next to it.
-GRACE: Okay.
Helen kept the nice tableclothsin the bottom drawer.
Grab one, press it up
-against the wound, okay?
-I got it.
GRACE:
As hard as you can.
Ah!
[grunts]
-Is that working?
-No, no, Gracey.
It...it...I'm pressing
as hard as I can,
and it's still bleeding.
Um...new plan.
Grab the candlestick
from the table.
-The candlestick?
-GRACE: Mm-hmm.
The brass holder.  We're gonna make a tourniquet.
Oh, o-okay.
I got it.
Okay, loop the tablecloth
around your thigh.
Place the candlestick
across the loop,
tie a knot around it.
Okay.
There.
[grunts]
Okay, now rotate the stick.
That should tighten
the knot, okay?
Keep going until
the bleeding stops.
Okay.
[grunts]
[whimpering]
It...it's working, Gracey.
It's working.
Okay.
All right.
Well, you just hang tight.
-[siren wailing]
-[whimpers]
The...the paramedics are here.
I-I can hear 'em.
Okay.
Okay, well, they're gonna
take good care of you, Dad.
STUART:
Gracey, thank you!
-You're...you're a lifesaver.
-[knocking at door]
Gracey?
GRACE:
Yeah?
STUART: Judd doesn't have
to know about this, does he?
[computers beeping]
♪
You guys are infor a treat tonight.
In what kind
of a demented universe
is quinoa a treat?
-[Paul laughs]
-I think it's farro, actually.
Come on, it's chock-full
of proteins,
antioxidants, and vitamins.
-You're gonna love it.
-Vitamins, yum.
Don't knock it
till you try it,
you bunch of ingrates.
[Buttercup whines]
-JUDD: Yo!
-MARJAN: Hey!
If it isn't Sleeping Beauty.
-TK: Hi.
-Hey.
-Hi.
-PAUL: My man.
-Hey, dude.
-Good to see you, man.
Good to see you, brother.
Thanks, guys.
[sighs]
-Ooh, ooh, ooh. Mateo.
-Oh, I'm so sorry.
-MATEO: Oh.
-TK: Shoulder.
Son, are you sure
you should be on your feet?
Yeah.
Can we talk?
Yeah, sure.
MATEO: Yeah, yeah,
looking good, kiddo.
MARJAN: Look who it is.Look who's back.
Don't forget about me.Don't forget about me.
OWEN:
How you doing?
Are you okay?
Is everything all right?
TK:
Yeah, yeah, everything's fine.
I'm good.
TK, I know your
"everything's fine" face
and that is not it.
I need to ask you a question.
OWEN: Sure.
Why'd you decide to be
a firefighter?
Why?
'Cause the Yankeeswouldn't take me,
and who wants to playfor the Mets?
Dad, I'm serious.
Did you always know
that this is
what you wanted to do?
Mm, not always.
I was gonna be a lawyer.
Really?
Why did I not know this?
Probably because I dropped out
of law school
the second year,
joined the fire academy,
and married your mom.
One lawyer in the house
was plenty.
Hmm.
So what changed your mind?[grunts]
Well, the summer
before I dropped out,
I had a job in East Hampton
as a lifeguard.
For the chicks.
-For the chicks.
-[TK laughs]
But mostly,
I just sat in the tower
and got very, very bronze.
I never had any chance
to even get in the water
except one time.
[solemn music]
There was this little girl.
She was probably seven
or eight.
And she was out
with her mother,
and they'd gone
beyond the buoys.
And before I had a chance
to blow my whistle,
they got caught in a riptide,
and they both went under.
Mom came up,
little girl didn't.
And I don't remember
jumping in.
I was just there.
[clicks tongue]
And, um...
I got 'em both
back to the beach.
Little girl was not breathing.
She was turning blue.
Mm.
And my several hours
of training...
training I thought
I'd slept through...kicked in,
CPR, mouth-to-mouth, and...
it worked.
I could feel myself
breathing life
into this tiny, little body.
And when she coughed up
seawater
and started breathing
on her own,
it was the most satisfying
moment of my life,
up to that point.
And I dropped out of law schoolthree months later.
You're an addict, just like me.
You are chasingthat first high.
Well, I don't...I think
it's more than that.
I think I realized
that being of service is a way
to give my life some meaning.
♪
Yeah, I can see that.
And all I've ever wantedwas to be a firefighter
for as long as I can remember.
I didn't plan anything else.
I didn't consideranything else.
I knew exactly what I wanted.
At least, I thought I did.
Lately, I've been wondering
if maybe whatI really wanted...
was a father.
TK...
Dad, you leftwhen I was seven.
TK, I didn't leave you.
Yeah, you did.You left our family.
That firehouse was your family.
That's the familythat you chose.
Do you want me to apologize
for the choices I made?
No, no.
343 firefighters lost
their lives on that day.
14 of them were from my house.
♪
I don't knowwhat I'm trying to say, Dad.
What you're saying is,
is you're not sure
if you want to come back.
I'm saying I don't knowif...if I can come back.
I don't knowif this is really who I am.
♪
That's not a question
I can help you answer.
I know.
♪
Well, you're right
about one thing.
The firehouse is my family...
and the 126 is
my adopted family,
but you...
are my kid.
And whatever you choose,
I'm gonna be
right by your side.
Well, good, because...
there is somethingthat I want you to do with me.
Hey.
Thank you for seeing us.
I can only imagine what your
family's been going through.
Nothing compared to what
yours has been dealing with,
Captain.
[sighs]
I can't tell you
how sorry we are.
I mean, Colt has just been
sick over it.
You've been in our prayers.
Thank you.
That...that means a lot.
Colt...Mr. Strand is hereto see you.
[birds chirping]
Hey, Colt.
How are you, buddy?
[gentle music]
♪
Hey, uh, Colt.
Do you mind if I join you?
♪
[grunts]
I used to love LEGOs, too.
What are you building
over there?
Police car.
Very cool.
You like cops?
They help people.
Yes, they do.
♪
I think that's a...
that's a three-bump one.
I think you need a four-bump.
Here, try this one.
♪
COLT: Thanks.
Colt, do you know who I am?
♪
I shot you.
Yeah, you did.
But you know what?
I'm here, and I'm okay.
And I just want to make sure
that you're okay, too.
So you're not mad at me?
No, no, not at all.
I know it was an accident.
Besides, you were protecting
your family,
which is super brave.
Sorry I shot you.
I know you are.
I won't do it again.
[laughs]
Okay.
Deal.
Deal?
♪
TK:
Hey, thanks for coming.
I don't think I realized
how much I needed that.
You know, in 26 years,
I don't think I've ever beenmore proud of you.
You're gonna makea great dad someday.
And so will you.
JUDD:Hey, Daddy.
[chuckles]
Look, I brought you "Suduko"...one of them puzzles you like
and then that Tom Landry bio
you've been trying to getthrough.
[monitor beeping]
You told him, huh?
-[inhales sharply]
-Squealer.
[chuckles]I'm sorry, Dad.
There are no secretsin this marriage.
Have I told you lately
she's my favorite?
-You and me both.
-[chuckles]
How you feel?
Ah, the doc says I lost
a whole mess of red blood cells
and I'll feel like hammered
crap for a couple of weeks
till my bone marrow
makes more of them.
Well, I just thank Godthat you're okay.
Let's hear it.
-Hear what?
-Riot act.
You're gonna tell me that I'm
not fit to live by myself,
and now you've got proof of it.
I mean, if what you're sayingis that this don't look good,
I agree.
Your mom and I
made that house our home.
We raised you
and your brothers there.
I'd rather die than leave it.
Okay.
What...what the hell does
that mean..."okay"?
It means okay.
I responded to a call
where a 35-year-old manput a toy car up his nose.
-[laughs]
-Okay.
So what I'm saying is,people are gonna do
whatever they're gonna dowherever they are.
You know...
I-I can't worryabout what I can't control.
Now, if you want
to live at home, Dad,
Judd and I are all for it.
And why is it that I smell
a "but" in there somewhere?
Mm, because
we have conditions.
Uh-huh.
What kind of conditions?
Well, for one,we are installing shower rails.
Sure are, yeah.
And, um...
Wow.
You get to wear this now, too.
I don't want to hear about it.Just put it on.
[groans and scoffs]
Because next time you mightnot make it to the phone, Dad.
[upbeat music]
All right.
I have a condition, too.
What do you want, big man?
When are y'all gonna give me
a grandbaby?
[laughing]
Well, what the hell
are you waiting for?
[stammering]
I think that, Grace, we haveplenty to worry about, uh...
for the time being, you know,ain't that right?
Oh, do we?
That's my girl!
-Y'all gonna team up on me?
-I got you, Dad.
-Don't worry.
-[laughter]
ANNOUNCER:
See 9-1-1 Lone Star.
Don't miss all-new episodes
Mondays on Fox.