Subtitles by:
omz007
AFRO SAMURAI
Episode 4
Add one more
body to the body toll.
May God rest this
poor bastard's soul.
Yo, Afro! Ain't you
gonna say nuthin'?
I'm talking to you.
I said I'm talking to you!
Long time, no see, Afro.
Hey, correct me if I'm wrong,
But, I don't think a teddy bear is
supposed to be walking around
a damn kimono strapped with blades.
I got a bad feeling about this.
You don't want to be
messing with this guy, Afro.
I'm telling you, man.
That sh*t ain't natural!
He might look cute and all,
but I got a suspicion this one's a pro!
He for real!
Look, I know you got mad skills and all
and I ain't trying to be pessamistic here,
But you headed
straight to the dirt nap.
[coughing] Please!
This time you could really bite
it, and I ain't going with you!
You sure about this?
Because if you is...
Suit yourself.
Oh, man!
Hey hey hey hey...
Yo yo yo!
Yo wait up, wait up, hold up!
Damn, you one
stubborn samurai.
Com'on man, chill, listen to
what I gotta say for once, please.
Ooooh, watch it!
He about to bust a two
sword move on you.
Oh, watch ya left, man.
No no no no no, watch ya right!
Why do you not draw
out your sword?
If you want the Number
One, you must first defeat me.
You have come to defeat
the Number One, haven't you?
If you wear the Number Two
band, then you must fight.
' the hell?
Perhaps the rumors of the
Afro Samurai are not true,
That he cuts all that
stand in his path,
That his only
movement is forward.
But you just look like
an afro headed coward!
Come to think of it, I can't even take a
warrior with such stupid hair seriously!
Afro!
What the dealio B'?
If you gonna run, run!
If you gonna fight,
then damnit, fight!
Such a fleeting moment in time...
Nothing remains,
Everything ends!
One!
There is no such thing as killing
with strength or speed only.
Kill the enemy with one calm, powerful stroke.
Two.
The only form is action. Striking without
thought is the only way to kill the enemy.
Stop!
Listen.
The point of dueling is to kill
your enemy.
Not twisting and turning, demonstrating
flowery form.
The only position is no position.
Where you hold your sword depends
on your relationship with your opponent
on the terrain and the situation.
Act as the sea when the enemy
is like the mountain.
Act as the mountain when the enemy
is like the sea.
Keep this in mind, all of you.
Yes Master!
Real attacks are not static or with
cooperative opponents.
Stick with the moves you've
learned in class and you will die.
Even a glancing blow can unbalance
your opponent and cripple his next
offensive.
Hey, Jinno.
I have a question.
Why do you use two
swords instead of one?
With two I can be
the best, Otsuru.
See, there're
lots of reasons.
For example, it's great if you ever
have to fight more than one opponent
at a time.
You see, with two smaller blades,
I can swing faster than a guy with
both hands on one big sword.
And I can attack and
defend at the same time.
I could even fight if one of my arms got
cut off, 'cause I'd still have one left.
It's really the ultimate fighting style.
Hmm?
Oops, sorry. Guess I
got a little carried away.
I'm... done.
Was your meal yummy Afro?
Jinno.
You're really serious about
sword fighting, aren't you?
Of course.
I have to protect everyone.
You. Afro.
All the students here.
When Sword Master
is too old to fight,
I'm gonna have to be strong
enough to look after this place.
I heard some pip-squeak's been
running loose, killing assassins.
That pip-squeak wouldn't happen
to be a kid like this one we've got
here, would it?
I think we got a match here, boys.
Eh, pip-squeak?
Wanna know where I
can find the Number Two.
Dunno nuthin' about it.
So what're you gonna
do about that?
'Cause you see, we're
on the same path, kid.
Rumors of the Number
Two led us to this dump.
And we can't have no
kid chasing our prize.
Afro!
Jinno!
What have you gotten yourself into?
Okay, you and I are
gonna talk about this later.
But first, I gotta
save your dumbass.
You son of a-
Afro!
Tell me what you know!
Where's the Number Two?
Number Two... is quite near...
Oh, it's you again.
There you go, sonny.
You just can't get enough
lemonade, can you?
Afro.
Forget avenging your father.
Live your own life.
Otsuru cares about you,
I care about you.
We're your family now.
Look at that.
So beautiful.
Wow.
Oh man.
Say, you reckon I could be as strong as Master?
With your skills Sasuke?
I'd say it'll take at least 50 years.
50 years!
Whoa! Check out that one!
To get as strong as Master takes
time.
His training must've been a
100 times harder than ours.
Man! I could be dead in 50 years.
Or even worse than that, old.
Dead. Man, Sasuke. Why do you
always have to be so dang morbid?
He is right in a way though.
I mean we can't know for sure if
any of us will be around 50 years
from now.
Or even, 10 years from now.
So there's no use in worrying about
being as good as the Sword Master.
That's why you always have to
live and fight like it's your last day
or eat like it's your last meal.
Wow. Cool. Wow.That is so bright!
Man, I sure hope my last meal
has lots of mushrooms in it.
I want my last meal to be absolutely
smothered in chili peppers.
Oh man. I could go for a chicken
cutlet.
Afro, what about you? What do
you want?
Afro wants linamode. Right Afro?
Otsuru, it's lemonade, not linamode.
That's not a meal Otsuru. Huh?
It's ok.
What would you like on your last
day?
I want those! Those fireworks
are my favorite kind.
Good day, sir.
Well, hello there.
Thank you always for
your kind business with us.
Say, that Sword Master of yours...
Is he alright?
Huh?
On the festival evening, I heard
that some rogue tried to start up
a fight with him.
There are some odd
talks around the town.
That some sword dojo master is the
owner of the Number Two headband...
And they say that his students have
been brainwashed to be watchdogs.
What? Our Sword
Master wouldn't!
Sorry! Sorry.
I didn't mean to...
I mean there are plenty of other
Sword Masters everywhere,
So it must be some other man.
Jinno.
Did I wake you?
You should get some rest.
Master...
I smell blood.
I was attacked, but that
fool lost his life instead.
Sasuke.
Jinno.
Afro.
On this day, we commemorate
your graduation.
You are now great warriors.
Use wisely the sword
skills you have acquired.
Master.
Yes, Afro?
There is something
I would like to know.
Afro.
Are you really Number Two?
After the midnight, before
the Boulè Tree, I will be waiting.
I meant to take the secret to the
grave, but I see I have no choice.
Choose, Afro Samurai!
Forget revenge...
Or fight me to the death for
the Number Two headband!
But know you well this truth.
If you win, you
will know no friend.
No joy. No love.
Only the murderous violence the Number
Two headband incites in the heart of every
man who desires the power of the Number One.
Truly, can you
handle that burden?
Afro!
Master, what's going on?
Master, please stop!
Afro, what are you doing?
Master?
There he is!
Quit your wasting your
time with that kid!
Jinno.
Fight us!
The Number Two headband is mine!
Master?
Jinno.
Take everyone and run.
Run and live.
Now you will see what it means
to wear the Number Two headband.
Master!
No!
Fool! Stay out of this!
Master!
Stay away from me!
Let's see what you've got.
Playtime's over, kiddies.
Sasuke! No!
Jiro! Matasaburo!
Otsuru!
Jinno!
Jinno...
Afro.
You have chosen your path.
Afro...
No... Don't...
Why?
Why did you kill our Master?
What have you done?
She's dead, and you...
You chose revenge over our Master.
Over everyone.
We're your family. Why?
For my... true father.
What about us?
I...
Treated you as my brother.
I will never forgive you.
Jinno!
Hey Afro.
Boo.
What you're waiting for?
You really sure that's
the right decision?
I mean, if you don't wanna
wear it, it's okay man.
Don't do it man, seriously.
Don't do it.
Damn, there goes
the neighborhood...
Good. I'm glad you've
lasted this long.
I want you to die slowly.
I want you to burn,
bleed, suffer as I have.
Come on! What is
taking so long?
Just finish him off!
I take orders from no one!
How dare you?
You will obey my orders
and finish the Afro.
You must not fail as
the Empty Seven have.
Don't compare me to them.
I don't care about
the useless headband.
I just want Afro!
I want him hurt!
I want him crippled!
He'll bleed for all the pain he's caused.
Do what you want, then.
You don't know
how long I've waited.
To avenge the deaths of those
who loved and trusted you!
My tears have
never stopped falling.
Since that day.
Jinno.
TO BE CONTINUED...
AFRO
SAMURAI
Subtitled for your Enjoyment by: omz007
Downloadable From SUBSCENE.COM