Subtitles by:
omz007
AFRO SAMURAI
Episode : 2
You can't get away, kid.
Don't make it hard on yourself.
Be a good boy and hand that Number
Two headband over nice and slow-like...
Stop right there, Kiddo.
You draw that sword and you're dead.
What the hell is with you kid?
You gotta learn to respect your elders.
Lookee here,
now I'm the Number Two warrior.
I'm coming for you, Number One.
What the hell is this?
This kid is really some kind of freak.
He's carrying a rotten head around
in his backpack.
Ew ! Wait a minute!
I know that guy!
Yeah, that's the old Number One.
Yeah you're right.
Here, give it to me.
You want this back kiddo?
Then catch!
Kids these days...
Yeah, they got no respect.
- Yeah, no respect at all.
Hey, wake up! Wake up! Wake up!
Oh sleepyhead! Hey Jinno, you
should come look at this!
Wow, check this out!
Some piece of work.
He won't wake up, Jinno!
What? Whoa!
Master! Master!
The bandits must have got him.
This is bad! Two guys yesterday,
and now a kid.
He is not a morning person.
My God! He's alive!
Master! Master! He's alive!
Mr. Sleepy.
Don't get up yet.
You've been badly wounded and
poisoned.
It will take some time for you to
recover.
We discovered you bleeding on
the river bank.
I am called Okiku.
You must rest, mighty samurai.
I will take care of you.
Don't be alarmed.
Of course we know you're a samurai.
For who else but a samurai could
clutch his sword in a raging river...
While poisoned, unconscious,
and with a broken hand.
Sleep... When you awake,
I'll have a meal prepared.
Damn, you're one lucky dawg, Afro!
You look like a mummy.
- Cut it out, Otsuru.
Do not worry, young Afro.
In my dojo, we are all wounded orphans.
You are among friends.
Treat him well, my students.
Yes Master!
Go! Go! Go!
Strike the ground with yourself.
How can you wield a sword if you can't
dig a hole?
You're mad at the dirt Jinno?
Your body is all stiff. Think less. Relax.
I'll stay calm and constantly flowing.
Like a river.
Cheer up, Afro.
Oh! I see we up!
Think I wasn't gonna find you?
I just took a little R and R but
look at you, boy!
Oh bright eyed and bushy tailed,
fish, flowers, sunshine...
I see somebody getting their little resort on.
HA HA!!!
Hoo, I bet ya that babe will...
wa-wa-what's her name? Okiku!
Bet she tastes a hell of a lot better
than trout!
Don't think I didn't notice her
checking you out?
Huh? Huh? Don't tell me...
You ain't noticed?
This place is bananas! Sh*t.
I'm thinking, sh*t, I'm even gonna
find me a little hottie to go kick it with...
Beats and cold, cool massage...
Get all sweaty...
If ya know what I mean.
She got a friend, maybe we can do an orgy.
Y'know, huh!? Huh!?
Awrightawrightawrightawrightawright, alright.
So you ain't the swinging type! Alright!
I still can get my sex on!
You know gettin' your jimmie waxed
might help you recuperate.
All right, all right, you relax.
You wanna do your night solo on
the low-low?
Cool! Don't forget, my cellie's off!
You must not fight over food.
Come on, Afro.
We're all waiting on you dude.
We got fishing duties, down at
the river.
Don't you remember? Come on.
We're gonna be late.
You know how everyone gets
when there's not enough fish
to eat around here.
Look, I don't mean to push. But,
you really oughta wolf it down.
You'll need all your strength.
Tricking fish ain't easy.
Wolf 'em down!
Come on!
Let's get to it!
Look, they're escaping!
Let's grab 'em!
- Yeah!
Yeah! grab 'em !
You're ready for this, Otsuru?
Yeah, a fish!
Nice and fat... just like the doctor ordered.
It's what the master calls the single beat.
Well, cook it up!
Then we can have a quadruple treat!
But there are six of us.
Isn't that a sextuplet treat?
Huh?
uh... I mean...
Oh, I must have disturbed you in
the middle of a dream.
Was it pleasant?
Forgive me, I'm being nosy.
It's time for you medicine.
Your wounds heal well, master samurai.
So tonight, I will cook my special
fish for you.
You do like fish, don't you?
Fresh vegetables! Fresh vegetables!
Not interested kid. Beat it.
No luck today. Let's go home, Afro.
So, 'bout Number Two... Is it true?
That's what they say.
Apparently, he's back in town.
Maybe I'll give it a shot.
Whatever. Like you got what it
takes to be the Number Two warrior
of the world.
What the f*ck?
What's this kid doing here?
Where is the Number Two?
Who?
The Number Two headband, tell
me who has it.
Er, I don't know what you're talking about.
Tell me where he is.
You little c*ck sucker!
You think you're a killer, boy? Huh?
I'll show you a killer.
When you fight to kill, finish the job.
Target is confirmed.
Yes, he's still injured. An easy prey
for my skills.
Yes, I understand your point...
But! My master brother, I would
give my life to work in your inner circle.
Can you do it?
Yes, please let me slay the Afro Samurai.
Your supper is ready.
What's the matter?
Thanks for everything.
You're leaving?
Tomorrow.
Please, keep it for your travels.
Thank you.
Will you not stay with me?
For just, one more day?
There'll be a summer festival
tomorrow night at the village below.
If it's not too much to ask.
Will you stay and watch the
fireworks with me?
Foolish boy!
Never speak to me of such things
again!
Games of power or revenge, they
lead to nothing!
Do you really know what it
means to be the Number Two?
It is a life of murder.
We are born men in order to live,
not to kill.
You must break the chain.
Only then can we be free of this
terrible cycle.
What is this?
Swampwater.
Just try it.
Will it put hair on my chest?
Eww. eww! Taste like crap!
Here Afro, you try it.
ewwww...
This boy's the only one with real taste.
Can I have some more?
Is he for real!
Afro, you don't have to be polite.
It's like I always say, if heaven could
be bottled, it just might taste like my
lemonade.
Le.. na.. mode?
Lemonade...
Lemonade.
Jinno - Lemonade.
Otsuru - Lemonade
Hey kid! We know it was
you that killed our brother.
Too bad you have to pay for it!
You little son of a b*tch.
What the... huh?
Hey, that's my knife!
How did you...
You little...
You ain't gonna get away from me!
This can't be...
I got him!
Good. Don't let him get away.
Now let's see you spit swamp water,
brat.
You are dead now.
Hey shorty!
What was that?
What did you just call me?
Sh*t!
Afro!
Yeah !
- Leave him alone!
Behind you!
Afro!
F*ckin' brats! What the...
Sh*t, it's stuck! Damn it!
I'll kill you!
Holy smoke!
Killing some little kid is
normally against my principles.
But when you cut my pal's brother,
you enter the world of killing, boy.
Before I kill you, remember this.
If you're gonna swing a sword,
you better be ready to get cut by
one too.
Say your prayers...
Damn it!
You missed!
You piece of sh*t!
Freaking kid... I should have...
Do you know where Number Two is?
What was that?
I want to see Number Two.
What for?
To kill him! I'll kill him!
Stop laughing and tell me!
He's already dead.
What?
There's a new Number Two.
You'll never find him.
He's probably long gone.
Yes. Yes.
No, I need more time.
I haven't acquired that data yet.
What I do have has been
downloaded onto my cellphone.
Yes. Yes. Understood.
Sorry.
Okiku.
Are you there?
Yes.
What is the matter, disciple Okiku?
Nothing.
Everything will be taken care of.
Yes, hello, Brother 2 here.
Yo yo yo yo yo, Afro.
Can I ask you something?
I know you cast away your feelings
and all...
But does that mean casting
away your manhood too?
Hoo my massage don't get
much better than no girl...
She's sweet, pretty, knows a first
aid, can brawl a mean fish dinner!
I call that practically marriage material.
Come on now, confess.
You wanna hit that booty.
I just wanna see my boy happy, you know.
Seriously man! Now don't you think there's
something vaguely familiar about that woman?
Look. If you ain't gonna
knock them boots, I will.
Go on then.
Care for some?
It's lemonade. Do you like it?
I do.
I'm glad.
Oh, they're beautiful.
This is my favorite time of the
year, fireworks and the festivities.
The people coming and going.
Everyone just simply having a good time.
May I ask where you're traveling to,
mighty samurai?
East.
Oh, don't you love the sky, they're
my favorite.
It's all because of you!
Forgive me ! I've become
a ninja of the Empty Seven clan!
I've been siphoning your
memories to copy your sword skills.
But I can't.
I can't do it anymore.
Tell me you're still that same boy
from those wonderful times so long ago.
Get out of my way.
Otsuru.
Run Afro!
Otsuru!
You f*ckin' whore! This is the price
you pay for your betrayal.
The data...
We have obtained the data!
That's enough, Brother 6!
We are leaving!
Damn shame, ain't it?
Just when you start getting your
groove on, sh*t always gotta get
killed, burnt down, or whatever!
Hey, ya know your afro got a little
scorched there, homie?
You listening to me?
Ha! Man, you really are a cold-blooded
motherf*cker!
Hey, how about we keep this little a...
momento of your lady friend, huh?
TO BE CONTINUED...
AFRO SAMURAI
Subtitled for your Enjoyment by:
omz007
Downloadable From SUBSCENE.COM
Subscene.com Afro Samurai Subtitles Page:
http://subscene.com/
Afro-Samurai--Mini/subtitles-69700.aspx