Don't worry about that, all right?
Look down. Look at the grass.
Kick off your shoes like this.
When was the last time you did that?
Feels good, right?
Yeah.
Grass between your toes.
Feels nice.
- Yeah.
Well, I think maybe...
Maybe it's time we go in.
We got a lot of work to do. We need
to get ready. You need to get ready.
If I were Schweikart and Cokely,
I'd seek a restraining order.
Turn this into a civil harassment issue.
Schweikart and Cokely can come
after me with a restraining order...
or anything else they got, I'll be ready.
Confidence is good.
Facts on your side, better.
Know what you're walking into.
- House needs a coat of paint.
- Yeah.
sync and corrections by othelo
addic7ed.com
I got her all her shots.
Healthy gums. And no worms. No fleas.
I promise you, if the little sucker
has fleas, I'll kick her butt myself.
Yeah, it's just, a dog...
Hey, it's good to have a dog around.
Bad guys think twice about
breaking into a house with a dog.
Yeah, I bet that one's gonna
keep a lot of burglars away.
It's just a thought.
You know, you can always
keep her over at my place.
Kaylee can visit her any time she wants.
Well, if you decide to keep her...
I got a giant bag of puppy
chow out in the car for you.
All the supplies. Everything you need.
All right.
What's that?
The dog can stay here.
You sure?
Yes.
Thank you.
All right. Done.
Excuse me a minute.
Yeah?
Sure.
Yup.
Got it.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. Just a lead on a job opportunity.
Your Honor, Mr. Schweikart and
his cohorts are attempting...
- to keep me away from their victims.
- Victims?
My clients. Yes. You're
denying me access.
Even the worst prisoners in this
building are allowed access to a lawyer.
Are you saying my poor, elderly clients
have fewer rights than jail inmates?
Not at all. And no one is denying
Mr. McGill access to his clients.
- We're denying access to the property.
- It's semantics.
Within Sandpiper Crossing's rights.
The building is private property.
- Paid for by the residents.
- But managed by licensed professionals.
Okay. One at a time, gentlemen.
Mr. Schweikart, you're denying
him access on what grounds?
These assisted living residents have
a daily routine that they're used to.
Mr. McGill, who is loud and flamboyant,
is a disturbance to these routines.
Residents who want to see a lawyer,
free to leave whenever they want.
Leave whenever they want? We're talking
about elderly and infirm people here.
The most common phrase in this place?
"I've fallen and I can't get up."
There's phone consultations.
There's mail and messenger services.
Plenty of ways to confer with clients.
But for residents who don't want to be
afflicted with Mr. McGill's presence...
this becomes an issue
of civil harassment.
Wow, you are stretching
that definition to its limit.
And FYI, old people adore me.
Okay. I've heard enough.
I have enough here to let me
rule on this restraining order.
Yeah. Don't worry, Chuck. That's
not smoke you smell. That's me.
This mo-fo is on fire. Your baby
bro kicked some Schweikart ass today.
What the hell's all this?
There was a delivery
while you were in court.
Schweikart and Cokely
sent this? What is it?
The served interrogatories
on each class representative.
This box is deposition notices.
Documents calling into question the
mental health of our elderly clients.
Attempting to stop the
class from being certified...
on the grounds they're not competent.
Oh, this is just the beginning.
They're gonna continue this document
dump until we're drowning in paperwork.
All right. We can deal
with this. I mean, hey.
It's... It's just paperwork. Right?
- It's no big deal. Just hit it head on.
- Jimmy.
Prioritize. The most
important stuff first.
Or is it better to deal
with the easy stuff?
You know, get that off the decks.
You tell me, Chuck. You just
point to a box. We can do this.
- Jimmy, we need to talk.
- Chuck.
- Sit down, won't you?
- No, I'm good.
I know you're not gonna
like what I have to say next.
But facts are facts.
And what we're facing here...
A case this size, it is not
a two man job. We need help.
- No.
- And for the good of the clients...
- we need to refer this case...
- Don't say it.
Refer it out to HHM.
Damn it, Chuck. No. Come on.
We can do this. We're
doing great on our own.
We don't need Hamlin or
anyone else. I mean, hey.
We can Erin Brockovich
the shit out of this case.
Erin Brockovich didn't do it alone.
She and Ed Masry brought
in heavy hitters...
from Los Angeles to get that
case across the goal line.
And that's what we need to do.
And there's no shame in that.
This is our case.
Yes, it's ours. And the
task ahead is monumental.
Could we do it alone?
Could two men alone build
the Brooklyn Bridge? Maybe.
But it would take forever.
Just how long do you think the
residents of Sandpiper Crossing have?
Referring this case to HHM is
for the good of the clients.
That argument you won today
against the restraining order...
the judge was never gonna grant that.
Schweikart is throwing softballs.
And he's gonna keep on
throwing them over and over.
We'll be busy swatting them away, we'll
never spend time on the actual case.
This case will span years.
And we don't have the capital
to carry it forward by ourselves.
We simply don't.
- Fine.
- So?
The case goes to HHM?
Hail Satan. I submit to the dark side.
I'll call Kim and arrange a meeting.
All right. Good, Jimmy. Thank you.
I know you'll come to see
that it's for the best.
I guess I'll have to get an
office right next to yours.
Finally out of the mailroom, huh?
Yes. Hello.
No. It's me.
- This the place where we wait?
- Think so.
So.
What'd our guy tell you about the job?
Not much.
It's a protection job. Civilian.
Guy is as green as they come, but we'll
be in there to make sure things fly right.
You been doing this long? I just
assume we're all heavy hitters.
And it makes sense. The vet
recommends the best of the best.
Dealing with some of these ethnic types,
blood tends to run a little hotter.
That's just science. Physiology.
There's historical precedent.
Know what I'm saying?
So, what you packing?
- A pimento.
- Sorry, what?
Pimento sandwich.
That's funny. Pimento.
No, I mean, what are you carrying?
You know, the piece? What's the make?
Pimento is a cheese. They call
it the caviar of the south.
You don't want to tell me
what you're carrying, so be it.
But you don't have to
be a douche about it.
Just told you what I'm carrying.
So you're saying you don't have a gun?
Is that what you're saying?
How are you here without a gun?
- You have a gun?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Of course. He's got a gun.
I got at least two guns on
me that I'll tell you about.
I go old school with
a Wilson Combat 1911.
I got a Glock 22 Gen 3. And those
are just the ones I'll tell you about.
I mean, what the hell? Really?
How do you not pack a gun?
Hi. Hello. My name is Price.
Actually, that's not my name.
But I have a nephew named Price.
I've always kind of liked that name.
Anyway, we're not
dealing with names today.
You can tell me or not tell me
yours. Or a fake one is fine.
If I need to talk to you, I'd prefer
something other than "Hey, you."
Either way, you all come
highly recommended so thank you.
First order of business, we
have a long drive ahead of us.
I have a cooler of water in
the car, some soft drinks.
I don't drink coffee, but
there is a diner on the corner.
Also a bathroom in there in
case you need to go before we go.
Second order. Money.
Just to be clear that the agreed
upon fee of $500 per man is...
agreed upon.
- If that's acceptable...
- Yeah, I have a thought.
Yeah.
How about you give me
and Man Mountain 750 each?
And send Uncle Fester there home.
He's not carrying a gun. He's useless.
- Is that true? You didn't bring a gun?
- I didn't think I'd need one.
It's a protection job.
It's basic common sense that you
need a gun to protect your employer.
You're dead weight.
- He's just a third wheel without a piece.
- I'll tell you what.
If I need a gun, I'll use one of his.
Really? One of my guns? How do
you picture that happening exactly?
Well, I guess I'm gonna take it from you.
That... That is just special.
Take. How are you gonna
take one of my guns?
Come on, Billy Jackoff.
Take my gun from me.
Let me see it.
Here. I'll make it easy for you.
You can make it not so easy.
Sure thing.
You got it.
What the...? Son of a...
Okay. Let's see what you got.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. A guy like you...
I'll bet you'd have an
ankle holster, wouldn't you?
You know, that's cute. What else?
Wow, now, that's impressive.
So many guns, I don't
know which one to use.
How about you? You want one?
All right.
Let's go.
- But we need three guys.
- No. No, we don't. Come on. Let's go.
Oh, he'll be fine.
And now that I'm doing the job alone, I
get the full 1,500. We agree upon that?
Sure.
You got this, okay? No problem.
Yes.
- Suit okay? Is it too tight or too hot?
- Yeah.
No, I mean. No. No. It's good.
Well, you look good.
Can't even tell that's under there.
It was a good idea.
Yeah. At any point, it's too
much, you're uncomfortable...
we'll turn around and come home.
You want maybe like a safe word?
How about "get me the hell home"?
That'll work. Okay.
Let's do this.
Okay.
Looking good.
We're just going for a little ride.
Here. Let me get that for you.
Here you go.
- Jimmy.
- Just a sec.
- Oh, crap.
- What is it?
I must have left my stupid
phone on last night. It's dead.
Well, could you put it in the trunk?
Yeah.
Okay. Thanks.
That everyone?
They'll be here in one minute.
Anyone still have a phone,
add it to the collection now.
- Okay. Shut it down.
- Okay. You got it.
- How you doing? You doing all right?
- Yeah.
Okay. Great stuff.
Okay. We're walking. Walking in, Chuck.
Here we go.
- Good to see you. Welcome home.
- Howard, you didn't need to do all this.
Oh, I couldn't have
stopped them if I wanted to.
- Come on, let's get you upstairs.
- Yeah. Sure.
Francis. Brenda. Jose, you shaved.
To date, we have 68 very
willing plaintiffs...
signed to the class-action with hopes
of raising that number to 350 or more.
Many more, now that we know Sandpiper
has facilities in five states.
Fraud, unfair and deceptive
trade practices, and racketeering.
Jesus. Guys, this is...
Well, no case is ever a slam dunk.
But I feel as confident about this as
anything that's come through our doors.
Francis, put together teams to travel
out of state. Talk to these residents.
Pair fourths with our best second years.
Laura will take care of the travel.
Kim, Daniel. Take the list
of clients Jimmy's signed.
Introduce yourself as the face of HHM.
Make them feel secure and confident.
Hey, Howard. I'm glad you're all excited.
But can we slow down a second
and discuss terms, maybe?
Oh, of course. Kind of shot
out of a cannon with this case.
- It's exciting stuff you have here.
- I get it.
Look, Chuck is already an equity partner.
You, as the lawyer who brought
this case to the firm...
we could guarantee
you, say, 20 percent...
of the common fund share
of the final settlement.
That will work.
That's a few years down the
road. As for money for you now...
we don't do referral
fees. Chuck will agree.
- HHM doesn't view that as ethical.
- As we discussed.
But what we could do is
arrange an of-counsel fee...
for the time you've already put in.
Time that you spent building the case.
I think we could go as high as 20,000.
- That, too, will work.
- Great.
Give us an invoice. I'll
have Helen cut you a check.
Oh, got it right here. And I'd
like to use 312 as an office.
- It's right next to Chuck's.
- I'm sorry?
Three-twelve. I know, it's got that view
that clients love, but you know what?
That's a waste of space. The waiting
area by the kitchen is just as good.
Well, come on, guys. I
mean, I need an office.
Can I have the room? Everybody,
please. Just give us a few.
- Howard...
- When the room's clear, Chuck.
Jimmy. Jimmy, I'm just gonna say it.
- You're not working here.
- What are you talking about?
- You said this case is a slam dunk.
- Yes.
We want the case. We don't want...
The case is all we want.
You gotta be...
You're serious?
I walk in here with a multi-million
dollar class action lawsuit...
on a damn platinum platter.
A case that I found, that I made happen.
And you don't want me? Why in Christ not?
Well, I know that you hate me, Howard.
You better believe,
feeling goes both ways.
But I'm willing to set that
aside to work with you on this.
Why can't you do the same for me?
What is it that you can't let go of?
What slight did I make to your fine,
upstanding character you can't forgive?
A majority decision has been
made by myself and the partners.
All due respect to you, Chuck, we are not
taking any new associates into the firm.
Bullshit. New associates?
Someone walks in with a case like
this, you beg them to be partner.
Tell me why.
You didn't want me then.
Okay. You don't want me now?
Explain it.
Howard.
I don't know what to say.
I am very disappointed. I really
think you should reconsider.
I'm sorry, but no. I think it's best
if Jimmy takes the of-counsel fee.
We could probably up
it a bit. Keep in mind.
You will be well compensated in the
back end. It's easy money, Jimmy.
No reason not to take it.
Go to hell, Howard.
I'm not giving you my case.
And I'm gonna tell every
one of those clients...
what a lying miserable
pig fucker you are.
I will burn the whole thing to
the ground before I give it to you.
Okay then. If that's your decision.
Good luck to you moving forward.
What the hell just happened?
Yeah. Come.
Hi.
Was wondering if you had a moment?
Sure. Just give me a second.
- What's up?
- I wanted to talk about what happened.
With Sandpiper Crossing,
things didn't work out.
It was unfortunate. It was a good case.
- But things happen.
- I'm just trying to understand why.
Jimmy found that case. He built it.
Did all of the leg work.
The class action doesn't exist without
him. He deserves a seat at the table.
I understand.
But the decision has been made, Kim.
Thank you for your input.
But why?
The partners have made a decision
and the why is not your concern.
I think it is my concern.
And why is that?
Because he's my friend.
And the way I see it, you're
not treating him fairly.
The way you see it?
I don't know what image you
have of him, past or present.
Or whatever he did or said to
you, but Jimmy is a good lawyer.
And he works very hard.
Did your friend send
you in here to say that?
No.
I'm saying it because I believe it.
Well.
Duly noted.
Want to know what I believe?
I believe that you're way out
of your depth in this matter.
So the next time that you want to come in
here and tell me what I'm doing wrong...
you are welcome to keep it to yourself.
Because I don't care.
Stop.
Close the door.
They're late.
Must be traffic.
I wonder how this is supposed to work.
I mean, who goes first? Do
I hand over the pills first?
Or do they give me the money
and then I hand over the pills?
I mean, I guess it makes
sense if we just exchanged...
at the same time, right?
I mean, that's fair.
Maybe we just count to three.
Probably the less talk, the better.
Right.
Yeah. I suppose you could really
overthink something like this.
Yeah.
- Well, in any case...
- Here is what is going to happen.
You're gonna take the money.
You're going to count it.
If it's all there, you
hand them the pills.
Easy peasy.
I knew we needed three guys. I
knew it. It's a three man job.
God.
Hello. Hi.
- Do you have it?
- I do.
Do you have the money?
Is it all there?
We're short 20. Twenty dollars.
That's fine.
Agreed amount or no deal.
You serious?
You saying I intentionally shorted you?
No. Mistakes happen.
You really willing to blow
up this deal over 20 bucks?
Are you?
It's all there. Eighty milligram
pills, still factory sealed.
You can pay me now.
How did you know?
How did you know not to bring a gun?
This 1,500? I'll just say
you're getting a bargain.
I put in a lot of leg
work before coming here.
Now, that fella you just met
with, name is Ignacio Varga.
He runs with a connected
crew of drug dealers.
This deal he's doing with you,
he's doing outside his crew.
He doesn't want his bosses to know.
So it was in his best interest
that things go very smoothly.
The lesson is, if you're gonna
be a criminal, do your homework.
Wait. I'm not a bad guy.
I didn't say you were a bad
guy. I said you're a criminal.
What's the difference?
I've known good criminals and bad
cops. Bad priests. Honorable thieves.
You can be on one side
of the law or the other.
But if you make a deal with
somebody, you keep your word.
You can go home today with your
money and never do this again.
But you took something that wasn't yours.
And you sold it for a profit.
You're now a criminal. Good
one, bad one? That's up to you.
I can get more pills.
And I am sure that
fella will keep buying.
Why don't you get us home? You
can sleep on it before you decide.
- Hey.
I was worried about you.
- I must have called a dozen times.
- Sorry. My phone died.
It's one of the perks of living
in Chuckland. Nowhere to plug in.
But tonight, it's Jimmyland.
I've got gin. I've got tequila.
I've got good Kentucky bourbon.
And you may partake with me in any
beverage of your choice on one condition.
You have to listen to me rant about
what an unwashed asshole your boss is.
- Jimmy...
- No. It's true.
Don't deny it.
He has reached a level of douche baggery
that will live on for generations.
Passed down by windtalkers and the like.
He'd rather tank a multi-million
dollar case than work with me.
That's sick. He has a sickness.
He hates me that much? I hate him more.
- What you drinking?
- Jimmy.
Yeah, I wanna grab him by that stupid
knit tie of his and swing him around.
- Jimmy.
- Hamlindigo blue.
- How about hamlindigo blow me?
- Jimmy!
I think you should take the deal.
What?
I think you should slow
down and think about it.
Because taking the deal really
is the best thing for you.
You'll find yourself a
proper office, your office.
You'll build your practice.
You'll leave Hamlin and HHM behind.
Be your own man.
You want me to give up the case?
My case?
I want you to be happy.
And I know you want
to stay with the case.
But you'll get all the financial
reward without the risk.
How can that be bad?
You come here peddling that
horseshit on me? God, you?
You sure know where
your bread is buttered.
Don't wanna go up against the
boss, that it? You're like a...
You're like a damn pod person.
What did Hamlin promise you? Please...
tell me he didn't buy you off cheap.
Did he promise you
the office I asked for?
Or did he just swear never
to move you back downstairs?
Take the deal.
Oh, son of a bitch.
Jimmy.
- Hey.
- Jesus, when did you come in?
I don't know. I left my watch outside.
Maybe an hour ago.
You doing some ironing?
Yeah.
Hey, I know things didn't
go well for us yesterday.
But being back in the office
sure felt good, really good.
I'm gonna be prepared in case
any more work comes my way.
And the space blanket lining in
the suit, what a fantastic idea.
It really made being
outside much more tolerable.
I'm thinking about taking a little
walk around the block later on.
That's great, Chuck. You should do that.
Jimmy, are you all right?
Well, I didn't sleep last night, so...
I was doing some soul searching,
and I came to a decision.
I'm gonna take that deal.
You're sure? This is what you want?
Kim talked to me.
I got pretty nasty. I'm not proud.
But thinking about what she said,
I'd be a fool to pass up that money.
It is a lot of money.
And I have zero interest
in working with Howard.
So it's probably best that we
keep to our separate sandboxes.
- Wish it could have worked out.
- Yeah. Imagine that, huh?
The two McGill boys side
by side storming the gates.
Righting wrongs, taking
down the bad guys.
And making a boatload of money to boot.
That would have been great.
- Right?
- The very best.
- Yeah.
I'll keep on Howard.
Won't badger him, but maybe
I can gradually wear him down.
- Get him to come around.
- That's...
Thanks.
I'm so lucky to have
you looking out for me.
I'll do what I can. I'm
not promising anything.
I get it. It's a long shot.
- Hey, he might change his mind.
- Yeah.
Hey, maybe there is a way that you
could get Howard to change his mind.
- How?
- Quit.
- Jimmy, no. No, no, no.
- No, no, it's perfect.
We've already been through all this.
The reasons I'm never gonna leave HHM.
But you don't have to really quit.
Okay? You just threaten to quit, right?
You get in a game of chicken with Howard.
He's gotta blink, or HHM goes
under. It's a perfect plan.
- Jimmy...
- If you want us working together.
You can make it happen easily.
I mean, hey, that reception
you got yesterday at HHM...
how about that, right? The whole
lobby of HHM applauding for you.
They love you.
Now, you threaten to pull out, Hamlin
would be insane to screw with you.
You've got the nuclear option.
Launch the doomsday device.
Game over. If working with me is
what you really want, right, Chuck?
You called him.
You called Hamlin.
I always turn my phone off
before I put it in your mailbox.
Two nights ago, it was
left on. Battery drained.
I was so damn sure that
I turned it off, you know.
Because I always do. It's a habit, right?
So it was nagging me. It was nagging me.
So I called the phone
company. Turns out...
there was a deleted call at 2
a.m. when I was asleep right there.
And you know whose number? Hamlin's.
The only person who could have made
that call and deleted it is you, Chuck.
Boy, that phone, huh?
Phone must have felt like
a blowtorch in your ear.
All that electricity.
All those radio waves right up
against the side of your head. My God.
What was so important that you had
to call Howard before our meeting?
The only thing I can think...
The only thing that makes sense
is... you told him not to hire me.
It was always you, right?
Right back to when I passed the
bar and tried to join the firm.
You didn't want me.
Speak up.
Tell me why.
It's the least you can do
for me now. I'm your brother.
We're supposed to look
out for each other.
Why were you working against me, Chuck?
You're not a real lawyer.
- I'm what?
- You're not a real lawyer.
University of American Samoa, for Christ's
sake. An online course? What a joke.
I worked my ass off to get where I am.
And you take these shortcuts and
you think suddenly you're my peer?
You do what I do because you're
funny and you can make people laugh?
I committed my life to this.
You don't slide into it like a cheap
pair of slippers and reap all the rewards.
- I thought you were proud of me.
- I was!
When you straightened out and got a
job in the mailroom, I was very proud.
So that's it then, right?
Keep old Jimmy down in the mailroom.
He's not good enough to be a lawyer.
I know you.
I know what you were, what
you are. People don't change.
You're Slippin' Jimmy.
And Slippin' Jimmy I
can handle just fine.
Slippin' Jimmy with a law degree
is like a chimp with a machine gun.
The law is sacred.
If you abuse that power, people get hurt.
This is not a game.
You have to know... On some
level, I know you know I'm right.
You know I'm right.
I...
I got you a 20 pound bag of ice.
And some bacon, and some eggs, and a
couple of those steaks that you like.
Some fuel canisters. It's
enough for three or four days.
After that, you're on your own.
I am done.
Jimmy.
Jimmy...
Jimmy, come back inside.
Jimmy!
Jimmy.
sync and corrections by othelo
addic7ed.com