Draka!
Where are you?
Here he comes.
We'll take care of the mother.
You keep him out.
-Come on. Push, my dear.
-Come on, push.
Draka!
Push.
The mother is dead.
The child lives.
Give me my son.
You can't have him.
He's under our protection.
It is our duty to raise him.
Until he's able to make his own choices.
The Dampyr lives.
Someone enjoyed themselves here.
Good of command to tell us
the town had been reclaimed.
Now we'll have to do
the gravediggers' job.
What the fuck happened to these bodies?
Where is the blood?
Looks like nobody was spared.
Military...
civilians.
Did they kill each other?
Don't talk shit.
Someone always survives a fight.
Looks like the work of wolves.
It was...
Easy.
...the devil.
It was the devil.
What happened here, old man?
They opened fire...
-my people in the church...
-Easy.
-...screams, "Blood, blood, blood."
Who was it?
Did you see them?
Dampyr.
You must call Dampyr.
-Dampyr?
-You must call--
Shut the fuck up.
Damn it, Stefan!
The fuck is the matter with you?
He was just some crazy old fool.
Call the others.
Get all the bodies gathered in one place.
We need to bury the dead.
Move!
Let's go.
Don't miss anyone!
Move them over there.
Harlan.
Come here to me.
-Another one of your nightmares?
-Yeah.
They're getting worse, Yuri.
Maybe if you quit drinking that crap.
You're too young to be my father.
But not too young
to be your manager, Harlan.
I want you in good shape.
We have a lot of work to do.
I'm in perfect shape. Can't you see?
Stop calling it "work."
It is work.
Puts food on the table.
-Where are you taking me?
-Jostanira.
Their cemetery is infested.
Weren't we there last week?
That was Jostalica.
-Come on, man. Try to concentrate, please.
-Easy.
I'm a professional.
The Dampyr.
Come closer. Please. Come closer.
The Dampyr is coming.
The Dampyr.
Citizens of Jostanira.
I know you're all worried.
Evil has reached your peaceful village.
And believe me when I tell you,
you are right to be afraid.
The devil's stench is everywhere,
infesting this place.
You are damned.
You heard me, you are damned
and you already know it.
But from now on, you will fear no evil.
Because today...
finally, here in your midst
stands the powerful...
Harlan...
the Dampyr.
The Dampyr.
Take me to the cemetery.
Get back. Give him room to work.
Get back. The Dampyr feels
the presence of a vampire.
Get back.
Out, damned soul.
Return to the hell that spawned you.
You don't belong in this holy place.
-Margherita pizza...
-What is he saying?
Esoteric formulas to seal the cemetery
and make it impossible for evil to return.
God, I could use a fucking drink
right now, Yuri.
Millennial knowledge.
Return to your homes in peace.
The monster that infected your cemetery
has been defeated.
Thank you. Thank you. Thanks.
Okay. Okay. Thank you. Oh, thank you.
Yuri!
Commander Kurjak to command.
Commander Kurjak.
Commander Kur--
Fuck it.
Now what?
We stay here...
and maintain our position.
I don't get Kurjak.
What is the point
of staying in this town, huh?
This ghost town will help us win the war?
Since when did you become
a strategist, Petar?
Hey. Isn't that what I'm here for?
You're here because you have smokes.
Give me one.
Maybe it will stop me
freezing my nuts off.
Help!
I gotta be dreaming.
Oh, you're not dreaming.
Help!
-Help me, I'm scared.
-Sure, baby.
I'll help you.
Come to Daddy.
Wait, Petar. You don't know
who the fuck she might be.
All right.
It looks like she's dying to know me.
Petar.
Help.
Petar!
Move!
Commander!
Who's shooting?
Came from down there where
those two idiots, Petar and Janko, are.
-We're under attack!
-Move. Three with me!
Move!
Who's there?
Tito!
-Move.
-Commander. We are under attack!
Commander!
Who attacked us?
Hey!
Hold your positions!
Hold!
What's going on?
Son of a bitch.
Commander!
Commander, we need help!
Come on!
Cover!
Get him down. Move.
Who did you see, Josif?
I shot him, but he didn't die.
He didn't die.
Josif. Josif!
Don't do that.
We have to call him.
Come on, asshole.
-The old man was right!
-Lazar.
Our enemies...
hellish creatures!
Undead!
-What is wrong with you?
-Our bullets are useless against them.
We have to find the one
who know how to beat them.
Who the fuck are you talking about?
I know him.
Let me go look for the one...
who can help us.
I hate it
when I have to do the whole show.
We're doing nothing wrong.
-You call this "doing nothing wrong"?
-The girl is already dead.
She won't feel a thing.
And her parents can go to sleep tonight,
knowing she won't wake up as a vampire.
That, in my opinion,
is what is called "doing good."
And it's all thanks to the great Dampyr.
Just give me the goddamn stake.
Save us.
-You're our savior.
-Dampyr.
Dampyr.
-Get back.
-Do you have to cut off her head?
She's my youngest daughter, Emina.
Save her soul, Dampyr.
Hey, let the Dampyr work, okay?
Please!
Forgive me, Emina.
Oh, my God.
Thanks. Thanks, but--
Thanks, but please keep quiet.
We are purifying the cemetery
of its evil spirits,
of which there are so many
at this time of death.
Thank you, thanks.
Show is over, kid.
You have to come with us.
We're arresting this fraud on orders
from our commander.
He won't be able
to fleece you suckers anymore.
Stay back!
If you arrest him,
then you have to arrest me too.
Beat it, kid!
-Down, boy.
-Not going anywhere without my manager!
I didn't recognize you.
Otherwise, I would have hit you harder.
You haven't changed a bit
since the day we met.
The advantages of living a healthy life.
You, on the other hand, look like shit.
The war does not agree with you.
You can't arrest us
for giving people hope.
"Hope." Too bad for those stupid fucks.
And we're not arresting you.
Our commander wants to talk to you.
Talk to us?
-What? Two useless, meaningless bums?
-Yeah, you're right, kid.
The truth is,
it's Harlan he wants to talk to.
What the fuck am I gonna tell him?
What's really going on here, Lazar?
Move.
Let's go.
Open up!
Hey, I'm his manager.
Butt out, kid.
Here he is, commander.
Well?
"Well," what?
You're the ones that brought me here.
I was better off
not seeing your ugly faces.
Show Commander Kurjak some respect.
Yes, sir, colonel.
Private Harlan reporting for duty.
No?
If we've finished with the introductions,
can someone tell me what I'm doing here?
I got nothing to do with this war.
Sit.
Please.
This war involves us all.
You too, Dampyr.
Something attacked us last night.
Killed my men.
Something not of this world.
I want to know what.
And they tell me that you know.
What exactly are you?
Me?
I'm a Dampyr.
A vampire hunter.
Me and my partner,
we go around making sure anyone bitten
by those hellish creatures
doesn't come back to life.
Then you know how to kill them.
Yeah.
But you really wanna know what I am?
I'm full of shit.
Vampires don't exist, you fucking fool.
Get him up.
I'm his manager. I have to be with him.
He has the right
to have someone defend him.
Hey. Harlan!
Harlan. You wanna tell me
what you did to my partner?
Here he is, all in one piece. For now.
Take a good fucking look.
I don't know who or what did this,
but the same could happen to you tonight.
Are you fucking crazy?
The Dampyr is bullshit!
Hey, leave him.
He's only saying that
just to save his own skin.
But we come from the same town
and we all know what he really is.
The son of the devil.
The proof is in the fact
that he hasn't aged a bit
since I first met him.
Let's see which of you
is telling the truth.
Lazar, give him your gun.
Move!
It's fully loaded.
Don't waste it.
Load up!
-You're gonna get him killed.
-Hey, we gave him a gun.
Your friend is the goat
to attract the wolf.
If he's what they say,
he's the wolf, not the goat.
Let's see how this plays out.
What a shitty night.
Help.
Hey.
-Hey, it's okay.
-Please don't hurt me.
What you doing in here?
I'm just trying to stay alive.
It's okay.
Please.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey.
The smell of your blood.
-What are you?
-What--? What am I?
What the fuck are you?
On your feet, handsome.
Time for dinner.
Harlan?
-We need to see what's happened to him.
-No one leaves.
What have you got against my T-shirt?
-Now I'm gonna ruin yours.
-No, Bojan, no!
He isn't human.
How the fuck did you do that?
Move!
Fire!
Kill him. Kill him! Kill him!
The Dampyr.
Dampyr.
Come back here, my children,
you cannot defeat him.
Not you.
You stay.
Stay with him and be my eyes.
He's still alive!
I thought I was gonna lose you.
Oh, my God, are you okay?
Yeah.
Kurjak, let's get the hell out
of this damn place.
If we stay here, we all die.
Yeah, they'll kill us all.
What the fuck did you do to him?
It was the sun.
There's a girl inside you should see.
Fuck.
Get inside.
You scared?
Are you fucking scared?
Lazar!
-Move! Inside!
-Move!
Move!
We have a prisoner.
Step back!
No one leaves.
Nothing personal, Kurjak,
but they didn't say anything
about fighting vampires when I signed up.
You want to face a court martial, Stefan?
You brought us
to this shithole of a village
to feed us to these monsters.
A bunch of our buddies are dead already!
Maybe you're the one
who should face a court martial.
And you...
if you really are a vampire killer,
then waste that thing.
Let's drag its ass out into the sun
and burn it like the other one!
Let's kill that mons--
-What the hell are you doing, asshole?
-Makes no sense killing her.
He's right.
That's the only thing that can tell us
what the fuck we are up against.
Let's leave Kurjak here with that thing.
-Right. They can kill each other.
-Fuck, yeah.
Let's get the hell out of here!
Let's go!
It's crazy to stay here, Emil.
Come with us.
-Let's cross the--
-I'm no deserter.
These things could kill us all...
and you want to walk away?
Pretend they don't exist?
Hey.
What the hell are we doing here
with this crazy soldier
and that monster over there?
Yuri, look, you...
You can't stay here, okay?
What?
There are some strange things
happening to me and I need to...
I need to stay here and figure them out.
-No, I...
-They'll be back. It's...
It's dangerous. It's not safe.
I'm not leaving you here.
-You gotta go.
-No.
No.
Harlan.
Take the boy with you.
Me and Harlan are a team.
Tell them, Harlan.
Harlan?
Hey, you said
we'd always stick together, you promised.
Let's go, kid.
-You promised me, Harlan.
-Let's go.
I thought we were family, Harlan.
Please, Harlan.
Please. Don't do this to me, Harlan.
Let me stay with you, Harlan, please.
Come away with us. Please, Harlan.
Harlan, please.
-Let go of me!
-Look at it this way, Kurjak.
Staying here could be the best way
to get yourself killed...
and see your son again.
Run as far as you can, Stefan.
Because as soon as command finds out
you're fucking chicken,
they will come for you.
Then we'll make sure
you can't tell anyone...
commander.
Door!
Lock them with the monster.
Let's go.
Fuck!
-How's that working out?
-Shut up.
Why?
You've got no fucking plan.
How about we start getting
some answers from that bitch?
Move.
No.
It's Tesla.
Not "bitch."
You defended me before, soldier.
And you...
Dampyr, you could have killed me,
but I'm still alive.
I owe you.
Remember whose side you're on.
You saw the hate in her eyes, right?
I don't hate you.
I hate Gorka.
Who's Gorka?
My master, Lord of the Night.
It's because of him I am what I am.
Lord of the what?
For a Dampyr, you don't know much, do you?
Unlike us ordinary vampires,
Lords of the Night don't fear
the sunlight.
Only Lords of the Night have power
to give life to other vampires...
and to generate those like you.
What do you mean, like me?
-Keep your distance from the beast.
-Shut up!
I need to know.
If a Lord of the Night mates
with a non-vampire woman,
she will give birth to a Dampyr.
-I'm not-- I'm not a--
-Your blood tells a different story.
I never knew my father.
He obviously hid the truth from you
to protect you.
The Lords of the Night kill
those like you at birth.
You're way too dangerous.
And now, from the moment
you killed one of his slaves,
Gorka knows you exist.
Which means what?
He'll do anything to exterminate you.
Javor.
Shit.
What's going on?
-Javor?
-What the fuck is happening?
Why did you stop?
Javor.
Javor! Javor!
Run, kid! Run!
Run, Yuri! Run!
Run, Yuri!
What's happening?
-The fuck are you doing to him?
-It's him.
Gorka.
Run!
Run, Yuri!
Harlan!
He's got Yuri.
He's got your men.
It's my fault.
Can you take me to him?
Please.
Yes, bring him here to my slaughterhouse.
Our pack was going back to the city.
I can help you find him.
Why the fuck would you do that?
Only a Dampyr can kill
the Lord of the Night.
If Gorka dies...
I'm free.
I don't trust her.
She's one of them.
She'll jump us the first chance she gets.
No.
She's scared of me.
I'll watch her, okay?
First thing we have to do is find a way
out of this fucking church.
Well, that's easy, soldier boy.
Nice handbag.
Come on, pretty boy.
I see you went shopping too.
Leave it.
That mask you're wearing suits you.
Don't you know that sunlight is bad
for the skin, soldier boy?
What are you?
Mom?
Monster! Monster!
You're damned.
And so is your mother, that filthy witch.
-My mother isn't a witch!
-Get out of here!
The smell of your blood. What are you?
-Mom!
-What exactly are you?
Monster! Monster!
-What do you mean, like me?
-Mom!
What exactly are you?
The son of the devil.
Harlan.
Come here to me.
Be careful, Harlan.
What?
What happened?
You tell me.
You blacked out in the car.
Started babbling like crazy.
Shaking like you were possessed
or something.
I've always had nightmares.
Now they seem more and more real.
Like memories trying to re-emerge.
I-- I don't know.
You must think I'm fucking crazy.
What we've been through
would drive anyone crazy.
Fuck!
Hey, she said
she was going for something to eat.
And we know what her diet consists of.
Her friends could show up at any moment.
I don't have any friends.
But I can hear you whisper from far away.
Didn't your mother teach you it's rude...
to whisper about people
behind their backs?
Soldier boy?
Besides, I've seen
the way you fight your war.
Do you think you're better
than those like me?
You know nothing of war.
Would you two just fucking quit?
Your wounds are disappearing.
You're just like us.
You can't expect Kurjak
to accept it as normal.
It's hard for me too.
Blood has memories.
Believe me, I'd rather forget everything
than live with the memory
of what Gorka forced me to endure.
And what he forced me to do.
Tesla...
I'm trusting you.
Don't worry.
What the...?
It gives me such pleasure
to feel the fear pulsating in your veins.
I shall never tire of playing
with your miserable lives,
whilst you pray in vain to be spared.
How does it feel
to know your life is coming to an end?
I have no idea what death feels like.
I can sniff a hint of it from your terror.
We have always existed,
and we always will,
being close to kings and emperors,
led them and killed them.
Whatever was necessary
to placate our thirst.
Past, present
and future are meaningless to us.
Only blood is important.
I will unleash you from your fear.
And you, faithful dog...
will join my army.
Everyone's trying
to get out of this hellhole...
and we're thinking of going in.
I know how to get us
around the roadblocks.
But once we're in...
once it gets dark...
if there really are more like the beast...
then this won't do any good.
You never know.
Now that the bloodsucker is
more comfortable,
you want to tell me what you have in mind?
You think it'll work?
You're the vampire, Tesla.
What do you think?
It could.
Could?
Let's fucking see.
Well...
guess we load them up.
Not just a pretty face, huh?
Here.
You want one?
Yeah.
The beast wants one.
You're dangerous enough without one.
You're right, soldier boy.
But if I wanted to kill you,
you'd be dead already.
But if I enter the city barehanded,
I'm dead meat.
Suits me. I won't have
to watch my back for you anymore.
You know,
you're really starting to piss me off.
Tesla! Just... let him go.
How about we see
if these new bullets work, huh, Harlan?
Go ahead.
Shoot.
It'd only be a liberation for me.
Your war is child's play
compared to what I've been through.
So do me a favor, soldier boy,
cut your macho-man bullshit.
Hey.
Tesla...
you know I could have shot you, right?
I know.
But you didn't.
Because you know what it means
to be different.
Be careful.
It's my blood.
Let's move, lovebirds.
I've done my bit.
Now it's the bloodsucker's turn.
Gorka's lair is under the old library.
We need to walk through this--
Move!
Come on.
Dad! Dad, wait!
Naya, come on!
Hurry up, hurry up!
They're coming.
-Let's go, let's go!
-Let's go, they're coming!
Let's go, let's go!
-What is it?
-It's better to avoid the busier streets.
Come on.
Follow me.
Something's wrong.
Tesla!
We've been walking for hours.
I think the bitch walked us
into a fucking trap.
I can't get you to him.
Gorka set it up.
-He knows we're coming.
-You warned him.
I didn't have to.
Lords of the Night know everything,
you can't hide from them.
You fucking warned him!
They're here.
Son of a bitch.
Fuck!
Move!
Stop, you bastards!
It fucking works! I told you it would.
Our new master...
wants you dead,
you son of a witch.
Told you war was bad for you,
you little shit.
Fuck you!
Need some help there, old man?
Fuck you.
Come on.
There we go.
The only one I wanted to kill was Stefan.
I know.
Wait!
Fuck this.
It's okay.
Harlan.
It's Gorka.
He's making me do this.
You can fight him, Tesla.
You're wrong.
He's too strong.
Move out of the fucking way.
You are not his slave.
I can't help it.
Move.
Kill me.
Please kill me. Please kill me.
Fuck it!
I'm sorry.
Harlan!
Hey. Come.
Come.
Fuck.
Okay. Clean the wound.
-It is going to sting.
-Okay.
-Ready?
-Yeah.
There we go.
Okay, okay.
-Drink.
-Yeah.
That's it.
You're gonna be okay.
-Brave boy.
-Yeah.
That photo in your pocket...
it was your wife and son, right?
Miklos and Miljiana.
Miklos was 9 when he was killed.
I'm sorry.
This is war.
Keep the pressure on.
From the moment you're born...
they tell you
that their way is the right way.
They teach you to the point that
not only do you believe it yourself...
but in the end...
it becomes you who teaches it to others.
To command it, even.
Maybe there is no right team.
Maybe we're all destined
to be on the wrong side.
Or maybe this is the only war
that deserves to be fought.
Please, don't!
You can't rebel.
We belong to the same master.
I belong to no one.
It's okay.
Love is so overestimated.
I prefer fear.
And you are scared now, Tesla.
Because you know, like a dog,
you have bitten the hand that feeds you.
A vampire and a Dampyr.
Don't you see the irony of that?
You are insignificant!
A puppet who only moves
when I pull the strings.
My property.
And mine alone.
The Dampyr will find you...
and he will kill you.
I want him to find me.
And then I will remedy the mistake
they made in allowing him to live.
You're not much of a nurse.
Is this how you watch over the dying?
You got a death wish? No?
Nice to see that when you were
patching me up, you took more of my blood.
Let me see the wound.
Shit.
-And it doesn't hurt.
-Never seen anything like it.
I partnered up
with a fucking superhero, huh?
Yeah.
Or maybe a monster.
This looks like the place.
What now, pretty boy?
Go in,
kill Gorka,
free Yuri.
Simple.
It's quiet.
Too quiet.
Let's meet upstairs.
Daddy?
Miklos?
Fucking hell!
Daddy...
why did you leave me?
Why did you leave me?
Kurjak?
Tesla?
Tesla.
Have a good nap...
commander?
Leave her.
Leave her!
Fucking leave her!
Stop!
You fucking piece of shit.
I've always despised you, Kurjak.
You and your obsession with rules.
Your fucking sense of honor.
They might have turned you
into a monster, Stefan...
but one thing will never change.
You're still a fucking pussy.
Gorka!
Yuri!
I've been expecting you, Dampyr.
You're too slow.
And now,
in my kingdom,
I can finally kill you.
You can try it, you fucking monster.
Monster?
Me?
You're the only abomination here.
Now that I have you in front of me,
your stink confirms
what I have always suspected.
You belong to Draka's lineage.
Draka was a fool.
He should never have let you
into this world or live so long.
And if he wanted to use you
solely for revenge...
then he miscalculated.
Just as I drove him from here
centuries ago...
now I will kill you.
Blood of his blood...
how dare you live so long?
Impressive.
Don't you think it's sublime...
the futility of all this?
No, don't faint yet.
I have someone who wants
to say goodbye to you.
A special friend.
Harlan?
Yu-- Yuri.
Yuri, forgive me.
For what? I knew you'd come for me.
Unfortunately, it's too late.
Yuri.
No!
I'm sorry, old friend.
Gorka is my master now.
I couldn't stop him. He was in my head.
I know.
I don't wanna live like this.
Please, Harlan.
It's okay, Yuri.
I'm here.
You're a true Dampyr, my friend.
It was great... working with you.
What a heartbreaking farewell.
The soldier and the traitor.
You fucking bastard.
You will remain buried here...
drenched in the suffering
these walls have seen.
And you will live
that suffering for eternity...
with every fiber of your being.
It's time to choose, Harlan.
I must know.
Harlan. Come.
Come here to me.
What is wrong, Harlan?
Are you afraid of your own father?
Or should I perhaps be afraid of my son?
Listen to your blood, my son.
Listen to who you are.
Why did Draka let you live, Dampyr?
Why?
I have lived like a god amongst creatures
that are destined to die.
But because of you, Dampyr...
now I know...
the brilliant glare...
of death.
You fought well, soldier.
Come on.
What is this place?
This can't have anything to do with Gorka.
Gorka said it once belonged to my father.
This is my father.
That's how I see him in my visions.
I guess ugly runs in the family, then.
There are many others like him.
Then it's going to be a long war.
Welcome to the world of nightmares,
soldier boy.
We're gonna become their nightmare.
Our son has made his choice, Velma.
He has become...
the Dampyr.
But he didn't agree to follow you.
Nor to become your ally.
He might try to kill you.
Perhaps.
Or...
perhaps he will heed
the call of his blood.
My blood.
For this is only the beginning.
The beginning of my war.