[birdsong]
I can't keep up, May. Are you eating
gluten or you're not eating gluten?
It's oats. It's no gluten.
[Helen] No gluten.
[phone rings]
I wake up with Today!
It's for you.
Yeah, it's my phone. Right?
Hello? Yeah, George, I know.
You texted me last night.
OK. I'll see you at work.
Hey, Graham.
You know, if you want to win money,
you got to register for that thing.
-They don't just ring random numbers.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Well, that's a waste of two years.
Well, what about that other show,
the, the Cash Cow? How's that work?
Oh, I think the cow just comes to
your house with a big bag of money.
-Is that right?
-No, May, I'm kidding.
-Come on!
-Oh, get out!
-See ya later, guys. See ya, Artie.
-Bye.
Helen!
Cake in the meeting room at 11.
Yeah, I know. You called me.
And texted.
And invited me to the Facebook event
'Cake at 11'.
-I'm excited. I got a mud cake.
-Boo. Mud cake.
So overrated.
Why didn't you get a fruitcake?
We're not in
an old people's home, Helen.
Rude.
Oh. Morning, Helen.
Morning, Roz.
Cake at 11 in the meeting room.
-Big announcement.
-Yep. George told me.
-Hope you like mud cake.
-Nope. Too wet.
-It's like it's not cooked properly.
-What's that, now?
I said, "Yep. Yummy.
Cannot wait. Mmm! Delicious."
My God, she's like a bat.
There we go. There's
an English breakfast. Alrighty!
Phil! Let's make a will. Go.
I want to be very prescriptive.
I don't want any fighting.
Good idea. Sensible.
So, shall we start
with the fitted sheet sets?
[laughs] Yeah.
I'm sorry. Yep.
You're serious. Ok. Sure.
"Fitted sheet set."
Who's the lucky recipient?
Forks.
Uh... uh, yes.
[mutters]
That's the linen cupboard complete.
-Well done us.
-Mmm!
Shall we move on
to the kitchen drawers?
-Mmm?
-Oh! We could...
The problem is,
coming up to 11, I'm afraid, Phil.
-Oh, really?
-Is that the hour gone already?
-Mmm.
-There's just so much to get through!
-Oh.
-Should we schedule another meet?
We could, or... I've had an idea.
Grab your stuff.
Oh.
Here's what I'm thinking.
How about you give me
that little book of yours,
I work from that, and
I give you a call when it's all done?
-What do you reckon?
-You might miss something.
Oh, no, I won't. Come on. Give me the
book. And then you pay a flat fee.
Otherwise I've got to charge you
by the hour.
Just... Phil, just let me...
OK. I've got half now, so you
may as well give me the other half.
And I'll tell you what,
you are gonna thank me for that,
so why don't you get out there,
enjoy all that extra time,
and money, I just saved you?
You're welcome, Phil.
[taps on glass]
Yeah, I'm coming, Roz. Jesus. I know.
Cake at 11.
Finally! Ta-da!
Mud cake! Well done, George.
Great work, Georgie!
-I'll plate up.
-[Roz] Alright.
Very exciting news.
We have been nominated
for a Local Business Award.
Great stuff.
I really want to win this one, guys.
Roz is back on deck next month,
and an award
would really help get
the stink of her suspension off us.
We've bought a table
for the awards dinner.
-And, uh, partners are welcome.
-As are famous fathers.
I'm looking at you, Fisk. Wouldn't
that stick it up the competition?
Supreme Court judge
on the Gruber table.
-Can I bring someone?
-[Ray] Yes. Bring your girlfriend.
Or your boyfriend.
Which is it, George?
-Ray, you can't ask that.
-[Ray] Why not?
You can. I'm pansexual.
Good! Great!
See? It's fine.
Mmm.
Alright. You bring your dad.
And you can bring Pan.
Let's win this one, guys.
Come on, Team Gruber!
-Team Gruber!
-[Ray] Yes!
-Hey, no, you two.
Mmm. Sit down.
Now, judging is done
by anonymous visit.
It could be anyone at any time.
And I want game faces on
24/7, please.
-Oh.
-It's just jokes, Roz.
I was having fun with mud cake.
Thought you didn't like mud cake,
Helen.
Well, it's still cake. I'll eat it.
I mean, God.
Hey, is Roz
really not suspended anymore?
[George] Oh, I don't know.
OK, Petro, go. Talk. What do you
need? What can I do for you?
I believe I'm the illegitimate son
of Georgios Papadakis.
-The newsreader?
-The beloved voice of the nation.
Well, I'm sorry for your loss.
A loss made all the more tragic
by the fact that I never met him.
Did you not just say you're his son?
-I believe that I am.
-Ah. Ok.
So, by any chance, would you be here
to make a claim
on the Papadakis estate?
This is not about the money.
I just want to be acknowledged
as part of the family.
Right. Do you have any proof
you're related?
Paperwork? A birth certificate?
I have this.
This is a restraining order
that says you are not allowed
within 50 meters of any member
of the Papadakis family.
That's correct.
It's upsetting for them.
I think because I remind them
so much of Papa Georgios.
It says here it's because you
jumped into the grave at the funeral.
Please. Untrue.
They asked
that family members step forward
and throw some dirt into the hole.
-You mean the grave.
-Yes.
But when I stepped forward,
Yiayia Papadakis,
she screamed and pushed me,
like this, and I fell into the hole.
-Grave.
-Yes.
So you don't want money?
Well?
Uh, well, I don't not want money.
What makes you think you're related?
[laughs]
Look at me.
Now look at him.
What do you see?
The future
if I don't stay on top of my waxing.
I can't believe
I never got to meet him.
Have you met your father, Helen?
Yes. Many times.
-Do you cherish that relationship?
-Cherish?
Oh... we text a lot.
But do you tell him
that you love him and cherish him?
I always send him a thumbs up
or sometimes clapping hands.
Do you know, I think the best thing
to do in this case is a DNA test.
[sighs]
Ok?
-Ok.
I assume you will leave the room.
That would definitely make me
more comfortable.
What?
Uh, is there a, uh, receptacle?
No. We're not doing it now!
And... and we're not gonna do it
from there! Jesus!
The first thing I have to do
is contact the Papadakis family.
Please...
tell them I love 'em.
Yeah. I will send them a thumbs up.
It's not the whole recipe,
'cause Mum won't tell me
everything that's in the marinade.
Georgios Papadakis!
My mum's favorite newsreader!
[laughs]
-Do you mind?
-Oh, I would be honored.
Oh, this is outrageous.
Hang on a sec.
Didn't you die?
[camera clicks]
Raymond, do you have a minute?
Make it quick, Roz.
With my reinstatement pending,
what is the plan vis-a-vis Helen?
Staying? Going? Thoughts?
[Ray] Yeah.
I am touching cloth here, Rozzie.
Put a pin in that.
We'll talk about it later.
[clicks mouse]
Are you ready for me, Roz?
Helen! Good.
-Yep.
-Come, come.
I need to talk to you about
the judging criteria for the awards,
specifically appearance.
Oh, Ok. Yep. Good. Sure.
This one brown suit of yours
you're so attached to.
No, it's not one suit. I've
got three of these, all the same.
-Good God, why?
-It's just easier.
Who can be bothered deciding
what to wear every morning?
Why is it so baggy? Did you
use to be fuller-figured? Plus-size?
-Saying did I use to be fat?
-No.
I'm just wondering, Helen,
if you could, just for once,
be a team player.
Maybe you could jazz it up
or get it taken in.
What about if I wore something loose
but more fashionable?
Don't you dare turn up here
wearing a caftan, Helen.
Ok. And in your mind,
is a caftan the same as a muumuu?
[clicks mouse]
Ok.
muumuu's a no-no. Got it.
No muumuu.
[man] 10 more seconds, Judge.
Stay with it.
Can you go the distance, J-dog?
I know you can.
In three, two, a...
and one.
Step down. Shake it off.
Good job, guys. Well done.
Sorry, Viktor. I'm a bit early.
-Oh, Christ, Dad. Are you alright?
-Yes, yes.
All well. I just need to, um,
shower off and... towel down.
It's just the after-shakes.
It's good. Means it's working.
-Right. Yeah. Ooh.
-Same time next week, guys?
-Yes, lovely. Thanks, Blayden.
-Yes. Perfect.
You know, actually, I might pop
upstairs for a shower too, I think.
-Not together, Tip.
-Oh, don't be silly.
[beeping]
Hey! Blayden Tork, T-O-R-K,
Torking Fitness.
-What's your FOC, Helen?
-My what, sorry?
Uh, FOC, fitness of choice.
What's your fitness of choice?
Oh! Um, I walk my dog every day,
so... yeah.
And for fitness?
Um...
when I'm walking my dog,
sometimes if I remember, I clench...
clench my bum, so, um...
so, yeah,
clench walking is my FOC, yeah.
Mm-hm. How about a quick shake
on the Vibratron? Get your buzz on.
Mmm.
Yeah.
-Can you feel the fat melting?
-[voice vibrates] Um...
Ooh. I can definitely
feel it wobbling.
Um! Oh. Egg?
Nah, man. I'm good, thanks.
Blayden Blast protein powder.
Free sample.
No.
Ok.
How long before I'm, like,
thin or whatever?
-Keep going.
-OK.
[loud rattling]
[Anthony] Sorry, what?
I said, I had a bit of a weird day!
I think my job is under review.
Uh, Tip. Tip.
Sorry.
-What was that, Helen?
-I think my job's under review.
I don't know
if they're gonna keep me on.
Well, I guess you'd better
make yourself indispensable.
Mmm! Not a good time
to be unemployed, Helen.
Yeah, I know that. Thanks, Viktor.
Not for you. You're driving.
Is there anything I can do?
Yes.
Could you please
come to the Business Awards night?
My boss would love it if you sat
at our table. He would love it.
-Of course!
-Oh, Helen, don't be silly.
-We'd love to.
-Really?
Thanks, Dad.
You know, I don't say it enough,
but I... I really...
I cherish you, Dad.
-What?
-You what him?
I cher... I cherish him.
-That's an odd thing to say.
-Is it?
-Do you need money?
-No! I'm being warm and loving.
Aren't I?
It's just making everyone
feel uncomfortable.
Let's eat.
Ok.
I need something smart,
like maybe a nice shirt or...
-Oh, just help yourself.
-What's mine is yours.
Ok. Ooh. Ok.
Did you find something to wear?
I've got that exact same shirt.
No, I did not. Ok.
These are some of my old work suits.
So why don't you see
if one of those fits?
Thanks, May. Great.
Ooh. Alright.
[door opens]
Webmaster! I've come jazzy.
What do you think?
-Nice badge.
-Yeah. It's covering the airline logo.
I'm actually wearing my aunt's
old flight attendant uniform.
Now, I've come up with a plan
about how we can get a DNA sample
from Thomas Papadakis.
Ooh! Me too.
We tempt him
with a delicious glass of Scotch.
And then we sit back and laugh
as he leaves his DNA all over it.
Yeah. I thought I could just ask him
to do a DNA test.
[tapping on glass]
Oh. There's the angry tapper.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
-Thank you.
-Morning.
Come and give me a hand, you two.
[door closes]
[Roz] Now... from today,
I want every potential mystery judge
to get a goodie bag.
-Ooh! Someone say goodie bags?
-Hey, Ray.
-Let's have a look.
-Good news for you.
Guess who's coming
to the Business Awards.
-My dad.
-Yes! Well done, Fisk.
What have you come as, Fisk?
Is that a Rex Airlines uniform?
I'm being a team player.
You're being a bit silly.
Look. Squishy gavel.
[gavel squeaks]
Ooh! In the tum-tum.
Mr Papadakis. Helen Tudor-Fisk.
Thank you very much for coming in.
I realize this is a difficult time
and I am sorry for your loss.
Goodie bag?
Can I just give you a DNA sample
and get out of here?
-That's what you want, right?
-Wow. Yep. That was easy.
Thing is, my client, Petro Andarakis,
he believes...
Yeah, yeah.
I know what that nutjob believes.
What do you need? Hair? Pubes?
What?
No. I really don't need pubes.
Not sure why everyone thinks DNA has
to come from your pants. It doesn't.
All I need is a couple of these
swabs, run that round your mouth
and then pop it back into the tube.
[door bangs]
Ok. And then...
Oh, you have got to be kidding me.
Ok. Or I could pop it back in
for you.
-What's he doing here?
-Oh, oh. Hey, hey, hey. No, no. Crap.
-You can't be here.
-Yassou, brother!
-No.
-Helen told me you might come in.
And I know it's against the rules.
-I'm not your brother.
Seriously,
what's wrong with this guy?
You need to leave, and you should
sit back down. We're not finished.
I just need one more swab from you.
Get out of my way, Ms Tudor-Fisk.
I've bloody had it with this guy.
I'm warning you, mate.
Do you see?
We're like two peas in a pod.
-The fiery temper runs in the family.
-I'm not related to you!
When will you get that
in your thick skull?!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Don't touch him. Don't grab him!
Does this look like
50 meters to you?
Take a photo of this.
I want evidence for the cops.
Please, Helen, take a picture.
Hey, hey, George. Give me a hand.
Sorry, Helen.
I'm not really a fighter.
-No, Thomas.
-No.
-Thomas!
-No!
-Helen, I'm so sorry.
-No.
Brother, we need to talk! I want to
explain about the funeral debacle.
Uh, please come back later,
when the real staff are here.
We're just temp staff
who work at lunchtime.
What was that?
Just covering us in case
that was the mystery shopper.
[exhales]
Welcome, sir.
May I offer you a goodie bag?
Stand down, George. He's not
the mystery shopper. I guarantee it.
-Hey, Blayden.
-[Blayden] Hey.
You're stretching? Heels and glutes
into the floor. Push it down.
[Blayden] Your dad said you needed
to bring in some new business.
-So I'm here to get my will done.
-Oh. Good on Dad. Ok.
Well, it's a $500 flat fee...
-500 bucks?!
-... for that, yep.
-Jesus! Are you serious?
-Yeah.
That's what one of
my signature Vibratrons cost.
How can a piece of paper
be worth the same
as a high-end piece
of wellness apparatus?
Uh, it's fairly standard.
[groans]
In fact, it's pretty cheap.
Yeah. All good. [groans]
Sorry. I think I just need a snack.
-I worked out pretty hard today.
-Mm-hm.
-You don't have a can of tuna on you?
-Uh, no.
-I don't usually carry a...
-Salmon.
No.
Some almonds? A protein ball?
I might... I might have a lozenge.
Would that be...?
-A protein lozenge?
-No, I don't think that's a thing.
Uh... oh! Ooh, ooh! Hey.
Hey!
Look what I've got.
-Blayden Blast. There you go.
-Blayden Blast. Hey.
Uh, uh, uh, mmm.
[swishes water]
Ugh!
That is the equivalent
of three skinless chicken breasts
and one egg white.
Ooh. All the tasteless white bits.
[snaps fingers]
-Delicious.
-Mm-hm.
I always thought you put it
into the water.
Alright. So the suit's been altered.
Now just got to add some jazz.
The awards are tonight, so...
I do still need to find something
to wear today.
May! Have you seen my grey pants?
-Hey, Webmaster.
-Hey, you look nice.
Thank you.
Bit late, though, don't you reckon?
Oh, mate,
after yesterday, we're fucked.
That's our new slogan, is it?
"Welcome to Gruber & Associates.
We're fucked."
I mean, what if I'd been
the mystery judge?
How did she even hear that?
Is she bionic?
-[Roz] Heard that!
-Oh.
Come on!
Mmm.
Alrighty, Phil, that's for you.
Repaired it.
You'll never even notice.
In case you do, just to show
no hard feelings, that's for you too.
Now, while I'm dealing things out,
let's get you signing.
-Okey-doke. There we go.
-That's a lot of paperwork!
Well, you had
a lot of instructions, Phil.
What's all this going to cost?
It must have taken hours!
-Told you, flat fee.
-Do you mind if I read it?
Yeah, be illegal if you didn't, but
do you mind if I stand up for a bit?
'Cause... oi... I'm wearing old pants
and they are tight.
Oh, did you include
the potato masher?
Check the index.
I added one at the back, in case
you need to cross-check or reference.
I'm just gonna... sit here.
Oh! How are your pants, Phil?
-That's better.
-Oh, I wear mine quite loose.
I... I like sitting.
I... I like to be comfortable.
Yep. I hear you. These used to
fit me, before the divorce.
-Mmm?
-Before I started eating my feelings.
-Hm.
-You know how it is.
Hm.
[sighs]
Ooh! My hibachi's here.
-Delivery for Fisk. Your name?
-Ray.
Ray Gruber.
[door bangs]
"Services rendered"?
What's that about?
[machine vibrates]
Nah, I don't like it.
It's rattling my skeleton.
Here, let me have a go.
You bringing anyone to the awards?
Yeah. My grandma.
She loves to dress up.
You wait till you see
what I'm wearing.
Oh, Roz, Roz! Come and have a go
on the Team Gruber Vibratron. Whoo!
Yes, I heard about
your dodgy contra deal.
You do realize we can get fined
for that sort of thing,
taking payments under the table?
No, it's fine. It's worth 500 bucks.
So I'm gonna pay for it
then gift it to the office.
It does feel weird, but then you get
used to it and it's quite, like...
[makes vibrating noise]
-What did I say?
-What?
I said best behavior from everyone.
I asked you to dress nicely
and then you turn up in fancy dress
as an air hostess.
-What about today? I look really nice!
-Too little, too late.
Apparently, there was a fistfight
in reception the other day?
You don't know... who told you...
-Oh!
-That wasn't my fault.
Fisticuffs! My God, Helen.
And then there was
the salty language
and the rolling around on the floor
in front of a client.
Well, these pants are really tight.
I said to Raymond from the start
you were not a good fit,
and if we lose this award
because of you,
I'm going to take
this stupid vibrator...
-Excuse me, Roz.
-and I'm going to stick it where...
A courier dropped off
this big body bag thing for you.
Thank you, George.
It's not a vibrator.
It's a Vibratron.
[Roz] I heard that.
Hello, Dad.
[indistinct chatter]
Is this fun Helen?
[laughter]
[man] Can I get a photo of you three?
-Who's the old woman?
-That's Dad's husband.
-That's Viktor.
-No. The lady in the leopard print.
-Oh, that's George's grandmother.
-Oh!
So 'pansexual' doesn't mean
dating old people.
No. Why would it mean... No!
-What?
-Pan?
Pandora? Wasn't she some old woman?
-Oh.
-Oh, hello.
Oh, what have you done, Roz?
[laughs]
This is magical!
-Absolutely wonderful.
-Thank you.
-Well done.
-Thank you very much.
Ah, and I see you've come
in fancy dress again, Helen.
No, this is my brown suit!
I did what you said. I jazzed it up.
I had it altered.
Look at me now.
I don't recall saying turn your suit
into a mariachi band costume.
[dramatic music plays]
Oh, it's starting. It's starting.
-You're sitting over there, Roz.
-Where?
You're not near me.
That's my dad, Roz.
-Oh!
-That's my dad.
Justice Fisk!
Justice Fisk,
what a delight to see you!
Champagne?
[man] Please welcome your master
of ceremonies, Mr Glenn Ridge!
[cheering and applause]
Thank you very much.
That's very kind of you.
Uh, Mr Mayor, distinguished guests,
ladies and gentlemen
and friends beyond the binary,
I'm Glenn Ridge, and
it's certainly great to be with you
as we're coming to you
from the elegant La Mirage ballroom.
I think you'll agree... Yes.
[cheering and applause]
I think you'll agree it's one of
the most versatile function rooms
in outer Melbourne.
There's no doubt about that.
But first the award
for the best wok-based takeaway.
And the nominees are...
... My, My, That's Good Stir-Fry.
[cheering and applause]
Congratulations to all the team
at Rock Your Locks Off hair studio.
A very popular win,
especially with the, uh, seniors,
and I do know that they do love the
Pension Tuesday $60 cut and Colour.
So well done, Antoinette.
Now, moving on
to one of the big awards,
which is
the Professional Services Award,
and, uh, to present this award,
I'm going to hand it over
to one of
our anonymous judging panel,
a man who's going to become
anonymous no more.
Ladies and gentlemen,
would you please welcome Phil Deacon.
[applause]
Helen, look who it is!
[Helen] I see it, George. Shoosh.
That's it. We're out.
It's the guy whose book you ripped,
remember?
It might be. It might not be.
I haven't got my glasses.
We can't tell from this distance.
-It is.
-Just... just shoosh. Just shoosh.
Myself and the other judges
have spent the past four weeks
visiting the 28 businesses
that nominated themselves
for this award.
-Helen.
-Shh.
-Hang on, Dad. This is our category.
-Y-y-yes. Of course.
-I might have to leave.
-No, no, no. You can't go.
'Cause if we lose,
they're gonna fire me.
I need you here. I need you here.
-Alright. I'll stay a bit longer.
-Just stay. Ok.
Thanks, Dad. Just sit down.
-Stop being weird.
-Yes. Good idea.
Uh, the winner of the
Professional Services Award is...
Don't make a fuss, Hels, but
I think I'm having a heart attack.
... Pike Probate Services.
Oh, God. Jesus! No, no, Dad!
Dad, Dad, Dad!
[Phil] And collecting the award...
-Oh, God!
-... Alice Pike.
Tony!
[cheering and applause]
-Helen!
-Yep, yep. I'm here, Dad. Yep.
-I cherish you, Helen.
-[sniffs] Oh. I cherish you too, Dad.
Yeah, we all cherish you.
You are cherished, my love.
-I cherish you most of all.
-It's not a competition, Viktor.
You're over-cherishing him.
[tram bell dings]
-Oh, what a night!
-It really was, wasn't it?
All the stars were out last night.
-Fisk!
-Morning.
-[gasps] How's Dad?
-Oh, better.
Out of intensive care,
so that's good. Yep.
-Thoughts and prayers.
-Thank you, Roz.
-That's very comforting.
-Did we send a goodie bag, Roz?
-Mm-hm.
-Yeah, yeah.
He loved the squishy gavel.
Got a photo.
There we go.
Oh, that's funny.
And the hat. Loving it.
Hey, Roz, I thought about
what you said, and you're right.
I don't think I'm a good fit here.
I know how angry you guys must have
been losing to Alice Pike last night.
Oh, not as angry as Alice Pike was
when she woke up this morning
and saw the front cover
of The Copeland Advocate.
-Have a look at that.
-[Helen] Ethical Business Person? What?
I accepted on your behalf.
Why?
Because you weren't there.
Your father had a heart attack,
remember?
Why did I win it?
Mystery judge Phil said you were a
rare fish in a world full of sharks.
He said you didn't take advantage
of a potentially vulnerable client.
He cited your attention to detail
and, if you can believe it,
your unique ability
to relate to people.
We did have a very good chat
about pants.
-Ta-da!
-George! You got me a fruitcake!
Yep. Old lady cake, just for you,
Helen. Congratulations.
Oh, George,
I was really looking forward
to that gorgeous mud cake.
-Are you kidding? That's not cake.
-[Roz] No.
Alright. Everybody out.
Celebration's over.
Ok. I'll take the cake,
but do I still have a job here?
Well, you did
until you ruined my day.
I was really looking forward
to the mud cake.
[laughs] Ok, it's good jokes,
but do I still have...
Get out, and take your
stupid block of raisins with you.
Ok.
-Straight to Facebook.
-Oh, you did it yourself.
[Helen] Would love to know
if I have a job or not.
[Roz] You still have a job, Helen!
[Helen] Ok. Mm-hm.
Here we go.
I'm so excited.
-Fingers crossed, eh, Helen?
-Yeah.
Oh.
Petro, I'm sorry.
Georgios Papadakis
is not your father.
Is he my half-father?
That's not a thing.
-Cousin?
-No.
Petro, you're not related
to the Papadakis family at all.
-But I really love those guys.
-Yeah, I know.
And you can still love them.
Just do it from 50 meters away.
Just do it from 150 meters away.
Ok?
Do you want those?
Mmm.
I have a scrapbook.
[machine vibrates]
[beeping]
Oh.
Roz?
Roz, I can't turn it off.
[beeping]
[vibration intensifies]