- Hey, Pete, you needed me?
- [Jessup] Do I have to...
[Broward] We're moving tonight.
A raid.
Garmen Harry reached out
to Ron Cuneo again.
Uh, you know, from the casino
and, uh, I was right.
The Mahabir family is closing
up shop pretty quickly.
Uh, we're gonna use NYPD
vehicles. We can't wait for...
ours to be dispatched.
Wow.
Okay, so [stammers] we're
running point?
[Sanders] Mm-hmm. Postal
Inspectors are running point...
but we are there to support.
All right. Um, FBI, you guys are
gonna go for the bank...
statements and hard drives, and
account records.
Do you need us to vouch
for that shit?
Or do you guys want to
attack it for yourself?
Well, actually, it's...
No, you're not expecting to find
anything because Savitri...
Mahabir wouldn't have all
that lying around.
Except no...
[deep breath]
that is not what that
actually is about.
Actually, you guys mind giving
Inspector Harmony and me...
the room for a moment?
- [Sanders]
Yeah.
- [Broward] Nope.
[Broward clears throat]
Surprised it took him this long.
[exhales]
Um, sorry, mine and Manny's...
informant is trying to yank off
his anklet. [annoyed chuckle]
Do you mind giving me a second?
Yo, Xavier. Your phone is off
and that is good...
but I know what you're doing,
and I see where you are...
and I'll know if you leave. So,
when you get this, call me...
back because we're due for
a checkup. Okay?
Uh, you know, actually,
can you, um...
Sorry. Just-Just one more call.
Sorry about that.
Hi, yes, room 924, please. It's
listed as House Anonymous.
Thank you.
[haunting instrumental music plays]
Um...
this talk, where you're gonna
tell me that Manny is point...
and I am not or something along
those lines.
Can it wait an hour?
Everything okay?
I'm gonna let you know.
I'm sorry, Pete.
[whispers] Fuck.
[music intensifies]
Fuck.
[forceful exhales]
[forceful breaths]
Xavier? Hello? Xavier?
USPIS.
Fuck.
[exhales]
[Garmen] First, you tell me what
you were doing there and...
how you ended up with
an ankle monitor on.
A lady grab me.
What she want with you?
How-How you know she?
I don't know. Maybe she
see me outside your house.
How she know you were there?
Huh?
- Because she was following Aked.
- Oh, Aked. Oh, how? How? How?
Hmm? She pick you up by
sheself. No one else was there.
Why?
I think she was acting
on her own.
- Uh-huh.
- I don't think anybody know.
What you tell she?
[grunts] Nothing, man. Nothing.
She knows everything. All right?
She-She-She...
[stammers]
She have-She have...
She-She know about...
"She-She-She"... What? What?
What? You can't talk?
And she know about the bum
we killed in the alley.
She have pictures of you and
Mrs. Mahabir. She have...
pictures of Quincy, and Ranwell,
and lots of people. No, man.
What about me?
Nothing. I didn't see
nothing about you.
- How about Len?
- Nothing.
Hey, why you not call me
when she left?
Because I know a lot of people
be after you. All right?
I thought maybe she might bug
the room or-or-or tag...
my calls, you know?
[heavy breaths]
Look, you know I want to go home
more than anything...
but why would I mess that up for
some crazy cop lady who's...
trying to keep me a secret from
her own people? [heavy breaths]
Paul, [exhales] I'm leaving
with me family.
Are you taking him with you?
Maybe. Question is whose side
is he on really.
Hmm?
[Xavier takes a deep breath]
What you do?
They been calling me
from Jared's phone.
Xavier. Thank you for calling.
I'm sorry I ain't been
connecting with you.
Me hear your message. You say
you got plans to leave?
[heavy breaths] We trying
everything, Xav.
We asked Edward Chung to help,
but it was a trap.
Was it you that, uh, that
swapped out Jared's body for...
some kind of dummy?
[crying breaths] I'm sorry.
We-We didn't think no one...
would know. I'm sorry, we...
I'm sorry, we didn't tell you.
We-We-We-We were scared.
[sniffles] [exhales]
How much was Edward Chung
charging to take you?
Nothing.
He was charging you nothing and
you didn't think it...
was some kind of trap, no?
It was my fault, Xavier. You
know me not clever like that.
Me sorry, man. Me so sorry.
And you say you're
getting money?
[whispers] Fifty-thousand.
Can you get him 50?
Maybe. Can try.
Why? Why you ask?
All right, well, Garmen Harry is
desperate for money...
and him leave tonight.
Him say if he has space on his
plane and he say "yes," can...
you get him 50?
Yeah, we can try.
[heavy breaths]
Okay, I'm gonna put you on mute.
[exhales] How many
seats you get?
Five seater.
My family and one more.
[cell phone speaker chimes on]
[exhales] All right, Louis.
[clears throat]
Garmen has assessed 60 thousand.
And he leave at
midnight tonight.
Imma call you when you
get the money.
So Garmen know about
Edward Chung?
No.
And I won't tell him.
I promise.
Hey...
[slight cough]
keep this hush-hush, right?
Because you know mouth open...
story jump out.
- Will do.
- All right. I'll see you later.
[clears throat]
Hannah-Estelle... [exhales]
you remember Xavier? He's going
to help you load stuff.
He's the fifth seat on
the plane and...
maybe he can help us when
we get back home too.
[doorbell rings]
[knock on door]
That's probably them.
[Gene takes deep breaths]
[Kristin] Thanks for seeing us, Cindy.
Yeah, well...
[kisses]
Okay. Come on.
[Kristin sighs]
Wow.
If you're this old what the fuck
does that make me?
[Jeff chuckles]
Not you, Kris. You look good.
So, why are we the most popular
people on the planet...
all of a sudden? Ah.
[chuckles]
- You know what? I bet I know.
- All right. Gene.
You're right. You're right.
Sorry. That's a...
Cindy gave me the comportment
lecture, so, I'm comporting.
Would you like to have a seat?
[Jeff groans]
[exhales] Well, we just want to
know what really happened.
[Jeff exhales]
[Gene chuckles]
And you come to us for this?
Well, in my mind, uh...
you know, uh... And it's gotten
worse by the way. I-I...
- And I'm sorry to hear.
- Really. All this. I...
From the moment that I got that
call that they got Jared.
I got that call, and then I'm
running to Sam's, and then...
And you thought, "My brother."
Because you felt guilty.
- For what?
- Guilty for turning me in!
- Oh. [scoffs]
- No!
I'm gonna save you some breath.
I've got the 49 report.
I've got...
I have a Xerox of an interview
that he did with Manny Broward.
An interview with who?
Twenty some years ago
when you turned me in...
you did an interview with a
police detective named...
Manfred Broward.
- I-I don't know who that is.
- Oh, stop.
Just save-save your dignity.
Will you? I'll get it for you.
Here we go. It's a witness form
that you fill out if you...
want to sweep something under
the rug. And a lot of the...
details are redacted...
but believe me, Jeff, there is
plenty here. There is plenty.
Case in point, "I met with
subject initials...
"J.M. who has requested
anonymity."
I never met with...
Seriously. I never met with...
"And who has confirmed payments...
-"initiated by J.M. to...
- I don't know what that is.
"...an account redacted..." I was
never supposed to see this.
And you assumed that I hadn't.
Ah! I never handle the accounts.
Ever!
Oh, well then I guess it was
some other J.M. at...
Jeffrey McCusker Foods then.
Oh my God!
God. We owe you an apology.
- What?
- Don't we?
[exhales]
Yeah, we didn't see it either.
Gene... [exhales]
Samantha is her middle name.
She always hated "Jolene."
It was "Sam" from the time
she was three I think.
[heavy breaths] Um...
[exhales]
[Sam] Mom, I understand this is
a conversation we all need...
to have. I just can't have it
right now. Okay?
Derek just walked in.
I'll-I'll call you later. Bye.
What was that all about?
Everything. [scoffs]
Are we gonna talk?
Sure. Me first. You need to go.
- We can make this...
- No, you need to leave!
- I want to make this work.
- There's only one thing I want.
It's for you to get
out of my sight.
[Harmony] Oh God.
This is the talk. From earlier.
You're telling me that Manny's
in charge of the raid.
Actually, it's because of
something I got this morning.
Manny's not running point?
No, he is. But it's
something else.
He sent the psych eval.
Damn it.
I knew he would do it
eventually. [exhales]
And I almost fired him for not
having sent it a year ago...
when he should have, but I
needed at least one...
of you on the raid tonight.
Until you got the thing that
we're about to talk about.
Mel, we got an IAB report about
a domestic incident...
case against you.
Carol?
And given it's the third
one in as many years...
with last year's leading
to the psych eval...
Did she include how we met?
How she was a witness in
one of your cases? Yeah.
- [exhales] Oh my God.
- Which of course...
just adds to the messiness. And
given the times and...
our other issues...
Yeah.
- I'm sorry.
- Uh, no, no.
I'm-I'm sorry.
I did this to myself. I get it.
I did this.
You'll officially be suspended
as of noon tomorrow...
pending a department investigation.
[slow instrumental music plays]
[Aked exhales]
[Gene & Jeff chuckle]
Uh, table for two, please.
I'm sorry. We're fully committed.
Do you have a reservation?
Actually, I have a few,
but we came anyway.
Actually, can you hang a sec?
Mm-hmm. Sure.
- Okay...
- What?
...what's about to happen now is
the best part of the whole deal.
Mr. McCusker, it is a true
honor to have you here.
- Oh, thank you.
- Please.
- [chuckles] Go ahead, Bro.
- Please. [laughs]
Holy Toledo. Are you fucking
kidding me? [chuckles]
Gene tried private security
for a while.
You know, jobs where
he could sit.
- Yeah.
- Schools. Jewelry stores.
Oh. It was worse, huh?
So finally he just had to
accept the fact that... [scoffs]
You were gonna be the
breadwinner. Sorry.
No, he did. And I was. So...
Hey, here's to...
Whatever the fuck [chuckling]
just happened.
Yeah.
What if he still doesn't pay?
Have you thought about that?
Shut up! I'm sick of you.
- I'm just saying...
- Nicholas!
Your dad don't want to pay, we
still give you back.
Even without the money.
What if I don't want to go back?
Hey!
Raas scunt. You going back!
Okay, so, this what we gonna do.
We gonna take you inside,
we gonna knock on they door.
What apartment they in?
I don't know. Six something.
Tell me now. What apartment
they in?
Louis.
- Eighteen J.
- Let go of him. Let go.
That's him. That's your daddy?
Go. Go! Go! They isn't inside.
Go! Go!
[Derek] Um, I just wanted to say
I love you and...
Me will come back just now.
[Natalia exhales]
[deep breath]
Sir? I'm so sorry for the wait.
Your suite's ready.
You'll be on the third floor.
Room 309.
Thank you.
- Enjoy your stay.
- Thanks.
[deep breath]
You're upset obviously and
you're not taking my calls...
or replying to my messages.
And this is another that you're
not even gonna listen to...
so what am I doing? [sighs]
[knock on door]
- Yeah?
- [Natalia] Mr. Browne?
[deep breath] Coming.
[exhales]
We got your boy. And we know you
don't want nothing to do with...
him so we gonna make
you an offer.
You have my boy?
Yes. And this is your other
boy's phone.
- Who are you?
- Doesn't matter.
You gonna let us in?
Us?
- Hey, Dad.
- Oh Jesus.
We coming in or not?
Yeah. Yeah, come on.
Okay.
Okay, okay. All right.
[exhales] Fuck.
First thing we're gonna do is
you're gonna call your mother.
He ain't calling nobody.
Look, let me make a call.
You ain't making no phone call
until we get a deal.
We know you paid a lot of money
so nobody knew about him.
All we ask is you pay again.
It's gonna be 60 thousand.
Or we gon' tell everybody.
Okay, well, why don't you go
ahead and do that then...
because everybody fucking knows
because you guys called...
my house last night.
Sorry.
Hey!
[Aked] Yo, Jared!
Where is she?
Where is who? Who are you?
- Huh?
- Okay. Okay.
[panicked breaths]
[impact grunts]
[Derek groans]
Where the fuck is she? Don't
play with me. [heavy breaths]
[Natalia cries]
Give me. [heavy breaths]
Nat?
[Natalia cries]
You lied to me.
You made an ass out of me,
but you lied to me, Nat.
[cries] I'm sorry, Aked. Please.
Please don't do this. Please.
You left me with no option.
[attack yells]
[Natalia gasps] [cries]
[gun fires]
[fight grunts]
[labored breaths]
[Natalia gasps]
[panicked crying breaths]
[Louis breathes heavily]
[Natalia sobs]
[Aked with labored breaths]
I'm sorry.
Just get out. Get the fuck out.
- Me sister phone.
- Just get the fuck out.
Come, come, come, Nat.
Come, come. Come on.
[Natalia with panicked breaths]
[Natalia sobs]
[Louis] Please.
[panicked breaths]
- Louis.
- Xav.
Something bad happened.
We ain't get the money.
Aked dead.
What you talk about Aked dead, man?
He tried to kill Nat.
Point a gun towards she.
Oh my Jesus Christ.
What the raas, Louis?
Aked dead. We ain't got
any money.
You think Garmen still gon'
take us home?
Man, how you ask that?
I don't know. [exhales]
- The painting.
- What?
[exhales] [sniffles] Xavier...
[crying] um, [sniffles]
there's a-there's a painting.
There's a painting worth five
times that much money.
We can take it.
I don't know. Me have to ask
him. All right?
Jesus Christ. It's getting all
too much.
Are you even sure you
can get that?
No. No, will he, will-will
he take it?
All right. I can ask. Let me
call you back after I speak...
to him. All right? [exhales]
[Garmen] Ameena, you can make
new friends. Better friends.
All right? I promise.
[Ameena] I don't want to make
new friends.
I coming back just now.
[exhales]
What happened? What is it?
Aked dead.
Oh Jesus Christ.
- [Ameena] Dad.
- I coming.
How you know?
I don't know. Something to do
with Louis and Natalia.
They just call.
- Ms. M. know?
- I don't think anybody know.
Keep it that way.
And one other thing.
They ain't got the money.
[scoffs]
But they say they got a painting
worth five times the amount...
if you can still get them home.
[Ameena] My suitcase don't work.
Baby, I coming just now.
All right?
Uh, paint-painting. Yeah,
listen, I can't deal with...
this right now.
Just-Just, um, tell them we
call them later. All right?
And-And don't lose touch
with them.
I won't.
[Police Officer #1] What's the
official time of death?
[Police Officer #2] It's on the
95 tag.
Any idea when the Crime
Scene arrives?
[Police Officer #1] Man, we're
gonna be here all day.
Is he all right?
He's got a ricochet wound to the
rear of his right shoulder...
and there are bullet fragments
and shrapnel from...
the tile as well.
You're welcome to come with us.
I'm sorry?
[Police Officer #3] We'll get
your statement at the hospital.
This way you can stay
with your son.
Stay with...
Right.
[ER Nurse] If I can just get a
little information from you.
I just called his mother. She'll
be here as soon as she can.
Oh, o-okay. All right.
Well, um, in the meantime...
if you wouldn't mind giving me
his date of birth, height...
weight, vaccination history, any
allergies to penicillin...
or anything.
Date of birth February 2007.
Okay, February 2007.
Do you know what day?
[clicks tongue]
All right. Um, uh, what about
how tall he is.
Do you know approximately
how tall he is?
- Five-eight, five-nine.
- Okay.
And approximately how much
do you think he weighs?
You know, we-we can wait for
his mom to get here for that.
Most importantly, any allergies
that you know of?
To penicillin?
Or any other medications
that he's taking?
I don't know.
[door opens]
[door shuts]
[keys drop on the table]
Mom?
Shit.
- Where's Dad?
- [groans] Hospital.
His, uh, his chess guy. The one
that, um, he was playing...
with in the park.
He, uh, had a stroke
or something.
Classic Jeff worried there's
some total stranger out there...
in the world that doesn't
love him.
Mom, have you been drinking?
Yes.
But only for [chuckling]
49 years. [laughs]
Wow. Okay. Well, I can't deal
with this headfuck right now...
so I'm gonna put it over here. Um...
Thanks, Mom. [scoffs]
[Kristin] How's Derek
by the way?
[exhales] [annoyed chuckles]
Derek.
Well, Derek is in a hotel...
because it turns out that
Charisse is not a place.
No. Charisse is a person.
So, yeah. Another
fucking secret.
Oh, it's not a secret, Sam.
Wait. You knew about Charisse?
Well, after Derek took
over the books for me...
I used to double-check
for a while.
What, because you didn't
trust him? W-What?
Yeah, I noticed that he had
taken some money out...
and then he put it back from a
different account.
It's very easy to trace.
Wait and then... [chuckles] And
then you trusted him?
After that? [stammers]
He paid it back.
Do you remember he never
wanted to live in New York?
But he did, for you.
He dug in and dedicated every
moment after that to you.
And to the Chef Jeff of it all.
And-And to Jared.
You're looking at me
like I'm crazy.
[chuckling exhale]
Like Dad looks at me.
- No, Dad's right. You're...
- Yeah, no, I know.
I know, it's his bit.
I'm the ostrich not the eagle.
But he's wrong, Sam because
I see.
Okay.
Well, if you're an eagle, you're
an eagle with her head in...
the sand which is fucking worse.
You didn't tell me about my
own fucking husband.
[laughs] Because you would never
have forgiven him! Would you?
And you would have lost him!
[haunting instrumental music plays]
[Natalia] Louis!
This from them.
From Saturday night.
Ms. Mahabir say a circle is
gonna protect everybody.
You think that shit works?
I don't know what's worse...
it works and it's all
broke up now...
or it never worked
in the first place.
[Harmony] Sam.
Inspector Harmony.
Uh, how can I help you? [scoffs]
Oh, I would perhaps limit to the
scope of that question being...
that I have been suspended
starting noon tomorrow.
Oh. I'm sorry to hear that.
No, you're not. Uh...
[Sam slightly chuckles]
Your case, by the way, uh,
it's almost been solved.
At least they're about to make
a bunch of fancy arrests, so...
And you came here
to tell me that?
Oh no, no. [chuckles]
The truth is...
Well, you're fishing.
What do they call it when a fish
is fished and then it's on...
the deck gasping?
Uh, flailing?
That would be me.
[elevator door chimes]
[Sam exhales]
Your Uncle Gene told
me everything.
Oh. You mean the disgraced
former cop who shot himself...
in the foot to avoid prison and
get a lifetime of disability?
I think you're saying that just
to try to scare me. [scoffs]
Doesn't really matter anyway
because why would you say...
anything to incriminate
yourself?
Well, especially when it has no
material effect on...
this investigation.
Or worse, possibly expose you
to all sorts of liability.
Nah, if I were you,
I'd be like...
"I worked hard for this life and
I'm gonna protect...
"the fuck out of it."
- Why are you here?
- The Series A Investments.
Who made them and through
which banks. We've hit a wall.
I thought you were fired.
It may help Roan Jessup find
other people from down there...
who are now in other
cities in other states.
Well, I-I... [exhales] Wait, he
may help you to find a job?
As I said, it's a Hail Mary.
And the ball's up in the air.
I don't know where it's gonna
land or if it's gonna land.
But you're right.
Because why would you fuck
all of this up for that?
You should probably get inside.
Where it's safe.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
[security alarm on door beeps]
[Harmony] So I'm looking for the
name of the person who...
rented the chalk cart and the
address it was sent to.
Thank you.
Could you spell that for me?
[Broward] All right. This is a
microphone and a camera.
Whatever you see, we see.
You know what you're doing?
Uh, [exhales] look at everyone,
uh, hold on them.
And?
[exhales] Say names whenever
I can.
Yeah.
[Sanders] If...
It's not weird.
Hey, Detective Sanders and I are
gonna be behind you...
the entire time.
And-And Agent Jessup is-is
ghosting you in a follow van.
Our eyes are gonna be on
you the entire time.
[Fong] How are we looking?
[Sanders] Mahabir is meeting at
20-hundred.
We're going in at 20:30.
Ah. Yeah. At first we thought
our error on the night of...
the event meant that our
rebirth would be impossible...
but then Mr. Willoughby
explained what we thought...
were mistakes...
were actually a series of
necessary turns...
that would expel the impurities
within our circle.
So now we are ready to go ahead
with what we're meant to do.
Oh.
I haven't had the same feelings
of enthusiasm and hope...
since the day we exchanged
rings, Ranny.
It's a new beginning.
I really think you'll be happy
with how this evening...
will turn out.