Have you, by any
chance, realized
the useless piece of
shit that you've raised?
You keep talking,
fucking porkies.
Off!
Hey, off, off!
Can you see this?
And let's see if you can
teach your little brothers,
you piece of shit!
How is this?
Make sure this grub
is ready soon, no?
Keep quiet!
Oh.
Father doesn't like you.
You stink!
You're not even our brother.
And lead us not into temptation.
I believe in God,
the Father Almighty,
creator of heaven and earth,
Jesus Christ his
only son, Our Lord,
conceived by the power
of the Holy Spirit
and born of the Virgin Mary.
I believe in God,
the Father Almighty,
creator of heaven and earth.
I believe in Jesus Christ
his only son, Our Lord,
born of the Virgin Mary.
I believe in God,
the Father Almighty,
creator of heaven and earth.
I believe in Jesus
Christ his only son,
who was born of the Virgin Mary.
I believe in God,
the Father Almighty,
creator of heaven and earth.
The kids are playing outside.
Jesus Christ his only son,
who was born of the Virgin Mary.
I believe in God, the Father.
Almighty,
creator of heaven and earth.
I believe in Jesus Christ.
His only son, Our Lord.
He was conceived by the
power of the Holy Spirit
and born of the Virgin Mary.
He suffered under
Pontius Pilate.
He was crucified,
died, and was buried.
Get out!
Give us our daily bread.
Lead us not into temptation.
You sick...
You sick bastard.
Hey, you sick!
You sick!
Satan runs our city.
He destroys our crops.
He enters our home, our family,
through promiscuity and hatred.
Together, we are stronger.
Only together we
will attain glory.
His salvation.
Jesus takes care for his
flock as he goes walking,
walking together, with the
principles of the Mother Church.
We cannot surrender
ourselves, we cannot give up
that fellowship in Christ.
And, now, brothers and sisters,
return with the
peace and the grace
of the Lord to your homes.
Grace to the Lord, amen.
Amen.
Is he dead?
I told you
not to hit him so hard.
Leave the little
sinner, Mommy boy's alone.
Where's our money?
Bastard.
Go on, get out.
Go!
Boo.
Little boy, today,
you will learn
what every father has to
teach his son to survive.
How to bring real food
home to us at the house.
What?
Your mother never told you
that the food you're eating,
that was, you are
eating the meat
that you were...
You see all this
stuff here, boy?
This is very expensive for me.
This costs me my sweat,
and I'm not going to be
able to feed you or your ma
or anyone with this here.
Today's lesson,
how to become a big man.
Or die
for Brazil.
Listen to me, boy.
I don't know if you know it,
but it's not easy to get
all this food, you know.
I want you to pay
close attention
this here.
Someone has to eat.
Someone has to do it, my son.
And there's not a poor,
little thing like you
that would let me
be less than I am.
Shut up!
You see this fucking
cursed worm, hmm?
Can you believe he was
robbing food in the fields?
What does he deserve, huh?
He deserves to be minced,
just like the military are doing
with the hippies
in the big city.
Do you want to talk?
Don't scream.
You're not going
to scream, right?
Promise!
Shh!
Do you see this
little thing here?
This little thing
here has already taken
a lot of people to hell.
She brings and takes,
brings and takes.
You're going to learn
how to kill a pig.
Shh.
And I've got a surprise for you.
Chan-chan-chan-cha!
Get me out of here!
Look in his eyes.
Look.
You recognize this
little worm now?
Are you seeing who this is?
I baptize you in the
name of the Father.
I believe in God,
the Father Almighty,
creator of heaven and earth.
I believe in Jesus Christ
his only son, Our Lord.
He was conceived by the
power of the Holy Spirit
and born of the Virgin Mary.
Creator of heaven.
Go on, go to your mother.
Now your goatling is baptized.
You monster!
Why did you do this?
I told you, you will pay!
I told you, you monster!
Monster, monster!
I hate you, I hate you!
Forgiveness from Jesus,
forgiveness from Jesus.
Jesus was crowned with thorns.
He cast out his
words, his thoughts,
his judgments, condemnations,
impurities, betrayals.
Forgiveness from Jesus,
forgiveness from Jesus,
who was crowned with thorns
because of his thoughts,
not his words and impurities.
Forgiveness from Jesus.
Jesus Christ his only son.
I'm done.
God knows that what
I'm doing is not a sin.
Oh my God.
I don't want to!
Both!
Come here.
What are you gonna do, freak?
Sit down, both of
you, come on, sit!
The Lord knows everything, shh!
He will guide us.
You will thank me later.
It has to be today.
There's no time.
What do you
want to do with them.
Take them
far away, please, Father.
I need them far away from
that house, that man.
Sit down.
You dirty the name of the Lord.
Stab your hands with
blood of sinners.
The devil has touched you.
You betrayed God.
You're evil, you
betrayed the Lord,
the Father Almighty
who hates liars.
There's only one way
for you to apologize.
You will kill Satan
with the hands
that killed the sinners.
You will put out defective
meat to feed to the pigs.
Only then, your soul
will perish in paradise.
No.
Here stay here.
You will do everything I say.
Hey, ha, ha!
Get outta here!
I can see you!
Get out!
What?
What's this, huh?
Fuck!
Where is that piece of shit?
And the hide of the goat.
I'll wear it.
And this wanker
God that you love.
Come here.
- I bought you one?
Come here to your captain.
Thank the
Lord for the food, first.
Look,
the only Lord here
in this house is me.
You dropped me.
Did you bring something to eat?
You are really
worthless, aren't ya?
You're not even capable of
bringing food to the house.
I tried to help you, my son.
As God as my witness, I
tried to help you, son!
I sacrificed myself
and for what?
For you, it's not
important, right?
My dear God, it looks
as though the devil
is trying to mess up my life!
Blessings.
Are you really going
to let your old mother
do this job for you?
Are you that useless?
I can't stand eating this meat.
Drop that!
There's no food for you.
Leave it!
The Lord is watching you
disrespect the Gospels, my son.
Honor your father and mother.
Will you remember that?
Do you know where God in
the Gospels say bad boys go?
The filthy sinner boys.
You don't know, don't ya?
You're useless.
How many?
How many what, huh?
How many laid in
this dirty bed, woman?
None of your business.
How many?
What the fuck, huh?
20, 30?
50?
You bastard!
What the fuck is this?
Where are you going?
Huh?
You're going to fuck
your own mother, right?
Tonight is a special night, son.
Dinner is reinforced.
It's the moment to
gather strength, my boy.
Here, we need to stay
together and be strong
to listen to what the
Lord is telling us.
Ma.
Don't interrupt me.
Listen to me.
You think I don't know
about your little calf?
Do you think I don't know
about the Mary Magdalene
you have seen in the dark?
- Listen, Mom-
- Shut your mouth!
Respect me!
You're going to
bring me that calf.
And now be quiet, and you
follow me on my prayers.
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou amongst women
and blessed is the
fruit of thy womb Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of
God, pray for us sinners
now and at the
hour of our death.
Amen.
You're dead.
There's something
bad behind me, woman.
What?
I'm seeing...
It's...
I don't know what I'm seeing.
What?
Don't laugh.
Shut up.
That's all
I need right now, hmm?
You don't understand.
Huh?
It's behind me.
- This little boy crap.
Come here.
Hey, what is this?
What the hell is this?
- It's here.
- Look up.
- What is here?
It's cold.
Wake up, wake up, stop it!
Stop, stop, stop it, hey!
What is it, what is it?
What is it, huh?
Get what out, get what out?
What are you talking about?
Stop it, stop, stop, please.
Stop it, stop it.
What is it, hey, hey.
Calm down.
What was it, huh?
Yeah.
We have to think about
that baby in there.
Can you see how big it is?
Look here, look at this.
I've already bought
this for you.
- Oh, really?
Can use that one.
And look very nice.
I know.
It's because when he's born,
everything has to be
tidy and neat, right?
- It will be.
- If it would be
up to that useless
brother of yours.
I don't know how he
got you pregnant.
Don't talk!
Shut your mouth!
Sweetheart, darling,
have you had dinner yet?
Let's eat, no, no, no,
no, no, we pray first!
We pray now!
You want some food, my love?
You're gonna want some food.
I'll feed you.
You don't want some food?
It smells delicious.
Let me see here.
Mother, aren't you happy
about your food, Mom?
My loving, darling mom.
I'll bring you some
food every day, Mama.
Every day.
Shut your mouth!
I'm speaking now!
I'm gonna talk now!
We pray now.
No one eats before praying.
Mother.
Mom.
Days of rot.
Hard times.
You have no idea, my dear,
how hard it is to
get food every day.
Real food, good food.
Not that shitty crap they
insist on having us swallow!
What world is this?
My dear, you don't wanna know.
Dog world.
You do very well by
being quiet here!
When did humanity
begin hiding true love?
Sincere love, my darling.
But we didn't.
Not us, right, sweetheart?
Or the name of the God
had been drugged too.
All these people,
those who no longer
believe in true love anymore.
Not us, my dear.
What lovely days.
Let us know.
♪ Is
from my sweet ♪
♪ She had hard eyes ♪
♪ That look ♪
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no.
I was never good at this.
Calm down, calm down.
Aye-yai-yai-yai-yai.
My mother, she's been talking
crap to you again, right?
Mom!
She's not like the
other ones, no ma'am!
She's my real favorite, my girl!
You son of a bitch,
I hate you, I hate you!
I hate you, let me go!
Let me go!
Release me, release me!
Calm, calm, calm.
Stop, stop, stop,
stop, stop, stop, stop!
I'm sorry.
I hate you, I hate you so much!
Release me!
My little girl,
my pretty flower.
You're beautiful.
I will never feel cold again.
Let me go.
Never again.
You're disgusting.
- Pretty flower.
- Stop!
Release me.
Let me go.
I'm still very cold, you bitch.
Stop it.
I am cold deep inside.
- Stop it.
- It is my soul,
you terrible bitch.
- Stop it.
You're just like all of them.
Warm me up, my darling.
Warm me up, my compassion.
Please.
Stop it.
♪ The goddess from my sweet ♪
Please, stop it.
Please, stop.
- Rosalita.
- Please.
Release the flesh dear God.
Blessings.
Hi, useless.
Hi.
You are useless.
There is a black coffin passing
through the middle of the crowd.
I see people crying
for the one inside the coffin.
They arrive at the cemetery
and put the black
coffin on the marble.
You bastard.
You took her from
me, my Rosalita.
You took her from me.
The only thing I truly
loved in this world!
I hate you!
I hate you, Mommy!
You didn't take care
of me, Mommy.
I'm getting cold, Mommy.
Today, I just want
to know if the Lord
is seeing all of
this, and, if he is,
I hope he knows he's a
great motherfucking liar.