Thank you.
Japan was a place
where you could make money.
The strategy was to gain economic power.
Thousands of young people
have joined the Unification Church,
which began in Korea.
I believe he's a prophet
in a similar position to John the Baptist
to prepare the way
for the Second Coming of Christ.
Long live the true parents!
Long live!
We love our children.
They're beautiful.
They've been the subject
of a strenuous brainwashing exercise
by Moon and his people.
In the battle against communism,
Reverend Sun Myung Moon
has launched a crusade on a global scale
to bring about the total defeat
of this godless empire of evil.
Reverend Moon faces
an 18-month prison sentence
for failing to pay income taxes
on the interest from large sums
of church funds
held in his personal bank accounts.
Seems to me that IRS and the government
have overstepped their boundaries
in terms of separation
of church and state.
When I think of The Washington Times,
I think of a publication that has brought
much-needed balance
to the way
Washington is covered these days.
True Father,
thank you
for your unparalleled investment.
Father, we're so grateful
for the Second Amendment.
Long live the true parents!
The world is getting crazy.
It's all a play, isn't it?
Now that's the truth.