Good morning.
This is your wake—up call.
Thank you for staying
at the new dannin inn.
The time is 10:30 am.
You have no new messages.
- Johnny?
Yeah?
Where are you going this time?
I travel...
How i make my living.
Data storage, remember?
You have no new messages.
Nas: Nerve
attenuation syndrome...
Cause unknown. Cure unknown.
Where is home, Johnny?
Home?
Would you believe I don't even know?
- Yes, I would.
- Going out?
- Just getting some ice.
We've got... ice.
Pick it up, Ralfi.
How about it, Ralfi?
You said you'd lock down
a date for the procedure.
And hello to you too.
Ralfi, the date, when?
I'm sorry, Johnny.
The Shiba neurosurgeons
have changed their quote.
- You told me 800k would cover it.
The fee for removing the
implant is now 1 million—5.
That is complete memory recovery.
If you don't want it all back,
I think they will come down.
If I just wanted the silicon
dug out of my back brain,
I could go to Mexico City.
I want a full restoration!
I want it all back!
Johnny, the shiba
boys, they set the price.
- I've done what I can.
- Come on, ralfi!
- One more run, Johnny, and
then you could cover it,
provided it's a rich one.
Yeah...
- So, what have you got?
- — It depends.
Did you get that upgrade
we were discussing?
- — Yeah.
- Very good.
Pickup is in central Beijing
tomorrow night, 10:00.
This is a big one, Johnny.
Don't be late.
Please disperse immediately!
Crimson Turner World
Broadcast Satellite News Net.
Live from Central Beijing.
Where police tactial squad are
clashing with demonstrators...
Protesting the Chinese government stance
on Nerve Attenuation Syndrome.
Paging Mr. Smith.
Paging Mr. Smith. (Mandarin-Chinese)
Nas, the so-called black shakes,
first identified in 2010...
in a small population of
nonnegian information—...
- Snatch back your brain, zombie!
Snatch it back and hold it.
Sorry, technical difficulty.
Please come in.
Activating pemex memory doubler.
Your present capacity: 80 gigabytes.
Doubler loading.
Your storage capacity
is now 160 gigabytes.
Warning: Do not exceed capacity.
The courier is late! — be calm.
Relax... watch TV.
- Double cheese, anchovies?
- You are mister... — Smith.
- You are late.
- Right.
Question. — yes?
You don't look like the kind
of people I usually work for.
- We are new at this.
No shit.
- We approached you through
the correct channels.
We paid half in advance
to the Swiss account,
exactly as your agent instructed.
Here's your ticket, first class.
- Let's see what you wanna upload.
Motion detector.
In case the natives get restless.
How much am I carrying?
- 320 gigabytes.
Your storage capacity?
Where am I taking it? — Newark.
- Your storage capacity?
- More than adequate.
MAN: So you'll take him to Las Vegas?
WOMAN: I just started...
It is extremely dangerous
If the upload volume exceeds
your storage capacity.
Synaptic seepage can kill
you in two or three days.
Plus, the data may be corrupted,
and coherent download will be impossible.
We don't have a problem with that, okay?
We loading or not?
Your ticket.
Ralfi, your agent in Newark,
will arrange the meet for the download.
When
the counter approaches zero,
click on three frames
off the TV, any three.
They'll meld with the data and
I won't know what they are.
That's the download code.
You get a hard copy.
You fax one copy to your
connection on the other side.
When I get there, we feed
in the code and download.
Understand?
Upload begins when you press here.
- — Who's the target?
- Scientists.
Pharmakom r & d people, defectors.
Hit me!
- The access code.
Mr. ... Smith?
Where's the bathroom?
What? — the toilet.
Destroy the original!
Fax the images to Newark.
Aah! Oh, Jesus!
Jesus! Shit! Ah— aah!
Water temperature is 17 degrees.
Next time, knock, baldy.
Transmission commencing.
Transmission interrupted.
Get him!
You, where is he going?
- Where is he taking the data?
- Newark!
Immigration
control. Please insert passport.
Beginning scan.
Warning: Implant detected.
Scanning dyslexia prosthesis implant.
Government approved.
Warning: Detected synaptic seepage.
Neural failure within 24 hours.
Seek medical attention immediately.
- — Thank you.
- Welcome to Newark.
Final boarding call for Western Pacific Air
Flight 86, Gate 1 1 3.
(Little girl giggling)
Papa it's new.
I'm sorry to disturb you, Mr. Takahashi
Shinji's here.
Tokyo wants me to
recover the stolen data
for pharmakominat industries of Zurich.
Our operation in Beijing
met with limited success.
The pharmakom traitors are dead.
The courier, however,
escaped with the data.
He's on his way here to Newark.
I didn't want to disturb
you in your time of grief.
It must be very difficult
to lose an only child.
I assumed you would be unavailable.
I'm not at Liberty to say.
I've been charged with recovering
the head of the mnemonic
courier, cryogenically preserved.
Preserved?
The traitors wiped
the pharmakom mainframe.
If we lose the courier,
they've lost the data forever.
If the courier is in Newark,
it's my responsibility.
You have part of the
courier's download code.
Get me Pharmakom.
Make you own images, get your life back!
The human race is waiting for you zombies!
- Just what's the deal here?
- Johnny boy...
- Johnny boy, my ass. What's
the fucking score here?
I'm way overloaded, man.
You would not believe how much.
- You told me you got... upgraded.
- Yeah, yeah, I did.
I got the goods, Ralfi.
Now I just wanna get them out of my head.
Did they get the code out?
— don't worry.
They said they can extract.
— extract?
Ex—
What's going on, Ralfi?
This feels like a blown deal, man.
- You say you have to get the data out.
They are the only ones who can do it.
There's no other choice. Trust me.
I will tell the driver where to take you.
- Yeah, sure.
- I need to get some work.
- About these episodes you've been having,
I wanna get you back to
the shop for some tests.
Hey, are you listening?
No more playing doctor, remember?
Oh, that's not what I meant.
Look at them. They must be
the oldest bodyguards in town.
I'm twice as fast as they are.
Not worried about your speed.
I'm worried about your nervous system,
especially if you wanna
continue being a bodyguard.
Get out of here, bitch.
Take it easy!
Your hired muscle is
aging on you, Ralfi.
I could've done ya.
Time you hired yourself
some young and fast, hmm?
- You mean, like you?
- You're the best agent
for bodyguards in town.
I'm the fastest thing going,
now spider's jacked my system.
- Hold out your hand.
Okay.
Fine. Just hold it there.
- So?
- Just hold it there.
You can hold it there, baby, can't you?
- Yeah, sure.
See?
- Cheap street implants hahaha.
- You're damaged goods, bitch.
Spiderman jacked you up, all right.
- Jacked her up so tight, she shakes.
- I cannot use you, not for muscle.
Ever considered something a
little less actively physical?
Like on your back, babe?
Ah, ooh! Or on your knees.
I'll get a gig, Ralfi.
- Then I'm coming back for you.
- Sure.
Yo, J-Bone.
What you clocking, man?
- Some suit out from the city.
What for? — I don't know.
Suits don't come out here.
You're Johnny?
- Am I?
- I sure hope so.
Come on in. We're here to help you.
We've gotta
stop meeting like this.
- Baldy!
- — doctor will see you now.
You lied.
Yeah.
Time to die. — time?
We've got all night, asshole!
Let me see that...
- Yo, toad, I said shut up, man.
Yo, J-man.
You weren't on the menu.
I want you to do something for me.
- — Do?
- Yes. Say bye.
Hold it right there.
(Laughing)
You tooling up for an
evening of this stuff, huh?
As long as you understand
one thing, we're even.
I don't owe you shit.
Who are you?
I'm J-Bone.
I run "Heaven".
The Lotek Headquarters.
Papa...
It's new.
(Little girl giggling)
How sad...
So very sad Mr. Takahashi.
The lost of a child...
For I am, Mr. Takahashi...
There is only... memory.
memory on the play of conscience.
An endless reckoning of the score.
When i see you there, i know you...
your purpose is lost.
At the very core of all your power...
There's only an emptiness...
Hollowness...
Carved in the shape of the absent child.
Papa...
j' easy as apple pie j'
j' easy as j'
Johnny!
They were waiting for me, Ralfi,
two big nasty men!
- Johnny, please, let me explain.
- Johnny!
- You set me up, my friend.
Johnny, it's not my fault.
There's been a screw up!
You're dead if you don't
get this batch of product
out of my head.
- Shit!
Not on the head!
Don't tell me you hit him on the head.
You know i haven't been in
one of this in years?
This way.
Hooky, give me my shit.
Come on.
How are you feeling, Johnny?
What'd they upload, Ralfi,
the goddamn library of congress?
Feels like my brain's gonna explode.
I think yourfriend here,
he can take care of that.
Ralfi,
you lying sack of shit.
- Please let's work
this out like gentlemen.
Johnny, in this business,
you only fuck up once with Yakuza.
- We'll need a bucket.
Pheww.. it's not sterile.
Put it here beside the table.
- Can we talk about this?
- Talk?
I have one image of the access code.
You have the other two.
I'll give you the data. Everybody happy.
You don't understand.
They don't just want the data,
they want everything
it's ever been stored in.
There's less danger of information decay.
And we don't have to worry
about anyone going in
with mnemonic sensors.
These days, you see,
Dead men can tell tales.
- There's gotta be a way to work this out!
There is.
- Would you hurry it up, please?
It's getting disgusting.
What the fuck is going on?
I'll slit his fucking throat, bitch.
- So? Other guy gonna
cut his whole head off.
- Jane, Jane, what say we
pay you for a night's work
and you just walk away?
— I'll pay you 20 grand.
You wouldn't
believe the shit you're in.
- 50.
Deal!
Ah, you bitch!
We'll be okay, I got the gun. Let's go.
Time to go!
Bitch!
- You could have fucking killed me!
Get out of the way!
What are you doing? — my gear.
In here.
- Back door. — thanks, J-Bone.
We'll find you again! Count on it!
Down!
You loteks will regret this.
I have to get online.
Must be somebody I can
talk to to square this.
- 50 thou, you said.
Time I see the color, right?
— right.
You were terrific.
So if you'll just point the way out
and give me an account number
for the cash transfer—
Account number?
I'm on you till you pay, mister.
How come they wanna cut
off your head anyway?
I mean, usually they just
off people around here.
Long story.
Well, I'm gonna be around
until I get paid, so...
I can carry nearly 80
gigs of data in my head,
160 if I use a doubler.
Trouble is, somebody stuck
in a lot more than that
and I don't know how to get it back out.
Okay, so wait a minute. Wait a minute.
You're a smuggler? In your head?
Hey!... What's wrong?
Come here. Sit down, sit down!
Oh, man, you are fucked up severe.
Stay quiet,
Shh, okay? Okay?
(Little girl giggling)
Papa.
It's new.
(Little girl giggling)
Papa.
- Takahashi, how sad, the loss of a child.
They know that your purpose
in life has been lost.
It died with your daughter.
You have become a risk to them.
Take a good look at their errand boy,
the one who wants the courier's head.
He's plotting to destroy you.
You must neutralize him, Takahashi.
Now!... Then we can talk.
I promise you,
the courier, what he carries
can give you new a purpose in life.
I was Pharmakom. And I...
They're listening.
They're everywhere.
Excuse me Sir but Shinji's here
with two of his men.
You can't just walk in here!
I told them to wait, Takahashi-san.
Who are they?
They are my Kobuns. (protégés)
Don't let that happen again.
Locate him... inform me!
I will supervise his capture.
Understood?
(Kids laughing)
Uh.
It's just my stuff.
Mace, throwing spikes, grenade,
everything a girl needs.
- You let me sleep?
- You needed it.
I told you I was in a hurry.
I'm a dead man if! Don't
get this out of my head.
- Hey, do you ever sneak
a look at what you carry?
- Usually, there's a code, like a lock.
Well, when there isn't? — no.
It goes with the territory.
Safer for me, safer for the client.
How come you knew those...
— oh, call them "Loteks".
I sort of hung with them when I was a kid.
Say, how do you fit all that
shit in your head, anyway?
Must've been pretty
good at memorizing, huh?
Implant, wet-wired.
I had to dump a chunk of long—term memory.
- You had to dump a chunk of what?
- My childhood.
- — your childhood?
Really?
All of it?
You can't remember a thing?
- Maybe there's some residual traces.
Every now and then, there's something,
but I.. I can never hold onto it.
That's a seriously
weird—ass thing to do.
Yeah, well, maybe I didn't
lose anything I wanted to keep.
I needed the space for the job.
Well, you got parents and stuff?
- You got parents and stuff?
- — yeah.
Once, but I haven't seen them in years.
Yeah. Anyways, I don't
think about it much, okay?
- So, what do you think about?
When you're alone?
I think I want to get
out of this rat hole.
I want to get online. I need a computer.
Where'd you learn to do that?
- I used to have a summer
job breaking and entering.
I need a Sino-logic 16,
Sogo 7 data gloves, a GPL stealth module,
one Burdine intelligent
translator, a Thomson iPhone.
Password, enter.
Welcome to brt online.
Global net selected.
What are you doing?
Making a long—distance phone call.
Beijing, a hotel.
Beijing selected.
Access denied.
Access granted.
Hotel Beijing selected.
General accounts selected.
Fax charges, suite 2571, 15 January, 2021,
7:15 pm. To 11:30 pm.
He'll try to make a move.
He'll use his connections on the net.
Narrow the bandwidth. Go low rent.
Online translation.
— translator selected.
Shit. It's just an all—night copy shop.
They were sending the fax to
a copy shop here in Newark.
Local net selected.
Hold it. Hold it.
— command terminated.
- Come on, baby, all
the way back to Newark.
- Yeah, it's here.
- Fax buffer selected.
Part of it's here in the
buffer of their fax modem.
Nothing but a name, Dr. Allcome.
Nothing came through. Shit!
- Let's go, okay?
No, I'm gonna try something
else, a guy called Strike.
He runs a board in this
sector, owes me a favor.
Maybe he can find this doctor for me.
We locked on him.
He's using a sino-logic
16 gpl stealth module.
Crazy Bob's computer shop,
5326 Sutton Plaza, backroom.
Initiate the virus.
- Access denied.
- Come on, let me in!
- Access granted.
- Get off my board, man.
You are too hot.
You're a hit waiting to happen.
- Off!
- You owe me, strike.
I don't owe you that much.
- I could crash you from here, man,
wipe out your entire fucking board!
Johnny, don't, man.
That's my livelihood.
Then stop bullshitting me!
I need to know what I'm holding, Strike.
Why is the Yakuza after it?
Who's Dr. Allcome?
All I know is, you've got
a head full of Pharmakom data
and they've hired the
Yakuza to get it out.
Pharmakom?
Shit! They put a virus on us.
- — Shit!
- Get out of here, man.
I never heard of any Dr. Allcome.
Johnny. Hurry, Johnny, they're coming!
- — Who the hell are you?
- Gotta go now.
Come on.
Just my beer opener.
Inform Takahashi his tracker was late
in locating the courier.
It seems he's already departed.
Mr. Takahashi,
Shinji has failed again...
to locate the courier.
Get me Karl.
Church of the Retransfiguration.
Thank you for calling.
- I need your services.
- We hold services nightly.
- You should join us.
- A special one.
- Do you need someone brought to Jesus?
- Or to you?
- Only one part, his head.
And who is this lost soul,
this sinner unrepentant?
- A courier, last seen at the drome.
Name is Johnny.
If you get me the head in
24 hours, triple the fee.
Karl, do not fail me.
Can't use any of this.
Yakuza's watching the net,
Waiting for my first transaction.
Hey! What are you... what are you doing?
Mind if! Use this?
— man owes me 50 thou
and he's scamming my phone card.
And it's still our first date.
Welcome to AT&T.
Enter password, please.
This is an unlisted
number. How did you get it?
Don't like surprises? — no.
And it's a federal offense
to hack shielded lines.
I have 320 gigabytes of pharmakom data.
Don't bother. I'll be out
of here in 20 seconds.
So, what exactly is it that you want?
- Your data out of my head.
- — that can be arranged.
Let's meet. — where?
You're crazy, man!
They're gonna chop your fucking head off!
No. They'll negotiate,
they're corporate.
- So is the yakuza.
Listen, if you don't come, fine.
It's a business meeting,
it's not your kinda scene.
If it works out, I'll pay
you the money I owe you.
If it doesn't... — if it doesn't,
you're one dead Johnny is what!
I'm gonna be dead anyway
if I don't get this shit outta my head!
Listen.
I know this guy Spider,
used to be a doctor.
He could help you. He could fix your...
Hey, what's with you?
I'll be all right.
- Jesus, you're sick.
You strung out or what?
You got nas! — no!
You have the black shakes.
Whatever it is you have,
you're sidelined, right?
I've gotta make this meeting.
Hey! Hey, can you hear me?
Spider! He could help you.
He could help me.
I—  too was stricken by the sickness that
devours the silver pathways of the soul,
but the lord came to me and i was healed
and made post-human!
The darkness lays upon you now,
but I've come... to lead you
My children, I sense the need
for meditation,
I must leave you now, the sermon is over.
If you're not expected,
then you're not invited!
So fuck off, okay?
- It's Jane! She says you know her.
Get down here, man. She's sick.
Look, I gotta run. — shut up.
Give me that muscle relaxant
over there, the red one.
- It's NAS, right?
- — yeah, the black shakes,
like half the people on the planet.
Let me tell you something
so you get this straight.
It's not my work that got her
this way. My work is clean.
Besides, you don't get
this shit from amp jobs.
That's just a myth.
- So, what does cause it?
- What causes it?
The world causes it. This causes it!
This causes it! This causes it!
Information overload!
All the electronics around
you poisoning the airwaves!
Technological fucking civilization!
But we still have all this shit
'cause we can't live without it.
Let me do my work.
Whoa, street preacher's out.
J-Bone, you copying?
That son of a bitch doesn't have
one natural bone left in his body.
- He really a preacher, J-Bone?
Preacher?
That motherfucker's got god
and technology ass-backwards.
He'll kill for anybody money
just to keep his body full of implants.
- — Want me to follow him?
- No, stay away from him.
He's too crazy.
Anna Kalmann, founder, former CEO
of the multinational
Pharmakominat Industries, Zurich.
Born the 1st of August, 1965.
Died the 3rd of September, 2015.
Died?
Six years ago?
She was imprinted to Pharmakom's
neural-net installation
in Zurich prior to onset of morbidity.
Imprinted?
Her neural—net persona
has Swiss citizenship
under the Artificial
Intelligence Laws of 2006.
She advises the current board
from this state of being.
Pharmakom, Newark.
- Johnny. — what are you doing?
Just looking.
— don't touch anything!
Who the fuck are you anyway?
- Johnny. — Johnny who?
Just Johnny.
Ugh!
It looks like a full—service shop here.
How are you on brain implants?
Silicon implants, neural
overlays, memory augmentation?
- We don't get much of that out
here in Newark, just Johnny.
Kind of upscale for us, you know?
Got mine in Singapore.
- Oh, yeah? What's your deal, just Johnny?
I got this problem, up here.
"They err in vision.
They stumble in judgment."
"For all the tables are full
of vomit and filthiness,"
"so that there is no place clean."
- You should have seen it before.
- Isaiah.
- — Isaiah? Mine's Hooky.
Hey! Hey!
Aaargh!
The girl.
The girl that took Ralfi's
boy out of the backroom,
who is she?
- Do you expect me to
remember half the shit—...
Heal!
Aaah!
Oh, man, why'd you
have to do that?
Who's the girl? — a wannabe.
She's always hanging around
here looking for a job.
Name? — it's Jane.
More. — ooh.
One of Spider's jobs. — Spider?
- He's a flesh mechanic.
- Implants and shit, you know?
They said he used to be a
legit doctor once, but...
Where?
They did some serious
shoehorning to get that in there.
Skip the technical critique,
okay, I need some help here.
You don't know the half of it.
You must be hurting like hell.
Think I need
you to tell me that?
I got 320 gigs in here.
— oh, yeah?
What is it exactly? What kind of stuff?
I haven't got a clue.
And I don't have a download code either.
Hey.
You doing okay?
- Good girl, Janie.
You brought him to the right place.
- You can fix him?
- — I don't know.
With his seepage, if I
could work a download,
I don't know if the
product would be coherent.
Fuck the product! I just want it out.
I wish it was that simple.
Allcome. Dr. Allcome,
ever hear that name?
- Maybe. — where is he?
- I said maybe!
- Why do you wanna see him?
- Oh, come on, Spider!
I'll make sure just Johnny gets to see
who he needs to see.
But you, you need bed rest, downtime.
- He's my client.
I'm telling
you, you gotta sleep.
Just tell me where to go.
All right. I'll drive you.
— right.
Halt, sinners! — fuck!
Spider, look out!
- — Who the fuck was that?
- You don't wanna know.
Jesus.
Where are we? — you'll see.
He's been
this way for an hour now.
I don't know what to do with him.
If we still got any
paralon b, give him 20 mgs.
Fucking Pharmakom, man.
That shit costs 2 grand per clinical unit.
Keep him warm and bring me
his charts when you can.
- Here are the charts, doctor.
Where's Dr. Allcome?
Dr. Allcome is a name used in hospitals
when we got a major problem
and don't wanna spook the patients.
- — What?
- "Doctor all come to Ward 7,"
and we drop everything
and haul ass to wherever.
Usually means we got a
crazy, somebody violent.
But I saw it on the fax buffer.
That fax was meant for us.
Who's us?
Hey! Hey, wait a minute!
Who's us? — the NAS underground,
people who keep this place going,
people like me.
Get on the table.
- Why?
- — don't be a bigger asshole
than you have to.
Just get on the table.
All right.
Jack in.
Lie down.
Let's take a look at this shit.
No access code?
Except for one image, out of three.
It won't help.
What did they use? Random images?
Yeah, from the TV.
- I've got some decryption codes here.
I'll run them, see if we
come up with anything.
Janie, you should really try and lie down.
- Can you break the code, Spider?
If I get lucky, really lucky.
Fuck!
- No dice?
- — no. But I can get it out.
How?
— with a general anesthetic,
a cranial drill, and pair of forceps.
- And I could die too, right?
It's gonna kill you
anyway when it ruptures.
I take it out, you'll probably survive.
You'll probably lose
some fine motor skills,
you might not be able to remember anything
for more than three minutes at a time.
Fuck that!
Let me tell you something!
Let's just start with
what you got in there
and what it's worth,
what it's worth to the world.
You're carrying the cure for NAS.
You're telling me I got-—
— Pharmakom's complete R & D
on their cure for nerve
attenuation syndrome.
Plus the records of the field
trials to prove that it works.
And it really works.
You mean, like, a real cure?
They could have you straightened out
in three weeks, Janie,
you and everybody else.
- Everybody's trying to cut off my head.
- So they can take it back to Saigon
and run it through a quantum
interference detector.
But then, they would have
the cure and we wouldn't.
You keep that thing in your
head and nobody can save you.
Plus, the cure is gone forever.
I can save the cure.
Even if we had the code,
the seepage is so bad,
it would probably come out as garbage.
What's it supposed to
matter to me if I'm dead?
- Follow me?
- The cure can save millions.
You're gonna die anyway
if we don't get it out.
All I know is that
whatever's in my head is
worth a lot of money.
Why should I trust you?
You're supposed to be my
bodyguard here. Bodyguard!
You're not walking outta here,
not with that cure in your head!
The sinner's sinner's head
hold the Lord's cure!
That cure is mine!
Behold, your savior!
- Jane, get him to Jones!
Go! Get him to Jones!
- It's your only chance! Go!
Go!
Who's Jones?
He's that guy who fucks
your mother.
Where are they?
Aaah!
I couldn't make the meeting,
but I'm still up for it.
Are you?
- Certainly.
This time, on the bridge, landfill 5.
Bring the rest of the code. I'll find you.
I'll be there.
I want to negotiate.
- Yes, sir.
Great! Now if they don't
kill you, J-Bone will.
Listen to me, Takahashi,
before it's too late.
We're running out of time.
He's carrying the cure for—...
Hey!
I told her if she wanna get with me,
then I wanna get with her.
And screw the physical disability.
Hey! — you know what I'm saying?
Because it's about the feeling, right?
What's up?
Wind maybe.
Listen up!
Hey!
What do you think?
I mean, it's crazy,
but if it's really the
cure to NAS in my head,
it could save you.
I mean, it could save everybody.
Well, who is this Jones guy
spider said was our only chance?
He's...
He was in the Navy.
Yeah, in the war.
You know, they put a lot
of stuff in his head,
kinda like you.
Oh, yeah, like memory augments?
I don't know.
You'll see.
Hey!
- Man, somebody crazy down
there is getting on my nerves.
Rat lands are full of crazies,
stick. Ignore it, man.
Come on! Hey!
No, man.
Right down there! It's spider's Van!
Yep. Better tell J-Bone.
— I got an idea.
Hehehehe!
Let's drop a bug on Spider-man.
- — Forget it, Stick.
- Hey, check it out,
- I'm gonna do it.
- Hey, don't even say that.
J-Bone will shit if he hears you.
You know how jumpy he is lately.
No, I'm gonna do it.
— hey, wake up, damn it!
Hey, shit, man!
— "hey, shit" nothing.
That's what they're for.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! — hey! Hey!
Fuck! Shit!
Man, you are an idiot!
What the fuck is going on?
You know,
all my life, I've been careful
to stay in my own corner,
looking out for Number One
no complications.
Now, suddenly, I'm responsible
for the entire fucking world!
And everybody and his mother
is trying to kill me, if,
if, my head doesn't blow up first.
- Maybe it's not just about you anymore.
Listen. You listen to me.
You see that city over there?
That's where I'm supposed to be.
Not down here with the
dogs, and the garbage,
and the fucking last month's newspapers
blowing back and forth!
I've had it with them!
I've had it with you.
I've had it with all this!
I want room service!
I want the club sandwich!
I want the cold Mexican beer!
I want a $10,000—a—night hooker!
I want my shirts laundered,
like they do at the Imperial Hotel
in Tokyo.
We gotta see Jones.
Spider sent us.
Where's Spider?
- He's dead.
Not in there. Earlier, at the hospital.
If spider sent you, come on.
Whoa!
J-bone, help me.
Come on. Keep it together.
Come on.
Hoist it up!
— need help, right here.
You two.
I got him. I got him!
He'll be all right. Go on.
Tell Shinji,
meet me at the bridge.
He's on his way, sir.
My helicopter?
— It's waiting, sir.
- You okay?
- I'm alright.
- I saw...
I almost saw
as if it was
a memory.
Ehmm...
We have
a room especially for that.
Time to meet Jones.
We tapped into the main line,
get all the juice we need.
Stored up, battery.
We built heaven completely
out of straight—world junk,
all hauled up here piece by piece.
We work with Spider and his people
and anybody else who's
fighting the system.
We out shit for them.
- What do you mean, "out?"
Heaven, it's heart and soul.
This is where we fight back.
We strip the little, pretty pictures
from their 500—channel universe,
recontextualize it, then we
spit the shit back at them.
Special data, things that'll help people,
like stuff we get from Spider.
We wide—band it.
- Wide?
- Broadcast it. Go global.
Bounce it off the satellites
that Jones hacks for us.
The way the Navy got him hooked up,
he cuts through hard encryption
like a knife cuts through butter.
- Code breaker. Good.
I can't wait to meet him.
— right this way.
Jones.
It's a fish.
It's a mammal.
He's a friend! He's a friend, sailor!
Not only is he a mammal but he's a junkie.
Navy got him all addicted to this
to make him work,
I just give it to him so he thinks
he's still swimming... hehe.
This was Spider's best bet?
Hey, one thing spider wasn't was stupid.
Jones is set up to sample
software from enemy subs,
infrasound scan, right through the hull.
Jones will feed you can opener codes.
We'll try to get you out in time.
Wait a minute. Have
you done this before?
Has the fish?
- How dangerous is this?
- Look... just keep your head still.
Jones has to triangulate infrasound
into your implant
If you move around too much,
could microwave your frontal lobe.
Forget it.
Look, man, at least you got a chance.
It's up to you.
Do what you gotta do.
Give me what you got
of the download codes.
I will tell what sectors to hit.
Use the rocket launcher only if we
loose the element of surprise.
Fan out, prepare to go up!
Lynch and Maroni, remain here.
Set up the broadcast antennas.
Everybody... clear out of the
infrasound zone.
Now.
Waste extra hours of this horse shit
- Oh, you know, we were
just having a good time,
just fooling around.
Well, I don't wanna do nothing no more.
And I don't care what it takes.
Hear what I'm saying, buddy?
Hey, buddy?
Maroni!
Motherfuckers!
Stations! You all know the drill!
What did you get?
— we didn't get it.
We're not gonna get it right now.
The only way left is
to hack your own brain,
and then loop it through Jones.
- J-bone, the fuel tanks!
Shit, it's the Yakuza.
Give me that bow.
I was almost there.
I could feel it starting to...
Mr. Smith?
Pharmakom?
Not really.
- You can't shoot me.
Not in the head.
Takahashi!
Do you know what this man
is carrying in his head?
He's carrying the cure for NAS.
Your daughter died to protect
Pharmakom's profit margin.
Treating the disease is far
more profitable than curing it.
They had the cure eight
months ago, Takahashi.
Pharmakom, the company that I created,
let your daughter die.
- Shinji.
Hello, Johnny.
Raise your chin.
Let's make this clean.
If I fall, you don't get the head, right?
If you lose the head, you're fucked!
- Jesus time.
Jesus is waiting.
- Come to Jesus.
The cure...
The holiest of communions ...
and when i hold God's cure,
- Jones!
- I  will be God!
Please help me.
He's made you
the vessel of his mercy
as I am the vessel of his wrath.
- Jones...
What spawn of Satan?
Now!
-Jane?
I'm all right.
- Piece of shit.
- Hook me up.
The second image.
Sit down.
- Get the power up.
Johnny...
I knew their secrets.
The image...
The company has forgotten for me.
Now they erase me,
burn me out of the mainframes,
one memory after another.
How very kind of them.
Johnny...
The dolphin can take you into the data,
find the third image.
Johnny...
Look, if we gonna do this
download, we gotta do it now.
We're out of power.
Remember, we gotta loop
it through Jones. Johnny?
Alright, let's get ready.
Okay, let's do this.
One problem, we do it the easy way--
we get garbage because of the seige.
Now if I loop it through Jones,
save the cure
It will probably kill you.
- Loop it.
Listen up, world.
This is the last blast from
Lotek world headquarters.
And believe this, we're
going out with a bang, baby.
So get your VCRs ready
because we got what you need.
We got the cure to NAS.
That's right, the cure
to the black shakes.
And it's coming to you live
from the labs up at Pharmakom.
And believe this,
they did not want you
to get this information.
So here it is, coming at you, Lotek style.
Watch you ass in there.
No telling what Pharmakom stuck in there.
Might be Ice on it, virus programs.
Hit me.
Intruder alert! Intruder alert!
Unauthorized interface attempt.
Lethal neural feedback now in effect.
Final warning: Do NOT attempt interface.
He's doubling himself.
You...
That's the double, don't worry.
The only way is to hack your own brain.
Loop it.
Entrance code accepted.
Code accepted.
Send it out!
Happy Birthday, Johnny!
- Happy Birthday, Johnny.
- — thank you, mommy.
- It's payback time.
Just garbage. Get that outta here!
j' I can see j'
j' see the signs j'
j' I've been waiting here for you j'
j' I but nothing's getting through I j'
j' I am gone j'
j' up in the clouds j'
j' praying I can turn I
j' I turn myself around j'
j' a year ago j'
j' I gave it a year j'
j' I hoped it wouldn't happen j'
j' I now it's here j'
j' I it took so long j'
j' I can't carry on j'
j' I know the reason that you left me I j'
j' I you had nothing more to give me I j'
j' no more love j'
j' some nights I feel I j'
j' I like I have died j'
j' or something deep inside is dying j'
j' I try to understand my crimes j'
j' I but there's nothing
here that really matters I j'
j' I don't want to believe in you j'
j' I can't believe in you j'
j' I don't want it, I don't need it I
j' I don't want it I
j' I but I can't stop myself j'
j' mouth curling to a question Mark I j'
j' head back describes an arc j'
j' jaw's really slung, imprisoned words j'
j' breath escaping, lips
long tightly sealed j'
j' sentence is repealed j'
j' I left without obeying j'
j' internal is revealed j'
j' can't hear a word you're saying j'
j' this cell is so cold cold,
this cell is so cold cold j'
j' mouth curling to a question Mark I j'