For those regarded as warriors...
when engaged in combat...
the vanquishing of thine enemy can be the warriors only concern.
Suppress every human emotions and compassion...
kill whoever stands in thy way,
even if that be the Lord God, or the Buddha himself.
This truth lies at the heart of combat.
Look at me, Matsumoto...
take a good look at my face.
Look at my eyes.
Look at my nose.
Look at my chin.
Look at my mouth.
Do I look familiar?
Do I look like someone you murdered?
Welcome...
We have a customer.
Bring out some tea, quickly.
I'm just watching my soap operas.
Lazy bastard.
Screw your soap opera...
The tea is hot. Why do don't you serve it yourself for once?
Hey, what the hell happened to the tea?
Hurry up... goddammit!
Lazy oaf.
What'd ya want?
One warm sake!
Sake? In the middle of the day?
- Day, night, afternoon, Who gives a damn? Get the sake!
How come I always have to get the sake?
Listen carefully...
For 30 years you make the
fish, and I get the sake.
If this were the military,
I'd be a General by now.
Oh, so you'd be general, huh?
If you were General, I'd be Emperor,
and you would still get the sake.
So shut up and get the sake!
I'm not bald, okay?
I shave my head.
What do you want with Hattori Hanzo?
I need Japanese steel.
Why do you need Japanese steel?
I have vermin to kill.
I wanted to show you these.
However...
Someone as you, who knows so much, must surely know...
I no longer make instruments of death.
What I have here...
I keep for their aesthetic and sentimental value.
Yet proud as I am of my life's work...
I have retired.
You can sleep here.
It will take me a month
to make a sword.
I suggest you spend it practising.
I complete doing...
what I swore an oath to God, 28 years ago,
To never do again.
I created something that kills people.
And in that respect, it is a success.
I've done this because I am sympathetic to your aim.
I can tell you with no ego, this is my finest sword.
If on your journey, you should encounter God...
God will be slashed
Yellow-haired warrior. Go.
Do you like Ferraris?
Ferrari... Italian trash.
Do you want to fuck me?
Don't laugh! Do you want
to fuck me. yes or no?
Yes.
Haw about now. Big boy?
Do you still wish to penetrate me?
or is it I...
who as penetrated you?
Boss Tanaka. What's the meaning of this outburst?
This is a time for celebration.
And what exactly are we celebrating?
The perversion of our illustrious council?
Tanaka, have you gone mad?!
I will not tolerate it!
You're disrespecting our sister!
Apologize!
Tanaka—San, of what perversion do you speak?
My father along with your, and along
with yours, started this council.
And while...
you laugh like stupid donkeys...
they weep in the afterlife...
Shut up!
Over the perversion committed today.
Outrageous! Tanaka, it is you
who insults this council!
- Bastard!
- Fuck face!
Gentlemen.
Tanaka obviously has something on his mind.
By all means allow him to express it.
I speak of the perversion done to this council,
which I love...
more than my own children.
by making a Chinese Jap-American half breed bitch its leader.
So you understand how serious I am...
I am going to say this in English.
Gentlemen, this meeting is over.
You have to say, "Yes, yes, yes" to any selfish demands they make.
They demand ridiculous things.
Shut up... do you know what would
happen if they hear you?
What's gonna happen?
Ever heard of the Tanaka clan?
You're gonna get your head chopped off.
No I do not want this.
Yes speaking.
If you give us a contact
number, we will get back to you.
Who do you remind me of? Charlie Brown.
You're right, he does look like Charlie Brown.
Charlie Brown, four pepperoni pizzas.
That's not on our menu...
I do not care. bring them, goddammit.
Hey... hey... Charlie, give me a kiss.
You and I have unfinished business.
Charlie Brown, beat it.
Tear the bitch apart!
Gogo, right?
And you are Black Mamba.
Our reputations precedes us.
Don't they.
You call that begging?
You can beg better than that.
Those of you lucky enough to still have your lives,
take them with you.
However...
leave the limbs you've lost.
They belong to me now.
Where was it made?
Whom in Okinawa, made you this steel?
You lie!
Swords, however, never get tired.
I hope you have saved your energy.
If you haven't...
you might not last five minutes.
But as last looks go,
you could do worse.
Attack me...
with everything you have.
For ridiculing you earlier...
I apologise.
Accepted.
Ready?
Come on.
That really was a Hattori-Hanzo sword.
Burn in Hell you stupid, stupid blonde!
I'll tell you nothing.
Master.
Your Mandarin is lousy.
It causes my ears discomfort.
You bray like a donkey.
You are  not to speak unless spoken to.
Is it too much to hope you
understand Cantonese?
I speak Japanese very well.
I did not ask you if
you speak Japanese.
I asked if you understood Cantonese?
You are here to learn
Kung-Fu, not linguistics.
If you can't understand me, I will communicate with you like I would a dog.
When I yell, when I point,
when I beat you with my stick.
Bill is your master, is he not?
He tells me you're not entirely unschooled.
What is your training?
"The exquisite are of the samurai sword." Don't make me laugh.
Your so-called exquisite art, is only fit for...
Japanese fatheads!
Your anger amuses me.
Do you believe you are my match?
No.
Are you aware I kill at will?
Yes.
- Is it your wish to die?
- No.
Then you must be stupid... so stupid.
Rise, and let me look at your ridiculous face.
Rise.
So, my pathetic friend, is there anything that you can do well?
What's the matter?
Cat got your tongue?
Oh yes, you speak Japanese.
I despise the goddamn Japs!
Go to the rack.
Remove the sword.
Let's see how good you really are.
If...
you land a single blow,
I'll bow down and call you "Master"
From here you can get an excellent view of my foot.
Your swordsmanship is amateur at best.
Your so-called kung-fu
is really quite pathetic.
I asked you to demonstrate what you know and you did...
Not a goddamn thing.
Let's see your Tiger-Crane style
match my Eagle's Claw?
Like all Yankee women
all you can do is order in
restaurants and spend a man's money.
Excruciating, isn't it?
Yes!
If it was my wish, I could chop your arm off.
It's my arm now. I can do what I please.
If you can stop me I suggest you try.
I can't!
Because you're helpless?
Yes!
Have you ever felt this before?
No!
Compared to me, you're as helpless as a
worm fighting an eagle?
- Yes!
- That's the beginning!
Is it your wish to possess this kind of power?
Your training will begin tomorrow.
Since your arm now belongs to me, I want it strong.
Can you do that?
I can, but not that close.
Then you can't do it.
What if your enemy is three inches in front of you?
What do you do then?
Curl up into a ball,
or do you put your fist through him?
Now begin.
It's the wood that should fear your hand, not the other way around.
No wonder you can do it, you acquiesce to defeat before you even begin.
If you want to eat like a dog,
you can live and sleep outside like a dog.
If you want to live and sleep like a human,
pick up those chopsticks.
Elle, you treacherous bitch...
I give you my word...