London in the 1960s.
Everyone had a story about the Krays.
You could walk into any pub
to hear a lie or two about them.
But I was there
and I'm not careless with the truth.
They were brothers,
but bound by more than blood.
They were twins as well,
counterparts.
Gangster princes
of the city they meant to conquer.
Ron Kray was a one-man London mob.
Bloodthirsty, illogical
and funny as well.
My Reggie was different.
Once in a lifetime do you find
a street-fighting man like Reg.
Believe me when I say
it took a lot of love
for me to hate him the way I do.
- Morning, Albie.
- Morning, son.
- Is that tea for two?
- All right, Albie?
Hello, boys.
How you doing? You all right?
Got you a cup of tea here. You fancy it?
Yeah? No?
What's this?
The old Dagenham Anglia?
Naught to 60 in, what, 40 minutes,
something like that?
Phwoar! It's a bit of you, that, innit,
all black and cramped and very sharp.
This one's really milky, for you.
Why don't you fuck off, Kray?
All right, I will. You know,
I wouldn't want to keep you,
what with all them rapists and murderers
you gotta lock away, Nipper?
Where do you take a turd in there?
I suppose you just hold it in,
don't you?
All right, then, have a lovely day.
Cheer up. It's nearly Christmas.
Sorry about that.
Where's me driver?
Where's Frank?
- Can't get out of bed in the morning, Reg.
- You what?
He ain't here. He ain't showed up.
His heart ain't in it.
All right, OK.
Well, let's go get him, then, shall we?
- Where is he? On Ormsby Street, yeah?
- Yeah. Jump in, I'll give you a lift.
Nah, you're all right. I'm gonna walk.
It's a lovely day for it.
Don't forget this lot.
They're very important.
I won't.
Come on.
I shall walk incredibly slowly.
- All right, Vera?
- All right, Reg?
- How you doing? You good?
- Yeah.
Lovely.
Rita.
I was going to knock on your door.
Me mum said you left that in the kitchen.
- Oh, I did.
- That yours?
- It is. Oh, thanks ever so much.
- Not a problem. You're welcome.
Isn't he sweet?
East Enders.
They won't talk to a policeman,
but they'll kiss a gangster?
The filthy cockney bastards.
How about we clean your car for you?
You get the bumper
and I'll get the lights.
Frank about?
Frank!
Who are you?
Frances. Frank's sister.
Hang about, I recognize you.
See, I recognize you.
You was a little bit younger then.
You got all grown up, didn't you?
It happens.
What have you got there?
A sweet.
That's not any sweet, is it?
That's a lemon sherbet, that is.
Mind if I have a crack?
All right.
Thank you.
Oh, that's nice, innit?
- You're not supposed to chew it.
- No?
How else am I supposed to get
to the sherbetty bit?
- By being patient.
- Nah!
Being patient doesn't get you
what you want, does it?
Half a minute, Reg. Right down.
- Is he in trouble?
- Yeah, he is.
Will you go out with me?
I'll go easy on him if you do.
All right.
But not for that reason.
Saturday night.
Who are you talking to?
You're half-dressed,
talking to a man in the door.
What's wrong with you, Frances?
Get back in the kitchen,
finish them dishes.
Hey, this is yours.
Thank you.
Oversleep again, Frank, all right,
and it's back to the cheese shop
or the fish shop
or whatever shop it was
you come from.
Print.
Print shop.
Oh, yeah?
You'll be back to the fucking shit shop,
you understand?
- Yeah.
- What does your sister do?
She goes to one of those,
Pitman Colleges.
You know, typing, shorthand.
- Yeah?
- Yep.
She's got a bit of class, mate.
She's very elegant.
Where you been hiding her?
She been away.
She's a bit, fragile, Reg.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Stop here, Frank.
Five minutes. Won't be long.
How long you reckon it'll take
for him to twig, Albie?
Little bit of cat and mouse.
Nipper Read was the copper
on the Krays' case.
And he made his presence known.
He was heavy-footed, as they say. '
And I'm staring
at the back of this geezer's head.
The whole time I'm thinking, you know,
"Give Ron Kray your sausage.
"Give Ron
"your fucking sausage. "
You know?
I was drilling my eyes
into the back of his head.
Till I'm not even thinking it anymore.
I'm not... I'm not even thinking.
I'm broadcasting it.
Until he turns around
and you know what he says? He says...
"Hey, Ron, do you fancy my sausage?
I've got... I've got no appetite for it. "
Interesting.
When my future brother-in-law
said "interesting"... '
Ain't it?
... it meant he had no fucking idea what he
or you or anyone else was talking about. '
Fascinating, Ron.
Fascinating.
Ron had been sentenced
to three years in prison
for grievous bodily harm.
Near the end of his sentence,
he was certified insane
and remanded to a mental hospital.
What was wanting
was a friendly psychiatrist.
What's that?
When you say
you want to "raspberry' this man,
I'm not sure of your vernacular.
What do you mean?
Raspberry ripple, cripple.
You want to cripple someone?
- Yep, that's right.
- And why is that?
Because, Doctor,
I'm afraid he may not be inclined
to provide a favorable evaluation
of my employer.
And who's your employer?
Ronnie Kray.
Is there hope, Doctor?
Excuse me a moment.
Take your time.
Ronald Kray possesses
possibly the soundest mind I've seen
in 26 years of psychiatric practice.
In my view, to keep him here
would be a waste of public resources.
A lifetime's integrity down the toilet.
The Queen would survive,
but God save the rest of us.
Mr Kray.
I hope you know what you're doing.
Yeah, I know what I'm doing.
I'm going back to London, gonna take the...
Your brother has no real idea
who or what he is.
Nor does he trust his own senses.
I've never seen a man
so desperately in need of reassurance.
We all like a nice little compliment
now and again, don't we?
Your brother is arbitrary,
violent and psychopathic,
probably paranoid schizophrenic.
What I'm trying to tell you
is that he's off his fucking rocker.
It's called Stemetil.
You need to give it to your brother
twice a day
or there's going to be serious trouble.
Oi, Frances, the car's outside.
Oh!
You've got glamour, Frances.
You're like an East End starlet.
East End harlot's more like it.
They're trousers, Mum.
She doesn't look like a harlot.
What she's wearing
doesn't matter.
When people see her with Reggie Kray,
they'll think she's a tart.
Why would you say that?
He's a gangster, Frances.
The Krays are gangsters.
- Well, I think he's sweet.
- Oh, God!
And I'm going to kiss him.
Do you hear me?
- Hello.
You look lovely.
So do you.
Hello. This is Big Pat.
- Hello, Big Pat.
- Reggie.
- How you doing? You all right, mate?
- Miss. Nice to see you.
Big Pat's here to keep riff-raff out.
Always.
So how come you're
letting us in, then, mate?
Have a good night.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, mate. Cheers.
Oh, hello, here's trouble.
Hold the phone.
- Oi, you. How you doing, big man?
- You all right, boss?
- Are you well?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- You behaving yourself?
- Always. I'm a teddy bear, me.
Go easy. If he gives you any trouble,
come and speak to me. Come on.
- You all right, ma'am?
- Yeah, I'm good. She's good.
- Hello, Reg.
- Hello.
Reg, you all right?
Mr Kray.
- Everyone here knows you.
- Yeah, well, I own it, it's my club.
- You mean it's your local?
- No, I own the place. It's mine.
I've been by here 10 times,
I never knew it was yours.
Well, you can get away with a lot in life
if you keep your mouth shut.
That's Teddy.
Hang on a second.
How you doing? You all right?
Good to see you. You good?
How's the family? Excellent.
- What?
- Those men look frightening.
No, no, they're just East End boxers.
They're lovely.
I let'em drink in here for free,
you know.
Reggie, that's Joan Collins.
Yeah, might be, yeah.
We had that Barbara Windsor in here
the other night.
- Really?
- She comes in quite a bit, actually.
She loves it.
And, that's my formula.
What I like to do is I like to mix celebrities
with a few, just a few, East End villains.
The punters, they love it.
It's really good for business.
Would you like a seat?
Excuse me, Reg.
Have you, got a moment?
No, I don't, actually.
I'm busy. All right?
- Nah, it's important, Reg.
- This is important as well, so...
- Reg.
- All right.
Frances, would you mind if I...
if I take care of some business
just for a moment?
- No, of course not.
- Excuse me. Be back in a minute.
You sit with her. What is it?
- It's back here.
- What?
- Hello, Reg.
- All right, mate?
In fact, if you don't know,
you don't fucking know.
- You know what I mean?
- Reggie.
How are you, Reg?
I'm all right. I can't complain.
Who'd fucking listen?
- What's the palaver? Go on.
- Sit down, Reg. Sit down, please.
All right.
You had a question about our take
in the purple heart business. Pill game.
- Go on.
- Jack here would like to explain himself.
Go on.
Go on, Jack.
Tell Reggie what you told me.
Well, Reg...
- Yeah?
- I...
The thing is, under normal
circumstances, my accounts...
Are you going to take all fucking night,
mate? Cause I've got things to do.
Tell him, Jack. Go on, spit it out.
- I borrowed a few quid off the top.
- Right. All right.
- I sold a few pills on the side.
- Yeah, there's a surprise.
Things have been a bit tight at home
and I was just trying
to keep the wife happy.
Trying to keep the wife happy.
Is this why you brought me in here,
for this? This nonsense?
- It's important business, Reg.
- It's important, is it? Yeah?
- You should know about this.
- All right, let's deal with this business.
Tomorrow, you come back to work,
and you pay back every fucking penny.
- I was going to suggest that.
- Good. Right. Are we done?
Everybody happy?
All right, then, can I get back
to my fucking evening?
Thank you.
Thank you very much, Albie. Cheers.
- Sorry for wasting your time, Jack.
- Thanks.
Thanks for coming in.
Here you go, mate.
Good?
You fucking little thieving cunt.
You understand?
I heard me. Yeah?
Next time I'll finish you off,
you little slag.
- Get him out of here. Fuck him off.
- Fuck!
You fucking what?
What did you say?
Don't you swear in my club.
Get him out of here right now.
Don't swear in my club. Wanker.
- Listen, there's something else.
- No, there isn't something else,
'cause I've got a young lady in here
and I'm entertaining.
- Have a look at that. See that there?
- I see it.
I'm entertaining, all right?
So I'm gonna have an evening to myself.
- This is important business.
- Can't be. My business, innit?
It's my business. I would know.
Night, Albie.
Hello.
Did I miss anything important?
- No, just me.
- Now, that is important.
- Is it?
- Very important.
Thank you.
So, your brother, he was telling me
that you, you're going to college
to... to study to be a secretary.
Is that right?
Yeah, anything
to get out of the East End.
What's so bad about the East End?
I've just got bigger dreams than pushing
a pram or haggling with the butcher.
I just don't quite know
what they are yet.
Well, the East End's not that bad.
The center of the earth
can be anywhere you like.
- Even here?
- Yeah, even here.
- In Bethnal Green?
- Yeah, Bethnal Green.
Do you like being a gangster?
I'm not a gangster.
I'm a club owner.
I like the money and I like the respect
of being a club owner.
But I'm not a gangster.
I could have been a boxer,
but then, you know... hello, mate...
I'd end up looking like
some sort of potato.
And I wouldn't even know
what day of the week it was.
This way, at least I know
who I am, you know?
More so, I like the fact that
I've made a little something of myself.
I don't owe the world anything.
So long as the world agrees with you.
I think the world will be all right.
We shall fight on the beaches.
We shall fight on the landing grounds.
We shall fight in the fields...
... and in the streets.
We shall fight in the hills.
We shall never surrender, and if...
Hey, Ronnie!
Ronnie, come on out.
You've got visitors, mate.
Watch your step. It's a bit wet.
- You all right?
- You must be Frances.
- Hello.
Hello, Frances. Hello.
Welcome to the family.
Well, it's a bit premature,
that, is it?
- You don't have a beer that I could have?
- Yeah, of course I do. Help yourself.
Don't mind if I have a beer, do you?
I'll let you get to know each other.
Want a cup of tea?
I just put the kettle on.
Take a seat. Go on.
Sit down anywhere you like.
Needs a bit of warming up. So...
What do you think?
Do you think that we look alike,
me and Reggie?
Oh, yes, certainly.
No, you don't.
You think that he's beautiful
and I've got a face
like a gorilla's arse.
It's all right, don't worry about it.
- No. I wouldn't say that.
- I'm used to it.
Stop doing your hair, right?
Get me stuff out of the car.
Do something fucking useful.
Yeah, go on, then.
I'm homosexual, Frances.
Well, I am a, I'm a giver, right?
I'm not a receiver.
There is a difference. I'm not a faggot.
But I do believe that, you know,
you should not hide what you are.
You shouldn't hide what you are
'cause it'll make you very sad, you know?
It'll make you very sad.
It'll make you very unwell.
- I agree completely.
You know, me and my brother,
we're going to rule London.
The Krays' main rivals
were the Richardsons of South London.
They were called the Torture Gang.
For the benefit of the jury,
on whose behalf were you operating
on this side of the river?
Come on, Charlie, please.
I'm begging you.
No, no, no. You do business
with the court as an entity,
- therefore, address the court.
- What?
- What? "Your Honor"!
- Fuck!
You say "Your Honor".
By saying "Your Honor",
you gain the court's attention
and open up a channel
of communication, a conduit.
So, we'll try again.
For the benefit of the jury,
on whose behalf were you working
on this side of the river?
- Please, Charlie! I fucking beg of you!
- Order!
Order in this, my court!
Fuck!
You're in Indian country, old son.
That's what them cockneys
call south of the river, innit?
Indian country.
Well, what are you doing
on my reservation without my say-so,
filling up your canteen
from my fucking watering hole?
You ain't got the bottle to do that
on your own, son. Who do you work for?
I don't know what you're on about, Charlie.
I don't know what you're on about.
- Say their names. Say it!
- Fuck.
- Buzz him.
- Objection, Your Honor.
My client is an upstanding citizen.
Objection overruled
on the grounds it's boring.
Oh, well, fuck him.
- Say it. Say "the Krays", you daft cunt.
- Fuck it!
No, no.
No leading the witness, Eddie.
Fuck off!
Alexander might have been great,
but he wasn't a Greek.
- No?
- No. He was a Macedonian.
But he loved them, though,
Aristotle and that lot.
He was deeply impressed
by them flash Hellenistic cunts.
Christos, get us some more
of that awful retsina.
Charlie, we've got to fucking sort this.
You're absolutely right.
Christos, where's my retsina?
The Richardsons
sent George Cornell to call for a truce.
All they were saying
was give peace a chance.
- Fucking Frank'll win.
- What the fuck!
- Are you wearing your bravery jacket?
- We're here to parley.
I will fucking map you up, Southie.
No, no, no. Go on, let him in.
He's only little.
Things have got out of hand.
Charlie wants to meet.
Pig and Whistle. Neutral ground.
Just him, you two and Eddie.
Yep. And how do we know
that we're going to be safe?
Well, that's a little thing
called trust, ain't it?
Trust? You always got one bloke
harping on about trust, don't you?
But then you look
over your shoulder, right,
and you see there's another bloke there,
right, with his Hampton in his hand
and he's preparing to shove his cock
right up your arse.
Well, you wouldn't mind that.
You fat poof.
No. No, no, no...
Right, you, get him out of here.
Go on, fuck off.
- One hour. We'll be with you.
- That's it, bye-bye.
Fuck off, George.
There's the door, go on.
- Bye-bye.
- Take that dead fox with you. Go on.
Get out, you prick.
What a fucking liberty.
Big Charlie, please could I have
another egg?
I've eaten this one.
I don't like it, Reggie.
Nah, it's all right.
I know them. I know the pub.
We'll be all right.
You got to clean that fucking toilet, mate.
It stinks.
Mate, I paid a girl to do it.
It's not my fault if she don't.
- What are you having to drink?
Forget it. They just walked in.
- Mate, can I get two Guinnesses, please?
- Hang on a second.
I just gotta go down
to change the barrel.
Reg. Ron.
The Richardsons were
unexpectedly engaged,
so we're going to look after you.
Oh, it's all right. The landlord's gone
to change the barrel for me. Thanks.
You don't mind
if I pull myself a pint, do you?
- What is that?
- What do you think, poof?
It's a fucking tool.
No, it's not. It's a fucking rolling pin.
Who are you, Fanny Cradock?
What are you gonna do with that?
You gonna bake me a cake?
You gonna sing me a song,
watch me blow out me fucking candles?
I come here
for a fucking shootout, right?
A proper shootout
with some proper men,
like Colonel Custer and Geronimo.
Have you ever heard of 'em? No.
Cause you were too busy in your pinny
baking fucking fairy cakes, weren't you?
Reg, this lot are fucking nonces, to a man.
They're fucking nonces.
Get out of me fucking way.
Go on, get out. Go on, fuck off.
Call yourself a fucking gangster?
A shootout, right,
is a fucking shootout!
Like a Western.
Wankers! Fucking embarrassing.
Waste of my time.
Fucking waste of my time.
Well, your brother's done a runner.
He's just genuinely disappointed
with you. That's all.
Look at that. Full of iron, that is.
See, it takes a while, that does,
you know, to settle.
Charlie Richardson said we're to knock
the granny out of you, Reg.
Oh, yeah? He did, did he?
That's good of him. All right, listen.
When you see him next,
you tell him from me, yeah,
that I say... fuck Charlie, right?
And fuck his brother, yeah?
And fuck that fat Georgie Cornell
that hangs out with him.
Fuck your face. Yeah, yeah?
And fuck the fucking lot of you as well.
What do you think of that?
- You like that?
- You won't mind if I fight back, will you?
- You think you can manage it?
It's more for me pride, really,
to be honest.
I warn you,
I'm not gonna fight fair, though.
So I brought these.
All right?
Now, before we start,
I got a little joke for you.
You'll love this one.
Paranoid schizophrenic,
he walks into a bar...
Yeah.
You fucking...
Fuck off!
They never stood a chance
against my beautiful Reggie.
Gang war seemed certain. '
Fucking hell!
But on the day of the World Cup final,
Scotland Yard had its say as well.
There's Ball, running himself daft...
Goal! Get in there, you cunts.
Police!
- Stay where you are!
- Oh, come on, boys. Not tonight.
What do you mean, no goal?
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
- 'It's a goal!'
- It's a goal! It's a fucking goal! It's a goal!
Charlie Richardson
was sentenced to 25 years
for fraud, extortion and assault.
London was an open city
and the Krays moved in.
Glad you could come, Mr De Faye.
Mr Payne.
I'm not often intrigued,
but your message...
- It intrigued.
Sit down.
These are the Kray twins.
Ronald and Reginald.
Yes, I've, heard of them.
You'll find them useful friends.
What's this about, Mr Payne?
This is about a gambling casino in
Knightsbridge called Esmeralda's Barn.
- I'm not familiar with it.
- Really?
Well, you'll be shocked to learn
that you earned Ł24,000 from it
in the last three months.
My friends and I would like
to purchase it from you.
We have the contracts ready
for your signature.
Ruling London involved
intelligence and intimidation.
It's not for sale.
You might find that in the future,
there is a less polite approach.
The trick was to cultivate
a quiet certainty
that should it be needed,
violence was on offer...
Yeah.
... and would be happily applied.
Leslie Payne was a fronter and a fixer.
Reggie found Payne useful,
but Ron was suspicious of him,
afraid his scams were the opposite
of what a gangster should be.
- Consider Las Vegas.
- All right.
It's all legal, all run by the Mafia.
Soon, London will be the same.
What with Havana gone,
the Mafia is moving in.
Meyer Lansky
has already made inquiries.
- Meyer Lansky?
- Yeah.
What, as in the Meyer Lansky?
Meyer Lansky.
Are the Americans gonna try
and muscle in on us?
No. They don't work that way.
They don't want a war, Ron.
- They're businessmen.
- Well, maybe I want a war with them.
Now, look.
What they do want is to know
who is the up-and-coming local firm,
because they will colonize London
by financing that firm,
then franchising the city.
So you have to prove to the Americans
that the Krays are the only game in town.
Yeah, very fucking interesting.
The world could be our oyster.
- Payne.
- What?
You say "our" a lot, right?
You say "our"
and you also say "we" a lot.
Do I?
My question is,
is your last name Kray?
Listen, Ron, you keep the pearls.
I'm perfectly happy with the soft bits.
Yeah, I bet you are.
I bet you are.
Reggie, I say it's a very bad idea.
It's just a bad idea.
I say, right, that we meet these
Mafioso scum at London Airport, right?
We pick them up, we chop them up,
put them in their fucking luggage
and send them straight home, mate.
That's the plan.
Well, I'm glad
we could have this meeting.
Mr Lansky has taken an interest
in the Colony Sporting Club.
He has his casino people there
right now.
Well, Mr Lansky might want to know
that we happen to have
a casino of our own.
Really? Your own casino?
Well, you see, we own Las Vegas.
But here,
the Atlantic Ocean is in our way.
So Mr Lansky lacks the ability
to, ensure the physical security
of his property,
from both outside muscle and the cops.
He thinks the Kray family could help.
London is going to be
the Las Vegas of Europe.
We need someone to front
and someone to muscle for us.
I mean, look,
we can do your security, right,
that's not a problem, you know,
but we don't want to work for you.
I mean, we'd much rather
that we work with you.
What Reggie is trying to say...
I think he knows what he's trying to say.
He just said it.
- We're in your backyard.
- Yeah.
And Mr Lansky is open
to discussions of this nature.
He sends this as a goodwill gesture.
Just a taste. For expenses.
Open it, please.
Now, the second briefcase contains
business of my own I need to take care of.
Please.
Bearer bonds. Free money.
A hundred grand
in negotiable bearer bonds.
Jacked from a bank in Montreal.
Too hot to move in North America.
That's a hundred grand.
Could you guys handle that?
Yeah, we can handle it.
Really? Good.
Boys who jacked it get 20%.
We split the rest 60-40.
If this works out, Reggie,
I got a $2 million backlog
of those scharoles.
Does that sound
like you're staying out of our way?
50-50, mate.
I like you, Reggie.
50-50 it is. Done.
I'm glad we could make a deal.
- Yeah.
- Now, this feels right.
Listen, you come to Philadelphia
any time,
you see what you want, any size,
any shape, right? We'll get it for you.
A nice Italian girl.
Little spaghetti and meatballs.
I prefer boys.
Excuse me? I didn't catch that.
I said I prefer boys.
Italians, actually.
Sometimes Greek,
but I am not prejudiced.
No. Because I happen
to have had a Negro once
and a Tahitian,
who I bent up like a pretzel.
I really fucking hurt him.
You got a lot of fucking balls
to admit that, kid.
You know what? You got
some fucking set of castagnas on you.
You know what I say to that? Bravo!
Salute! Come on. Salute!
- Salute.
- Am I right, fellas?
- Cheers, mate.
- What fucking balls! Salute!
- Cheers.
- Salute.
Marrone.
Cheers, mate.
You don't understand!
He's not what you think he is! All right?
He's really sweet.
And it's exciting being with him!
Just because you have a boring life
doesn't mean I have to as well!
The reason I have a boring life
is because I gave up my life for you!
Oh, Frankie, you take my breath away.
Well, you can have mine.
You're a joker.
Go on, get in the car.
'Esmeralda's Barn
made money like a dream,
'Ł2,000 a week pure profit.
'There was nothing to do but enjoy it.
'Owning that casino
meant everything to Reggie.
'He'd finally crossed the line
between the old East End
'and the green pastures
of the Golden West.
'He was becoming a celebrity himself.
'As long as their health didn't suffer,
'the high rollers loved rubbing elbows
with gangsters. '
Come and dance. Come on, darling.
'Aristocrats and criminals
have a lot in common.
'They're both selfish, get bored easily
'and have access to wads of cash
they didn't have to work honestly to get.
'The topper, neither have any interest
in bourgeois rules or morality.
'Put it all together
with roulette wheels?
'A stunning recipe for success.
'Ron was the odd man out.
'His pills stabilized him,
but they'd never cure him.
'Clubland held little charm
'and he yearned for Reggie
and the darker side of gangland. '
As soon as you turn your fucking back,
life, it just plays dirty tricks on you,
you know?
'We wouldn't spend
Christmas together that year.
'There was an old warrant on Reggie.
'The last six months of the sentence
was on appeal, but it was denied.
'He was to surrender in the morning.
'My real life was about to begin.
All right.
- All right?
See you in a bit.
- See you later, Reg.
- Ta, Reg.
Oh!
Frankie.
You look after your sister
while I'm away.
- All right, Reg.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
Good lad.
Move it, Kray.
Stop on the line.
You're nothing in here.
Nothing!
Fuck him up.
Fuck him up!
Leave him alone!
Bury 'em, Reggie!
Shut up, all of you!
Fucking let 'em have it!
Go on, Reg!
Ain't so tough now,
are you, hey?
Easy.
Get him in.
You're nothing in here.
- Nothing.
- Please, no more, guvnor! Please.
"Please, please, please. "
That's more like it, Reggie.
- "Please."
- Please!
A bit of respect.
Doesn't hurt, does it?
No more.
I have shit bigger turds.
Please, water.
Oh, you want some water?
Look at that, gents.
He's only begging for water.
What do you make of it now,
your famous Reggie fucking Kray?
- Fuck you!
- Begging for fucking water.
What has he come to?
Here you are, Reg.
Now, don't spill it.
'Cause you've had a little tumble,
haven't you?
Here it is.
Good boy.
- Can I have water?
- Here he is, look.
Look at this. Reggie Kray.
Begging fucking water...
Reggie! Reggie! Reggie...
Hello, Frances.
- Hello, Ron.
- I saw Reg today.
He sends his best. He says it's probably
best that you don't go and visit him yet.
Did he say why?
Nah, didn't mention it.
Do you know it is possible, right,
for a person to become a ghost
while they're still alive.
You think so?
Well, it's happened to you, ain't it?
No, no, no. No, look.
- Listen.
- "No" what?
No, no, no. Please, please.
Just for a moment, just listen.
Gambling clubs are legally obliged
to pay winnings on the spot.
And that is why we insist our gamblers
pay their debts on the spot as well.
Yes, I know. I've heard you.
But that's your problem. Right?
That's your problem, not mine.
Mine is that I want Ł50,000.
Here you go again
with your Ł50,000 to go to Nigeria.
No, it's not just
to go to Nigeria, is it?
I want to set up a company.
All right?
I want to build a city in Nigeria,
for the children.
- Near Enugu.
- Enugu.
- Yes, Enugu.
I told you, Enugu! Right?
You don't know everything,
do you, Payne?
Did you know that "Enugu"
is the African word for "utopia"?
- No.
- No, you did not.
Did you know that "utopia"
is the Greek word for "nowhere"?
For Ł50,000,
I can make that somewhere.
I can turn it into a place
where people will smile at me
- and children will dance...
- I will smile for you, Ron.
I will smile for you if you tell me
where I can get Ł50,000.
I'm telling you. I'm fucking telling you.
Just pull it out of the casino.
- I cannot pull it out of the casino...
- Just pull it out of the casino, you cunt.
Do not meddle with a foolproof way
of making the money!
I'm not a fucking banker!
I am not a fucking banker!
- Right? Am I?
- Genius! Look at that.
That has made it
all the more manageable.
- This man who wants to build a city!
- Don't you fucking threaten me!
Don't you fucking dare
talk to me like that, you cunt!
Reggie is not here now, all right?
He's fucking gone, ain't he?
So you work for me, Ron Kray!
So you will trot along down
to the fucking bank,
and you will fetch me my Ł50,000.
Yeah, I'll go down to the bank
and see what I can do.
And I'll tell you what,
I may work for you, Ron,
but I'm certainly not afraid of you,
all right?
Well, that is fucking stupid as well,
because you fucking should be.
Because if my brother hadn't have
vouched for you, you'd be fucking dead.
What happened?
What are you doing here?
Didn't Ronnie tell you not to come?
- I missed you.
- Look.
Frankie, I don't want you to come here
and see me like this, understand?
- Who did it?
- What?
Your face.
Was it one of the other prisoners?
No, no.
It was one of the guards, all right?
- Well, have you reported them?
- No.
But you know what?
When I get out, I'm thinking
I might go to the Houses of Parliament,
have a word with the Prime Minister,
'cause he will listen, he will.
Frankie, this is prison, OK?
That's what this is.
It's the law of the jungle in here.
But don't worry about it,
because I'm a big boy,
I can look after meself
and I'll be out very soon. All right?
Go on, have a look at that lump
over there, you see him?
With the big hat.
There's a very good reason
why we all call him Handbag.
All right?
I don't want a life like this.
- Just waiting, while you're in prison.
- I know. I know.
- Frankie, it won't happen again.
- How can you be sure?
Because I know. Because I promise you
it won't happen again.
All right?
I know how you can be sure.
- Go on.
- You could go straight.
Be a casino owner, a club owner.
You enjoy it.
Just forget everything else.
It really is that simple for you, innit?
Yeah, just go straight.
Babe, life isn't always the way
we want it to be, you know.
Life has other plans. It...
- It's the way it is. It's life.
- I love you.
I love you.
I never loved anybody before,
but I love you, Reggie.
And I love you, too.
You think it can protect people?
What?
Love.
I like him. Yeah, he got
something about him, ain't he?
Do you know
what I reckon it is? I think it's his hips.
I want to blow the soul
out of that horn.
You feeling a bit horny, are you, Ron?
I am. I am.
- Go on. Do it.
- I will. Yeah.
I want to blow the soul
out of that horn.
That's what I'm gonna do.
OK? OK?
Tiger!
That's it, Ron, give it a fucking blow.
Kill it.
Oh, fucking hell.
Right.
Hello. Hello?
Yes, Ron. Hello.
Do you know when I plan to die?
- When, Ron?
- At the very last minute.
Don't fucking encourage him,
for fuck's sake.
Look at you, you flash fuckers.
Now, I may not be very good, granted.
But good gangster?
Oh, yeah.
I'll fucking claim that title.
And how many titles
could you claim?
Superficialite.
Oh, yeah.
Dripping in your synthetic opulence.
Ha!
It's disgusting. Really is.
Yeah.
Right, a bit of magic.
You love magic, don't you?
All kids love magic.
You might all be aware
that there are three magic Cs, right,
in the word "carpaccio". Yeah?
But how many Cs...
...are in the word "cunt"?
Just you.
You're free.
What are you doing
throwing stones at the window?
They're not, they're not stones.
These are... these are lemon sherbets.
Here you go.
Oh, well played.
Why don't you ring the bell?
Well, your mum.
I mean, I'm not being funny,
but the thought of your mum answering
that door is a bit shocking, so...
I thought she'd give me grief
on account of where I've been.
- You mean prison?
- Yeah, prison. You look beautiful.
You look beautiful, too.
I know it's a bit late, right, but...
I've got your Christmas present here.
- Do you want me to throw it up?
- No.
What? You want me to deliver it?
I ain't going through that door.
All right.
You cheeky bugger.
Be careful.
A bit late now, innit?
Right!
- Your flowers.
- Thank you.
And...
...your Christmas present.
Sorry it's late.
Go on, open it.
Frances Shea, will you marry me?
We'll live free and above-board?
On my honor.
Yes, Reggie Kray, I will marry you.
That one of mine?
Cheeky.
That's it.
Come on,
show us your fucking hoochie.
- Give us a fucking look.
- You're not listening. You're not listening.
All I'm saying, all I'm saying is
crime is still a business.
You need a public relations department,
and we've got Joseph Goebbels.
Is he the fat one?
You read lips. What's he saying?
What's he saying, Les?
I'm struggling, but I think he's saying
something about gobbles or no balls?
That's very strange.
He ain't happy. You'll see.
Nice, innit?
Oh, he looks lovely, Ron.
He's put on
a little bit of timber, ain't he?
He's going to be very, very upset.
Did I miss something?
Is this not...
This is Friday night, right?
Well, I tried to tell you.
Yeah, but it's Friday night, right?
You didn't tell me
that it was this bad, did you?
It's Ron, innit?
He's run the place into the ground.
He's turned a straight money earner
into a financial wreck.
And another thing: This place will crash
when we get our tax bill next week.
What's he saying? What's he saying?
He's just told him that you're missing
tax payments. Silly cunt!
Let's go.
This is tomorrow's business.
Do you understand?
That's very rude.
- Oi, where are you going?
- It's fucking criminal, mate!
Criminal!
Hey, where are you going?
Oh, there he is,
my beautiful brother, Reggie.
A toast to my beautiful brother.
Home at last,
like Agamemnon returned to Ithaca.
And beautiful Frances.
Where have you been?
It's as if you've returned
from the dead.
What are you doing, mate?
What are you fucking playing at?
I'm not playing at anything.
It's you.
You come in here.
You don't even say, "Hello, Ron. "
You don't even have a drink.
You just bugger off.
- Hello, Ron. Cheers, mate. Fuck you!
- What are you shouting at me for?
Because you had the world
on a string, yeah?
But you couldn't hold it together
so you fucked it up.
- Don't... Listen, you was away.
- I was in prison.
I had to make do with what I had.
You going Ron or Reg?
- Score?
Reginald. He'll never go down
in front of the missus.
- You had everything, mate. You had it all.
- I didn't have you, did I?
- Reggie, please.
- It's all right, honestly. I got this. It's fine.
Yeah, actually, he's got this.
Thank you very much. He's a big boy.
We're talking about earning a living.
We're talking about being gangsters,
right, which is what we are.
- So you can just fuck off. Go on.
- Don't.
You know, one of these days, Ron Kray,
your miserable life will swallow you whole.
You should know all about that, because
I've heard all the stories. They're not good.
Your mum did palm us off
with the damaged goods, didn't she?
You're very, very damaged, aren't you?
All right, just get in the car.
- Don't ever speak to her like that again.
- Yeah, that's right, Frances.
Blood is thicker than water,
and I've been with Reggie since the womb.
Ron, shut up. I want you to apologise
to Frances right now.
- Right.
- All right.
Right, right. Frances.
I'm sorry, all right? Yes.
I'm truly very sorry
the club's very, very empty.
A bit like you, really. There's fuck-all in it,
apart from my brother's cock.
You, all right,
are a fucking disgrace, mate.
You hit me.
Yeah.
- No! No!
- No, Ron.
No! No!
I fucking did, you fucking cunt!
Fucking cunt!
- Fuck's sake!
- Not the bottle. Not the...
No! Not the balls!
My fucking nuts! Wanker!
Sweetheart, please leave.
Biting! Biting cunt!
Give me that.
Never mess with a man's jewels, mate.
What the fuck...
Now what are you doing?
No, Ron. No. No, no. That's a bottle, Ron.
- That's a bottle!
- I'll serve you up, you fucking cunt!
It's a bottle, Ron!
That's enough.
Pack it in. That's enough!
- I'm going to split them up.
- Shut up, mate.
Get back and sit down in your chair.
No. They're family.
Stay back.
Get out of the fucking way.
Put it down!
OK, now, I told you!
Come on, that's enough.
No.
Enough, Reg, mate.
You just don't understand,
you don't...
Fuck.
You don't understand me.
That's probably 'cause I don't want to
fucking understand you right now, Ron.
I wanted to just, you know...
There's no point in
fucking explaining it to you, either.
It's fucking hopeless.
Come on, help me up.
Just help me out here, will you?
- That fucking hurt.
- All right, mate. What are you doing?
For fuck's sake, Ron.
Reggie, what I'm trying to tell you
is very simple, all right?
Listen.
I am very, very, very fragile,
myself.
All right?
Yeah, fragile, I've got it.
- Very fragile.
- I've got it.
All right, come on, now.
For fuck's sake.
I'm not myself, am I?
I mean, this isn't me. Is it?
This isn't us.
None of this is us, is it?
- I'm very sorry.
- It's OK.
Are you done?
Has she gone?
- Yes, she's gone, mate.
- She's a keeper.
She is. Thank you, Ron.
Thanks.
- There she is.
- Yeah, I got her.
All right, stop here.
That girl's gonna be the death of me.
Mind how you go.
Frankie. Frank.
Excuse me. Sorry.
I need to have a word with you
about something.
I don't care if you forget me.
- Don't say that.
- It's true.
You don't mean it.
Don't tell me what I mean.
I know what I mean.
Come on, Frances, please.
Can't we just start again?
From the beginning, you know.
We can get rid of everything that's bad,
and we'll just keep everything that's good.
- What about Ron?
He's not exactly a good bit, is he?
Well... I mean,
he's not exactly a bad bit, either.
- He was awful to me.
- Yeah, he was. But, you know, that...
That's Ron. If he don't take his tablets,
he's like that. He's a nightmare.
He's not always like that, you know.
He's got a heart of gold.
He loves you to bits.
He thinks the world of you.
Honestly, when you left,
he was in pieces.
He was like, "Where's she gone?"
I said, "She's left. "
"Well, you better get after her
'cause she's a keeper. "
You are a keeper. So he's right.
He said, "Tell her I'm very sorry. "
He is sorry and I'm sorry.
We're all sorry. But you know, that...
That's what happens sometimes.
Families are stupid, aren't they?
You know, they fight,
you know, they make up.
And ultimately, you know, they stick
together 'cause they love each other.
It's what they do.
Don't tell me about forgetting you,
'cause that ain't happening, either.
I spent the last six months
thinking about nothing but you.
- So I get out and the club's gone up...
- All right. All right.
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
'It was time for the Krays
to enter the secret history of the 1960s.
'As absurd as it seems,
'it grew out of Ron's nutter dream
of building a utopian city in Nigeria. '
Some are born to be Ronnie Kray,
and some have Ronnie Kray
thrust upon them.
'Lord Boothby
was a distinguished member
'of the House of Lords. '
- Ronnie.
- Yes.
I regret that my answer is no.
Nigeria is simply too far away
and I never involve myself
in a thing I can't control personally.
I'm so sorry.
He's really lovely, isn't he?
I take it you like ice and a slice,
my Lord?
Ice and a slice.
Please, Teddy Bear.
And don't spare the horses.
Do you know where I hear the lemons
are particularly lovely and fresh?
No, where?
Enugu, Nigeria.
You are very well-informed, Teddy.
Very well-informed.
Down the hatch.
Do you like it down the hatch, Teddy?
'Boothby declined,
but friendship ensued
'and the perverted peer
was soon a guest at Ron's flat.
'The ripples would spread far and wide. '
Do call me later, Tom.
Harry, all alone?
No need to be,
plenty of fruit on the tree.
Tom, not in the
House of Commons tonight?
Yeah?
Fucking look at me, you cunt.
Go on, fucking look at him now.
Fucking look at me.
But he looks up at me!
Good Lord,
that's Bob Boothby.
Yes, Prime Minister, sir.
At an orgy.
The Tories are going to have trouble
explaining this.
Here, sir.
Is that Tom Driberg?
In fact, yes, sir.
There's no moral advantage to my party
if my party are also involved.
It gets a bit stickier, sir.
- Where were these photos taken?
- Cazenove Road, Hackney.
What in God's boots
were they doing in Hackney?
That's where it gets sticky.
I thought the orgy was the sticky bit.
It gets stickier still?
We've had two brothers, gangsters,
under surveillance. The Krays.
The photographs
were taken in Ronald Kray's flat.
Orgies aside, we're tracking fraud,
protection rackets
and the American Mafia
might also be involved.
'London's bottom
had reached her top.
'Scandal loomed. '
The elections are in 10 weeks.
They'll vote out
both sides of the House.
What exactly are you doing about it?
Bugger all, by the looks of it.
Is that Italian?
- Don't know.
- Is it a Daimler?
It's nice, that is.
Oh, what do you want for Christmas?
I don't know.
- You don't have to get me anything.
- You don't have to get me a present.
- That's ridiculous.
Not get you anything for Christmas?
All right, well, just surprise me, then.
Surprise me.
I'll get you a sock full of coal,
you lucky thing.
What about that?
What about it?
For Christmas.
For me?
That's gonna be my club.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
In the West End, just a touch of class.
That's our ticket out of here.
It's snowing.
Yeah.
Gone.
'What did I want for Christmas?
'My Reggie, free and above-board.
'But Ron wanted his Reggie back as well.
'He longed for his gangster twin.
'And Reggie,
he chose a hideaway instead.
'The owner was Hew McCowan,
the son of a baronet.
'Though he was not usually
intimidated by the working classes,
'he agreed to sell half the club.
'Reggie knew he'd get the rest in time.
'A dirty deal for a clean life.
'Ron was terrified
of Reggie leaving him behind.
'He sent Mad Teddy round
to kill the deal. '
Listen, gentlemen...
I'm sorry. I can't look at you, darling,
I'm gonna get lost in your eyes.
- I've got a deal with Reggie...
- It tastes shit.
- I love your mouth!
- I signed the contract.
I have an arrangement
with Reggie, ask him.
- Crap.
- Gentlemen, please.
- Please, I have customers.
- Out of the way. That's it, come on.
Please! I have customers here!
Gentlemen, please. I've spoken to Reggie.
We don't work for Reggie.
We work for Ronnie.
'Ron almost got what he wanted.
'McCowan backed out of the deal,
but he also called the police.
'Reggie and Ron
were both charged with extortion. '
Franny, I'm telling you,
the police stitched me up.
- I am innocent. I'm completely...
- Even if you are...
- What?
- You're back in prison.
You made a promise to me.
And it still stands, it stands.
I'm fucking innocent!
I'm sorry, I don't mean
to swear at you, all right? I just...
I really want you to marry me.
Please.
If you're innocent and acquitted,
I'll marry you.
If you're guilty,
I never want to see you again.
Why would you say that?
Franny, that...
Franny... Frances.
'Strangely,
it was Lord Boothby who saved the day.
'His walk on the wild side
had not gone unnoticed. '
I found the photo.
It's been forwarded
to the proper places.
Say "Enugu".
Enugu.
'The photograph taken
in Boothby's flat ended up with the paper,
'along with a story of sexual misconduct
'between a gangster
and a member of the House of Lords. '
The problem is, Arnold,
that unfortunately,
it's all true, for once.
I don't care about the truth, Harold.
Except that the greater the truth,
the greater the libel.
'An election was looming,
'so the Prime Minister brought in his fixer,
Arnold Goodman, to sort things out. '
Get me Cecil King at the Sunday Mirror.
'The great and the good
engineered a cover-up,
'a cracking good one.
'When the Krays' defense threatened
to call Boothby as a character witness,
'the implication was clear.
'The government
would have to drop its case
'or face the consequences.
'It was this that made the Krays
the untouchables of London crime. '
New information casts poor light
on the prosecution witness, Mr McCowan.
Case dismissed.
'That night, the Krays held
their celebration party at McCowan's club.
Reggie had bought the Hideaway
that same afternoon. At a discount.
Thank you.
So, why are you here, then?
I've come to see
the difference between you and me.
The difference, yeah?
Right.
- What do you know?
- I grew up poor, like you.
- Yeah?
- I boxed as a lad, like you.
But it didn't turn me into a thief.
But it did turn you into policing,
didn't it?
Yeah.
It did turn you into handing your own
over at the bar, didn't it?
You know, the difference
between us, right,
apart from, you know,
the obvious and that,
is that I, right, I work for me.
And you...
- Well, you work for them.
- Sir, I can explain.
- This is Scotland Yard.
And this investigation will end at once.
But there's so much more
that we can get them on.
Your investigation into the Krays
will end at once!
- All right, all right.
- She's wearing black.
Yeah, I know, I know.
She's read it wrong, hasn't she?
- She thought it was a fucking funeral.
- Wearing black, that fucking bitch.
Don't drive yourself mad.
Wait till you see the daughter,
she looks unbelievable in white.
What do you see in her?
Well, I see...
I see meself, yeah, I see...
I see what I could be.
You know?
- If I weren't so scared.
- You're not afraid of anything.
Yeah.
Yeah, well, only meself, you know.
And you.
What's she doing?
Well, you know
what she's gonna be saying, OK?
So, just take it easy. Deep breaths.
Why are you not inside yet?
Are you sure
you wanna go through with this?
- Mum, please, don't start this again.
- It's all right, Frank.
I love him.
"Love"...
Do you even know
what love is, Frances?
I know it's not an answer to anything.
But love is a witness.
Reggie sees me,
and I see him.
And who are you to refuse that?
I'm your mother.
Hey, East End starlet, Frances.
- That's you.
- Thank you.
All right. Look at her, mate.
She looks beautiful.
Gracious God,
accept our prayers
for Frances and Reginald,
that they may reap
the harvest of the spirit
and reflect your glory
through Christ Jesus, our Lord.
- Amen.
Fucking sing!
'We honeymooned in Greece.
'The Parthenon
had stood for 2,400 years.
'Reggie's promise to go straight
lasted two weeks. '
The Two Aces,
the New Mill,
the Gigi Club
and let's not forget Ronnie Scott's.
And this is the bearer bonds
cashed in Hamburg!
Kettle's on the boil.
It's tea.
'We started out
near Marble Arch in West London.
'But we both missed the East End.
'And so we took an empty flat
below Ron's at Cedra Court.
'Like all else in life, it was supposed
to be temporary. Not very clever. '
Rattle the monkey.
Rattle it, monkey boy!
'Ron's parties would
keep me awake at night
'and clubland kept Reggie out
until all hours.
'He enjoyed being a gangster,
after all. '
We heard that you were
down the Regency the other night.
Waving a shotgun.
Those bastard Barry brothers
blocked me from coming in.
They said I was drunk.
You were.
You was drunk as a skunk.
Waving a shotgun?
No.
Now, you know
we look after that place, right?
So, no more of your
messing around down there.
I spiced the evening up for people.
"Spiced it up".
Here you go.
Now, you're not gonna do that
anymore, are you?
No, sir.
Good lad.
Oh, bollocks.
Get up, Jack, fuck off.
This is so kind of you.
- Treat, isn't it?
- Lovely, yeah.
Oh, hello.
Oh...
- Is that OK?
- No, no.
No, Frances. That won't...
That won't do.
Go and sit with Mr Kray
and I'll sort it out.
All right.
She can't even make
a decent cup of tea.
Poor Reggie?
It was a good effort.
She looks like a budgie
in that dress, doesn't she?
The rag-and-bone man wouldn't
pick her up if she was laying in the gutter.
Really.
Oh, well.
Poor Reggie.
Right, I shall,
Might as well flush that.
'I left without saying goodbye.
'A sad victory.
'I'd never be good enough
for their Reggie.
'He was Nipper's Reggie as well.
'Read couldn't rest unless he clapped
eyes on my husband once a day.
'I often had to settle for the same. '
Wherever you're going,
don't stop till you get to the sea.
'But we all need something.
'And what I shared with Ron was
needing pills to get through the day.
'Sleeping pills helped sometimes,
'other pills helped other times.
'They were like a friend
who held no judgment
'and only wanted to be loved in return.
'Mother's little helpers.
'They were very well-named. '
Don't go too fast.
We're not going anywhere like too fast.
We're on the grass.
- All right. Almost there.
- All right.
- Bit more.
- OK.
OK.
- You ready?
- Yes.
- Ready ready?
Oh, my God!
- Do you like it?
- Yes, what kind is it? What's it called?
- It's a Triumph, a Triumph Spitfire.
- Can I get in?
Yeah, of course you can, it's yours.
Happy birthday. There you are.
- Happy birthday, Frances.
- Thank you.
Will you teach me how to drive?
I can.
- Now?
- Oh, not today.
- Why not?
- I just... I can't. Not today.
But I can tomorrow.
- All right.
- Sorry.
Kray.
- Kray.
There's an inherent threat
in that one commanding syllable.
It's the only word some need to hear.
What does that mean, "the only word"?
Well, you're like Ford.
Or Shell.
Or Woolworth's.
Woolworth's.
Yeah, that's very interesting.
All I'm saying is Kray is a brand
and an established reputation needs less
maintenance, less violence, you know?
People fall naturally into line.
Clubs are asking for our protection
before we even offer it.
Yeah. That's true, actually,
they are. Yes.
I suppose that would leave us
with less straightening out to do.
- Exactly. That's right.
- Yeah.
Makes sense.
But I happen to like...
I like straightening out,
you know, once in a while.
Obliging someone in the old cobbles.
What's wrong with that?
I just think you could do better, Ron.
You know.
It'll keep you out of prison, I mean,
none of us are getting any younger.
You know, you need to leave
all this behind, I mean...
You got to look to the future,
you and that lovely young wife of yours.
No! Fairy tales!
That's fucking warning!
This is a firm, right?
I'm a fucking face.
I'll fucking serve you up,
you fucking cunt!
You're fucking bang out of order!
I don't fucking like him, I don't trust him.
He asks too many questions.
- I want him fucking dead!
- Leslie Payne, right, is our business,
and you want him dead.
- Have you been taking your tablets?
- Fuck tablets, right? Bugger tablets!
Bugger Payne,
the fucking pain in the arse!
And fuck his briefcase!
I don't give a fuck what's in there,
I want to know what's going on up there.
He knows too much about things.
Things about us.
Reggie, he knows
too many things about us.
He knows too many things about us?
Right.
Albie,
do you know things about us, mate?
Do you know things?
About Ron, about me,
about the firm, right?
You know about payments, right?
You know we cash bearer bonds, yeah?
D'you know we pay off juries to make 'em
look fucking favorably upon us, do you?
Yes.
You do. There's a fucking surprise.
Jack!
Mate, do you know anything
about fraud?
Anything at all? Take a punt.
Do you know anything about
how we pay off policemen
every fucking
final Thursday of the month?
- Do you know that?
- Of course I do.
Fucking surprise, that.
So why don't we kill Jack now?
Or we do Albie as well?
We do the fucking lot.
Or you can do me and I'll do you
and we're both fucking dead!
That's a genius idea!
Listen to yourself, Ron!
You're fucking nuts!
People who live in glass houses
shouldn't throw stones.
You know
I never drank gin till I came here?
Oh, well, next you'll be singing
God Save the Queen, won't you?
What did you want to have
a word with me about, Mr Bruno?
Things are going well,
we're very happy on my side of the pond.
Well, that's good.
You know, we're very happy also.
OK.
Cheers.
You realize I asked
to speak to you alone.
You see, in our line of work,
it's not good to be famous.
Anonymous is the goal.
This Mr Lansky, Reg,
he sees a lot of potential in you.
But he sees limitations
in your brother Ron.
Well, you know, maybe...
Maybe they could just sit down
and meet each other, couldn't they?
I mean,
he could come across for a chat.
A chat?
You guys crack me up, really.
You ever hear of the Gallo brothers?
- From Brooklyn?
- No.
Similar loose cannon situation.
You see, Ron is your Joey.
And it's not gonna end well
in either case.
What exactly are you
asking me to do, Mr Bruno?
I'm asking you
to do something about Ron.
I can't do that.
He's my brother.
OK.
- There's nothing I can do.
- I ain't finished with you yet.
- Mr Kray takes care of this warehouse.
- Now, you say Kray one more time...
...and I'm gonna hit you, you understand?
I have an arrangement with Mr Kray.
I didn't ask whether we had
an arrangement.
I asked if you understood me.
'The Richardson gang were away.
'But George Cornell had crossed the river
to work a protection racket on their behalf. '
I fucking warned you!
'Ron's response would secure
his place in gangster legend. '
What is that,
is that English breakfast tea?
I can tell by your face, Ted,
what you think of it.
- Lovely box, isn't it? It's beautiful.
- It's not English breakfast. That's not, no.
That's got pheromones in it, that's got.
It's musky.
That's a bit of magic, that is.
That's very beautiful, innit?
- I'm glad you like it.
- I do, that's proper.
Me mum will be very,
very pleased with that.
Did you have that away
from the old warehouse, did you?
- Yeah.
- Don't say anything. It's all right.
- Regards to Mrs Kray.
- Thank you.
- For the other matter.
- Yeah. What matter?
That?
- Yeah.
- All right.
I mean, I'm not in the mind
to hand out refunds, am I?
Can't you handle it yourself?
I pay you for protection, Ron.
- What are you trying to say?
- Nothing...
No, you just said it.
You just fucking said it.
You come in here
with your fucking nose, right,
and your tea.
Your fucking exotic tea.
Right?
And you say that.
I'm not very good at my job.
- I didn't mean it like that.
- You fucking did!
- No, I...
I'll tell you what.
This matter of yours...
- I'll deal with it for you. All right?
- All right.
You go with Teddy, right,
and you bring me Ł2,000, OK?
And in return, I promise
that I will have George Cornell killed.
All right?
- I didn't say...
- All right?
I didn't say
anything about killing, Ron.
You fucking did.
You fucking meant it.
Look at you, you meant it with your eyes.
Look at your eyes.
It's in your fucking eyes!
- Or are you threatening me?
- No.
'Cause there's death in your eyes
and you're fucking threatening me!
- Is he threatening me?
- It's hard to tell, Ron.
- I'll pay.
- You'll what?
- You will?
- Yeah.
- There it is. And a deal is a deal.
- It's done.
- Yeah.
It's done. It's over.
Teddy, take him.
Thank you.
- That's very kind of you.
- Thank you.
For the tea.
That's a good deal.
How do I look?
Fucking deadly.
- Do you want me to come in with you?
In there?
Come on.
You all stay in the car.
Anything you need to tell me?
Well, look what the cat dragged in.
Jesus!
Yeah, you're not laughing now, are you?
For fuck's sake.
Boss, the fuck...
Get the fuck down!
Don't say a fucking word!
What are you fucking looking at?
You didn't see nothing!
Fuck.
That's Ronnie Kray, that, isn't it?
Fucking hell.
Reggie.
Are you mad?
The Blind Beggar? Yeah, Cornell?
It's on the fucking radio.
Reggie.
Hi, Mum.
Oh. Thank you.
Oh! Look at you.
Look how handsome you are!
- I'll get you a cup of tea.
- Thanks, Mum.
- Albie?
- I'm all right, Violet, thank you.
You do look lovely, Reggie.
How many witnesses?
It was a quiet night.
- Seven?
Albert Woods was with Cornell.
Plus five regulars, don't know them.
And the barmaid, the blond, the one
with the big fucking pair of eyes.
For fuck's sake.
And you bring this here?
You bring it straight to Mum's?
Don't moan about it, all right?
It's done, innit?
What are we gonna do?
- "We"?
- Yeah.
Where's the weapon?
It's here, Reg.
There you go. Now...
- Here, let me have it.
- Would you like a piece of cake?
Do you know what? That would be lovely.
Yeah. Thank you, Mum.
- It is, it's lovely.
- Thanks.
I assume you were
in those clothes, right?
Yeah, yeah.
So where's his jacket?
Right, you need to burn that.
And that gun, we need to toss it
in the river right fucking now.
Go on, fuck off.
You are...
You're unbelievable.
Albie?
Whoever was in that pub,
we need to find out who they are,
get hold of them and just unravel
whatever they've said to the police.
We need to undo, so get Big Pat,
Bender, send them down there now.
- The barmaid I know, right?
- You know her.
Well, bring her to me,
I'll deal with her myself, all right?
Go on. Fuck off.
Oh.
Where's everybody gone?
Oh, Mum, it's late, it's late.
I wanted them out of your hair, you know.
You should get some bed time.
Why don't I give you a lift home?
Come on.
Oh, it's all right, I am home.
I've made a bed up for him.
He's not well.
He's...
He's got a fever.
He's going to stay here the night.
Teddy, would you like to stay with him?
Thank you, that'd be very nice.
Thank you, Violet.
Whatever he's done,
he's your brother.
Yeah.
Well...
Here's your Stemetil, mate.
You should take that.
Do you know what?
I'm going to have to go, actually.
'Cause, I left the lads at work
and I have to clean up.
So, I'm going to say goodnight.
Goodnight.
Teddy, now, you couldn't do us a favor,
could you? Be useful.
And when you take his trousers off tonight
and his shirt, can you burn them?
Yeah? And check in with me.
- Yeah.
- Good lad.
Night-night.
Goodnight.
Goodnight, Reggie.
He's lovely, isn't he?
'Not even Scotland Yard
could ignore murder on the streets.
'Nipper was back on the case. '
Gentlemen, your attention, please.
Now, you've been told that we're
conducting a high-level investigation
into a major corruption allegation.
In fact, we're going down into the sewer
after the Krays.
Any man with any objection,
come and see me.
See that lamppost up there, right?
That was known as a safety point
during the war, right?
So, if you could run to that lamppost,
you knew that you could make it
to the air raid shelter
before the bombs started dropping.
One night, right, me and Ron,
we just stood there and we watched.
We saw the old Stanton house
get blown to bits, they were still in it.
It's a wonder you lived through it.
Yeah, yeah,
especially with Ron, you know.
Every time trouble came on top, he was
always dragging behind, wasn't he?
He's got plenty of trouble now,
if the stories are true.
I heard it on the street, Reggie.
My own family and you didn't tell me.
Yeah, well, you know,
I didn't want you to worry, did I?
I don't worry about Ron.
- What do you plan to do about it?
- I'm not gonna let him go to prison.
- Why not?
Why not? Because he's my brother,
that's why not.
He'll still be your brother in prison.
No.
No, Frances, look, he belongs here, right?
He belongs with us.
He belongs with you, me and his family,
this is his home, all right?
I've been looking after Ron since we were
little boys, it's just the way it is.
You can still look after him in prison.
And he doesn't belong here
and you know it.
Right.
Right, well, you just don't understand.
- Yes, I do.
- No, you don't.
Yes, I do. You once told me
you don't owe the world a thing.
Well, you don't owe Ron a thing, either.
My loyalty for my brother is how
I measure myself, do you understand?
What about your loyalty to me,
is that not a measure?
So... what is going on
with your eyes right now?
Are you on something?
Are you taking something, Frances?
Are you taking pills again?
Let's have a look.
- Oh, hello. Look at that.
- Stop it.
Jesus Christ, how many
of these things are you on?
No wonder you're not making any sense.
You're a pill popper.
- And who made me that?
- What? A pill popper?
So, let me get this straight.
What you're saying is that
in order for us all to be free, yeah,
that we all have to be on our own?
That's great, Frances.
Let's just... I'll go with that.
- Listen, talk to that barmaid.
- Yeah?
Tell her when they line the suspects up
across from her
to point her finger at Ron
and say, "That's him.
"That's the mad hatter what done it. "
All right?
- Where are you going?
- Home.
- What about me mum?
- Fuck your mum!
- Take your time.
- No.
The man who shot Cornell,
he's not here.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Please, could someone
just take me home?
Miss.
I swear to God.
I smelt something,
I don't know what I smelt.
There were some good funny looks
in the room towards the judge.
A bit stinky, he was.
Right?
Am I right or am I wrong?
- No. No.
Just goes to show,
you can give a dog a bad name,
but when that dog's name is Kray,
it might bite you back. Well done.
Well done, Ronnie.
Justice is served.
- Mea culpa. Mea culpa.
- Drink to my little bunny.
Welcome home.
Maxima.
It's discipline.
Come and sit down, Vi.
No.
Give her a pink wafer.
What did you tell her?
I just said, "You might want to think
about your children. " You know?
I wish I could make you go away.
Well, good luck with that, Frances.
Yeah. Good fucking luck with that.
It's pouring down with rain.
What the fuck is she doing?
It surprises me
that some people still...
Still survive these days.
See you later, Albie.
- You all right?
- Yeah, go on.
You all right?
Look like you're struggling there.
Help me.
Help you?
What are you doing?
Help me put the top on.
- Oh, I'm not sure I can help you.
- Reggie, please, it's going to get ruined.
I can't, can I? I'm a club owner.
You know what I mean?
I can pick a nice model, all right,
in a nice color,
but I'm not very good at anything else.
I'm not a mechanic, am I?
I'm more of a... a gangster,
isn't that right? Yeah?
Please help me.
Please help you?
"Please.
"Please, Reggie. "
All right, let's help you, then.
Go on, then.
How's that?
It looks a bit
fucking fucked to me, mate.
Speaking of...
You look like shit and all.
Yeah.
What are you doing?
Reggie, stop it!
Stop it!
Reggie!
- Stop what?
- Please stop. Please stop.
- Reggie, please stop. Please stop.
- Stop what?
Please, no!
Please! No!
Stop it!
Where are you going?
I'm leaving Reggie.
Oh, that is a shame,
he will take that very hard.
Please get out of my way, Ron.
Unless you prefer me to stay.
All right, boys, go upstairs. Go on.
Would you like me
to help you with your bags?
- No, thank you.
- Oh, come on. Don't be daft.
Look at the size of you,
look at the size of me, come on.
Come on.
You know, Frances,
sometimes to achieve greatness,
you do, you have to cut off
a little piece of yourself
no matter how much it hurts,
in order to grow, in order to move on.
It takes courage
and I admire that, you know?
To be honest,
I think you're getting out just in time.
- You think so?
- Absolutely, yeah.
There's so many people
who know so much about us.
Not you, of course. You know.
Most people hate us.
Sooner or later, someone's going to talk
and that'll be it, it'll be over.
That wouldn't be so bad, would it?
I think God ought to cut us
some slack, though, don't you think?
Yeah, I'm sure God will.
That is...
That is bang out of order.
That's not how we were brought up,
not at all.
Ron, I've got to go.
Yeah, course you do.
Listen here, Frances, right?
We both love him, all right?
We both made the effort.
So we shall just have to see
what happens when we get there.
Where?
Heaven.
Goodbye, Ron.
Bye, Frances.
Listen here,
I always liked you, Frances,
I always did.
'Cause you have the ability
to see into the future.
You do.
And that's the same as me.
Bye, now.
All right, Reggie?
How are you?
Yeah. You all right, Frank?
Long time no see?
- I've been walking straight, you know.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- That's nice, innit?
That's nice.
What can I do for you?
Frances here?
It's just that I've been outside your
parents' house the last couple of weeks.
And they hadn't told me
that she left, so, you know,
I've been standing underneath
her window like a fool.
- Yeah, she's here.
- Yeah, I know.
- Reggie...
- What?
I haven't seen her like this
in a long time.
She's delicate.
Right. All right.
You tell Frances to come out here
'cause I had to come out here.
- Why don't you just go and get Frances?
- I'm not letting you see her.
- Don't fuck about!
- Frank?
Frances, get back inside.
What are you doing?
It's OK.
Hi, Reggie.
Hello, Frances.
Have you got a moment?
Let's have a little chat.
- It's all right.
- Are you sure about this?
Go inside and put the kettle on.
Frankie, come home.
I am home.
At least until I find somewhere else.
I can't go and live with my mum.
What can I do to change your mind?
You can't.
I've changed my mind
about one thing, though.
What's that?
I do want you to remember me.
Always.
That I existed,
that I once walked beside you.
What are you on about?
Frankie, come on.
I always imagined, you know,
I thought that we might have
a child or two, you know.
Why? So you could use them
to threaten me?
No.
No, because I still love you.
No, it's just a thing you say out of loyalty
to something
- that didn't exist in the first place.
- That's not true.
Loving you is the only thing
that holds me together.
You know, I...
I dreamt that we could live
beyond the place we were meant for.
But you're a gangster
and you love being one.
No.
No, Frances, listen.
Please let me make amends
for the suffering and the pain
that I have caused you, please.
Please.
- Just let me take you somewhere.
- Somewhere?
Yeah. Anywhere.
Anywhere you want.
Just the two of us
so we can be together.
It could be like
our second honeymoon or...
Or not. Just so that you can know
that I can change.
That... To be fair, I have.
I've... I've changed.
All I'm saying is
is that the center of the world
can be anywhere you want it to be.
Anywhere.
Ibiza.
- Who?
- Ibiza.
Let's go there,
I like the way the word sounds.
Yeah, you know what,
I like the way the word sounds, too.
You want to... We go to Ibiza?
I'll get the tickets today.
I'll book 'em today.
'God doesn't ask
if we accept this life.
'There is no choice.
'Life is forced upon you.
'The only choice is how you live it.
'Or not.
'That's a choice as well. '
'A cup of tea can solve anything.
'A bit under the weather? Tea.
'You've left your husband?
Tea is the answer. '
Frances? Bloody hell, Frances.
What have you done? Frances!
'In case you thought,
"At least Frances survived
"'or she wouldn't be
telling us this tale",
'well, now you know.
'But I was free at last.
'God had finally cut me some slack. '
Where is she?
In her bedroom.
'That afternoon,
Reggie would drink himself insensible.
'What do you do, after all,
'when the only person
who could ever get to you is gone?
'Cup of tea?
'I don't think so. '
One big hat.
Well, sit down. Don't stand around here
like some kind of lamppost.
Squeeze in.
Sweaty, what don't we have?
A bottle. Go on.
- Go on. Go on.
- Right on.
- You wanted to see me, Ron?
- Yeah, I do, actually.
I want you to kill somebody for me,
all right?
I'm gonna give you Ł1,000.
Leslie.
There's Ł500 there, all right?
So that's half. Yeah?
You get the rest when it's done.
You can count it all
'cause it's all there
and you can put it
in your little pocket.
That's for you.
Go on, put it in your fucking pocket.
We know you ain't got any money.
Don't be daft.
Who is it?
Mum, wait here.
- Stop, Mum, leave it.
- You killed her!
You killed my daughter, you bastard!
You killed her!
And your Ł100 a week
on flowers won't bring her back!
Murderer!
You're gonna rot in hell, Reggie Kray!
McVitie, what are you doing here?
I've got a message for you.
From Ron.
Fuck!
Shall I send a solicitor?
Or have you seen to that?
I want my wife and children's
safety guaranteed.
Payne.
He's given them everything.
Names.
Dates, times.
Documents. The lot.
They've put two and two together,
taken a dozen witnesses
into protection.
Nipper...
Yeah? Nipper what?
The barmaid.
He got the barmaid back in.
She ain't come out.
Where's Ron?
Oh, yeah.
This is a piece of me, this.
- Oh, yeah, I love this song.
- Yeah, it's your favorite.
Oh, fuck off, soppy bollocks.
What?
- Say what?
- Fuck off.
Cheer up, twinkle toes.
It's nearly Christmas.
Why don't you have a little dance
or something, you know?
What is the point of coming out
to a party like this
if you're not going to enjoy yourself?
I'm waiting for Jack the Hat.
Oh, right.
What's he been doing?
Has he been waving his shotgun around
in the clubs again?
What did you think going after
Leslie Payne was going to get us?
What do I think?
You heard.
Well, in case you ain't realised,
I don't fucking
answer to you, sweetheart.
Now we're back to business.
Here he is. Come on, come on, Ron,
show us how it's done.
I've got the moves.
- Hello, hello. Where the birds at?
- Hey, it's Jack the Hat.
Mr Bender, how are you?
Nice to see you.
- Esther?
- Jackie.
I should never have let you go.
That was an absolute mistake.
I'm gonna get myself a drink.
Then I'm gonna come back, and I'll
tell you why I shouldn't have let you go.
I promise.
Hello, Leslie. How are you?
Ron.
Teddy.
There you go, Ron, look.
Jack's here.
What's your stories,
morning glories?
Here you are, Jack. Cigarette.
I quit on the way down the stairs.
You got something on your mind, Reg?
Yeah.
Yeah, you're on my mind, mate.
Leslie Payne?
What the fuck were you thinking?
You've ruined this.
- I don't know what you're on about.
- Don't fucking lie to me!
- I don't want to be treated this way.
- How do you want to be treated?
- Ron?
- Shut up.
- He ain't gonna fucking help you, is he?
- You got a tin of worms in your head.
Don't take it out on me
what happened to Frances.
I'm sorry, what did you say?
It's not my fault Frances killed herself.
I never sold her the fucking pills.
You've got to be joking.
Are you fucking joking?
Reggie.
Go on, fucking shoot him.
Say that again. Go on.
Reggie.
Say her fucking name.
I dare you.
Frances.
Why would you do that?
Because I can't kill you.
No matter how much I fucking want to.
Reggie.
Reggie?
Reggie, look at me.
What the fuck's wrong with you?
You kill a geezer
in a room full of people.
Are you fucking mad?
What?
'Reggie once said,
"The center of the world
"'could be anywhere you like. "
'Even here,
in the East End of London.
'The world is quite like London.
'It's not good, it's not bad,
it just is.
'There's no morality or dishonor,
'just your own lonely code.
'Until your race is run. Until the end.
'Until we're all just ghosts of
the people we once thought we were. '
'Reggie spent 33 years
in prison for killing Jack McVitie.
'Through all of those years,
until the end,
'he carried a pair of tickets with him.
'Reggie, my prince,
'we were supposed to go
to Ibiza after all. '