(MALE VOICE)
Get out of my way, you damn lazy dog.
Here.
No good worthless old mutt.
(SIGHS)
Get out of my way,
you damn critters.
Here.
(BIRD CHIRPS)
Worthless buzzards.
(BIRD CRIES OUT)
(MOTOR STALLS SEVERAL TIMES)
(MOTOR STARTS)
(BELL TINKLES)
(FEMALE VOICE)
Coffee went up,
I had to short you some
canned goods to keep 'em at 20.
(SIGHS)
Is that a problem?
Take it or leave it.
Your friend find you?
- What?
- There was a guy here this morning looking for you.
Said he was your friend.
(SIGHS)
(MUSIC)
(CHICKEN CLUCKS)
Daddy, look what I found.
(MALE VOICE)
What is it, honey?
Hey!
Hold it right there!
Easy, cowboy, easy.
Who are you
and what do you want?
Lieutenant?
Oh, it is you,
you no good sombitch.
Private Henry R. Hocknell Jr.,
reporting sir!
Don't salute.
Oh, don't pretend
you don't remember!
Baby killing warmonger!
(LAUGHS)
Hocknell?
You bet your rosy red ass!
- Daddy!
- Vietnam in '67
Come here, it's okay, it's okay.
It's all right, it's all right.
My God!
Henry!
Yeah!
Come here!
Hey, how did you find me?
Well, it wasn't easy.
Nothing short of a
goddamn miracle, it was.
This is Lee, it's my kid.
I call her Lenny.
Lenny, this ugly bastard is Jake.
Eggs aren't collected
till the end of the day.
It's okay, it's okay.
Oh, he just looks scary.
Oh yeah, you got a little slice
of heaven here, Lieutenant.
(JAKE)
Yeah.
Your kid, huh?
Yeah, ended up
marrying me a gook.
Well, me and round-eyed women
never got along too well.
Been there myself.
So where's your wife?
Uh, she died.
Sorry.
Yeah, well, me too.
(LAUGHS AND CHOKES)
You still got that thing?
Forgot all about it.
Oh yeah.
Well, my dad gave it to me
on his freakin' death bed.
Said it was leading me
to where I was meant to go.
Guess it did.
Hey!
Don't do that.
You been to the Wall, Jake?
No.
Couldn't drag me there.
Yeah, well I...
I never thought I'd go
but I'm glad I did.
- You went?
- Yeah,
I went in the middle
of the night,
just me and my .38, I was gonna
blow my freakin' brains out.
Yeah. A final "F" you to Uncle Sam,
you know what I mean?
(CHUCKLES)
And then I looked
at all them freakin' names,
and all those people that had
their lives stole from them,
they didn't have
no goddamn choice.
But I did.
I mean, what are they
gonna think of me, sittin' there
drownin' in self-pity, some pathetic piece of shit.
(CHUCKLES)
So what'd you do?
I couldn't do it,
I couldn't do it to them.
So, I ended up
going back to the Nam,
to try to find whatever the
hell it was I lost over there.
So, you see, Jake, if I'd never
gone to the Wall, I'd never had Lenny.
If you came here
on some... mission,
preaching me about the Wall,
you're wasting your time.
No, no, I...
that's not why I came.
- Why did you?
- (CHUCKLES)
You know, I always wanted
to take Lenny to the Wall.
Yeah, so take her.
Nah, I can't.
What's stopping you?
Lung cancer.
Oh, Christ!
Yeah!
It's that Agent Orange shit.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah, go figure all that
goddamn crap I've been through,
some goddamn weed killer from
30 years ago is trying to kick my ass.
Yeah, I've got to see
some specialist back East,
and it's gonna be pretty rough.
Hell, we all gotta take a
dirt nap sooner or later, don't we?
(COUGHS AND CHOKES)
(CRICKETS)
(JAKE)
Oh no.
You're the only guy
I can trust, Jake.
Absolutely not.
Hey, it's just for a little while,
you know what I mean?
She could help
around the place here,
No!
Come on, Jake.
You took care of me.
You always took care
of all your men!
No I didn't.
She's all I've got
in the world, Jake.
And... and
I'm all she's got...
Forget about it, Henry.
It ain't gonna happen.
(MEOW)
You all squared away, honey?
Good, I'll be right in.
You... you're nice and warm
in there, my little princess?
(Chuckles)
Yeah.
Good, good.
Uh, you brush your teeth,
did you?
Wash your face and hands
hmm? Everything?
(SIGHS)
You, uh, got your clothes all set up for tomorrow?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah?
I'm okay.
Oh, I know you are.
You know...
...I love you very much.
(SLOW MUSIC)
Now, you know
what you gotta do, right?
Mm-hmm.
I know you're gonna do
a good job.
I know you will.
Yeah.
You're gonna make me very proud.
(WEEPS)
(KISS)
Okay, Lenny.
Okay, now. Okay, Lenny.
Now you be strong,
be real strong, all right?
(FOOTSTEPS)
You know...
...there's not a better
man alive than Jake.
And you can trust me on that.
(HENRY)
You can.
(MALE VOICE WHISPERING)
Look at those cute little kids, man.
A girl, that's all
the wife and I ever talk about.
A cute little girl.
(SMACK)
Good night, honey.
Good night, Daddy.
(HENRY)
Hey, Lenny?
I want you to say
"Good night" to mean old Jake here.
'Night, Lieutenant
Mr. Mean Old Jake.
(BIRD CRIES OUT)
Your dad in the shed...?
Your dad in the outhouse?
Did you hear me?
(SIGHS)
What's the matter?
(WEEPS)
I gotta go find your dad.
(WEEPS LOUDER)
(MUSIC)
Hey...
Hey... shit!
(SHOUTS)
Henry!!
Ow!
(SHOUTS)
Henry!
Where is he?!
He's gone!
What do you mean he's gone?
He left me here!
He left me here with you!
I... I...
when... when did he leave?
(WEEPS LOUDLY)
Ergh!
Oh, Christ!
Hey, let's go!
(SHOUTS ANGRILY, CRYING)
No!
Too bad!
(CRYING)
What hospital is he going to?
I don't know!
Goddamn it to hell!
(CRYING)
(SHOUTS)
Stop it!
(CRYING)
- Ice cream, you want some ice cream?
- No!
- What about one of them cheeseburger things?
This is a damn sheer waste
of my time.
Hey, what are you doing?!
I'm leaving!
And you can't stop me!
Hey! Hey! Wait!
Hey, stop! Hey, hey!
Hey!!
(CAR HONKS)
(JAKE)
Hey!
(LENNY)
Let go!
(JAKE)
No wonder your dad left you!
(LENNY)
No wonder your wife left you!
How did you...!
Why you little...!
Let go!
Let me go!
The truth is...
...she left me 'cause she wanted a
bunch of pain-in-the-ass kids like you
and I didn't!
(SHOUTS)
I don't like you!
And so what?
I don't like me either.
(LOUD THUD)
Get, get on.
Now I have to wait (INDISTINCT).
Get!
You better fix yourself
something to eat.
When your dad comes back and you're...
...dead because you ain't ate nothin'
it ain't my fault.
(LENNY, ANGRILY)
I can't cook.
Henry says you can cook!
(LENNY)
Only a little.
Jello.
Well, if you can find
the chicken that lays the jello egg,
you can cook it.
You yelled at me.
Get used to it!
(SOFT MUSIC)
Lieutenant.
Those kids...
- what if something happened to 'em, they're right in the line of fire?
- Shoot 'em all, cherry boy.
They're gooks and they're gook.
What?
Ain't no big thing.
Go to hell. Lieutenant,
I've got a bad feeling...
Get over it.
- Sir...
- Don't be a pussy Gardner.
Sir, we can't do this!
Shut up!
Let's rock 'n roll!
(SHOOTING)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
(WEEPING)
There aren't any seat belts.
Any what?
Seat belts.
We have to have seat belts.
We don't need
no damn seat belts.
(MUSIC)
(SIGHS)
Where we going?
Never you mind.
(PHONE RINGING)
(CLICK)
(SHOUTS)
Yeah, hello?
(RECORDED)
The number you have reached is not in service.
Please check the number
or try your call again.
Damn it!
(SHOUTING)
And damn you Henry!!
(CAWS)
You shouldn't wander off
too far by yourself.
I got some mean-ass
neighbors that hates kids.
They eat 'em whole.
Swallow 'em up
in one bite, they do.
It's time for you
to start earning your keep.
Get some feed
and feed the critters.
(MUSIC)
(SCREAMS)
For Christ's sakes!
Never mind.
(SIGHS)
(CRICKETS)
(SOFTLY HUMMING)
(SOFT MUSIC)
(SHOUTS ANGRILY)
Give me that!
Leave my stuff alone!
(SOFTLY WEEPING)
(WEEPS LOUDER)
(GRUNTS)
(SHOUTS ANGRILY)
Go away!
(WEEPING)
(THUD)
(BELL TINKLES)
Well, who's this little angel?
Her name is Lenny,
she be gone any day now.
Hi, Lenny.
My name is Kate.
You got my supplies?
Where you from, Lenny?
(JAKE)
Hey, we gotta get going.
Would you mind?
Uh...
Can I get something to eat now?
Hell no, you shoulda eaten
at the house.
(SIGHS)
You just help yourself,
anything you want.
It's on the house.
You shoulda asked me first.
Ask you? What?
You mean have a real
honest-to-God conversation?
Ask you, my ass.
No, not enough.
It's been getting tougher
to fill your order for 20 bucks a box.
$25?
Done.
Next time.
Is there change
for a phone call?
(METAL CLINKING)
This good?
Sure.
Here, here.
There you go.
Thanks.
So Lenny...
...where are your parents?
My mom's in heaven,
my dad...
left.
(SIGHS)
(KATE)
Oh.
You know people
in heaven too, don't you?
Yes, I do.
They love you even more
when they get to heaven, you know.
No matter what.
(JAKE)
Come on, let's go.
(LENNY)
That lady was nice.
(JAKE)
If you say so.
You better put on
your rain gear.
What?
Your coat, put it on.
I don't have one.
What?
What have you got
in that damn back pack?
Crayons,
a coloring book,
and a doll.
Damn it! You should have
brought some rain gear!
You're yelling at me.
Yeah you're damn right I am! You're
gonna catch a death of cold out here!
Sorry.
Never go into these woods
without at least
taking a jacket!
'kay.
Maybe next time
you'll tell me where we're going.
(SIGHS)
What's that for?
I'm helping some friends.
What's their names?
Don't know.
You don't know
your friends' names?
Nope.
Well, then how do you know
they're your friends?
There are some things
you just know.
Come on.
(GRUNTING)
Help me load this wood.
(LENNY)
Well, where do they live?
Out here, in the woods.
How'd you meet 'em?
Never met 'em.
Just heard they were
living out here,
so one day, I decided to
leave them a surprise.
How come?
I just thought maybe
it'd be good
that they know
somebody cared about 'em,
and was thinking about 'em.
And the next thing I knew,
they were leaving wood in return.
Well, how come
they live in the woods?
Some people just like
living by themselves.
Why?
(SHOUTS)
Because they just do!
You stay in the truck
and stop talkin',
you're wearing my ears out.
(MUSIC)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
Can I get out here?
I suppose.
(LENNY)
Cool, a cave!
(JAKE)
Hey, not exactly.
Old mining tunnel.
Come on... we'll take
some of this wood back to the truck.
Can I go inside it?
No!
Watch out. Come on, I'm freezing.
(SLOW MUSIC)
What's wrong, Jake?
Nothing.
(RAIN FALLING)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(CREAKING OPEN)
(CREAKING SHUT)
(SLAMS)
(WATER DRIPPING)
Shoo, shoo!
Here, git! Git!
(CAT MEOWS)
If you're not eating,
I'm not eating.
Does...
blue go with orange?
(JAKE)
I'm not so good with colors.
(JAKE HUMS)
Sorry for yelling.
Okay.
Sorry for... for throwing things
at you.
And for going
through your stuff.
And for not having
any rain gear.
And for making a mess of...
Stop.
Stop while you're ahead.
Okay.
(MEOWS)
What's the cat's name?
Cat.
Just Cat?
Yup.
What's the dog's name?
Dog.
Oh.
What do you call the chickens?
Chickens?
No.
Ladies.
Most of the time, anyway.
My daddy gave me a doll.
Her name is Annie,
but I'm gonna call her Doll.
(MUSIC)
(SIZZLING)
Sorry.
No, no, no, you're doing good,
it's the egg shape,
you're doing good.
Okay.
Mmm mm mmm...
(CHUCKLES)
Maybe we need to put
this in for a little longer,
let it cook on the
other side a little bit.
Lay it down gentle like,
a dog will sometimes turn on
you and bite when it's chowing down.
Most dogs anyway.
Let's go, ladies.
Hey, this is how you do it.
Will they bite too?
No,
but they won't eat
out of your hand.
They don't trust you.
(LAUGHS)
They tickle.
(SIGHS)
Let's go, we gotta feed the birds.
(CHUCKLES)
(CAW)
(LENNY)
Ooh, what a big black bird.
It's a raven.
"Follow a raven
into the shadow,"
"and you will
find the light."
That's from an old Indian
medicine man.
What does it mean?
They say the raven
brings people courage.
He's a symbol of healing.
Do you believe that?
There's not much
I believe in anymore, Lenny.
(CAW)
Do you feed it too?
Oh, be damned if I know.
I guess so,
but I've never seen it eat.
It just sits there in that tree.
(CAW)
It's pretty.
That it is.
You got running away
out of your system?
(LENNY)
Jake, look!
It's a beach!
That's where we headed.
Yes!
(MUSIC)
It's the best dinner I've ever had.
I can't even believe
we caught all this ourselves.
Mm-mm-mm.
Is this what your friends eat?
In the woods?
You know, I'm not so sure
what they eat,
but I bet it ain't this fancy.
Hey!
We should invite 'em
to go to the beach with us!
Then take them back here
and cook them dinner.
What?
Why would we do that?
'Cause that's what friends do.
Is that right?
Mm-hmm.
They wouldn't come.
Then we should go to them.
Let's have a picnic!
(SIGHS)
I'm not so sure
that's a good idea.
Wipe your mouth.
Why not?
Well, first of all,
they might not want
to have anything to do with us.
And plus, maybe I don't want
anything to do with them.
Maybe I'm happy
the way things are.
You don't seem very happy to me.
Everybody's happy at a picnic!
I'll do all the work, I promise.
(SIGHS)
(CLICK)
(GUITAR MUSIC)
♪ In this dirty old part ♪
♪ of the city ♪
♪ Where the sun ♪
♪ refuses to shine ♪
♪ People tell me ♪
♪ there ain't no use in trying ♪
♪ My little girl, ♪
♪ you're so young and pretty ♪
♪ And one thing ♪
♪ I know is true ♪
It looks good enough to eat.
(LAUGHTER)
I'm having fun.
You having fun, Jake?
Hmm.
(LOUD MUSIC)
You think they know we're here?
Nothing happens in these
woods they don't know about.
Besides, there ain't
a living thing in this valley
that can't smell
this food cooking.
(LOUDER MUSIC)
(CHUCKLES)
(FAINT MUSIC)
Do you hear what I'm hearing?
Sounds like somebody's
having a party.
(LOUD MUSIC)
(HAPPY GIGGLES AND MUSIC)
(MUSIC STOPS)
Nobody came.
I didn't really expect them.
Hey.
- Hey.
- Hey!
Uh, Neeley.
Oh yeah, I'd recognize
that truck anywhere.
(MAN)
Thank you, bro.
Welcome home.
You too, my man, you too.
- Mitchell. Chopper, '68.
- Grunt, '67.
This here's Lenny.
Lenny!
It is indeed my pleasure, ma'am.
(LENNY)
(GIGGLES)
Can I interest you in a beer?
Oh yes sir, you can,
you most certainly can.
We got some dead cow,
a chicken or two.
Yeah, my wife said
she smelled yard bird on the grill.
(CHUCKLES)
Ohhhh.
Goddamn it,
look at all this food.
It never crossed my mind that
any of you'd have a woman.
She's welcome too.
Oh, well, uh...
Cyd, she don't like
to leave the house much.
- Mind if I bring one of these back to her?
- Oh, help yourself.
Hey, Dinky,
get your arse out here!
Chickenshit!
Probably slobbering
all over himself from the smell,
but he hasn't got the guts
to come out on his own.
How many more of you
are out here?
Around here?
Well, there's, uh, Dinky and
Red and, oh and then there's
some other vets out in the deep woods,
we trade with them
every once in a while.
Dinky!
Come and get a brewsky!
Oh, there he is.
(JAKE)
Booby trap?
(MITCHELL)
Oh, no, no, he was running down an elk
fell and busted his leg,
he set it hisself but, uh,
it never did mend right,
did it, Dink?
(DINKY)
No, damn thing.
- Hey.
Marines, '70.
'67, Army.
Go on and get yourself
some grub, Dinky.
Who's the little kid?
Lenny.
Kid of a buddy of mine.
Looks like a gook.
Yeah.
Her real name is Lee.
She was born in uh...
her mom was a gook.
She was Vietnamese.
(JAKE)
Uh, yes, you're right. She was Vietnamese.
I'll be damned.
Lenny, these guys
were in Vietnam too.
Hi, girl.
How you doing?
You remember the word for crazy?
(FOREIGN TERM)
Tìm cái đầu
(DINKY)
You got it! (LAUGHTER)
Hell, honey, that's his name too!
Dinky-dod.
He's as crazy as they come!
Oh, don't shake
her arm off, Dink.
She could be my granddaughter.
(LAUGHS)
Sure is a pretty
little thing, ain't she?
Less talk and I've
got to get me a beer.
You know,
you and Lenny
should come and meet my wife.
She was a nursing nun,
used to hang out at
them orphanages and shit.
I got a lot of respect
for nurses.
So, who's Red?
Red? Well...
...he's one of us, sort of, uh,
...he lives closest
to your place.
He's watching us right now,
you can bet on that.
Can you get him to come out?
Maybe... maybe not.
He's, uh, got
kind of a short fuse.
Gotta be careful with him.
He's got so many booby traps around this
place I don't even go over there anymore.
'Fraid I'll get myself blowed all to hell.
(CHUCKLES)
That don't make him a bad guy.
Oh no, that's true enough.
I don't think he heard us
talking about your little girl there, so
it should be all right.
Is she a problem?
She could be.
(MITCHELL)
Might wanna keep your eye on her.
Got it.
(MITCHELL)
Hey, Red?
Red?
Got food!
Is that him?
(MITCHELL)
Oh, yeah.
He don't talk any.
That's just the way he is.
Might be he don't have much to say.
That could be but
funny thing is I ain't
never heard Red make a sound.
Not so much as a peep.
Walking body bag, that one.
He died in the Nam.
How you doing, Red?
Thanks for the grub, Jake.
(JAKE)
It was all Lenny's idea.
(DINKY)
Thank you, Lenny.
(JAKE WHISPERS)
Lenny.
You're welcome,
Mr. Dinky-dau.
(FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
- (SPITS)
- (SCREAMS AND SHOUTS)
(MITCHELL)
And you go! Go on!
(LOUD CRYING AND SCREAMING)
Hey! Hey! What the hell
is his problem, huh?
(MITCHELL)
Some gook little girl pulled a pin on a grenade
and threw it at him,
and blew half his face off.
Aw shit!
That ain't right!
That ain't right at all!
(SCREAMING AND CRYING)
(MUMBLES)
(JAKE)
Need reinforcements!
Radio! Radio!
Get Six on the phone!
Tell him we got heavy
automatic weapon fire!
Shit! Get down!
(WHISTLING)
(EXPLOSION)
(GUNSHOTS)
Shit!
Gardner!
Take out the hooch!
- Gardner!
- There's kids in there!
- They're killing us! Do it!
- But I...
- Now!
- No sir!
That's a direct order, Private!
(GUNSHOTS)
(LENNY)
Made you some supper.
Give it to Dog.
Yes, sir.
(SIGHS)
(THUNDER AND RAIN)
(BOTTLE CLANKS)
Where's my boots?
I always leave 'em
next to my chair, they're not there.
(SHOUTING)
Lenny! Answer me, goddamn it!
What the hell...?
Why are my boots under your bed?
I told you
to leave my stuff alone!
(WOOD SQUEAKING)
(THUDS)
(GRUNTS)
(KATE)
We're closed!
It's Jake Neeley!
- What brings you out?
- I need something to drink!
How about some coffee?
How about you give up
playing the social worker
and get me some whiskey?
How about you kiss my ass?
Hmm.
I only have beer and wine,
I'm not selling any to you.
I don't want no damn coffee, heh.
All right, where is it, huh?
Hey!
Knock it off!
All right, you want
to tell me what's going on
or do I call the cops
and have your ass hauled in?
I can't do this anymore.
She shouldn't be with me.
What do I know
about taking care of a kid?
I figured he'd be back
to get her,
but it's been weeks now.
He could be dead for all I know.
- Dead?
- Yeah.
He has lung cancer.
No relatives?
None that I could find.
Her mother's dead.
She should be in school!
Where is she now?
At my place.
You left her alone?
She's sleeping.
Probably.
Oh crap.
Maybe she should stay here.
With me.
What?
Well, you'd still be
taking care of her,
she'd just be staying here
with me.
You'd do that?
Why?
Well, certainly not for you.
She's a very special
little girl.
Yeah.
Well, think it over.
And now, if you are done
trashing the place,
would you like a cup of joe?
(MUSIC)
You take cream or...?
Hey!
Put it on my bill.
(EXASPERATED)
Ohh!
Why did that man spit on me?
Listen kid,
I'm not gonna explain
some damn thing to you
that you'd
never understand anyhow!
You're mean.
You think so?
Huh?
Well, fine!
Well, you won't have to
listen to mean old Jake
cussing and yelling anymore!
Tomorrow I'm taking you
to Kate's!
- What?
- I've had enough!
You're gonna stay at Kate's
until your dad comes back!
- No!
- Yes!
I'm not going!
I'm not going
and you can't make me!
(WEEPING)
Oh!
Jesus!
Lenny?
Let's go.
Time to pack your things.
Lenny?
(MUSIC)
Damn it.
Damn it to hell!
(BIRDS CHIRPING AND MUSIC)
Lenny!!
(REPEATED ECHO)
Damn it.
Lenny!!
Damn.
(GUNSHOT)
Lenny!!
(MUSIC)
Hey Lenny!!
Lenny!!
Lenny!
Answer me!
(SOLDIER)
Lieutenant, I got a bad feeling.
(MALE VOICE)
Dead gook's a good gook.
(GUNFIRE)
(JAKE)
Gardner, what the hell is wrong with you?
- I'm not killing any kids!
- I'm giving you a direct order, Private!
Take out that hooch!
- No!
- Damn you!
Give me that!
I'll do it! Agh!
Lieutenant!
(DRY SNAP)
(GASPS)
(JAKE)
You gotta do it, Gardner!
Shoot!
Now!
- (GUNSHOTS)
- Agh!
Agh!
Oh God!
I'm hit!
I didn't mean
to do anything wrong!
(JAKE)
Goddamn you sons of bitches!
I'm sorry! I...
(SCREAMS)
(LENNY)
Help.
Help me, please!
(LENNY)
No!
I'm not the girl who hurt you!
Lenny!!
Jake!!
(LENNY)
I'm over here!
Jake!
Hurry!
(JAKE)
Lenny!
(LENNY)
Jake!
Lenny.
(GRUNTING AND STRAINING)
- Lenny!
- (LENNY SCREAMS)
Hold on!!
Jake!
Hold on, Lenny!
Grab the branch!
Grab it Lenny!
Can you use both hands?
I don't know, I'm scared!
Go ahead, okay
now hold on tight!
(LENNY)
Don't drop me!
I... won't,
I won't!
Give me your hand!
Aghhh!
Oh!
Hey, you okay?
Who was shooting?
I don't know.
What happened?
I was running, and I slipped.
Damn girl, your dad
would've killed me.
Come here.
Oh! God, don't
scare me like that.
Oh, God.
Don't scare me like that.
Jake...
...my dad's gone.
(WEEPS)
He's not coming back.
He gave me this
the night he left.
He's dead, Jake.
I know it!
- I'm sorry.
(WEEPS)
It's okay.
Everything's okay now.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
I imagine you're pretty tired
with running away and all.
You probably want
to go to bed when you're done there.
Oh no, Jake, I'm wide awake.
See?
Let's fix up my bedroom.
Let's not.
'kay.
Will you read to me?
I don't have anything
you'd like.
What about this one?
Hmm, let's see
what we can find out about the raven.
"Voice... incredibly varied"
(DEEP VOICE)
"With low deep baritone,"
(CROAKING)
"Croaks,"
(HIGH VOICE)
"To high, bear like,"
(FUNNY VOICE)
"Twangy notes."
Kinda poetic, huh?
Oh, sorry. Does your arm
still hurt?
No.
Not at all.
Read.
"Has a long,
hoarse, croooooak."
(DEEP VOICE)
"Lower, hollow croak" (LAUGHTER)
"And deep resonant croaks are typical."
(LAUGHTER)
Shhh.
Go to sleep now.
Good night, Lenny.
Good night, Jake.
(ANXIOUSLY)
I won't do it ever again, I promise.
Don't worry about it.
Doll can have it.
Never really sat right
with me anyhow.
Lenny.
Hmm?
Why did you hide my boots?
So you couldn't leave me.
I won't leave you, Lenny.
Never?
Never.
You better go to sleep now.
'kay.
(KATE)
Put it on his bill, my ass.
(HUMMING)
(MUSIC)
Jake, look!
It's eating.
(JAKE)
That it is.
(MUSIC)
(HAMMERING)
(LAUGHS)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(GASPS)
(CAR APPROACHES)
(DOOR SLAMS)
You got it, Jake?
Ay, hold your horses, girl.
Any problems?
Nope. I fed birds and
ladies and Dog and Cat.
Even Raven came down to eat.
Well, I guess you can sit down
and close your eyes.
- No peeking!
- Okay!
Is it a book?
No.
Is it something for the cabin?
- No.
- (DOOR SLAMS)
Hold out your arms,
it's something...
...just... for... you.
(BLEATS)
Oh my God, it's a baby lamb!
Yes.
(LAUGHTER)
You gave me a baby lamb, Jake!
Yes, it's a baby lamb.
A baby lamb!
(LAUGHTER)
Thank you! Thank you!
You're welcome.
Oh, it's the most
absolutely most wonderful
thing that's ever happened to me!
Well, I know just how you feel.
(SMACKS TWICE)
Oh, cut it out.
(LAUGHTER)
Three, four...
four, five, six,
ten, eleven...
Thank you.
- Hi, Kate!
- Hi.
Oooh, your hair
looks pretty today.
- Thanks.
- Morning.
Yeah, it's pretty.
You have the list, Lenny.
Why don't you start?
Okay.
Umm, listen,
about the other night.
I could come in here
and act like it never happened.
Umm,
and, maybe... a
few weeks back,
I would've done just that.
I'm not the kind of guy
who likes to...
show that side of myself,
so to speak,
none of this happened, let me just...
Oh, please stop,
it was entirely an accident, I...
Is that enough?
Because if it ain't,
just tell me, I'll pay whatever you want.
(MUSIC)
It's been a long time
since I had any.
And, ummm,
I can't even remember
when the last time was
so I'm not up
on prices these days.
Fifteen, twenty, yeah,
whatever, you just tell me the price.
Okay, okay, I'm... I'm...
I'm sorry about taking the wine.
The wine.
And I know I've been
a real horse's ass
over the years
and I... it's difficult to apologize, but
I got something for you.
A peace offering.
Oh!
Well... you shouldn't have.
It's freshly picked.
Thank you.
It's very nice.
Sorry, uh, ten.
Ten's good.
(MUSIC)
Wait, wait, wait!
You forgot this.
Yeah.
He will like that.
(MUSIC)
(KNOCKING)
Hey, Mitch.
Hey, Jake.
(LAUGHTER)
(MUSIC AND CHATTER)
Yeah, Cyd, this here is Jake,
this here is Lenny,
there're the folks
I was telling you about.
You know, had the
barbecue the other day.
Pleased to meet you,
nice to meet you
thanks for all the supplies.
He's been bringing them
all these years.
I drew this.
Ooh!
You're quite an artist.
(GIGGLES)
There's no wood.
(SOBBING)
(LENNY)
How come Red didn't leave any wood?
(JAKE)
I don't know.
Is this the first time
he hasn't left any wood?
Yeah.
Why is he mad at me?
I don't think he's mad at you.
Yes he is.
Red's mixed up.
He needs help.
Can a friend help him?
I don't know hun, maybe.
(BIRDS SINGING)
How come you so quiet?
I don't know.
I think the school bus...
...will stop at the end of the driveway.
I've been thinking maybe
we can build a bench
for Dolly if you want.
Maybe tomorrow.
Okay.
Anything special you want to do?
Go for a walk or something?
I think maybe Lamb
wants to go for a walk.
You want me to go with you?
No.
No, that's okay.
All right.
Don't stray too far.
Okay.
I mean it, stay real close.
I don't want you
to jump off no damn cliff.
(LAUGHS)
(SMACK)
(MUSIC)
(BIRD CRIES OUT)
- (BLEATING)
- Come on.
(CLANKING)
(WOOD SPLITTING)
(BLEATS)
Shhh.
I'm not afraid of you anymore.
(BLEATS)
You want to pet Lamb?
It's okay.
I wanna be your friend.
Lamb, wait!
- (GRUNTS)
- (LENNY SCREAMS)
- (TWANGS)
- (GRUNTS AND GROANS)
(LABORED BREATHING)
Jake!
I'm here, what's wrong?
What is it?
Red!
I told you not to go far!
He's hurt, Jake! He's hurt real bad!
You gotta help him!
Okay!
Jesus! Christ, it's bad.
What... what happened?
Lenny, what happened?
He saved me.
God, I gotta leave it in.
Lenny, I need your help.
Come here!
Push down here
to stop the bleeding.
There, just like I'm doing.
I'm going to Mitchell's
for help.
I... Look, be as brave as
you can. He won't hurt you now.
All right?
Look at me.
You can do it, Lenny.
You can do it.
I'll be right back.
(MUSIC)
It's okay.
Hey! Hey!
Oh, you're so cold.
(JAKE)
Lenny!
I... I was trying
to keep him warm.
(CYD)
He's cold from losing so much blood.
I'll got get him a blanket!
- (GRUNTS)
- Red... Red, lie still!
(JAKE)
Lenny... No!
(EXPLOSION)
Oh my God!
(CYD)
Oh... oh Jesus!
(BLEATS)
No!!!!!
Lenny! Lenny!
No, Lenny! No!
(CRYING)
Cyd! Cyd... you can help her, Cyd!
You can help her!
Lenny... you're gonna be okay.
You're gonna be okay.
You're gonna be okay!
(PANTING)
Come on, come on, Lenny,
gotta get help.
I gotta get help!
Where are we?
Let me go!
Hey, Cyd!
You can help, Cyd!
Somebody help her!
(CYD)
She's gone.
(JAKE CRIES INTENSELY)
Somebody!
(BLEATING)
(CRYING CONTINUES)
(CRYING GROWS FAINT)
(SLOW PIANO MUSIC)
(RAIN FALLING)
(KNOCKING)
(KATE)
Jake?
(KNOCKING)
Jake, you in there?
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(SOFT MUSIC)
(BOARD CREAKING)
(KATE SIGHS)
Don't do this to yourself.
Jake!
I don't give a damn about you.
Give me the same respect,
and leave me the hell alone.
You're just gonna sit here
and rot?
Everything I touch,
turns to shit.
It's better this way,
better for everybody.
No, my ass it is!
(SIGHS)
This wasn't your fault!
You're so damn full of yourself
you think you have that kind of power?
Get the hell out of my house.
Fine.
But you're pathetic.
You don't understand.
Oh, don't I?
You think you're the
only person in the world
who's lost someone they love?
Well, you're not.
I know that.
Do you?
Do you know how my husband died?
No.
Did you know
that I had children, too?
A family?
No.
Then what do you
really know about anything?
Nothing.
They found this
when they cleaned out Red's place.
The chain's broken
but, otherwise it survived.
You know where to find me.
I have a son I never met.
Grown man by now.
Probably hates my guts.
We didn't know she was
pregnant, when we split.
She told me later.
I always wish she...
hadn't told me at all.
What?
Why?
You can't lose something...
if you never had it
to begin with.
What I wouldn't give...
to have
what you're throwing away.
(CREAKING)
(DOOR CLOSING)
(SOFT MUSIC)
(HENRY)
My dad gave it to me,
said it would lead me
where I was meant to go.
I guess it did.
(MUSIC)
(BIRD CRIES OUT)
(CAWS)
(LENNY)
Follow the raven into shadow,
and we will find the light.