Mr. Wilson.
This came for you through
the Carlson cover address.
There was no card.
There's been a potential compromise down south.
Ulysses
We can't wait another 24 hours.
If you can guarantee that all assets are in place
and prepare to move on my order
I'm prepared to move as well.
Go back to bed.
What were you talking about?
It's grown up talk.
I had a nightmare.
Everything's fine.
Can you stay with me another minute?
Try to get some sleep.
Yes
We haven't got time to be sure of this.
This whole thing hinges on support.
If we don't have the support I
can't guarantee the outcome.
I guarantee the support.
That's not a guarantee.
That's not an answer.
unintelligible conversation
Margaret tells us that
you work for the CIA.
My wife has a vivid imagination.
I'm a trade advisor.
Civil servant.
Good night.
How dare you speak to me that way.
Don't ever tell anybody
what I do. How dare you.
You are never to tell anyone
what is that I do.
Never. Do you understand?
Never. What you do?
I don't know what you do.
You leave at 5, you get home at 10
7 days a week.
You don't say a dam word to me.
I live with a ghost.
I don't know what you do.
phone ringing
Call back.
You're ready?
Launch the operation.
Say something.
I have to go now.
Say. Say something.
Talk to me.
Say something.
Look at me. Say something.
Remember what I said.
Don't touch anything.
Merry Christmas Margaret.
Edward.
Merry Christmas.
Is this young Edward?
Would you like to come inside
and meet a very special
guest this evening?
Oh. Santa Claus
Would you like to meet Santa?
Toddy is wonderful with children.
Yes. She is.
Would you like a drink Edward.
Thank you.
I believe congratulations are in order.
The doctor has no more patients.
The cost of malpractice.
Gentlemen.
Edward.
Hello.
Bill.
Gentlemen.
You can all be very proud
of what you've started.
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas Bill.
Say something.
Surprises are the best part of Christmas
Don't you think?
How about, games?
How about, ball games?
Oh!
Can I get you a towel?
I'm, I'm so sorry.
Are you all right?
All right, you poor thing.
I think we should go home.
Lower your voice.
You can use our bathroom if you like.
I might have some dry clothes.
Thank you.
Come with me Edward.
It's all right. Come with me.
Can I help you up Mrs. Wilson?
No.
Did you know that Philipp is going to be
on the Mayan Coffee
Company's board of directors?
Remember what I said
to you about friends?
You look good Edward.
How long has it been?
Seven, eight years?
A lot of water under the bridge.
Carolina and I, we just bought our first house.
And everything is already broken
and I spend my weekends fixing things.
By the time I get everything fixed
it'll be time to sell the fucking house.
Maybe you can give me
a heads up on somebody.
You're asking be to give you FBI files
on an American citizen?
You know I can't do that.
It’s against the law to spy on citizens.
Keep it.
Maybe someday you'll change your mind.
door knocking
May I come in?
You know,  I've never been in your office.
How was the fishing?
It was a bad year.
The water is too high.
I understand you wanted to personally give
me the operation Zapata list yourself.
There isn't one, is there?
You know it was a silent operation.
It wasn't silent enough.
I've been asked, by the President,
to suggest who we no
longer need with us.
Who would you recommend, Edward.
I serve at the pleasure
of the director, sir.
I'm just a gate keeper.
Why is it that people like us
chose to serve
for nickels a day.
In a profession that makes us
constantly look over our shoulder
to see who is watching us.
When will you make your decision?
Decision?
I serve at the discretion of the
President of the United States.
I will do what I think
is best for the country.
It's important that we
find out who's responsible.
Good night.
At 22:42 call received on Berlin
base chief's operational line
man says he is senior officer KGB.
Would not give name.
Open up. Thanks.
KGB officer asked when Mr.
Edward Wilson is coming.
He wants to know Mr.
Edward Wilson's response.
Tell him Mr. Edward Wilson is here
and would like to know what he
intends to provide us with in return.
He says, in return for safe journey
he will provide Mr. Wilson
will clear understanding of
last three losses in Moscow.
and identities of soviet agents in your country,
penetrations of Moscow's station.
Will also speak personally
with Mr. Edward Wilson about
Ulysses.
Things that only he knows of Ulysses.
How he thinks.
What he plans to do.
And what he wants Mr.
Edward to think he is doing.
To establish bonafides, he will carry with him
KGB surveillance photographs
of all CIA officers in Moscow.
I will be more than happy
to take
polygraph.
Ulysses.
Ask him what his weakness is.
The cold.
Let's get him over here.
My name
is Valentin Gregorovich Mironov.
My children's names
are Anatoly and Sergei.
My father played the cello
I play the violin.
But, you know this.
I risk my life to come all
the way to tell you this.
To confirm what you already know.
You failed the polygraph Mr.Mironov.
You know every Russian fails polygraph.
Your polygraph doesn't
understand the Russian soul.
What more do you want?
I've given you my bonafides.
The names of agents.
Who has been compromised.
Who you need to know about.
I wanted to speak to Mr. Edward Wilson.
We were told Mironov was with these men
the day the photo were taken.
We're not even sure that any
of the circled men are him.
I told you these 3 time already.
?????
I want to speak to Mr. Edward Wilson.
I would like some tea.
The isn't any.
I get thirsty when I say too much.
You are going to keep up this
inane questioning for much longer?
There is nothing you've told
us we don’t know, Mr. Mironov.
I think you better try a little harder.
I didn't come here to deal with children,
Mr. Lutz.
Or is it, Mr. Brocco.
We do our homework too.
Hello Mr. Mironov. I'm Mr. Wilson.
Hello.
Mother.
Ulysses is obsessed with you.
Night and day.
You are always on his mind.
He trusts nobody.
The only one whom he lets close,
is his aid.
Sasha.
He is methodical.
He plans things years in advance.
For instance
you should he has developed a friendship with a certain neighbor of yours
Fidel Castro.
A young man.  He has high hopes for him.
I understand you had a most
interesting fish swim your way.
Mr. Allen thought it may be
possible for me to speak with him.
With your chaperon of course.
I brought him a little gift I'm sure he'll appreciate.
Send Mironov immediately.
It'll be nice to be closely
working with you again.
I expect you to show me Washington.
We can paint the town red together.
Valentine Mironov.
Arch Cummings.
It is a great pleasure to meet you.
My pleasure.
Now please sit down.
Nice to have someone like
you on our side of the street.
I thought you may enjoy this.
It's something you might appreciate.
I hope you haven't read it.
Very clever.
Thank you.
All Russian is our orchard.
The land is great and beautiful.
There are many wonderful places in it.
Think Anya.
Your grandfather.
Your great grandfather.
This is very bad translation.
It is much funnier in Russian.
I'm due at a meeting.
Are you Laura?
What?
Are you Laura? I'm suppose
to offer you a ride.
Hello Edward.
Hello Laura.
Why all the mystery?
Do you have children?
I have a boy.
Edward Jr.
Do you have anybody?
A cat.
I often imagine what my life
would have been like with you.
And what do you imagine?
I thought you might teach.
Probably poetry.
I saw us living in a small college town.
You once said to me you were afraid
your life was already
planed out for you.
Are you doing what you want to do?
Life has been full of surprises.
You owe me a day at the beach.
How long do you think you'll be.
As long as it takes.
I think maybe I'll go ahead.
All right.
Mother?
There's an envelope for you on the desk.
Hey, you look lovely.
Thank you.
It's not enough that you
ignore me our whole life
you have to humiliate me?
You disgust me.
Your disgusting.
Let’s start from the last ?????
Mother forgot some of her things.
I'll see you at home.
Are you Laura?
Yes.
I was asked to give you this.
In an unprecedented effort
to improve US-Soviet ties
premier Khrushchev began his 10
day tour of the United States today.
The visit will start with a tour by President
Eisenhower of our nation's capital...
All right. Now set it down.
It's perfect.
Our glee club has been chosen to
compete in the national competition.
Won't you come with me?
Would you like me to?
Very much.
I'll get your things.
It's good to have you home.
How was your trip?
As smooth as silk.
Why FBI escort made the
trip her very pleasant.
Which one is your son?
Top row. Third from the right.
He's a handsome young
man. My congratulations.
We're particularly concerned about Cuba.
Your friend.
He's too close to home.
You don't appreciate him
breathing down your neck.
If we continue down this road.
There will be a third World War.
I don't think either
of us wants a real war.
What would you do for a living then?
If he keeps calling attention to himself
at some point
we might be forced to
send him a surprise.
and I don't want that to come
as a surprise to your people.
He is very important to us.
We would not like to be surprised.
Be well.
I am today
announcing my candidacy
for the presidency of the United States.
The presidency is the most powerful office
in the free World.
Through its leadership
can come a more vital life
for all of our people.
In it are centered the
hopes the globe around us
for freedom and a more secure life.
Senator Kennedy, if you don't
win the presidential nomination,
will you accept the vice presidency.
I shall not, under any condition,
be a candidate for vice president.
If I fail in this endeavor I shall return
and serve in the United States Senate.
We have a secure
?????, Stockholm Station.
Station reports they have a coronel,
directorate K, counter intelligence.
Do we have a name?
May I help you sir?
I'm a coronel with KGB requesting asylum.
What is your name?
My name is Valentin Gregorovich Mironov.
This other man who says he is Valentin Mironov
is not who he pretends to be.
Right? His real name is Yuri Modin.
He was Ulysses right hand
he is Ulysses'....
Will you just tell me your real name.
It is just Ulysses trying to discredit me.
My real name is Valentin
Gregorovich Mironov.
I was born in Brabusk in 1924.
Attended the State Institute of International Relations.
Served for 3 years in naval intelligence.
My wife's name is Tamara Nakovsky.
My children's name are Anatoly and Sergei.
My father is a cellist, I play the violin.
All I want is my freedom.
Pick him up.
Are you alright?
I'm sorry.
You see what you made me do?
Now just
tell me the truth.
Because, we're going to be here
as long as it takes.
I already told you.
I want to know
the truth.
Tell me
You know may name.
your real name.
Mr.  Please. I'm not lying.
I'd like to believe you
but I don’t believe
you. You understand?
Now tell me your name.
My name is Mironov.
It's Valentin Gregorovish Mironov.
Is that your name?
Yeah.
Is that your real name.
Yes. This is my name.
Tell me your real name.
I told you my name.
Tell me your name.
I told you a 100 times...
Because we're not going anywhere
I just want you to know that
we are not going anywhere
Today, tomorrow, next week, next month
He is your mold, I'm not your mold.
You understand?
I'll be right in front of you.
The same position.
What is your name?
Tell me your name.
Tell it.
Tell it to me.
Tell it to me again.
Tell me your fucking name.
Shut up! Shut up!
Tell me your name.
Tell
me
your
fucking
name.
Tell me your name.
Come on. Get it off. Get it off.
Put him down.
Your name.
Tell me your name.
What is your name?
Sir, this is Lysergic acid diethylamide.
It's called LSD.
We've had some very favorable
results as a truth serum.
signing in Russian
speaking Russian
Soviet power it a myth.
A freak show.
There are no spare parts
nothing is working, nothing
it's nothing but painted rust.
But you.
You need to keep the Russian myth alive
to maintain your military
industrial complex.
Your system depends on Russia being perceived
as a mortal threat.
It's not a threat.
It was never a threat
it will never be a threat.
It is
a rotted
bloated
cow.
I am
Valentin Gregorovish Mironov.
And I am
free.
Shit.
If you would like
I'd be willing to take
the truth serum at once.
I've nothing to hide.
I am who I say I am.
I know.
We sent those who are leaving us
to go into the World, with the knowledge
wherever they go
whatever they do
They will never be alone.
They will always be one of us.
And we sing
Bonesmen, all here.
All here.
singing
I didn't know you smoked.
There are a few things
you don't know about me.
I've spoken to a recruiter here.
I would like, very much, to join CIA.
There a lot of things you can do, Edward.
I'd like you to think about this carefully.
I have thought about it very carefully.
It's what I want to do
I want to join the agency.
I want to make you proud of me.
I am proud of you.
Well I've made up my mind father.
You can stop him.
He doesn't understand what he's getting into
you can stop him.
I can't tell him what to do.
Yes you can.
No.
Yes you can because
he is doing it for you.
Because he wants you to be proud of him
and he wants to feel closer to you.
You can have them rejected him.
Absolutely not. I won't do that to him.
Of course you won't.
You won't do anything for anyone but yourself.
That is unfair.
Unfair.
You abandon people when
they need you the most.
I don't abandon people.
You abandon people.
I do not abandon people.
It's true.
I've stood by you.
Stood by me?
For 22 to years I've stood by you.
You don't what it is to stand by somebody.
I've stood by you and I've stood by him.
You ignored him.
I've done everything to
be a good father to him.
You have done no such thing.
I married you because of him.
I know you don't love me.
But you love him.
And no matter what
you should stand by him
and you should protect him.
I don’t need you to tell me
I have to protect my son.
Promise me that you will protect him.
I'll protect him.
Today, in Havana, Fidel Castro expelled
high profile crime figures from Cuba.
He's taking control of their hotels and casinos.
Popular vacation destinations
for many Americans.
Castro has nationalized over a billion dollars
from US businesses in the past six months.
And there is not telling what the communist dictator
I want to see a man about a hat.
He had 3 casinos down there
until Castro sent them home.
These people know how to be discreet.
With the right encouragement, he could help.
And he's very patriotic.
Jimmy.
Mr. Carlson.
Tina. The kids.
Alright. Come on kids.
Sit down.
Some water, some coffee, whatever?
Is there someplace else we could go.
All right daddy. We're going down to
the beach. We'll be back in a while.
Make sure they don't go into the
water unless somebody is watching them.
No, I'm going to let them down.
Make sure they put their shoes
on. They'll burn their feet.
Yea. We're getting their shoes.
All right come on. Let’s go.
So, what do you want
to talk to me about?
The government is about to deport
you, for certain activities.
I've been in this country
since I'm two months old.
What’s that make me. Italian?
I'm American.
And they are trying to send me back?
They can have the deportation order reviewed.
Have you classified as highly sensitive
for national security.
I can take the government off
your back it you can help us.
You are the guys that scare me.
You're the people that make big wars.
No. We make sure the wars
are small ones, Mr. Palmi.
Let me ask you something.
We Italians, we got our
families and we got the church.
The Irish, they have the homeland.
The Jews, their tradition.
Even the niggers. They've got their music.
What about you people, Mr. Carlson?
What do you have?
The United States of America.
The rest of you are just visiting.
The president wants the noise
level on the operation turned down.
How many men are involved?
Fifteen hundred.
Tell them we are going instead to Bahia de Cochinos.
Noise level will be way down.
See you inside.
Could you hear what
we were talking about?
No. I didn't hear anything.
If something was heard.
It has to stay in this room.
Oh, I know that, father.
All right.
Bonesmen.
All here.
Agency first.
God second.
Thank you Lord.
For bringing us here safely here
to be with our brothers
and loved ones again.
Our prayers are with our brothers
whom God has seen fit to take
into his gentle arms this year.
The honorable Senator
John Russell Senior.
Mr. Stephen Lummis Evans.
Would you like to dance Clover?
I haven't been Clover for a long time.
I'm going to Phoenix
to live with my mother.
Based on the ringing of the church bells
we're going to assume the recording was made
at the same time the photograph was taken.
We've check the schedules for
flights leaving major airports
at or around 10 o'clock at
night for a two week period.
There were flights leaving nine cities.
Six were places that would also
potentially have a fan made in Belgium.
Five of those places were also either
tropical or in their summer seasons.
Three of those were places
where French is spoken.
We think the tape was made in either
Dakar,  Abidjan or Congo Leo.
It is all gone.
Hello mother.
Let me show you.
As you see, no cameras,
no tape recorders.
There is nothing else to know.
Can I play something for you?
Everything is a secret.
?????
What was such a big secret
that his own son couldn't know?
He was standing outside talking.
I heard something I wasn't supposed to,
and he knew I'd listened his conversation.
I heard him say something in Spanish.
Bahia de Cochinos.
I'm afraid of him.
Your are safe here with me.
People who really love each
other don't have secrets.
I have something for you.
I love you so much.
She's been an active asset
of ours for some time.
Until now.
She loves your son.
Sometimes even
spies fall in love.
We can protect him.
Make him safe.
Nobody would know. Not even him.
All it would require is for you
to help us.
When your help is needed.
I thought you would like to see this.
She is a very pretty girl.
It is easy to see why he fell for her.
I know it is an extremely
difficult situation for you.
But I am afraid I'm going to need your answer very soon.
You must decide
what is of more importance to you
your country or
or your son.
She is not who you think she is.
She's not a friendly, Edward.
I don't believe you.
Why should I believe you?
You told me yourself not to trust anybody.
You're the master of creating the truth.
I love her.
I've asked her to marry me.
I will not let you
take that away from me.
I can't protect you anymore.
I can't keep you safe.
Safe?
I never felt safe.
I was always frighten.
I always lived in fear that something
awful was going to happen to you.
Or if not, to mother or to me.
I was always afraid because
everything was a secret.
Edward.
Hello, may I come in.
Yes, of course.
Is everything all right?
I was on my way home from work
and I had this overwhelming desire
to hear you play the violin.
Play the violin?
Edward, I am so tired.
Can't this way until tomorrow?
I'd appreciate it if you played it now.
Now.
I just wanted to hear something
from you that was true.
He was careless.
FBI.  You're under arrest. Stand up.
Didn't learn how to hide in plain sight.
Where are they taking me?
I can't go home.
You know they can trust me anymore.
You know what they will do to me?
Sorry Edward.
I truly did like you.
In another world we actually
would have been quite good friends.
Hey.  Are you still there mother?
Your worst fear has come true.
Alone and friendless.
Without a country of your own.
We have a whole new place to fight over.
The stars.
Your offer.
I have to decline.
You've succeeded in stopping
us from taking back Cuba.
The damage is done.
There is no need for you to hurt my son.
Let’s just leave it between you and me.
Very well.
I will wait.
But there will come a time
when I will ask you with a problem
that wouldn't cost you much
but would be of some value to me.
You never know what
the future will bring.
Friends can be enemies
and enemies friends.
This girl.
Neither of us can be sure about her.
But she's about to be
a part of your family.
I believe in family.
You want her to be a
part of your family.
Don't you?
It was good to see you.
We will talk again.
My dear friend.
speaking Russian
Sorry to bother.
I want to buy a little
souvenir to my daughter.
They have no change.
speaking Russian
What does it cost?
Here. It's a gift.
Regards from the United
States government.
It's a cardinal rule to
be generous in a democracy.
Thank you.
So where is she?
We are going to meet her at the church.
I can't wait to meet her.
Yes. That's good.
Come on in.
Hello Margaret.
Well let's celebrate.
I'll get some champagne
How was the flight?
It was long.
How do you like living in Phoenix.
It's the first time I've slept in years.
Here we go.
To your happiness.
Your wife.
What have you done.
Will you go inside mother?
You can go inside, mother.
Please, just go in the church.
She's pregnant.
You can't know the difference.
No.
I love you.
I love you so much.
Mr. Wilson?
Mr. Hayes.
You've been here before Mother?
No I haven't.
Who's idea was that?
It's classified.
Mr. Allen has notified
the President he'll resign.
Something about Swiss bank accounts.
Where did these come from?
They were in the car.
I thought you had them sent down, sir.
Seems the greedy bastard has
been hiding money away for years.
Whoever had the statementsm
sent it to him in a box of Swiss chocolates.
Wasn't you, was it.
The President asked me to become director
and do a complete
housecleaning at my discretion.
I need someone I can trust.
After all, we're still brothers.
This building doesn't get built without you.
Your're CIA's heart and soul.
Who knows.
You might have a secret about
me in that safe of yours.
This whole wing
will be your part of the World.
Counter intelligence.
Take a look around. I've
got an oversight meeting.
Can you imagine?
They think they can look into our closet.
As if we'll let them.
I remember a senator once asked me,
when we talk about CIA
why we never use the
work THE in front of it.
And I asked him,
do you put the work THE in front of God?
They are right what they said about me.
I was weak.
A coward.
I compromised myself
My honor, my family.
My country.
I am ashamed of myself.
To my wife.
I'm sorry I've done this to you.
To my son.
I hope you will grow to be a courageous man.
A good husband.
A good father.
I hope whatever you decide to do
you lead a good full life.
I hope whatever your dreams may be,
come true.
Your loving husband and father.