Well first I want to say that there
the will not be under any condition
be an intervention in Cuba
by Unites States armed forces.
This government will do
everything it possibly can
and I think it can meet
it's responsibilities
to make sure that there are no
Americans involved in any actions
inside Cuba.
Excuse me sir.
Do you have change for a dollar?
Thank you sir.
You're welcome
From our friends on Wall Street.
Miami?
Right away.
Cardinal is interested.
So the weatherman says
Sunday is the perfect day
for a trip to the beach.
I hope you can still dance Edward.
In a couple of days we will be doing
the cha cha in El Comandante's bedroom.
I'll try to remember to bring
my dancing shoes, Richard.
Good morning Ray.
Mr. Hayes.
Miami.
And our Op center off Guatemala.
Pack a bathing suit Mr. Brocco.
We're going for a swim.
What do you make of
our chances for success?
If we get the support
that we've been promised
I'd say it's fairly certain.
But if there are any doubts
I can still put out the fire.
It's gone beyond that.
Rocking chair is still smiling.
door knock
It's the White House.
Everybody is waiting for the good news.
Godspeed!
When your back
come up to the mountains.
We'll go fishing.
Yes sir.
He's been put on notice.
In Cuba,
sometime before dawn,
The invading forces' B-26 bombers
give air cover to men
landing on the beach.
As the sun rises
there is a surprised attack
from Castro's air force.
The B-26s are shot down.
Without air cover, the anti-Castro
forces' ships are attacked.
And the men are cut
off from their supplies.
The situation looks dire.
Where is the air support!
Where the hell is the Navy.
Would you throw something into
this vital point of the battle.
Enemy in red trucks
coming from red beach
are right now 1 km from blue beach.
Two thousand militia
attacking blue beach
from east to west.
We need
close air support immediately!
Well, I am destroying all my
equipment and communications.
I have nothing with which to fight.
I'm going to the woods.
I cannot wait for you.
They knew where to find us.
There's a stranger in our house.
I love you.
People who really love each
other don't have secrets.
You are safe here with me.
I love you.
People who really love each
other don't have secrets.
You are safe here with me.
unintelligible conversation
I love you.
People who really love each
other don't have secrets.
You are safe here with me.
The president is saying they're going
to break the CIA into a thousand pieces.
Somebody on your desk
gave away the store.
Told the Soviets where to
find you at the Bay of Pigs.
You've got a problem very close to home.
There will be an extensive house
cleaning on your side of the street.
Fucking cigarette.
Are there any regulars
that can fit me anymore?
They didn't get it all.
I'm sorry.
Be careful.
Your name is on a must worry list.
Right at the very top.
You forgot your hat.
Somebody left a package
at my doorstep last night.
Have tech wash them right away.
I've been trying to reach you.
Well, I haven't been staying
at the compound. ?????
I heard there was a setback.
Sometimes the best laid
plans of mice and men.
Be very careful.
I'll be fine. You worry too much.
Just please be careful.
Everything is fine.
Goodbye son.
Goodbye father.
music
singing
Ms. Buttercup.
Skull and Bones. Accept or reject?
Accept.
Not a word to anyone.
How does it feel being a woman.
Why do you want to know?
laughter
Gentlemen!
I will remind you
you've all taken an oath
of secrecy.
You have been chosen
to become members of
America's most secret society.
For over a hundred years
Skull and Bones members
have included a president,
vice presidents,
Supreme Court justices,
congressmen and senators,
captains of science and industry.
The very best of America.
secret oath in Latin
cheering
Come on!
I don't think this is for me.
You can't take it personally.
Getting pissed on is
personal Mr. Russell.
So I take it very personal.
Edward!
We're all in this together.
Come back inside.
We're brothers for life.
Tell us Mr. Wilson, brother to brother
something you've never
told anyone before.
Your most guarded secret.
Something you will
need to trust us with.
It was the 4th of July, 1925.
I was six.
I was playing tag with a friend of mine.
and I tried to get away from him
so I ran up the stairs
into my parents room.
And I hid in a closet.
I looked at my father's clothes
and hanging there was
his admirals jacket.
And then I heard a sound.
and I saw my father
and I must have made a
noise because he turned
and came into the closet
and opened the door.
Have you ever made up a story Edward?
Told your friends something
you knew wasn't true?
And you know that if they found out...
they wouldn't like you anymore.
Why?
Because you lied to them.
You understand?
And he asked me if I knew was trust was.
And I said... trust is when
you feel safe with someone.
Like with my friends.
Like with you and mother.
And then he said.
Don't ever lie.
You shouldn't lie to your friends.
They won't trust you.
And you will have nothing.
And you'll never be safe.
He told me to go downstairs
and watch the fireworks.
Because they'd started.
And then he shut the door.
The sound of the gunshot was very
different from the sound of the fireworks.
And even at six years old I new
there was a big big difference.
There was a lot of blood.
Father?
And in his left hand he held a note
that was sealed.
I don’t know why, buy I took the
note and I put it in my pocket.
I always said it was an accident.
It wasn't and accident.
My father killed himself.
singing
Congratulations Mr.
Wilson. I'm Richard Hayes.
Master of secrets and orders.
What did the note say?
I told you I never read the note.
You didn't read the note?
No.
My father said your father
was going to be appointed
Secretary of the Navy
until his loyalty
was brought under question.
We're not going to have a
problem with your loyalty are we?
And yet ...
a certain word
a glance, a guise,
will mirror never show?
reflecting not my gaze
but my uncertain question caught
inside a shadow of our shifting eyes.
That really is quite elegant Mr. Wilson
Good order. Very precise.
Feeling of the unknown.
Fine poetry is the music of mathematics.
Numbers.
Singing.
You have to look behind the words
to understand their meaning.
Right. Well, good night gentlemen.
Mr. Wilson
May I see you in my
office for a few words?
I am recommending you as editor of
our poetry magazine, The Politicus.
I'm honored. Thank you.
I appreciate your faith in me.
Never be ashamed of
your abilities, Edward.
Isn't there a picture that used to sit
on the mantle there, and there
was a group of soldiers...
It's my father's Crimean War regiment.
The ?????
I remember.
I'm having it mended.
I remembered it because it
reminded me of my father.
He was in the war.
I think we're being watched.
Watched? What do you mean?
There's a man in a hat.
I don't see anybody.
You know. There's so much I'd
like to share with you Edward.
and I hardly know
anything about you at all.
Other that you being a
particularly bright student.
I feel that we have a
kind of kindred spirit.
I really should be going.
No. I've started to write something.
Perhaps you'd like to hear it?
A bud has burst on the upper bough
the linnet sang in my heart today
I know where the pale green grasses show
By a tiny runnel, off the way,
And the earth is wet.
A cuckoo said in my brain.
Not yet. Not yet.
I haven't finished it.
Excuse me.
Please.
I'm sorry.
I can't hear.
What's your name?
Edward.
I'm sorry. Would you say it again?
I have to read your lips.
Edward.
Hello. Edward.
I'm Laura.
I'm sorry.
Would you say that again?
There isn't one person in a hundred
who would walk by a hat on a bench
without giving it a second look.
That says a lot about you Mr. Wilson.
You don't distract easily.
She's a very pretty girl.
Sam Murach. I'm with the
Federal Bureau of Investigation.
Mind if I walk along with you?
I had a chance to have a talk
with a fraternity brother of yours.
John Russell. The senator's son.
John said you might help us.
You're friendly with Dr. Fredericks?
He's my thesis advisor
if that's what you mean.
He's been recruiting faculty members
and students to join an organization
called the American-German
Cultural Committee.
It's a Nazi front.
Does he talk to you about that?
I'm a poetry student Mr. Murach.
I'm not political.
We'd be very interested in
finding out the names of some
of the other organizers
for the cultural committee.
Are you asking me to
spy on Dr. Fredericks?
I'm asking you to be a good citizen.
You blow that thing up it'll be fine.
I'll be seeing you.
In Poland, Hitler watches German
regiments steam across the river San.
This was part of the river line
which the invading army
forced in its flanking drive
through southern Poland.
The Nazi Fuehrer make a quick
tour in the conquered nation
among the soldiers in captured towns.
Hitler has given the
word of War and War it is.
Poland has been guaranteed
by Great Britain.... ?????
It is a great privilege to have
with us here tonight Mr. Haupt.
The Fuehrer’s education minister.
Mr. Haupt.
Good evening.
Thank you Dr. Fredericks,
and members of the
American-German cultural committee
for giving me the opportunity
to come to you here.
Germany has always been a country....
Excuse me.
Someone's in here!
Are you enjoying yourself Edward?
Very much so.
I'd like you to meet,
Mr. Haupt.
Dr. Manheim
Yes. We met.
I've been asked by the faculty chairman
to relinquish my post here at Yale.
Now, you'll hear many
reasons to what caused my departure.
Suffice is to say
I'm leaving with my name intact.
Good luck in your endeavors.
Oh, Edward.
What did I do to deserve this?
Have you such little regard for me
that you betray me for my
political beliefs?
You know and I know
Trumbull Stickney wrote
that poem in 1902.
You were my teacher.
You betrayed me.
piano playing
I thought we were going to a party.
You want to protect me
from them. Don't you?
No.
You think they will make fun of me....
That's not it. That's not true.
It's OK.
I'm happy to be with you.
Would you like to dance?
I'm not a very good dancer.
That's alright. I'm not
a good dancer either.
How does this song go?
Blue sky
smiling at me
nothing but blue sky
do I see.
Excuse me everybody,
I have an announcement.
I've just been told England and
France declared war on Germany.
But please continue dancing
and enjoying our music
and I'll update you as
information comes in.
Thank you.
Before long, we'll be at war too.
Would you like to get a room for us.
Turn down the light.
I can't.
Good night.
Thank you Edward.
For what?
For being so nice.
In view of the fact we're taking a
propaganda lambasting around the world
Why is it not useful, Sir
for us to explore with you
the real facts behind
this or our motivations.
There's an old saying that a
victory has a hundred fathers
and defeat is an orphan.
And I wouldn't be surprised if...
Hello Edward.
What are you doing here.
There are only a handful of us
until moment zero
who know where we were
going to land in Cuba.
One of us couldn't keep a secret.
I know it wasn't me.
Mr. Allen ask for
the Zapata list of personnel
who participated in the operation.
I don't have one.
Tell Mr. Allen I give
him the list personally.
We're in the same boat together.
A leaking boat.
Don't ever think we're in
the same boat Mr. Hayes.
We're either going to sink or swim.
Together
People like us..
we don't let each other drown.
I've said as much as I
feel can be usefully said
by me.
In regard to the events
of the past few days.
through the statements,
detailed discussions.
I'm not to....
Mother. Father.
This is Edward Wilson.
Mrs. Russell.
Senator.
Yes. It's a pleasure
to finally meet you.
Phillip and Toddy Allen.
Mr. Allen was president
of Bones class of '12.
Welcome to our little clubhouse.
Thank you.
Where's Clover?
Ah. There she is.
This is my sister Clover.
Hello. I'm Edward.
Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you.
Bonesmen.
All here!
Reverend Collin will offer grace.
Bonesmen first. Dear God...
God second
we thank you for guiding
the Evans' family trust
in the care of our beloved island.
So that we may come here with
our families and our friends
In comfort and in privacy.
He said he was going to ask me to dance.
Here we go.
Don't you dance Mr. Wilson.
Nobody asked me.
Oh.
Well.
I think I will take my chances.
I'm asking you.
John is very fond of you.
And I am very fond of him.
He's talking of going off
to fight with the English.
My father isn't particularly
pleased about it. Because
He's one of the organizers
of America First.
I'm not very good for an
isolationist's son to go off to war
what if....
Your brother John is a
man of great conviction.
I admire him.
What about you Mr. Wilson?
What do you believe in?
Are you in school?
You don't say very much. Do you?
When there is something worth saying...
Oh!
Well.
I think I'm going to like you.
Mr. Hayes.
Gentlemen.
General William Sullivan.
Mr. Edward Wilson.
It's a great honor sir.
I'd get up and shake your hand
but my fucking feet are killing me.
Something about too much
sugar in my blood and my urine.
So when do you boys start
your pissing contest?
I'll excuse myself.
Thank you Phillip.
Why don't you sit down.
You understand that whatever we
discuss here doesn’t leave this room?
Of course.
We'll eventually get
involved in this war.
Not because we want to
but because we have to
and we should.
And the president has asked me to look
into creating a foreign intelligence service
and if that happens
I'll be looking for patriotic,
honorable, bright young men,
from the right backgrounds to
manage the various departments.
In other words no Jews or negroes
and very few Catholics.
That's only because I'm a Catholic.
You'd be trained and commissioned
in the Army and posted overseas.
If it's something you’re interested in you'd
have to be ready to leave at a moment’s notice.
I don't want your answer
now. Just think about it.
But this isn't a bunch of fraternity boys
sitting around playing with their pricks.
This is for real.
For America.
Let’s go.
Have fun.
Behave yourselves.
I'm supposed to be looking
for the perfect husband.
Are you the perfect husband Mr. Wilson?
Perfect in every way.
Then is there some reason that you won't
put your arm around me?
You are the one...
I like this.
Very smart.
... or under the sun.
Whether near to me
Do you have a problem
with woman Mr. Bones.
Do you love me?
What?
Tell me you love me.
Do you love me.
I love you. I love you.
No. I still don't believe you.
Say it. Say it.
Look at me.
Stop. Stop.
I love you.
As soon as the world comes to
it's senses, I'm going to travel.
London. Paris. Rome.
You can come with me.
Is everything alright?
Fine.
We are worlds apart.
What do you mean?
I feel like I'm just a curiosity to you.
That. That is not. That's not true.
I feel like
I'm not real to you.
That is not true.
Anyway...
That's not how I feel about you.
Edward.
John?
I've been looking everywhere for you.
My sister.
She's pregnant
I know you'll do what's expected of you.
Do you Edward L. Wilson
take Margaret N. Russell
to be your lawfully wedded wife.
to love, honor and cherish
in sickness and in health
in good times and in bad times
until death do you apart.
I do.
I now pronounce you man and wife.
A man if uniform want to see you.
Excuse me mother.
Did your mother or I ever
tell you where we ....
Mr. Edward Wilson.
We need to speak alone sir.
Would you like to sit down?
No. Thank you sir.
General Sullivan sends his regards.
and to ask you if your still interested
in seeing the rest of the World.
Yes I...I certainly would be.
Good afternoon sir.
Thank you.
My orders came through.
I'll be going overseas.
When?
In one week.
What are you going to do Edward?
Save the World?
Your are safe here with me.
The photograph is particularly dark.
As we can see there is a Caucasian man
and a negro woman.
The resolution breaks
down pretty quickly.
The film stock is definitely Russian.
Low grade.
One of the areas we've been focusing on
is the mosquito netting...
The mosquito netting is predominantly in
Africa, southeast Asia,
any tropical climate.
The window curtains here
have a distinctive pattern
on them of Baobab trees.
Also seen in Africa.
Next to the curtains
we can see the building's ballestry.
There's a pigeon here. It's
kind of hard to make out.
Pigeons are mostly found in urban areas
town squares...
If you listen closely
you will hear an airplane.
We've washed it out.
By the sound of the
thrust of the jet engines
we can determine that
it's a plane taking off
no more than 1000 feet off the ground.
Which would further
suggest a large urban area.
On a section of the tape
when you clear up background noise
you can hear a female voice.
I love you.
People who really love each
other don't have secrets.
Your are safe here.
Assuming we're talking
about the same woman,
the linguists tell us
her accent is French.
There's one word here
we can't make it out yet.
There is an unidentifiable
noise washing her out.
Placed throughout the
recording at a high frequency
suggests an air raid siren of some sort.
We're going to keep playing with it.
This is the time fore
everyone to stand together
and hold firm
as they are doing.
I express my admiration
for the exemplary manner
in which all the air raid
precaution services of London
are being discharged.
May I help you?
Yes.
I here to see the tailor
about a fitting for a new suit.
Certainly, and what kind of suit
would you be interested this evening?
A tweed or worsted.
Perhaps a nice gabardine.
Perhaps, a worsted and a tweed.
Both single breasted?
Yes.
Two or three buns, sir.
Three buns.
If you might come this way, please sir.
Please.  Our senior tailor
will be right with you, sir.
Thank you.
Welcome to London.
You're going to have to learn
as quickly and thoroughly as  possible
the English system of intelligence.
The black cards, particularly
counter intelligence.
The uses of information, disinformation
and how their use is ultimately...
power.
They've agreed to open
their operations to us.
They can't win the war without us
but they don't really want us here.
Intelligence, is their mother's
milk and they don't like sharing
the royal tit with people
that don't have titles.
Your London tutor is
waiting to meet you.
This way sir.
I should've know better
that to use Stickney.
Job well done Mr. Wilson.
You blew a two year operation for me.
I told general Sullivan
to keep an eye on you.
Just as well, really.
I was beginning to long for
the bone chilling cold of home.
It isn't personal.
Mr. Carlson.
Is this the American Trade Bureau?
Which product?
Dried goods.
You’re late.
Yeah. That's what my mother said.
Raymond Ducca Brocco,
born may 8th, 1907, New York City.
St. Ignatius High School,
Fordham University.
Married Anita Delveccio.
2 children...
Stephanie and David.
Six foot two, 182 pounds,
black hair, brown eyes,
military record, 5 years,
intelligence.
Anything you'd like to add?
You want to look up my ass too?
You're working for me Sergeant Brocco.
I'm working for the
Unites States government...
In this office I am the
United States government.
You're pretty sure of yourself
for somebody who just began...
They wouldn't tell me your name.
Then how do you know you're
not in the wrong place.
They said you were a serious SOB
that didn't have any a sense of humor.
Can't be two of you.
phone rings
Are you going to answering it.
Depends if I'm working
for you or if I'm not.
One of your jobs, sergeant,
is answering the telephone.
Yes sir.
Use your tradecraft well,
particularly in the
use of black propaganda.
and the ingredient known as playback.
Understanding how effectively
your own disinformation
is actually working on the enemy.
It's almost four.
How do you spell syphilis.
Is it one L or two.
Syphilis.
One....I think.
It's vital to penetrate the
enemies intelligent services.
Push them into an
unreal world, as it were.
Doctor in England today
announced that medical records taken
from Adolf Hitler's personal physician
Dr. Theodore Morell
reveal that Mr. Hitler
had contracted syphilis
while serving the German armed
forces during World War I.
The very qualities that make
a good intelligence officer
a suspicions mind
a love of complexity and detail,
are the very qualities of
someone you've been observing.
Good evening Lord Cooper.
I have some information that
might be of some interest to you.
The mental facility to detect
conspiracies and betrayal
are the same qualities most likely
to corrode natural judgment.
Everything that seems clear is bent
and everything that seems bent is clear.
Trapped in reflections
you must learn to recognize
when a lie masquerades as the truth.
And then deal with it efficiently,
dispassionately.
We know you've been passing
information to the German high command.
Don't give anyone time to think.
Now, I'm going to offer
you one of two choices.
You set the tone of the discussion.
And quickly come to the point.
Either you can be executed for treason
or you can continue to spy for the enemy
and provide them with the
information we provide you.
Pass this on to your German friends
and if I find out it wasn't done
there won't be a second chance.
You, quite simply, behave as a spy.
Do we understand each other?
How do we know he won't
be working for two master?
Precisely?
We don't.
How do I know if I can even trust you.
You won't.
I mean, I hope you're lucky enough
you'll meet someone you trust.
I've got to say....
I haven't.
You must be young Edward.
Dr. Frederick has told
me so much about you.
Arch Cummings.
Nice to meet you.
I understand we are like
minded on many things
Good school boys. Yale. Cambridge.
Dreamers.
They say he's been an
exceptional intelligence officer.
You have to have a steady mind and
and an unwavering sense of
belief in what you're doing
and to be a hopeless romantic.
phone rings
American Trade Bureau
It's overseas. It's
Senator Russell, for you.
Hello.
Yes, Yeah Ah, Yes. I can hear you.
Thank you for telling me.
Good bye.
We had a boy.
Would you mind if we called him Edward?
If we called him Edward Jr?
I love that. I think it's perfect.
Fit of a king.
That's what I was
thinking. Fit for a king.
You like Edward?
Oh. I think he likes it.
So how are you?  Are you
saving the World and keeping us safe?
Sometimes.
What color are his eyes?
static
Hello? Hello?
When he's old enough
you can read it to him.
It's a first edition.
Charles Dickens. A Christmas
Carol. It was my fathers'.
He would read it to me when I was a boy.
Thank you.
I had an unfortunate discovery today.
A man that works for me said just as at my
door I found out he had given a rose to a woman.
with a small note, the rose was quite lovely.
An Abyssinian rose.
With stem neatly wrapped in silk paper
quite beautiful and touching.
Save for the fact
that the paper was filled with
secret writing for her German friends
detailing changes to the
American order of battle here.
Excuse me sir.
Thank you.
Thank you sir.
How did the Irish poet say it?
Hmm?
E'er friend for today,
is tomorrow's heartbreak
Do you know what my deepest fear is?
That I will end up....friendless.
Completely alone.
I think you two know each other.
Richard!
Hello Edward.
I didn't expect to see you.
Mr. Hayes has come over to work
with us in special operations.
I hope you don't mind I invited
him to join our conversation.
I'm afraid our dear English teacher has
a bad habit of making easy friendships.
You know, of course, about
his ridiculous sexual tastes.
I'm afraid he is not being very
discriminating in his partners.
Some people are extremely
worried about his exposure.
I hope you two can help sort this
rather delicate matter out for us.
Seem to me to be a
problem for the Bristish.
Why are we involved?
The British are a civilized people.
They don't ????? their own.
They have somebody do it for them.
So why are you telling me.
I'm giving you an opportunity to handle it.
Or somebody else will.
I'm sorry you've been brought into this.
If the headmaster won't listen to
reason who might want to tie your shoe.
Sorry it has to be this way.
It's not something I'm happy
about having to be doing.
Have you thought at all about
maybe going back to
teaching again? Sometime?
They are concerned about my
personal associations.  Aren't they?
Cambridge boys stick together like glue.
I'm far too democratic in my taste for them.
They like pressed trousers
and proper buttons.
No.
I've done all the
teaching I intend to do.
I am who I am.
I'll suffer that.
Please. You've given them all the service that you can.
It's time to retire.
The good schoolboy will be close by.
You won't want to know my response.
I understand.
If you want to tie your shoe.
It's a dirty business Edward.
I've been part of it for far too long.
You might want to think about getting
yourself a new pair of shoes Edward.
There's a wonderful shop at St. James'.
Mr. Pendingbones.
He's boot maker to the king.
But then....
I suppose we all  are in our own way, aren’t we?
boot makers to kings.
Get out while you still can.
While you still believe.
I'm sorry.
He knew too much.
You understand?
It appears the word we couldn't make out
had it's sound wave significantly
clipped by whoever made this tape.
We restored it by amplifying specific frequencies
seen on the oscilloscope.
Cochinos is Spanish for pigs.
Let me hear it again.
cochinos
And the siren noise we couldn't
pinpoint before were hiding church bells.
For some reason other noises
were added to distort the bells.
In the makeup table's mirror
we can actually make out the
reflection of a church steeple
whose three belfries correspond
with the bells you hear.
The volume indicates that the church is across the street.
Again, possibly on a town square.
On the night stand, we can see a clock radio.
It reads almost 10 o'clock
which would correspond
with the church bells.
I also have audio of the ceiling fan.
It's a four blade standard ceiling
fan. We don't know where it's from.
There is something here....
could be nothing significant.
Maybe a candle, a paper weight.
Or it may be something personal that we
can identify the people in the room with.
We are going to wash it
again. Maybe see what's there.
How long till there some
definition as to exactly where we are?
We're going as quickly as we can sir.
How are Clover and your little boy?
Good. Thank you. You
know he is almost five.
You may ????? for yourself in London.
The World War is over.
The war for the World has just begun
and in every liberated country
there will be a battle
between us and the Russians
for their hearts and minds.
Since we dropped the Bomb
they're feeling a little
short between the legs.
But the Russians still live in the nineteenth century.
Beets and potatoes.
All that will change dramatically.
But right now, they're gobbling up territory
taking home every
scientist they can steal.
In ten years, they'll have a Bomb.
We have to get anyone that can
be useful to us out of Berlin
before they do.
Churchill was right.
We shouldn't have stopped
marching until we reached Moscow.
They're from Switzerland.
I had them sent, with a pouch, to Berlin.
They're a weakness of mine.
When I was a child, my mother would
always reward me with a chocolate.
It's a dreadful habit.
The chocolates or seeking approval?
Both.
He was an officer it the Abwehr,
German military intelligence.
He says he knows the location of certain
Nazi V-2 rocket scientist in hiding.
Ask him where he wants to go.
He wants to go to Chicago.
He has relatives there.
Tell him if he provides us
with the names and locations
of the scientists I'll
arrange an exit visa for him.
As soon as he serves his purpose,
turn him over to the Nazi catchers.
The next ????? is a group commander
would like to speak with you about asylum.
It's very ugly, isn't it?
It isn't meant to be jewelry.
I lost the sound in one ear, altogether.
I can hear with the help of the apparatus
out of this ear, but they
say in one year or so....
You hardly notice it's there.
The Russians are interested
in making a prisoner swap.
We're prepare to offer you some
Jewish scientists liberated in the east
for some Nazi scientists
living here in Berlin.
These are the names
we're willing to discuss.
I understand your
cryptonym for me is Ulysses.
Isn't that from the James
Joyce book or the Greek myth.
Do you what our code name is for you?
Mother.
A took the first hot bath
yesterday I've taken in three years.
Since the siege of Stalingrad.
I sat for hours...
looking out the window,
soaking.
When I was a soldier
my fingers we're frost bitten.
Since then, when I get cold
there is a pain.
Maybe you shouldn't live in Russia.
We all have our weaknesses.
What is yours?
I had heard you were silent.
Made of stone, they said.
What is the expression?
The silence is deafening.
You're going to be a formidable
adversary, Mother.
I look forward to our association.
I hope it lasts for a long time.
I love you.
People who really love each
other don't have secrets.
You are safe here with me.
We were able to make
out the brand of the fan.
It's called a ?????. It's Belgian.
The object on the night stand
we're still trying to find out what this is.
We just can't get any
more definition out of it.
Who is this?
Hello father.
You have a birthday coming up.
I'm going to be five soon.
Well you're a big boy.
?????
Is your mother there?
What? I can't hear you.
She's getting dressed
to go out with her friend.
He has a new car.
He lets me drive with him.
Hello Mr. Wilson, this is Edna.
Mrs. Wilson is upstairs.
She's getting ready for dinner.
I'll tell her you are on the phone.
I'll call back.
door knocking
Pardon me.
Do you need me for anything else?
No. Thank you.
Guten Nacht.
Do you ever eat Mr. Wilson.
I like to cook.
Would you like a home cooked meal?
Have you ever read Ovid's
Metamorphosis in the original Latin?
It's quite beautiful.
I grabbed the pile of dust
and holding it up
foolishly ask for as many
birthdays as the grains of dust.
I forgot to ask that they be years of youth.
Bravo
I should be going.
Would you like to stay?
Would you like me to.
I would like you to very much.
Maybe we can go somewhere together?
The lakes in Bavaria are so beautiful.
There was an inn there before the war.
where they served
breakfast in bed all day.
Yena ?????
I hope you never go home.
Bavaria is a really beautiful place.
I was born there.
My grandmother
lived there.
I really miss her.
Why don't we go.
I let a stranger into our house.
door knocking
Dies da?
Danka.
Mother. Father is here.
Mother.
Hello Edward.
Hello Clover.
I ah.
I like to be called Margaret now.
It's very nice to see you.
It's good to see you too.
I made something or you.
You see?
It's a ship.
But it's got
the flag of England.
And then I put a pirate flag there.
And if you like
you can count
how many sails are there.
You want to try that?
Fifteen.
That’s right.
No. No. It's yours.
I made it for you.
If it's alright with you I thought
maybe we could sleep in
separate beds for a while.
Just until we can get
to know each other again.
I made up the spare room.
All right.
What do you hear from your brother John.
I thought you knew he was killed in Burma.
In 1944.
You never mentioned it
in any of your letters.
There wasn't very much to say.
Six year is a long time.
I was lonely.
And I was with a man, once.
He wasn't very interesting.
Were you with anyone?
It was a mistake.
Thank you for the
ship you made.  For me.
Your welcome.
I'm glad you like it.
Mother said you were at the war.
Did you fight? Did you kill anybody?
No.
Good night.
Hello Father. Hello Edward. Hello
Hello dear.
There is somebody waiting
for you in the den.
General!
Edward.
I'm sorry to barge in on you like this.
You wife kindly helped me to a drink.
My feet!
I keep cutting off pieces of them.
It's not dignified for a man
to have to die from the feet up.
Well, while everybody has been
feeling good about themselves
the Soviets, without firing a shot
have taken over half the World.
They're breathing down our necks.
They'll be in our back
yard before you know it.
So I've been telling the President
about our need to create a
foreign intelligence service
one that will do in peace time what
it was asked to do during the war.
Phillip Allen will be heading the agency
Richard Hayes will be his exec
and you'll be taking division C.
Special operations that
report only to the director.
It will be limited to overseas, obviously.
Subversive operations,
intelligence gathering and analysis.
And I'd be interested in
your thoughts about this.
Particularly, in your area of
expertise. Counter intelligence.
I'd be glad to help in any way I can.
That's all right.
Edward. Go outside.
Excuse me sir.
Margaret.
Thank you.
I have to tell you, I have some
real problems with this whole thing.
Despite how much we need it.
I'm concerned that too much power
will end up in the hands of too few.
It's always in someone's best interest
to promote enemies, real or imagined.
I see this as America's eyes and ears.
I don't want it to become
it's heart and soul.
So I told the President,
for this to work
they’re going to have to be some
kind of civilian oversight.
Oversight?
How can you have a covert organization
if you have people
looking over your shoulder?
You know who gave Hitler his power?
The clerks and the book keepers.
The civil servants.
I have this one weakness.
I believe in a just God.
I always seem to err on
the side of democracy.
This must be a nice
place to raise a family.
I never had the time.
I'll be dead in less than a year.
I love this country.
We all do sir. We all do.
No matter what anyone tells you,
there'll be no one you can really trust.
I'm afraid when it's all said and
done we're all just clerks too.
I was under the impression that
Dr. Ibanez supported a democracy.
I'm afraid he's changed his mind.
The doctor started to
believe his own propaganda.
I mean you dream this guy, Edward.
Help, get him elected.
Those are the Soviets
International Department
of Central Committee members
Trudnikov and Kosholnikov.
that have become overly interested
in their natural resources
particularly coffee.
Our economic interests
have become compromised.
To say nothing of the dangers of
a Soviet presence so close to home.
For security ????? we must
establish our own presence there.
Stop!
Can you go back.
Go. Go back a little bit.
Run it from there.
I just thought I saw something.
I want you two to put your
heads together on this.
Michael will be going down there
as an agricultural specialist
with the Mayan Coffee Company
non official
He'll be our eyes and ears.
Congratulations.
Thank you sir.
Good luck.
Thank you.
I wouldn't wear my
class ring down there.
Yes sir. Of course.
I want all intelligence on this
sent directly to me and no one else.
I believe that's what
you're looking for.
That'll do it.