SE-YEON
JUNG-YUN
SEO-YEONG
SEO-HYEON
SANG-WON
HEE-JI
JI-MIN
YE-RIN
JI-WOO
PYEONG-SEOK
NINETEEN TO TWENTY
Remember how I said...
that I want to stop going
on dates earlier?
I feel like I rejected the date
without giving you a proper reason
when you might not know anything
about what's going on,
so I felt really sorry.
I wanted to apologize.
To be honest,
I was thinking
about the worst-case scenario
while you were out with Jung-yun.
I thought
that if you reject the dream date,
I'd ask you out on a casual date.
But if you refuse that too,
I would just remain in House 20.
To me,
the dream date
isn't what's really important.
You were the most important.
I want you to tell me how you really feel
without worrying about hurting me.
-Please be honest.
-I...
Before going on my date today,
it's true that I was attracted to you,
and when I said it was half and half,
I really meant it.
I genuinely thought
that you were a really attractive guy.
But I feel like
I've come to a decision now
because I really enjoy going
on dates with you,
and you're really cool and sweet,
but I keep thinking of Jung-yun.
I keep feeling guilty toward Jung-yun,
and I keep expecting more from him.
When I was with you,
I kept thinking about Jung-yun,
but during my date today,
I didn't think about you.
Before, Jung-yun didn't express
his feelings for me.
But today, he kept expressing himself
even though it was a bit awkward for him.
And he told me firmly
that he only has feelings for me,
and that it wouldn't change.
And even though it was
just a typical date,
I felt really happy just being there.
So I realized that
I definitely have feelings for Jung-yun.
And I came to the conclusion
that I shouldn't go on
a dream date with you
while I feel that way.
I would be hiding my feelings,
and it wouldn't be right
to do that to you.
To be honest,
I obviously guessed how you felt
when you cried
in front of me because of Jung-yun.
I feel like I made you confused
because I wasn't sure
about my own feelings.
But I'm finally sure about how I feel,
and I'm really sorry
that I'm only telling you how I feel
the day before the last date.
I really don't want you
to feel sorry about that.
I started liking you because I wanted to.
I only expressed my interest in you
because I truly liked you.
Last night, I actually realized
that I wasn't just interested in you
and curious about you.
I realized that I truly like you.
I only went on two dates,
and both were with you.
And I was really happy and excited
during every moment.
And because I expressed
my feelings honestly,
I don't have any regrets.
Even if I could go back in time,
I would still go on dates with you.
I would totally understand
if you were upset
or disappointed with me about this,
but I'm really grateful
for you saying that to me. I really am.
You're...
really attractive and really pretty.
And I feel really grateful that you let me
experience so many great things.
Why am I crying right now?
It's okay.
I was...
really sincere
about my feelings toward you.
I just hope you know that.
Of course.
I never expected myself
to fall for Ji-woo this deeply.
For over half my life,
I was solely focused on sports.
So I never imagined
I would go through such an experience.
And...
I'm grateful to Ji-woo
for letting me feel these emotions
as soon as I turned 20.
I feel happy for having a chance
to go through this.
My feelings for Jung-yun were growing to
the point that even Se-yeon could notice.
But I was confused about my own emotions
and took too much time realizing them,
hurting Se-yeon in the process.
So I felt really sorry.
Q. ANYTHING YOU WANT TO SAY TO SE-YEON?
Going on dates with Se-yeon...
I feel like I'm going to cry...
I really enjoyed going on dates
with Se-yeon,
and it's true that I was really happy.
And I want to let him know
that I was genuinely attracted to him...
It must have been difficult,
but they ended it well.
Right, it must have been hard.
But their ending was beautiful.
How could they
have a conversation like that
-at that age?
-Aren't they cool?
She apologized maturely,
and he accepted it maturely.
How could 20-year-olds talk like that?
They're so mature.
Rejection and breakups
-are usually unpleasant.
-You get really emotional.
-Or you'd just hide to avoid them.
-Right.
Yes, but these two...
-They ended it well.
-They accepted it.
It was admirable.
I feel like this was possible
because they were both
100 percent sincere the entire time.
DAY SIX AS 20-YEAR-OLDS
6:30 A.M.
-Hi.
-Did you sleep well?
-Yeah.
This is nice.
-It's nice?
-Yes.
-Let's go see the sunrise.
-Right.
You must've slept right away.
Yes, I did.
You must be tired waking up so early.
Yes, but I want to see the sunrise.
The sunrise at Jeju Island with you.
I love it.
I'm so excited.
I don't think I've ever seen the sunrise.
Neither have I.
I can't believe I'm seeing
the sunrise in Jeju Island.
-Did you wear the bracelet?
-Of course.
Ji-min!
Hang on. Where did I put mine?
Where did I put it?
"Where did I put it?"
-He'll get upset.
-Oh, no...
-This is awful.
-He's going to be really upset.
You told me to wear it,
so I made sure I did.
Ji-min!
Why didn't you bring it?
I did think something was missing.
Why didn't you wear it?
Are you hiding it in your mouth
or something?
Is it a prank?
In her mouth?
I wish it really was there.
He must be pretty upset.
No way...
-It's fine.
-No, I'm sure it's in my accessory pouch.
-Our bracelet isn't important.
-It is.
-It must be there.
-I'm sure it is.
-I'll look for it.
-Okay.
TOMORROW'S YOUR LAST DAY IN HOUSE 20
EXPRESS YOUR FEELINGS TO THE PERSON
YOU LIKE BY MIDNIGHT
We're going to see the sunrise.
I wanted to start our relationship
right as the sun was coming up.
So I decided to ask her out
during sunrise.
I thought a lot
about how I should ask her out.
-This is so much fun!
-That's pretty fast.
He had time until midnight...
-He's doing it right away.
-In the morning.
At six in the morning.
He's fiery.
-But I'm curious what he'll say.
-Right.
-Let's get off.
-Yeah.
Let's go.
-I'm so happy all of a sudden.
-It's beautiful!
It's all pink.
The sky...
-Isn't it pretty?
-Yes.
It's so beautiful.
Even the waves are pretty.
Like someone, right?
-Who do you think that is?
-Right, like you.
How did you feel being away from me?
-We were apart for a bit.
-I really missed you.
-You did?
-Yes.
But why didn't you say,
"I'm going to miss you"?
I felt a bit shy.
Me too.
-I'll keep doing it from now on.
-You'd better.
I hope the sun comes up soon.
What are you planning?
He's going to tell her!
He's telling her soon!
What are you going to say?
It's getting brighter.
Where's the sun?
It's getting brighter, though.
It's getting brighter,
but I don't see the sun.
-Actually...
-Yes?
The sun's already up.
It's just covered by the clouds.
No way!
What?
-What do we do?
-Hold my hand.
-Let's just watch the waves. It's nice.
-Okay.
-During our date...
-Yes?
-I was surprised.
-Why?
-When we were eating...
-Yes?
-You looked so pretty.
-Me?
Yes.
Does it look okay?
-You look pretty.
-It is? Let's eat.
I'd been thinking of you as just a friend,
but whatever you did, you looked so cute.
So I wanted to take care of you
and stay by your side.
And since then, I kept thinking about you
before I went to bed.
I kept looking through our photos.
I kept missing you.
I felt happy thinking about
seeing you again the next day.
I want to keep looking at our pictures
and seeing you in person.
-I want to keep seeing you.
-Really?
-How?
-So I want to say something.
What?
I want you to be my girlfriend.
-That was romantic.
-Can you place the sun there?
-With computer graphics?
-Yes.
I want you to be my girlfriend.
I never imagined I'd hear this on a beach.
And your answer?
My answer?
Can't you guess?
-Is that a yes?
-Isn't it obvious?
Yes.
This is crazy.
They're the first couple.
I never expected this couple, though.
Me neither. I never expected this.
Oh, my gosh.
I didn't know I'd feel so shy.
-What?
-I felt shy getting asked out.
I felt shy saying it.
So what are we now?
-A couple.
-Right.
I'm never gonna let your hand go.
I'm not letting it go.
I did think that Ye-rin would say yes.
But I still felt really nervous.
Now that we're 20, we'll be experiencing
many things for the first time.
And I want Ye-rin to be by my side
when I'm experiencing them.
The dream date with Ji-min
will be a date
I'll never be able to forget.
I'll think of him if I see a lighthouse
or even if I just see the ocean.
Or if I see black pig.
I feel grateful toward him
for giving me memories
that I'll never forget.
I want to visit Jeju Island again
with Ji-min.
It's covered by the clouds.
Make them disappear.
I feel shy.
Let's go for a swim!
-Bye!
-Let's go!
It's not coming.
Why isn't it coming to us?
Because it's me.
-Because it's me.
-It's us.
Because it's us.
Stay back!
-Oh, no!
-You were really slow.
I'll dig through the fridge.
All right.
-Hey!
-What?
-Look!
-What is it?
"Express your feelings
to the person you like by midnight."
As soon as I saw it,
I began wondering
how to express my feelings honestly
and let Ji-woo know how I feel about her.
-Did you see the notice outside?
-What is it?
We have to express our feelings
to the person we like by midnight.
-Express our feelings?
-Yes.
-Seriously?
-We have to tell them.
I thought, "This is it."
I'm going on a dream date
with Pyeong-seok.
I want to tell him how I feel at the end.
"Tomorrow's your last day in House 20.
Express your feelings
to the person you like by midnight."
It gave me a lot to think about.
I was thinking about how I should express
my feelings to Hee-ji.
And I also wondered
what Hee-ji was thinking.
-Where's Hee-ji?
-Call her name.
"Hee-ji, come out here!"
"Come out here!"
Hey, don't forget the thing.
Clapping as you enter the house.
-Yes?
-Hee-ji, let's go.
-Hang on.
-See you later.
-Bye.
-You'd better come back as a couple.
-Go.
-I'm excited.
-Our last...
-What?
-Can I laugh?
-Why?
-It's just...
Would it be weird if I talk to you now?
-Go on.
-Okay.
-Can I come in?
-Something important? Sure.
Well, it's like preparing
for something important.
-The cafe?
-Yes.
-Like when?
-I mean, let's go.
Okay.
-Hurry up.
-Okay.
-Get ready.
-All right.
Was that it?
We're finally back.
-They must be there, right?
-I hope they are.
-I'm exhausted.
-I'm not exhausted at all.
Then is it called "Han River" in English?
Yes.
Hey, they're here.
Your dad was worried!
I can't believe you guys went
on an overnight trip.
That was exhausting.
How was it?
-How was it?
-Isn't it obvious?
Ji-min, where's the stuff we bought?
They're here.
-What did you do there?
-So...
-Us?
-Us? We went to the beach.
-Was it fun?
-It was so much fun.
I already ate some of this, though.
And a bit of this.
Is that a matching set?
-That's cute!
-Matching pants! Tangerines.
-But he said they're carrots!
-Carrot pants.
What were you doing?
-Right, did you see that?
-It's today's rule.
-Actually...
-I already did it.
-By today.
You have to tell them.
-I already did it.
-Hey.
-What?
-You're dating?
-You're dating now?
-What?
-Hey! Sit down and tell us!
-This is crazy.
-Come on. Sit down.
-No way!
-You're dating?
Sit down, guys.
-Sit down?
-Sit.
-Make an announcement.
You seem to have something to tell us.
Come on. Who's going to tell us?
Well, I expressed my feelings
while watching the sun come up.
No way!
-Hold hands!
-Yes, that's it!
Show them.
-Today?
-You said yes?
-Did she?
-Yes.
-Yes, we're dating now.
-No way!
He confessed his feelings!
He did it this morning!
I can't believe it!
Oh, my gosh!
-This is embarrassing!
-Hey, don't touch her!
Keep your distance, guys.
I don't want to see couples.
We ate so much there.
-Ten servings...
-Your hands...
-Ji-min!
-Hey! No!
-Come on!
-What?
What are you guys doing?
Actually...
I knew it.
Right when the sun was coming up...
I was really surprised.
He said it just like that?
-What did he say?
-He's romantic!
-Why should I tell you that?
-It's a secret?
Those two look good together.
-Yes, you're right.
-Right?
-Congratulations!
-Congrats!
Congratulations!
-Congratulations!
-I can't believe it.
Ji-min and I became
the first official couple of House 20.
I was happy because I could spend time
with him more comfortably.
-Have a seat.
-This is nice.
It's our last day... Almost our last day.
How has it been?
I feel like I might cry.
I feel like I got so used to
being with everyone.
Right. It was so much fun.
-The school, and...
-Right.
-It was...
-What?
There was some drama, but I think...
it's all fine now.
Sure.
Remember that crazy day?
When they announced
the Busan and Gyeongju trip.
I still remember that.
-Some were crying.
-It was crazy.
Right.
-We were growing up.
-Right. We were becoming adults.
-What?
-Thinking back now, it was fun.
All of this will not be a big deal
once time passes by.
They're all just nice memories.
-Right. Good memories.
-Yes.
Like talking with the guys before bed.
I don't think I'll ever forget
our time here. Going from 19 to 20.
I have no regrets about the two weeks.
And I didn't want to have any regrets
so I wanted to stay true
to my feelings and tell her.
Should I tell you how I feel first?
What I wanted to say to you?
To be honest, what I want to say
is more about a beginning than an ending.
-Right.
-So...
I really liked you.
I mean, I still like you.
I really like you.
I like you now,
and it's been like that for a while.
I like you a lot.
When I first saw you at School 19,
you were there before me.
-Right.
-Ever since I first saw you...
Well, I thought you were pretty.
-Really?
-Yes, I mean it.
When I saw you...
-Hello.
Hello.
And my dream is to be an architect.
Nice to meet you.
I think it was PE class.
I was the last one left.
Where is everyone? Sang-won...
Sorry. I took so long.
I was the last one left,
but I was happy because you were last too.
And when I got the book,
I had butterflies in my stomach.
I gave one to you, and you gave one to me.
My heart fluttered.
And I asked you the most questions
during Ask Me Anything.
After that...
I saw you giving your everything
and always being passionate.
You looked really cool,
but then also seemed clumsy sometimes,
which was very cute.
My feelings for you kept growing.
And when we entered House 20,
I was happy to be able to spend
more time with you.
I really enjoyed hanging out with you.
And especially our date at Lotte World.
I'll never be able to forget it.
I feel dizzy.
-From happiness?
-I'm really dizzy.
I'm dizzy with excitement.
I've been thinking...
This was a special situation
and we only had two weeks.
So it's true that I was being
a bit more rash than I normally am.
And I think I seemed a little impatient.
But even so,
I'm certain about my feelings.
I truly do like you,
and what I want to say to you is...
I want us
to get to know each other better.
I believe I can show you
an even better side of me.
I want to know if you'd like to keep
seeing me and getting to know me better.
I wanted to ask you that.
Did I come on too strong?
Well...
I...
I feel like I wasn't entirely
honest about my feelings...
I felt pretty confused,
and I've been thinking about us.
But...
it's true that
I was attracted to you the most in school.
But I think
my heart fluttered for all those
romantic moments and not you.
So my conclusion is that right now,
I'm not romantically attracted to you.
Okay.
I wanted to be honest about my feelings.
After we ended school
and entered House 20,
I could feel how much you liked me,
and that actually felt
a little overwhelming for me.
-And that drove me away a bit.
-Right.
Yes.
What?
Do you feel better now?
This really isn't easy.
So I just wanted to tell you...
-How you feel?
-Yes.
Right. Thanks for being honest.
I have some regrets.
I don't regret getting closer to you,
but I do think that it might've been
better if I acted like I normally would.
But I did what I did.
I want to say that
I'd like us to remain good friends.
I had fun.
So we're...
-friends?
-Yes.
We decided to remain as good friends.
Even without a romantic interest in her,
Seo-hyeon's really fun to be with,
and she's a really cool friend.
So I was able
to accept her decision calmly,
even though I was a bit disappointed.
Until now, when Sang-won
expressed his feelings toward me,
I kept changing the subject
or joking around awkwardly.
And I didn't have the courage,
so I had a hard time
telling him how I felt.
But after being honest about how I feel,
I feel much better.
I finally feel a little more relaxed
and comfortable.
Honesty is the best option.
You're right.
It's hard to reject someone.
Sang-won took it very calmly.
Maybe Sang-won kind of knew
how she felt about him.
-Yes.
-It seemed that way.
I feel a bit sad for him.
Still, he expressed
his feelings without regret
-and tried his best.
-Right.
HEE-JI & PYEONG-SEOK'S DREAM DATE
I can't stop smiling.
-What?
-You seem excited.
Let's go.
Are you sure you won't get
motion sickness?
I might throw up.
-I like the vibe here.
-Yeah.
It's pretty.
-So pretty.
-Yeah.
It's your first time here?
Visiting Han River?
-Where should we sit?
-Here.
This is nice. I think it'll be even
prettier when it gets dark.
Yeah.
I've never eaten at a place
like this before.
Really?
You too, right?
-Yes.
-Of course.
It's my first time.
Something smells good.
Excuse me for just a moment.
Sure.
-I'll pour the drink for you.
-Thank you.
Enjoy.
-It's so cool being here.
-Yeah.
-It's nice here.
-It's even more fun.
It's our last date.
Last... No, it's not our last.
-It's not?
-It's not.
It's the beginning.
I should come back in spring.
With who?
You.
Who?
Kim Pyeong-seok.
Stop smiling.
We should stop smiling too.
Let's all stop smiling.
-I thought she was talking to me.
-This is crazy.
-I feel so happy watching them.
-They're so cute.
Our food's here.
Enjoy your meal.
I feel like I shouldn't ruin it.
Should we try it?
It's good.
My favorite, shrimp.
Shrimp.
Shrimp is the best.
Right, you love shrimp.
It's so quiet here.
Say something.
There was something I did want to say,
so I was anxious thinking about it.
It was hard to say it.
Pyeong-seok!
-He's going to say it.
-He's telling her soon.
Who will say it first?
-It was always my first time.
-What?
Everything I do with you is my first time.
Yeah.
I wish we could have fun every day.
Me too.
I'll be so bored when I go back home.
Me too. How will I live?
I'm doomed now.
Come into my pocket.
Take me.
-Can I squeeze you in?
-Yes.
We were together for a week.
Time flies.
When did we get so comfortable?
I feel like at some point,
I felt so comfortable.
Yeah.
When did you feel that?
For me...
After our first date?
What about you?
During our first date,
when we clinked glasses.
Cheers.
It's good.
I only noticed yours, though.
-Because it's so deep?
-Yes.
"Gyuka"? Gyukatsu?
What's gyukatsu?
After we rode the taxi...
Yeah.
-Relax this finger.
-Relax.
-Make a fist like this.
-Like this?
Fold it.
-There.
-Got it.
It feels like
you're looking at me with four eyes.
I thought your name was cool.
-Kim Pyeong-seok.
-Pyeong-seok.
I was watching you,
and I thought, "New student!"
I remember it clearly.
Hi, my name's Kim Pyeong-seok.
I want to become a Hapkido instructor.
"Hi, I'm Kim Pyeong-seok."
You were shy.
You're so shy.
"Any questions?"
"Ask me anything."
"Anything you want to know?"
Is there anything you want to know?
I'm usually kind of quiet...
Awkward, right?
We were talking from a distance.
Yeah.
I still remember the vibe back then.
I've improved a lot.
-Yes.
-I've grown.
-You've grown.
-I'm all grown up.
Not all grown up.
Not enough?
Jeez...
It got dark.
-Let's go look at the city lights.
-It's so dark now.
It's so pretty.
-It is.
-So pretty.
-Right.
Hey! I think it's snowing.
Is it snowing?
It's faster than I thought.
Is it red? Very red?
It's like that shrimp.
-The shrimp?
-Yes.
Are mine red too?
This is so nice.
Should we go on a date every day?
Yes.
Would you be my boyfriend?
What?
-What?
-Do you want me to be your girlfriend?
You mean it? I was going to ask that.
That was my line.
Well, I said it first.
I'm so happy. I want to shout.
I want you to be my girlfriend.
-Let's date everyday.
-Let's date.
I feel so weird!
I wish everyone in the world knew.
-What?
-That I'm so happy.
It was really dark,
but everything became pink.
Everything looked like hearts.
It was like a dream.
-They did it.
-Hee-ji's so cool.
She was so cool.
She's so cool!
It's a perfect happy ending.
-Those two were perfect from the start.
-Yeah.
-It's the perfect scene we wanted.
-Yes.
We're a couple now.
-Starting today, we're a couple.
-Yes.
Today is our first day as a couple.
Right.
Can I hold your hand?
Yes.
What? Are we arm wrestling or what?
-Is that a full moon?
-It's round.
It's very round.
Your hand...
It's hot.
-I'm so happy.
-We should've taken a photo here.
Should we take one now?
Sure.
-We should take it like this.
-Yes.
Wait...
Oh, my gosh!
Pyeong-seok!
He froze!
-I want to look closely.
-Look at him.
Did she kiss him?
Nothing happened.
-I won't shower today.
-Did something happen?
I won't wash my face.
I can't shower today.
That feeling...
I was so surprised.
It's hard to describe
how I felt at that moment.
I was really happy.
Q. DID YOU NOT WASH YOUR FACE?
I did. Very hard.
I washed this side gently,
but very hard here.
Our signature pose.
Our first day!
Look over here.
-What?
-It's a video.
-Our first day.
-Our first day as a couple.
With Pyeong-seok.
My dimple.
Let's make a dimple here.
I told the others yesterday
that I'd come back clapping
if I'm in a good mood.
-Really?
-Yes.
I should enter doing a headstand.
Your nose is red.
-It's cold.
-Right?
We dressed too lightly.
It'll be long-distance.
Lots of couples do it.
We can meet up often.
-Heart?
-One, two, three.
What? Once more. One, two, three!
-Smaller.
-One, two, three.
-I think it worked.
-Once more.
One, two, three! Go!
The heart is...
Nice!
We're clapping a lot today.
We now have the second official couple
of Nineteen to Twenty.
They're both worried
about dating long-distance.
Still, they'll be able to meet
on the weekends.
Pyeong-seok's working
at the Hapkido center with his dad.
He might rush over as soon
as the center closes.
-He might.
-He would.
-At that age...
-And he can drive.
He'll say,
"I came just for a bit, Hee-ji."
-Just to see her for five minutes.
-He really might.
Imagine he gets a new member
and it turns out to be Hee-ji.
Guys, this isn't a romance drama.
I really hope they stay together
for a long time.
I hope they get married.
-I want those two to last forever.
-Yeah. They look so great together.
It's kind of cold.
How is it like being my boyfriend
at House 20?
I love it.
That's it? That was too short.
You tell me, then.
I like being with you.
That's way too short.
-Choi.
-Lee.
-Cross.
What if another girl does this?
What if I do it?
If you do it?
What will you do
if I do this to you, then?
It's nice wherever we are.
Yeah.
As long as we are together.
-Hi!
-Hey.
I'm back.
-You're still here, Jung-yun?
-Should I be somewhere?
Seo-hyeon said she was going somewhere,
so I thought she was meeting you.
We're going to have a meal together later.
EARLIER TODAY
Hurry.
-Hurry.
-I don't want you to feel pressured,
but let's just have a...
-What? When?
-Have a dinner together.
-Between 5:00 p.m. and 7:00 p.m.?
-Okay.
Where are you going?
I don't know.
She just wanted to eat together.
What did you say?
-What did she say?
-I got rejected.
You got rejected?
Did you tell her how you felt?
-Yes, a bit...
-What did she say to that?
She said she wasn't interested in me,
so I just said all right.
Oh, no...
-Don't mess it up at the end.
-I'm still so confused.
Why does she want to see me?
Do you know? Did you hear anything?
-No, nothing.
-But why...
-I'll see you later, guys.
-Bye.
HWANHUI
CASUAL FUSION RESTAURANT
-I'm here.
-You're a bit late.
-There was traffic.
-I waited for so long.
What should we get?
-Did you order something?
-No.
-Why is this so funny?
-Your expression...
Let's enjoy our meal.
I'll talk when we're done.
-Okay.
-Brace yourself.
-Brace myself?
-Yes.
-I'm getting anxious.
-Why?
Do you know what I'll say?
-No, that's why I'm anxious.
-You have no clue?
During my date with Jung-yun yesterday,
I realized that I have more feelings
toward him for sure.
And I wondered how to express
my feelings toward him
while I waited for him to come back.
-This is so good.
-Eat up.
I'm full.
Okay, let's hear it.
-What's this about?
-At first...
I wanted to pick fights with you.
In the beginning?
-I see.
-Every day.
-Keep picking fights and argue...
-Right.
And tease you.
-Like now?
-Yes.
-You're doing that now.
I kept acting that way.
I kept doing that to you in school.
-Did you feel that?
-Yes.
I'll show you my skills.
Great.
-No, don't do that.
-Jeez.
Don't do that pose.
-That's my signature pose.
-No.
You look great right now.
Should I have a meeting as well?
Let's have a meeting.
-We need to do a meeting.
-Right.
Everything Jung-yun does is so funny.
The way he talks is funny,
and his expressions too.
-I...
-Hey...
-I just...
-You're so funny.
I didn't do anything.
I just looked through the window.
-Jung-yun's so...
-Jung-yun's just so funny.
I think it'll be fun
to do it with Jung-yun.
-It's been quite a while.
-Right.
-She's been interested in him.
And that didn't change
when we entered House 20.
I kept wanting to tease you.
-Right.
-Yes.
Seo-hyeon, your shoulders look wider.
These are just shoulder pads.
Aren't they great?
-You'll end up... Don't stop him.
-Slow down.
What's wrong with you? Manager Lim...
You got your nails done.
Isn't it cute?
Ji-woo and Jung-yun were basically
dating right next to me.
I didn't get to listen properly
because I felt so irritated,
but they seemed to be having fun.
Q. WHY WERE YOU IRRITATED?
It's nothing.
-Did you enjoy it?
-Yes, it was good.
I asked when the Lunar New Year was,
and you said so confidently...
I just heard you wrong.
Oh, that's a first.
You got it. Put your right foot there.
I just felt a bit...
I thought about it,
and I realized that I wanted to tease you
because I liked you a bit.
-You realized it a bit late.
-Yes.
I felt it.
-But I teased you a lot too.
-You...
You were joking around,
but your eyes were always
focused on Ji-woo.
Only Ji-woo.
Yeah, so...
Honestly, that's why I told myself
that I was wrong.
I told myself you're just a friend
I feel comfortable with.
Yes... That's what I tried to think.
But this was sudden for me too.
It's very sudden, because until now,
I was quite confused
because of my feelings toward Sang-won.
So after I made up my mind and thought
about my feelings,
I came to this conclusion.
Right.
So, how do you feel?
-It's unexpected, right?
-Yes.
-You had no idea?
-Yeah.
I didn't know it either.
Things might have been better
if I had realized it sooner.
So I decided
that I would regret it less
if I told you how I feel today.
I had no idea that Seo-hyeon
had been feeling that way towards me,
so I was surprised.
I thought, "Seo-hyeon must have
gone through a lot."
But I thought she was quite brave
for still telling me her feelings
at the end.
I didn't even realize my own feelings,
and I couldn't do anything.
You should've helped out.
-Me? How?
-Yes.
We should've at least gone
to eat hanwoo omakase.
You wanted to go there?
Sang-won and I came back
from our date at three,
and everyone was asleep.
And I saw that hanwoo omakase date.
-Go and shower. I had fun.
-Goodnight.
-See you.
-Okay.
DREAM DATES: FULL RENTAL OF A MOVIE
THEATER, HANWOO OMAKASE
But even back then...
Even if I knew my feelings,
I wouldn't have had the courage.
-Right, courage is important.
-Yes.
I really felt it this time.
Mustering up your courage
is really important.
I really felt it recently.
So I'll be braver from now on.
Anyway, that's it.
I'm rooting for you.
I hope you succeed
and get to marry her.
Jung-yun
is the first guy
I confessed my feelings to,
and the first guy I got rejected by.
I guess he's my first unrequited love.
But after telling Jung-yun
how I felt about him honestly,
I feel like I could end things
without any regrets.
I feel pretty relaxed now.
She's so cool.
-I want to say good job to her.
-Yeah.
That was quite a surprise, though.
Seo-hyeon already knew
that Jung-yun wouldn't accept
-her feelings.
-Right.
-But she still told him.
-Right. About how she feels.
I wouldn't have had the courage.
It was so clear.
-Ji-woo and Jung-yun...
-Right.
I would've thought,
"What's the point of telling him now?"
-Right, I understand.
-She was brave.
-Yes.
-I feel like I'm learning from her.
Are we going to confess
our feelings tomorrow?
-Let's all do it.
-For real.
I feel like
I should be doing something too.
-We should do something.
-Should we do it too?
-Confess our feelings?
-Right.
-I'll do it.
-It feels like we should.
-"I think I like you."
-We should.
-What?
-Hey.
What were you doing?
-What were you doing?
-Waiting for you.
-Since when?
-What?
Since when?
I don't know.
-Did you fall asleep?
-Yes.
I slept here, and upstairs,
then down here again.
What should I say first?
Well... I...
Ever since the beginning...
and until now...
I've liked you, and I'll keep liking you.
-Right...
-So...
let's keep seeing each other
even after we leave here.
-Okay.
So...
let's keep seeing each other.
You...
were also the first guy
I was attracted to.
I felt confused for a bit
in the middle of all this,
but I realized it was you that I like.
-So we're just getting started.
-Right.
Right.
-Our new beginning.
-It'll be fun.
-Why is your hand so cold?
-I was outside.
It was cold outside.
It's snowing right now.
-It's snowing.
-What? Why?
I don't know.
-No way!
-Right?
-No way.
-So nice, right?
-Why is it snowing now?
-Isn't it the first snow of the year?
-It is.
-Right?
Cool.
On our last day... I mean, our first day.
-Our first day?
-Yes.
First day, first snow.
-The snow...
-It's so pretty.
I had no idea it was snowing.
-I didn't, either.
-It's so nice.
We're seeing the first snow together.
You're right.
What do you want to do when we leave?
-When we leave?
-Yes.
Anything would be nice.
As soon as I saw her,
I began to like her
and that feeling continued.
-How did you feel when you saw me?
-I was thrilled.
-What?
-I was thrilled at the news.
-Really?
-Yes.
Two, three, cha-cha-cha.
-Hey, you're good.
-Two, three, cha-cha-cha.
Do you want to go on a date with me?
Do you want to?
We talked about going to the theater,
the Han River,
and an amusement park together
when we leave,
so I'm looking forward to that.
If Jung-yun's hands are cold,
I'll warm them up for him,
and if my hands are cold,
Jung-yun will warm them up for me.
-The first.
-Right.
-Should we go?
-Shall we?
-Let's go.
Why do you keep laughing?
TOMORROW'S YOUR LAST DAY IN HOUSE 20
EXPRESS YOUR FEELINGS
TO THE PERSON YOU LIKE BY MIDNIGHT
Congratulations.
-They finally ended up together.
-A happy ending.
They went through so much
and ended up together.
They're our third couple.
Our third couple.
This is what
we've been waiting for so long.
Right.
-We were waiting so desperately.
-Seriously.
It was cute, though.
Jung-yun seemed to have run a simulation.
-Yes.
-He said what he memorized like a robot.
Right. Ji-woo was half-asleep.
He suddenly came up to her and said it.
-It's just like him.
-"Let's keep seeing each other."
It all went naturally.
-It's just like him, though.
-Ji-woo would think it was cute.
I think she was like,
"Did he just ask me out?"
-Bye.
-See you later.
-No.
-What? Okay.
I mean, all right.
I have to pack up.
You were busy today. Hurry.
Go and pack up.
-What?
-Bye.
-No way!
-What?
-What did I just see?
-Hang on.
-What?
-Did you hold hands?
-No. I was sending him away like this.
You held hands!
-What?
-You did, right?
-And I spotted you!
-What?
-Hey!
-Guys!
-What are you doing?
-Jung-yun and Ji-woo held hands.
-I...
Hey!
We can't allow that.
-Did you guys talk?
-You and Jung-yun?
-Yes.
-And you're dating?
-Hey, they're dating!
Don't say that so loudly!
My babies.
-What?
-Hey!
-Hee-ji?
-Are you dating too?
-Tell us. What happened?
-Are you together?
-What happened?
You're together too?
-Did you say it?
-Yes.
-Who said it?
-I did.
So what happened? You're dating now?
Yes.
Crazy!
There are three couples now.
-Jeez!
-Three couples.
-Hey.
-I'm back.
-You're back.
-Hey.
-Did it go well?
-How did it go?
Well...
-Did it go well?
-So what happened?
What happened?
-Well...
-Come on. Spill.
Everyone, clap your hands!
Pyeong-seok! You did it!
It's snowing a lot.
-Do you want a photo?
-Yeah.
Guys, stand back to back.
Look in opposite directions.
Yes, like that.
All right. One, two, three.
One, two, three.
-You guys look alike.
-Should we look at each other?
That looks nice.
-It looks pretty good.
-I love this photo.
Isn't it awesome?
One, two, three.
-Got it.
-It's amazing.
It's snowing
-on our last day.
-Tell me about it.
-Try it.
-Oh, I like that.
Mine is broken.
My heart's broken.
It's snow.
HOUSE 20
It's so pretty!
Another feast?
-It looks so good.
-I can't leave.
-I won't go home.
-This looks delicious.
-I've seen this before.
-Didn't we see this before?
-Our first day.
-The same food.
Right.
Guys, I'll pour you all a drink today.
Okay. I'll just open this for you, then.
Careful!
It might pop at any moment.
Oh, no!
-Pop!
-It's not working.
Hurry...
Awesome!
-I'm getting good at this.
-Yes.
-My gosh.
-This sauce...
-Our eldest...
-Thank you.
-Thank you!
-Hang on.
What? What is it?
What is he doing?
He's so weird.
-He learned something from the restaurant.
-Have a good day.
Hey, this is all just foam!
There's nothing to drink.
Don't do it. Just stop, Pyeong-seok.
-You're so bad at this.
-What's with this?
Guys, it's our last night here.
Hey, be quiet.
-No, we...
-It's okay.
No.
Shall we toast?
Nineteen!
-To Twenty!
Cheers from afar.
-Can you drink more now?
-It's not... It's good.
-Do you like it or not?
-It's good.
I think I'm going to cry.
Ji-min!
-So good.
-You drank it all up?
So good.
He drank it all.
-The champagne's awesome.
-Is it good?
-It's tasty!
-Ji-min.
-He's going to change soon!
-Right!
We're going to see him drunk again.
Please...
FIRST DAY AT HOUSE 20
Thank you for your hard work.
Hey! Don't try to be funny.
You just dropped...
His facial expression's totally
different! Look!
-My gosh!
-This is good.
Ji-min, don't drink again. Okay?
-Let's just eat.
-All right.
Are you embarrassed of me
as my girlfriend?
Hey.
Let's just eat.
Yes, ma'am.
Are we giving a recital?
LIM JUNG-YUN
CHOI SEO-HYEON
OUR MOTHERLY HEE-JI
LOVE YOU, SEO-YEONG
HI, SE-YEON. IT'S SEO-YEONG!
Here.
Moon Se-yeon.
This is way too long!
-Oh Sang-won.
-Thank you.
Hang on. I don't think I can read this.
Se-yeon, I mean what I wrote.
-What?
-I mean what I wrote.
-Seo-yeong!
-I can't read it.
THANKS FOR THE PAST TWO WEEKS.
Se-yeon.
We both had feelings for Ji-woo,
so we could have become
awkward and distant with each other,
but now...
Want to drink beer outside?
Let's go, buddy.
But you always spoke to me first,
and you were so friendly,
so we were able to stay as close friends
and hang out together.
So I'm really grateful.
Let's hang out often after we leave.
Jung-yun.
You seemed to be someone special
from the beginning.
I feel like we've become
really close friends
who can share anything with each other.
And I really hope that
you'll date Ji-woo without any regrets.
And I hope we can continue to be friends
who can keep in touch
and hang out regularly.
Se-yeon, you were the one
who made my heart flutter
when I first entered School 19.
I struggled a fair bit for a while
because of you,
I mean, thanks to you.
But let's root for each other
as good friends.
Ji-min.
Well... I hope
you will care for Ye-rin
as much as I liked you.
I hope I'll see you around. Bye.
Ye-rin!
-Don't cry.
-I'm not crying.
-I cry when I see others cry!
-Who's crying? Hee-ji?
Come on!
She's really crying, though.
-She started crying.
-Why are you crying?
Hey, don't cry! Why would you cry?
I'm not crying.
I'll write you all letters tomorrow.
-Okay.
-You mean it?
I got to know you guys a bit late...
-I remember when he first came.
-He didn't talk at all.
He's totally different now.
I remember how he smiled
while hugging that cushion.
-Oh, that?
-The photo in the lounge.
-This is embarrassing.
-Your smile is great!
Hey, you look so adorable!
-Pyeong-seok.
-Go on.
Thank you for...
-Don't cry!
-What?
Hang on.
It's not like I'll never see them again,
but knowing that it was our last day,
I felt so sad about it.
I...
He's really crying.
-Hey...
-Thanks for taking care of me.
-No!
-Hey!
Don't cry!
-His eyes are red.
-I don't usually...
I start crying when somebody else cries.
-I'm not crying.
-Don't cry.
-He's really crying.
-Come on.
Thanks for taking care of the quiet
and dumb new student.
Oh, no. He's really crying.
-Are you crying, Ji-woo?
-I'm not.
-Thank you!
-Thanks, everyone!
Why do I keep getting teary eyed?
Thinking about Hee-ji just makes me cry.
-Really.
-Hey.
Why are you crying?
Stop crying. I cry if someone else cries.
Hee-ji was always
taking care of the rest of us.
Hee-ji took good care of us
although it must've been tough.
It wasn't tough at all.
It must have been tough.
It must have been so hard.
Choi Seo-hyeon.
Locking eyes with Seo-hyeon made me cry.
We all went through a lot.
I guess we could say the two weeks
were short yet long,
but I think we all managed
our emotions well
and maintained positive feelings.
Thank you for that.
And I am so happy.
Thank you, guys.
Thanks, everyone.
-Thanks.
Our happiness is just starting.
-Right, this is just the beginning.
-Of course.
I want us to remain as friends
and even if we do part...
What do I do?
-That's in your mind already?
-Don't cry.
Even if we part...
You shouldn't be laughing.
Let's all just get along. I'm so happy,
-and I really love you guys.
-Thank you.
Our life in House 20 is over,
but our 20s just started.
To our 20s.
-Cheers!
It was like a blissful memory
of spending my last days as a 19-year-old
and first days as a 20-year-old
with wonderful friends.
I wondered if I'd be able
to feel those emotions again.
I feel like I've matured in many ways.
I believe I'll be a much better person
when I step into society.
I realized and learned
how to be honest about my feelings.
It was a very meaningful time.
I believe all ten of us
were able to have a special experience
compared to other 20-year-olds.
I think we've ended our teenage years
full of happiness,
and the beginning
of our 20s was full of ups and downs.
I believe we were able to learn
and grow a lot.
Living with everyone for two weeks
helped me grow as well.
School 19 was full of joy,
and we spent time
getting to know each other.
Then House 20 allowed us to see
every aspect of each other.
We all grew to care a lot
about each other.
I hope we can all remain friends
for 10 or 20 years after this.
I wish that we had
more time together.
I will never be able to forget
this memory.
I won't be able to forget this experience,
and I thought to myself that it would be
nice to return to House 20 someday.
I hope we can gather here
in winter again someday
and watch the snowfall together.
Nineteen!
-To Twenty!
All right.
Nineteen to Twenty
was like a coming-of-age drama.
Two weeks isn't really a long time
if you think about it.
But the kids seem to have matured a lot.
I learned a lot too.
Like, "I should muster up my courage."
They made me think a lot about
when I was 19 and 20.
I thought about how I was
when I was at that age,
who my friends were at that time,
and how I hung out with them.
Things like that.
And seeing them,
I also wished that their friendship
would last forever.
I was totally immersed.
I felt like I was part of the group.
-I'm rooting for them.
-Yes, right.
I feel like I'll keep thinking
about this for a long time,
and I felt proud seeing them grow
as if I'd raised them myself.
And I feel envious as well.
Seeing them go to sleep feeling excited
about the next day,
I thought to myself that I should
live each day happily and joyfully
without losing spirit.
It's the most innocent
and beautiful time of your life.
The moment you turn 20.
So I felt envious of them.
When I was little,
I just wanted to grow up.
-Right.
-But when I became an adult,
I could understand why grown-ups
want to go back in time.
-We can never go back.
-Right.
Unless we have a Thirty-Nine to Forty...
Thirty-Nine to Forty?
-Instead of Nineteen to Twenty?
-Yeah.
-That'll be fun.
-So...
So I hope a lot of kids
who are just turning 20 will watch this
-and feel their youth too.
-Right, I agree.
-Kids at that age.
-Right.
LAST DAY AT HOUSE 20
It's really our last day?
We're really leaving now.
We're really leaving.
-Bye, House 20!
-Goodbye.
Bye, House 20.
-Shall we go?
-Let's go.
Let's go.
I feel sad.
Time flew by.
Doors closing!
-Let's go.
-Goodbye.
Bye, House 20.
Bye.
We're leaving.
Goodbye!
Say bye.
Bye!
Do you like me? That's all that matters.
Do you want to have dinner
with me tomorrow?
-Dinner?
-Are you down?
I mean, then he shouldn't have
made it sound like he liked me.
I'm a woman. I'm a woman.
You. I wanted to get to know you more.
I'll be the chef today.
-Three!
-Two!
One!
Happy New Year!
Subtitle translation by: Juyoung Park