At the outset, I believe you have a
statement you should read in the record.
Yes, Your Honor.
We are not judges, doctor.
Your Honor
Naturally.
Who is the security point?
The so-called
investigative information.
Your charge against
me says it's impossible.
I understand this quite well outside
the context of my life and work.
How long did he testify?
To be honest, I don't remember.
The whole process
took one month.
Time to know?
I only read the transcripts.
I want to justify their life.
You were not there?
I was not allowed to
do that as president.
Will they really ask?
Years ago
Four years ago.
I meant.
Oppenheimer is
still dividing America.
The Committee will want
to know what his position is.
Senator Thoreau,
don't ask me not to hear.
like in court.
No, it works
differently, just sit down.
Really, Mr. Thoreau?
Absolutely yes.
Admiral Thoreau is an image.
Toto is a formality.
President Eisenhower has
asked you to join his cabinet.
The Senate has no
choice but to confirm it.
And who should they
confirm, Oppenheimer?
When they brought
up Oppenheimer.
Answer honestly.
No senator can deny it.
He accomplished your mission.
He will be uncomfortable.
We will justify all their lives.
Why don't you leave
the United States?
I wanted to study a new physics.
Was it nowhere to be found?
I thought Berkeley had a major
theoretical physics department.
Yes, one side built it.
First I had to go to Europe.
I went to Cambridge to
study with Patrick Blackett.
You are happier
there than in America.
Happier?
Yes.
NO.
No, I'm... nostalgic,
emotionally mature,
Visions of the human
universe disturb me.
You heard laughing.
Hi Oppenheimer
Are you sleeping?
Restart
I have to go to class, sir.
Why?
It reeks of boredom.
I think he's gone.
Naturally.
Let's go
You are not strong, Oppenheimer.
You have completed
the Coachman's Seat.
Quantum physics
is not a step forward.
It is a new way of
understanding reality.
Einstein opened the door.
Now we look through you, we
see the world in us the world is
a world of energy and paradoxes
that not everyone can accept.
Naturally.
Fields, meet J.
Robert Oppenheimer.
What does the
abbreviation J stand for?
Nothing.  Nothing at all.
You are in my class.
Ask the only good question.
No one denies his understanding.
This is laboratory work
that requires some willpower.
I've heard him give
the same answer.
Yes, and you are
asking the same question.
Why are you asking me again?
I want your answer.
Did you like it better yesterday?
Too
You can lift a stone
without they were
ready for the serpent
that appeared.
Now you look ready.
But you don't like the lab.
So walk out of Cambridge
with every glass and potion.
Go to a place that
makes you think.
you have to be born.
Go to Germany.
Works under Max Born.
Learn the methods of the theory.
I will send a message
Or more.
How are you doing with math?
He's not good enough.
The physicist he wanted to be.
Notes similar to algebra.
It is not important that you
know how to read music.
Have you heard?
Can you hear the music, Robert?
Yes, I feel it.
I am interested as Admiral
Strauss, Senator from Wyoming.
Dr. J. Robert Oppenheimer.
Did you meet him in 1947?
Right.
Was he a commissioner of
the Atomic Energy Commission?
I was, but I actually
met Robert at an event.
Board member of the
Institute for Advanced Studies.
World crown at Princeton after the
war, he was a great metaphysician.
I was determined to get
him to run the institute.
Dr. Oppenheimer, Mr
Strauss.
Pronounced Strauss.
Open, Hagar, the name of the war
you served and the land of the Jews.
I am the president of the
Manuel Manhattan Temple.
Strauss is just a
sudden pronunciation.
Anyway, welcome
to the institute.
I think you will be
very happy here.
Yes, if you like
the community, the
escort comes to that
house for your wife
and your two children
Yes, two.
I'm a big fan of your work.
I am very correct about
the education of Mr. Strauss.
Excuse me, I'm
calling the room at four.
You know I'm not trained in physics
or anything, and now I'm on my own.
I can tell it like this.
Really?
Yes, my father was.
This would be your office.
It seems that most of
them exist after that too.
You know, I've
always wondered why.
did not include it in
the Manhattan Project.
of time.
Einstein published
the theory of relativity.
More than 40 years ago.
I remember it was quite
moral and informative.
God does not roll dice.
Exactly.
I've never considered
studying physics, Mr. Strauss.
I had writers, but I
decided to sell shoes.
Louis Strauss was a
men's shoe salesman.
Not just a shoe salesman.
I would like to introduce you.
Louis.
I've known him for years.
Albert.
What was it?
What did you say, O?
Is fine.
Mr. Strauss, you should
know something about my past.
As head of the ADC, I have access
to his security file at Red Hood.
You are not worried.
After all you've done for your
country, why should I be afraid?
Times have changed, Mr. Strauss.
Well, the purpose
of this institute.
provide a haven for
independent minds.
You are
You are the right
man for this job.
Well, I don't think about it.
See you tomorrow
at the ADC meeting.
This is one of the most prestigious
nominations in the country.
Yes.
Great trip
That's why I'm thinking.
Did Dr. Rabinheimer
draw your attention to
past associations before
she mentioned him?
Yes.
And you weren't interested?
But then I was
completely absorbed
Einstein with the things he had
to say to make him mad at me.
But then?
We all know what happened next.
Doctor Yura, his
time in Europe, her.
You seem to have met many
physicists from other countries.
Yes, it's true.
A little Russian?
Not in this matter of reason.
If you'll allow me to continue
my remarks... Stay here.
You will have many
opportunities to cross-select.
After enrolling, I moved to Leiden and
Halbens, where I met for the first time
OK?
Hi Yang.
Lecture on new physics.
I need to hear this.
I am an American.
What a surprise.
Let me know if you
need help with English.
What's written?
No thank you.
The road to Zurich is long.
Here we take each volume.
We will lose you
among the sea cushions.
I am one of them.
I am a knight.
I followed your
lesson on molecules.
I have received some.
We have some
novelties to choose from.
How do you know?
I thought I'd find out too.
But I came here
around this time.
Learned enough
Dutch in six weeks.
to take a course in
quantum mechanics.
I had to challenge myself.
Quantum physics
wasn't hard enough.
Exhibitionism.
Dutch in six weeks, but
you haven't learned it yet.
I'm not just saying it, it's
on my side of the park.
Shit.
You're homesick, or you know it.
If you feel that not everyone
is welcome, it's just...
They are all Jews.
Eat
This is the German you
should be looking for.
Hasbro.
Correct.
can lead to the
following hypothesis:
The quantum world
still hides the real world.
Causality is valid, but these
speculations seem to us wholly fruitless.
Okay thanks.
Good day
What do you think?
Doctor Oliver.
OMG
Yes.
I like your paper
and your molecules.
Probably because
you are inspired.
Let me know if I inspire
you with anything else.
We can publish together.
I have to go back to America.
Why?
Nobody takes quantum
mechanics seriously.
Here because.
He misses the Latin canyons.
The canyons of New Mexico.
Are you from New Mexico?
No, from New York.
But my brother and I have
a ranch outside of Santa Fe.
This is the America
I miss right now.
Then you better go home, cowboy.
Haha.
Here we are.
No, me and the horses.
I do not think so.
Nice to meet you.
Have you ever met
Harrison Burke?
Not separated
No, but it can be said that
our paths have crossed.
I go back to America.
There I accepted positions at
both Caltech and David Burke.
Dr. Lawrence, I assume?
You must have left
while I was working.
Yes.
I heard you want to open
a school of quantum theory.
I'll start next door.
They put you there.
I thought I was closer
to you experimenters.
Theory can only take you so far.
We are building a machine
to accelerate electrons.
Magnificent.
Do you want to help me?
Build?  Negative
Haha.
NO
But I'm working on theories
that I want to test with him.
When do you start teaching?
I'll have the first one in an hour.
A seminar?
Student.
A student
That's all?
I teach something that
no one is trapped in here.
But when people start hearing about
what can be done, they keep coming back.
I... Mr. Lomont?
NO.
Yes.
That's all
Please.
Sitting
What do you know about
quantum mechanics?
I have an overview based on
And you are doing it wrong.
Is light composed
of particles or waves?
The focus is on
quantum mechanics.
How can it be both?
AK But it is.
Paradoxical
And it still works.
Fine thanks.
Mr. Lomont, you'll be fine.
Mr. Snyder.
Now let's think about a star.
A star in a giant
fiery furnace in space.
Fire pushes up
against its own gravity.
Balanced
But if this sentence stacks
up, gravity starts to win.
Bargain
Density increases.
Correct.
Increased gravity.
Increased intensity.
And it's a vicious cycle,
until... What's the limit?
I do not know
You see, when math guides us,
I guarantee you it's a place
no one has ever been before.
AND?
Yes, you and your calculations
are better than mine.
Dr. Abenheimer provided
details and activities at Berkeley.
Why did he file it before
Dr. War Abenheimer?
You'll have to ask Mr. Hoover.
I'm asking you, Admiral Strauss.
Well, I think he was addicted.
leftist political activities.
You shouldn't have had your
politics written in class, Bobby.
I wrote
Lawrence, you have
revolutionized physics.
Do you see it elsewhere too?
Picasso, Stravinsky, Froy,
Marx... This is America.
We made our revolution.
Really.
Stay away from the lab.
My lab roommate is
discussing tonight's dinner.
Interesting.
I did some research on
Berkeley's political climate.
All just the philosophy
graduate students
and communists who
talked about integration.
You are not interested
in integration.
I don't want to talk
about it, I want to vote.
Especially Friday.
Come on, let's eat.
I have to meet my brother there.
And how do these activities run
counter to the purpose of the FBI?
If I remember correctly,
The FBI was taking the plates.
number of meetings of suspected
communists on the island.
Name removed
For the love of God
I am sorry
Honestly, but...
I remember Jackie.
Good night
Robert, I want you to meet John.
Hopin Stavallier,
Dr. Robert Oppenheimer.
Pleasure
This is my little brother Frank.
And this... Always Jackie.
Hello again to Jackie.
Stavallier, you speak in tongues
and your reputation recognizes you.
what you heard
I'm glad you taught me a
new approach to physics.
I do not have the ability to
understand, but I did not hear.
You are a party
member, but I am not.
Not yet
Frank and I agree.
I support a number of policies.
It was a civil war
Democratic republic overthrown
by fascist thugs who don't.
Government
They think the greatest threat
to their fascists is socialism.
Not for long.
Many other Nazis
come from the Jews.
I send money to my colleagues in Germany
so they have a bigger eye to do something.
My old work is very abstract.
What are you working on?
What happens to
stars when they die?
Do the stars die?
If they do, they cool
down and collapse.
In fact, the more massive the star,
the more severe the extinction will be.
Their weight becomes so
dense that they engulf everything.
Anything you might like.
Can it really happen?
The math says it can happen.
If we publish it, maybe one
day an astronomer will find it.
but at the moment i only have one
theory that it can't affect people's life.
Well if you are sending money
Spain, do it through
the Communist Party.
They can take him to the front.
Sorry, I said you
were happy, I'm Jane.
Robert.
Conchobelia, you and I
were on duty last month.
Right, right, yeah.
Well thank you.
Robert claims he
is not a communist.
But he doesn't know enough.
His Wife covers all
three volumes.  Count
He'd make you read the bloodiest
members church or something.
Thinker.  The property is theft.
Property.
Property?
Goods, not pollution.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.  I read
it in the original German.
It's not about the book.
It's about ideas.
And you speak objectively.
I dedicate myself to thinking freely
about how to improve our world.
Why limit yourself to a dogma?
You are a physicist.
You choose the rules.
Or do you use discipline to direct
your energy towards progress?
I clean with the room.
You always speak
along the party line.
I also like my room to
be on the same level.
What?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I've been waiting... What is it?
For a physicist.
You have a shelf full of Freuds.
Well, I actually have more...
Young Ian?
Know the analytics.
I had some trouble in Cambridge.
And you?
I tried to poison my teacher.
Did you hate him?
I really like.
You just have to lie down.
It took my analyst two
years, and I don't think that
I wonder if they have ever
expressed it so succinctly.
Everyone has convinced you that you
are more complex than you really are.
I believe you are
all simple souls.
Reading
What is this?
Sand cream
You can read this
Reading
Read this
This is where the fish leave the
low arm system.  Do you know that
Read the words
And now I'm dead.
Worlds destroyed.
That's all.
A little break before dawn.
It will get colder
during the night.
Just before dawn.
No break
So I will get married.
Frank, congratulations.
Thanks Jackie
Yes, for Jackie.
Garlic
I will be your rightful owner.
He relaxes
I will see him
talk to the stars.
All your talk about
the common man.
Jackie is not enough for you.
We join the party and you can
no longer hide your discipline.
Why?
Why is it worth it?
I didn't sign up
for a party, Frank.
And I don't think he had
to convince you of that.
Half the faculty is gone.
Yes, it's half.
I'm your brother, Frank,
and I want you to be careful.
And I want to steal your neck.
I will not live my life with
the fear of making mistakes.
You are happy
I am happy
I'm glad you're
happy that I'm happy.
When you look, I see one of the
dark stars you've been working on.
You can not
It is the entire center of
gravity that absorbs light.
It's like some kind
of hole in space.
Is Frank okay?
Yes.
He's just a fucking
brother talking.
When I was little, I
thought if I could find a way
combine physics and New Mexico,
my life would have been perfect.
Is it a bit far for that?
Yes.
Let's sleep a bit.
Today we saw New Mexico.
One of my favorite
places in the world.
Tomorrow's weather
What is his name?
Poplars
I didn't expect
to see you today.
I'll have to make
an appointment.
Robert
Tommy!
What?
What is that?
They did it.
They disintegrated
the uranium core.
WELL?
I'm worried about neutrons.
It's nuclear fission.
They did it.
They split the atom
Stop my skull
I will try to reproduce it.
Can you see it?
It can not be done.
Very stylish.
Very clear
There is only one problem.
Where is it?
Another door.
Alvarez did it
You see
These fission pulses are huge.
I've seen 30 in
the last 10 minutes.
Theory can only take you so far.
During the process an
external transport office
can be used to transfer
more uranium atoms.
Chain reaction
You are thinking what I think.
You're strange
Every other physicist in
the world has seen you.
Are you wondering
what we are all thinking?
Bomba, Alvarez.
Bomb
I told you Rob, no
more bullshit flowers.
I do not understand what you want.
I don't want anything from you.
But you say it and then you call.
Do not answer
I always answer
Naturally.
Only there are no more flowers.
They are arriving
You need to know when
you're defeated, Robert.
It's not that simple, okay?
Barlier, it's good to see you.
We don't have
Barbara, nice to see you.
And the famous Dr. Rottenheimer.
Like Alton Tippett.
NO
What's wrong with
me, please, please?
May I say a few words
about organized work?
It's passing, it's passing.
I work at Shell.
We turn to chemists
and engineers.
There is science
in this position.
Teachers are unionized.
Why?  Professors.
Don't have a place to stay?
Lawrence, also legal academics.
Look, it's not that.
A group is coming.
Let's go in.
Not this one
That's all.  Dr. Bush.
What brought you north?
Richard, tell Ruth I'll show
you around on Thursday.
April black holes, here it is!
Where's Harvard?
Take Harvard.
September 1, 1939.
The world removes this thing.
Harlan, our newspaper
goes to press.
You were at the top of the leaderboard.
I lost more and more sympathy
during the Battle of Britain.
with a policy of neutrality
supported by the Communists.
Hitler invaded Russia
and we became allies.
Will these communists
simply organize their return?
NO
I should clarify that my
changed views on Russia
it did not imply a clean break with
those who held different opinions.
For a year or two during
my previous marriage, my
wife Kitty was a member
of the Communist Party.
It is true.  It's a good thing.
I love it, Mr. Paulman.
I live with them,
I'm from the port.
do you believe in something?
Look at Ruthie.
So you are a biologist.
Somehow I graduated
to be a housewife.
Can you explain
quantum mechanics to me?
It looks bad
Yes it is.
Well, it's glass.
It's a drink.
This is a work plan.
Our bodies
Everything
Mostly empty space.
Clusters of small
interconnected energy waves.
What is that?
Attractive forces strong
enough to convince us.
it is solid.
It's not my body
passing through yours.
You are married to Dr. Harrison.
I'm not married
There's someone I feel...
That's how they feel.
Sometimes I don't know.
You know, going to New Mexico,
you should come to
my farm with my friends.
I met your husband
Yes, you have met him
Because you know there
won't be a better difference.
Why did you marry him?
I'm lost
He was a good person.
You lost?
Your previous husband is dead.
At 28 she was not yet
ready to become a widow.
Who is your first husband?
Nobody
My second husband
was Joe Dallad.
he was full of money, like me.
but he was a union
organization in Youngstown, Ohio.
What a difficulty.
How hard is that?
The next four years are going to be tough
enough to live on beans and pancakes.
They were returning the
Daily Worker to Regatta.
At 36, I told Joe I
couldn't take it anymore.
Leave the party
Then you want it back.
He is not a day laborer.
He sleeps well and will
meet you on my trip to Spain.
I'm going to a lawless country
Then he went to
Regatta and I waited.
TO...
Joe killed himself the first time
he pulled his head out of the ditch.
My ideology killed Joe.
For nothing.
What kind of republic
is this?  Nothing?
My husband offered
to come both to avoid it.
so that a fascist bullet
stuck in the mudbag.
This is the
definition of nothing.
It seems a bit reductive to me.
Magnetic
Now I'm here
Who the hell is that?
I didn't hear anyone
else in either unit.
At least you didn't
bring me flowers.
Two in one, that's not
what you want, Jane.
Yes, but the door is closing.
NO
As far as I'm concerned, no.
You knocked him
down.  Don't work too fast.
I can't hold a good man.
Yes.
I need him.
He knew what he wanted.
And the husband?
We were talking.
They are divorcing.
So we can get married
before it starts manifesting.
I would have asked.
Idiot.  This is your community.
Think the rules don't
apply to the Golden Child?
Bright strokes abounded.
Don't alienate the only people in the
world who understand what you're doing.
You may need them someday.
FAED
Federation Dext Department.
Engineers, chemists, technicians.
brightness.
How much do you get per month?
The point is nothing.
What does all this have
to do with agriculture?
workers and longshoremen?
Too
All out?
NO!
Is not you
What are you doing?
This is a union.
FAED We have been
dealing with this for a long time.
I would like to try to forgive you.
They won't let me take you to the
project because of this nonsense.
They won't even let me
say what the project is.
I know what the project is.
Really?
We've all heard of Einstein
and Sitter's letter to Roosevelt.
He warned him that the
Germans might build a bomb.
And I know what it meant
for the Nazis to have a union.
But not me?
I'm not your people.
They vandalized the field.
this is me
You think I'm telling
them about your politics.
When you come
home from a meeting,
Do not look in the
rear view mirror
don't listen to the
voices on the phone
get in line and
stop being so naive.
I really care about what I do.
Because you're not just pretentious.
You are really important.
Certain.
And if you can be
a little pragmatic..,
I'll talk to lenders,
I'll talk to others.
You do not have to worry.
It's all right.
Alliance.
Then comes the war.
I filled out my first safety
questionnaire and was good to go.
I have reportedly
joined leftist groups
my work on the atomic
program will not lie.
Why wasn't this done during
the communist associations?
were wars seen as
a security bailout?
Senator, I can't
answer due to security.
I looked into Grant's background
years before I met him.
What's up?
And what will happen now?
After the war,
Dr. Oppenheimer was one of the
most respected scientific
voices in the world.
That's why I asked
him to join the Institute.
He was then a consultant to
the Atomic Energy Commission.
And who is he?
They really blame me for this.
I think they just want to know what
happened between 1947 and 1947.
1954, to change his mind about
Oppenheimer's authorization.
I wasn't.  I was president
of the AEC, but he was not.
I'm the one who made the
accusations against Robert.
Who did it?
I am a former employee
of the United Congress.
Advise.  Here is the rabid
anti-communist Borton.
He wrote to the FBI
and asked to intervene.
The FBI doesn't
go to the AEC, Rick.
And you get a
knife in your hand.
Did Borton have a son?
It was the McCarthy era.
People lost their
jobs because of him,
He was caught reading
Oppenheimer's security file.
brother, sister and girlfriend,
best friend, minister's wife.
Even before boarding
the AEC institute.
How does Borton get access
to Oppenheimer's security file?
Because someone gave it to him.
Someone would also have
observed Robert's silence.
WEAVING?
Who knows.  Robert was
careful not to get angry.
Power brokers in Washington.
His views on the atom
have been defined.
And he always lacked
patience with us mortals.
I have been subjected
to many cruel treatments.
The AEC votes on the
export of isotopes to Norway.
And they designed it to
make me look stupid, Robert.
But, Dr. Oppenheimer, we learned
from Admiral Stross what happened.
Isotopes could be useful to our
enemies for building atomic weapons.
Countess Menyuk used the Space
Shuttle to build atomic weapons.
And what have you done?
You can use a bottle of beer
to create atomic weapons.
You actually did.
I'd say the isotopes are
less useful than the electronic
ones in weapons, but
more useful than a sandwich.
Genius is no
guarantee of wisdom.
Look at this man
who sees me so blind.
kittens?
Received.
I'm there
I am in
Let's celebrate
Don't you have to go?
I've been looking
for it all day.
I do not know how to say it.
I'm embarrassed to ask.
Something?
Marry Peter.
Naturally.
I've known him for a while, Hulk.
An.
Does the kitty know you?
Yes, of course he knows you.
Of course he knows.
We are terrible people.
Selfish and terrible people.
He forgets I asked you.
They do not know
They are selfish and awful.
Sit down, sit down, sit down.
Robert, you see beyond
the world we live in.
This has to be paid for.
Of course we will help you.
Everything changes, Robert.
Boy Harry has always changed.
The world is turning
in a new direction.
reform the world
This is your moment.
We are forming a working group.
We have to do everything.
You have to.
Lawrence can't do it.
We were told, “Monor
Ravi, you will make it”.
Who are the unicorns?
I thought you might have them.
Roger, Robert, this
is Colonel Brooks.
This is Lieutenant
Colonel Nichols.
Get a drag link.
That's how you treat
a lieutenant colonel.
I have come to see how the
humble are treated, this is his son.
I'll let you know if I
meet him one day.
How much?
Theaters of war
around the world.
But I have to stay
in Washington.
Why?
I built the Pentagon.
Nebraska liked it so much that they let me take
over the engineering district in Manhattan.
Which?
Whatever it is
The biggest smartass.
You know very well what it is.
You and half the physics
departments in the country.
This is problem number one.
I thought the number one problem
was finding enough uranium ore.
1200 tons
I bought it the
same day I bought it.
Is it processed?
Work begins in Oak
Ridge, Tennessee.
I am looking for a
project manager.
And my name came up.
NO
Even if it brought quantum physics
to America, which gave me pause.
What did you discover?
You are a dilettante, a womanizer
and a suspected communist.
I'm a New Deal Democrat.
I said suspicious
Unstable, theatrical,
selfish, neurotic.
There is no good.
No, he's not even a genius.
In your environment, on the other
hand, brilliance is taken for granted.
then no
The only person who had
anything to say was Richard Tolman.
Tolman thinks
you're being honest.
But he also seems to me a person who
knows more about science than people.
And here you are.
You don't need a lot of trust.
I take nothing for granted.
Why don't you
have a Nobel Prize?
Why aren't you a general?
That's what they made me for.
Maybe I'll have the same chance.
Nobel prize for
building the bomb?
Add the Nobel
prize for dynamite.
And how to proceed?
You're talking about
turning theory into a
practical weapons system
faster than the Nazis.
We have a 12 month head start.
18.
How do you know?
Our search for fast
neutrons lasted six months.
A man who was doubted would
make an immediate discovery.
Who do you think
they put in charge?
Bernard Heisenberg
The most intuitive understanding
of atomic structure he's ever seen.
Know your job.
I know him as well as Walter.
Both Isaac and Diebner, we
Germans win his direct competition.
We have only one hope
and that is... anti-Semitism.
What Hitler called
quantum physics
Jewish science is the
opposite of Einstein, we
can only hope that Hitler
was so blinded by hatred
Heisenberg's denial
of his own sources,
because it will require
enormous resources.
The best scientists in our
country are currently working
together, they are disorganized,
which gives us space.
To contribute effectively, all
brains must see the task as a whole.
Poor safety can make
us inefficient at running.
The Germans know
more than we do.
The Russians don't.
You remind me
who we're fighting?
Someone with your background doesn't
want to be seen as underestimating them.
the importance of the
security of our communist allies.
We understand it, but
we don't understand it.
You can't tell me no.
My job is to tell you
no, and you're wrong.
So do you already have a job?
Think
I'm starting to understand
where his fame comes from.
My favorite answer is that Oppenheimer
couldn't run a hamburger stand.
I couldn't do it
But I can handle the
Manhattan Project.
It's just a way to
balance things out.
Establish a proper laboratory
under Lawrence here in Berkeley.
He recognized it
in his Chicago lab.
A large number of search
terms in Tennessee.
in Hanford
All America, industrial, mining,
scientific innovation, connected
by railroad, to a single point in
space and time, to a single goal.
And here it all comes together.
A secret laboratory in
the middle of nowhere.
A safe and self-sufficient
structure that hosts the works.
Keep everyone there
until the job is done.
They will need a
school, shop or church.
Why?
If we don't allow scientists to bring their
families, we will never have the best.
And do you want to
create security in the city?
Build fast.
Where is it?
Welcome to Los Alamos.
There is a boys school
which will have two things in
common and local Indians
can be prepared for burial rights.
But nothing.
40 miles in any direction.
I have to find the
perfect place for success.
Build a city fast.
We hire scientists.
Why do I need my parents?
I told you you can
bring your family.
I'm not a soldier.
I am a soldier
This is a general
I have all the soldiers I need.
What can I say?
How does it look to you?
NO?
They were both bored.
What do these men
have in common?
The greatest points of
view on atomic theory.
Understood?
As many as you want
Can you smell my
food in your balls sir?
You know isotopes and explosives
better than anyone in the world.
But you can't tell
us what you did.
I don't know if the
Nazis will have them.
Messengers in
Nazi-occupied Copenhagen.
Has Princeton stopped
printing newspapers?
Why go to the middle of
nowhere for who knows how long?
For a year, two or three.
Imagine the country.
Give us a minute.
It is about unleashing
a powerful force.
Not before the Nazis.
OMG
The hills don't
work for the Nazis.
Never.
They are owned by them
Not us
That's why I need you.
Why do you think
I should do this?
Why?
And if that was the
most important thing
Something that has never
happened in the history of the world?
And this?
I do not think so
They won't let me
leave this project.
And I can't get
security clearance,
for a career even after the war.
So you are travel companions.
One of them
This is a national emergency.
I have skeletons.
They entrusted me.
They need us.
Until they do.
Is there a chance to
get bored in Denmark?
Yes, no way.
I checked with the British.
There's no other way until we can get
the allied ships back to the continent.
Is it that important?
How many people do you
know in real dance time, Paul?
It would really be
faster to go by plane.
No, the plane is too risky.
The country needs us.
Dad, guys, it's not a building.
That's it for the cyclotron.
Count the architects
When is this place
supposed to open?
Two months
Robin, you're a great improviser,
but this... doesn't work in your head.
Four topics
Experimental
Theoretical
Memory diary
Transcending theory.
As?
Here's what I was afraid of.
You smeared it too much.
So in theory, take it.
I'm not coming here, Robin.
Why?
Throw a bomb and it will
fall on the just and the unjust.
I do not wish the
peak of three physical
centuries were a weapon
of mass destruction.
And he?
I don't know if such a
weapon can be trusted.
But I know the
Nazis can't do that.
We have no other choice.
The second thing to do is list
Holmes Bethe will head
the theoretical department.
Ray, first things first... Take
off that ridiculous uniform.
You are a scientist.
Groves insists we unite.
Tell Groves to go fuck his hat.
They need us as we are.
Then be yourself.
It's better.
This is the only key.
The cashiers are already here.
I can show you?
No, let's wait for the others.
let's begin
Device.
Yes Madam.
So we'll be working here until the
Los Alamos T section is finished.
Edward, can I?
This is more important.
Can I calculate
the chain reaction?
I find this possibility
quite disturbing.
No, but it can't be a lie.
Show me how you
created your population.
Yes.
It's a fantasy.
The teller's calculations
cannot be corrected.
Do you know what I
have in Princeton, sir?
What is it for?
I talked to Einstein.
There are not many
comments on the truth.
That's why I need to
know his point of view.
Albert.
No, Dr. Albert Heidman.
How did you meet Dr. Gert?
We come here almost every day.
Things are the most
inspiring structures.
Albert, I have to tell you something.
Of course not.
I was just reading.
Some days she refuses to read.
Even in Princeton he believes
that the Nazis can poison his food.
Whose world is this?
scrutineer
What does it mean?
Vchod, broken
heart, püstüte mum.
Entry, entry into other nuclei.
What can criticality do, a great
irreversible explosive power?
Stopping time of
a chain reaction.
It would set the atmosphere on fire.
If we blow up the atomic
device, we can launch
a chain reaction that
could destroy the world.
So are we here?
Lost in a quantum world made
of probabilities and certainties.
Can you do the calculations yourself?
NO
The only thing you and I have in
common is that we despise math.
Who is working on
this project in Berkeley?
Hans Beidman
All right, you'll find the truth.
What if it was a real disaster?
Then you stop and share
your findings with the Nazis.
So neither side is
destroying the world.
Albert,
this is yours, not mine.
house cashier,
He is at home
Now that you've told us the critical
assumptions, a picture emerges.
Scheme
The probability is not there until
the nuclear reaction approaches zero.
Nearly zero?
This is good news.
Can you make them work again?
No, you will get
the same answer.
Until you fire one
of these, that's
the best guarantee
you'll ever get.
Almost zero.
Space can only take you so far.
HI.
We miss
You want to adopt a child
He's kidding
We wanted to see you.
What have we left
For the unknown parties.
Do you know who I
met the other day?
Eltonton.
Michelle McAllister
Are you a new man?
Yes, a FAZIO man.
He complained about
our handling of the war.
Plus the lack of
cooperation with our allies.
The government does not appear to be
sharing any research with the Russians.
He said most scientists
think politics is stupid.
Yes.
If someone has something
he wants to pass on,
he bypassed the official
channels where he could be of help.
He will lead to self-production.
Yes, certainly.
I thought you should know.
Bra underneath
We are drinking martinis.
We arrive directly.
There he struck
up a conversation.
Nothing in our long friendship
would make me believe that.
Chevelia was actually
looking for information.
and I'm sure he had no
idea what I was doing.
It had already been clear to me for some time
that I should report the incident immediately.
Oppenheimer's case highlights
the tension between scientists
and hopes of learning how
to make a safety device.
the candidate dealt with these
issues during his tenure at ABC.
A scientist will appear
before the commission.
They are carrying them.
Didn't they tell you?
Mr. President, if I may, I have been nominated
for the position of Commercial Secretary.
Why?
Ask scientists
for their opinion.
The toilet is a column table.
We're looking for a
broad range of opinions.
I would like to know the names
of the scientists who testified.
I want to be able
to cross search.
This is not a process.
Formality?
Unconfirmed since 1925 no
presidential cabinet
appointments.
Here's how to play.
In your pocket, Lewis.
Then play well.
Are they bringing scientists?
You don't know scientists
like me, counselor.
Everyone is annoyed by judgmental
questions, especially everyone.
I was president of ABC.
I can easily be blamed
for things going wrong.
But we cannot allow the Senate to
take over the scientific community.
He doesn't support you, sir.
Or should we?
What happened?
invasive
I fought Oppenheimer
in the United States.
I don't think it's
time to talk about it.
Is there anyone we can call
to find out what happened?
Tell him
They will make a
good impression.
Can you find out the names of
the scientists they are looking for?
Most likely
Find out if he lived in Chicago
or Los Alamos during the war.
Who cares?
If he lived in Chicago, they
too worked on their own.
silver to confirm that
there is no obvious cult.
Poplars
Robert built this place.  He
was the founder of the Air Sheriff.
He honored him with a.
This means a greeting.
no kitchen
Billy
What was it?
Barbed wire
Weapons
Naturally.
Burnt war, Hans.
Halifax
1917.
Carver's ship carrying
ammunition explodes in the harbor.
A large and sudden
chemical reaction.
The largest man-made
explosion in history.
Now let's calculate how
much more destructive it will be.
it was a nuclear reaction,
not a chemical reaction.
Express the force
in tons of TNT.
But it would be Salsas.
Then kill all shades.
Using U-235, the bomb
will need... I'm sorry
The bomb will need a
33-pound ball of this size.
Or, using plutonium,
a 10 kg ball.
Here's the amount of uranium
Oakwood refined last month.
And Hanford's plan
with Antonio this month.
Now we can enrich these quantities.
We have to find a way to detonate them.
Are we boring him, Edward?
Partially yes.
I asked why.
We all knew that an
effective bomb was possible.
How about leaving
him something new?
For example?
We use hydrogen instead
of uranium or plutonium.
Heavy hydrogen
deuterium.  You see,
we shrug under heavy
pressure to trigger
a fusion reaction.
And we don't buy
kilotons, we buy megatons.
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
How do you generate enough
energy to fuse hydrogen atoms?
Small goldfish.
Since we'll need it anyway,
let's get back to work.
The isotope question was
not the most important one.
Disagreement in politics
with Dr. Abenheimer.
It was a hydrogen bomb, right?
Colleagues, we agreed to
disagree and agreed on many issues.
One of them was the need
for the H-bond program.
Yes.
Banks, convenient and quickly.
I know, take me.
What do we know
One of our B-29s in the North
Pacific has detected radiation.
Do we have any filter papers?
There is no doubt what it is.
White House officials
have been fired.
I fear it is an illusion.
Are they filter papers
for long range detection?
This is an atomic test.
The Russians have the bomb.  We
should be years ahead of them, but...
What were you doing at Los
Alamos with the safety tank?
Of course it was.
You were not there.
I'm sorry doctor.
But I was there.
Now we can deal with the
mechanics of the explosion itself.
Some idea?
I call it "shooting".  Burning
a piece of fissionable material
to the larger sphere with enough
force to reach a critical point.
what do we think?
I was thinking of an implosion.
the balls explode inside
and crush the material.
I would like to explore this idea.
I'll talk to the Ordinance.  Okay,
you're blowing everything up.
Push forward
It's a pleasure for
me to see you too.
Meet the British contingent.
This is Oppenheimer.  And Suks?
How long have you been English?
Ever since Hitler told
me I wasn't German.
I have a stamp in Los Alamos.
Suppose I ran?
Distant?  It always works.
This is one of the many
ways we support employees.
Is it Mr. Silver?
Yes i did it.  I have offered jobs to
all men, librarians, for the computer.
Downsizing, keep
families together.
Are these women qualified?
Do not be ridiculous.
These are some of the
brightest minds in our community.
And they are already
safe, they are clean.
I've notified General
Grills that you will.
lead local deficit
discussions each evening.
Turn them off.  Compartmentation
is the key to safety.
Only the best men.  Who can
communicate with subordinates?
These men are not stupid.
They might have some common sense.
I don't like.  You dislike
nothing enough to take a fair test.
Once a week.  Only the best men.
We want to bring my
brother here.  Negative.
I'm Nicholas.
I'm still nervous about
the security clearance.
It's there and...
Go to Chicago tomorrow.
No, you have to wait.
You know the Nazis
started two years early.
Albenheimer, the
truth about your security
hard to get certified,
it's not my fault.
It's yours?
Maybe it's not your
fault, but it's your problem.
Why am I leaving
And how many people participated
in these open discussions?
Too many departments
should have been logged.
You are in the race against the Nazis.
No, the contest is
against the Soviets.
Not before starting.
Robert, the starting
gun has just been fired.
What is the nature of the
price of their detonators?
The Daily reported that these
are plutonium detonation devices.
Like the one built
at Los Alamos.
The Russians have a bomb.  Truman
needs to know what's going to happen.
What's next?
Talk about weapons.
He's talking about weapons.
Naturally.
What other superman does Truman know?
Will we become famous for this?
Not particularly.
We still don't know if he
underwent a hydrogen operation.
Technically feasible.
It is true.  From what I understand,
it was the cashier who suggested it.
Yes.
The teller design has
always been wild is not
practical.  You will have
to deliver it with an ox cart.
It's not a plane not me
Doctor Albinheimer bread.
He's coming
NO.
Because if he can get us
going again, the President
The United States needs to know.
And if the Russians
know about it since then
He's a Los Alamos
spy, so we should go.
There is no evidence
of a spy at Los Alamos.
Robert.
Put it under a football stadium.
It won't work in the morning.
Likewise
Poppy, it's time to get down to business.
What was that?
My marriage
Yes, do you have a small town?
Yes, I'm at sea.
How can one trade
in such a place?
Everyone goes crazy.
Thank you for your trust, Soled.
Are we really thinking
about this nose thing?
Will you try?
We did
A diversified and self-sustaining
nuclear chain reaction.
Did any group tell you that?
Dr Albinheimer?
I tried with the staff.
I asked if I should write it.
You can do it?
Harvard forgot to teach it in its
chemistry undergraduate program.
London, leave our sword here.
What the hell are you doing in Chicago?
Visiting men.
Why?
You can not
We have all rights.
You only have the
rights I grant you.
Neither more nor less.
We are adults looking
to start a project.
This is ridiculous.
Tell him
Separation is the
protocol we agreed on.
Enough of this madness, no
one can work in these conditions.
You know it?
General Lee Simo, I'm done.
Thanks for nothing.
Better without him.
Are you no longer worried
about his common sense?
We will have him killed.
I am joking.
It's me, not America.
General, not everyone
has trumps like me.
I don't think I understand.
You wouldn't hire me
despite my background.
That's why you hired me.
So you can check me out.
No, I'm not that kind.
I'm just a humble soldier.
You are neither
humble nor just a soldier.
You studied engineering at MIT.
Guilty of being guilty.
Well, now we understand each other.
Maybe you can give me
my security clearance.
so I can do this
miracle for you.
General Groves, Doctor Open
On the left when
did you name him?
I knew there were
doubts about him.
I knew he had a very
liberal background.
Do you think you could ever
knowingly engage in unfaithful behavior?
I'd be surprised if he did.
He had full confidence
in his honesty.
Alamos.
Yes, that's exactly
how I recognized him.
General, your security
guards on the project
He advised you not to ask
Dr. Oppenheimer's permission.
They couldn't and wouldn't
clean it until I insisted.
And we can say with certainty
that you had a good experience.
Information on
Dr. Oppenheimer's safety dossier.
I'm not
I have only one
question to answer today.
In light of current AEC guidelines,
Dr. Oppenheimer's endorsement?
Do you have any directions?
Under current AEC rules,
Dr. Openheimer today?
Physics and New Mexico?
OMG
No number
That's why you
need to communicate.
My name is Lominance.
It will all be fine
This way, gentlemen.
I have two hearts.
Ms. Lee, I'd like to remind you
of what we discussed in Berkeley.
Department, I
totally understand.
I'm here to update you on our
progress and to ask for your input.
I'll have to share a
few things for this.
Things General
Groves told me not to do.
Sorry, general, I
said I understood.
Not that I agree.
Well, guys, work.
There were unsubstantiated
rumors of espionage by Los Alamos.
It is assumed that there were Communists
knowingly involved in the project.
I just want to know if anyone is
having discussions with Super.
I remember you asked your
brother to come to Los Alamos.
Meanwhile, my
brother left the party.
And Lominance?
Lominance was never
used at Los Alamos.
He was a collector.
As ex-Colonel Nichols was well aware,
our security arrangements were strict.
Our security was
as tight as possible.
notable personalities, but
attempts have been made.
What does it mean?
We have read all
your posts here.
Do we need to talk
about Gene Tatlock?
Or the Chevalier story?
Excuse me
Just a minute.  Just a minute
Hi Rusty
What?
Okay, calm down.
They just enlisted Lominance.
We're at war, Doctor.
Don't be an idiot,
Nichols.  We need this guy.
Can you fix it?
It wasn't a mistake.
Your friend Lominance
was trying to assemble
the radiation lab.
You promised yourself
you'd finish it all.
Well, he doesn't.
The Berkeley security
guard is concerned about
Communists infiltrating the
FA FACD through this union.
Anyway, next week I'll
be there and visit him.
Your education has passed.
It is important that you do not maintain
or renew any suspicious relationship.
Doctor, social relationships
between one person and another,
Who engages in covert warfare
and are communists dangerous?
Today I would be
more aware of the risks.
It is fair to say that
during the war years:
they believed such contacts
were potentially dangerous.
Are we unthinkably dangerous?
Really?
No communist
You see
For a long time I have had
many secrets in my head.
It doesn't matter who I go out with.
I will not talk about these secrets.
You said in your statement that you
must have seen Gene Tatlock in 1943.
He walked away.
Not a word.
What did you think you were doing to me?
Written by
Pages of nothing.
Where did you go?
I can not tell you.
Why?
Because you are a communist.
Why did you have to see it?
He said he wanted to
see me before he left.
I couldn't do it at the time,
but I felt he needed to see me.
He was in psychiatric care.
He was extremely unhappy.
Did you find out why
he has to see you?
He sat there with me.
You spent the
night together, right?
Yes.
You walk in and out of my life
without having to tell me why.
And this power.
Not that I like it.
I'd rather be here for
you than need you.
But now you have other priorities.
I have a wife and a son.
Neither of them talk about it.
Gene, you asked me to come.
And I'm glad I did.
But I can't see you anymore.
But what if I need you?
You said you'd always answer.
Is it a word?
Did you think that was consistent
with uncertainty?  It actually was.
Slovakian Ani
Did you see it after?
I never saw him again.
I can take the last
train to Princeton.
I didn't tell you anything
that I already told you.
Isn't this the day
to tell the tale?
It's very close to you.
If not, we'll use the
transcript and show it to you.
I will send it
You ask me when
did you see Geno?
No, you... You're sitting there.
Every day we let them
tear our lives apart.
Why don't you fight?
Dad, I'm not putting it in there.
Doctor Rama, this is art.
Please sit down.
Maybe... I just wanted
to see if I could do it.
Considering your concerns, he should have
spoken to you in more minutes while I was here.
I'd say it's up to you,
professor, but I'd be careful.
She understood
And as for the Union,
I wanted you and
a man named Elton
to watch your back.
Attention?
Yeah, maybe he's
watching it himself.
I would like to
have more details.
I have an idea, but now and
tomorrow I will leave early.
I'll be back anytime,
if you have time.
You came back the next morning.
I did, I had to.
Really?
This time there
was a different man.
He said his name was Pasha.
Pas.
You met Colonel Pasha.
Colonel Pash, please.
Is he reading his
memorandum of June 29, 1943?
Recommended by the
monitoring results of the subjects
other possible links with
the Communist Party.
Subject met a person
and spent a lot of time
From Gene, Tatlock, a
communist, whose card is attached.
It's about Dr. Raupmanhund.
Yes.
The person you haven't met yet.
Not that, but right after.
He's the project's head of
security, shouldn't I know him?
No, he should recognize you.
I will never put you in the
same room with Pasha.
Why?
When Pash found out, he told
the FBI he was going to kidnap him.
board the ship and interrogate
him the Russian way.
General Groves has given
me some responsibilities.
and its like having a
baby and i cant see it.
I have a remote.
So we need you.
I won't take up much of your time.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll tell you the truth.
Mr. Johnson told me about
yesterday's conversation.
that he really interested me.
He said he worked all day.
Yes, I didn't want to talk to
Luminance without permission.
I have no particular
interest, but...
something more, I
think more serious.
Now that the FBI has
highlighted such a thing.
the information will not
be admissible in court,
Pash made it clear that
he didn't have that intention.
Leave no witnesses
for the prosecution.
The FBI talked him out of it, but
he's the guy you were dancing with.
Did you hear that together
there are also other parties
interested in the work of
the radiation laboratory?
A man of the Soviet Council
through the law of mediation
who was able to convey information
to people involved in the project.
NO,
Honestly, I see it happening.
argument that the commander-in-chief
must provide information
The Russians are
allies after all, but I don't
like the idea of ​​it going
through the back door.
Maybe that wouldn't be bad.
I'll keep an eye on it.
And did you tell the Pasha?
I was trying to place it in the
context of Russia, not Germany.
Ors Pash is the son of a
Russian Orthodox bishop.  he born
here but returned to Russia
in 1918 to fight the Bolsheviks.
This is a man who killed the
Communists with his own hands.
I don't decide who has
information and who doesn't.
It's my job to legally
prevent him from graduating.
Can you be a
little more specific?
There is a man whose name has
been mentioned a few times.  Eltonton.
I think he's a Shell chemist.
He was talking to a friend who
knew someone from the project.
And he thought he would be fine?
Tried to give them
Eltonton without opening it.
A can of worms, a rooster
for you and a ghost, I told them.
Do you let the general grow too?
Negative.  I confess
to him that I want to die.
Do you remember his
speech on the Chevalier affair?
I've seen too many versions, but
I've never gotten confused before.
but now I will definitely come.
What was your conclusion?
A typical American student
is under the influence of
the idea that there is
something wrong to tell a friend.
Naturally.  When can we
expect to be contacted?
People who are not included
in this project are not included.
Is this person a
member of the project?
Faculty member yes,
but not project member.
So Eltonon made his approach
Through a Berkeley
faculty member?
As far as I know, yes.  More
people could have been involved.
If I sound uncooperative, I
think you can understand why.
I can't accept my insistence on
keeping innocent people out of trouble.
You're trying to protect your
partner.  Who is protecting you?
You did it.  If you gave me a name,
you are giving me an order.  I will do it.
It's a mistake, Robert.  You
must enter this name voluntarily.
Why are you without?
He did, but that's
not the point, is it?
Negative Negative.  It actually
happened a few months later, right?
It was not like this.
It seems that he is
the one who insists.
Well, you... you're
pushy, but that's your job.
And my job is to protect
the people who work for me.
Instead of going through some
steps that may distract you and
might interest you, I would like
to talk to you about them first.
I'm making a plan, I'll
have to digest everything.
In the months
between your interview
and Dr. Oppenheimer
and his possible name
Knight, you have
wasted resources.
are you trying to find out
the name of the broker?
Relevant sources, yes.  Our
anonymous activity was extremely difficult.
And when did you get your name?
When Oppenheimer
proposed, he walked out.
distant?
They thought it would be better
to spend my time in Europe.
Where can I find the status
of the Nazi bomb project?
Who made it?
General Groves.
He moved me to London.
It's a little early for
a Christmas party.
Something is happening.
Looks like he's gone.
Where is it?
The ancient city of Ruth.
Come on, think about it.  You
can't tell me who you can tell.
What makes you
think I know where it is?
Because you know damn well what
Mr. Dorman is when it comes to him.
Like now?
Attention!
An early Christmas
present for you all.
The British driver caught me on the basketball court.
They filled me up with oxygen, but I screwed it up.
I was unconscious when
I opened in Scotland.
But I pretended to sleep.
It's a core group.
Big enough to end the war.
Heisenberg called
me in Copenhagen.
I'm cold, my former
student worked for the Nazis.
He said a few
things to get me out.
Permanent fission
reactions in uranium.
It looks more like a reactor than a bomb.
Did you mention gas diffusion?
It seemed more
focused on heavy water.
As a moderator?
Yes, instead of graphite.
What?
He went the wrong way.
Or head.
And you were here
to help us, Nils?
Will you excuse us for a moment?
I wasn't here to help Robert.
I knew you could
make it without me.
where do you come from?
We'll talk later.
The power you are about to
unleash will leave the Nazis forever.
And the world is not ready.
You took the stone unprepared
for the pain that would result.
We need to let politicians know
that this is not a new weapon.
It's a new world.
I'll do my best
there, except for you.
You are the Prometheus of America.
The man who gave them the
power to destroy themselves.
And they will respect it.
And your work
will start very soon.
Sorry, Oppie, but I got a call.
Zo San Francisco.
Robert
What happened?
My father called
We found it in the
bathtub yesterday.
WEAVING?
He took some pills
He left a note when he saw it.
He was taking barbiturates
with Nils Chloraleiride in his blood.
There was a note.
He looked out of the castle.
We were together
Said you needed me, I...
I do not know
I do not do it.
I can not come
No, it wasn't me.  It was me.
you can't come to the city.
the whole nose stinks, so
every particle has an outcome.
Poor insult, Dickens.
It will be clear that
he will bow to you.
Donald, would you like
to contribute here please?
you're awake
Mom, I won't quit my job
because plutonium is radioactive.
We don't know what it can do to
the female reproductive system.
Your reproductive system
is more exposed than mine.
Please tell me
Zoom the device to nowhere.
Not everything can be rushed.
Well, the rush is there
and it's coming, so take it.
You are right.
A man who does his job.
Tell us what's going on.
You are no help
For weeks, I've been asking for the pops
at the bottom of your fluorescent lenses.
The British can do it.
Insurance
Absolutely yes.
It's your job, Tada.
do a search
We hide neither.
We don't even build them.
I brought one to the event.
Leave him
his departure
Is that Prima Donna?
I accept.  She has to go now.
Naturally.
Kisti, swap Metabytes.
Seth, I'm giving you plutonium.
Lily, go see Kisti.
Fuchs, take the role of
Tad because he needs you.
I'll only grant you
the explosive device.
And nobody leaves Los Alamos.
Both believed.
Negative.  I won't let you go.
Forget Hans.  Forget Fuchs.
He stays here.  Find out what you want.
Fuchs and the hydrogen bomb.
However, we will
meet to discuss.
You don't have time to go out.
You're a politician now, Robert.
You dropped out of
physics many years ago.
A week.  At one o'clock.
Me and you.
Now remove the damn barrier.
So the lack of development of
your Los Alamos watch was great.
Yes.
Yet after the war you tried
to deny that it was feasible.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Technically, I claimed the opposite.
Didn't you try to kill him at the AEC
meeting after the Russian bomb test?
No, no, no.  But that was the
recommendation of the AEC, wasn't it?
The best answer after
hours of discussion.
The hydrogen bomb is a thousand
times more powerful than the atomic bomb.
His only target will
be the biggest city.
A weapon of mass genocide.
It's circling this
side of the map,
Where will they take us,
starting from New York?
I'm in Washington.
It's an offensive weapon.  There is
no difference in terms of deterrence.
Do we really need a greater deterrent
than our slow nukes that are our friends?
If you drown in three meters or three thousand
meters of water, what's the difference?
We might drown anyway.
We can only drown on two legs.
As I said, the treasurers'
proposals are still there.
it is not as practical
as during the war.
A hydrogen bomb
might work, I'll know.
I don't think we should devote all
of our resources to this opportunity.
So how would you like Truman
to reassure the American people?
Simply limiting the
spread of atomic weapons.
through international
control and nuclear energy.
I mean a world government.
The United Nations
was Roosevelt's intention.
I asked what Truman
was supposed to do, right?
It is communism, not fascism,
that will change the world.
which now
threatens our survival.
Lewis, do you realize that if
we build a hydrogen bomb,
the Russians will have no
choice but to build their own.
Maybe they are
already working on it,
Information obtained
from a Los Alamos spy?
No spies at Los Alamos.
Friends, let's not
divert the subject.
I think we should use this momentum
to get concessions from the Russians.
promising not to build
a hydrogen bomb.
In this way, it
reveals its existence.
You convinced yourself
that they already know.
Sure sure.  Right now, I
want committee members
They met privately and
finalized our proposals.
Not sure if you want
to go just for that.
With all due respect, we are an
advisory board.  We will recommend them.
Naturally.
Doctor Oppenheimer
HI.
William Borden.
He joins the Atomic
Energy Commission.
This.
I was a pilot during the war.
One night, returning from a
raid, I saw an incredible sight.
I have a meteor.  The V-2
rocket was headed for England.
I can't help but
imagine what an enemy
missile carrying atomic
warfare would be like.
Silence
Let's make sure it's not us.
Bobby, I don't think
you want to face Shros.
If we both talk,
they'll listen to me.
They hear the prophet
when you speak.
When Shros speaks,
they hear each other.
Listen to the Prophet
A prophet cannot be wrong.
Not even once.
Did you accuse Oppenheimer of
sabotaging the development of the super?
I've never been one to
misunderstand terms like sabotage.
But was Mr. Borden?
As I understand it, maybe.
How did Mr. Borden draw
up such a detailed indictment?
He was no longer
a public servant.
Apparently, Dr. Oppenheimer had
unlimited access to his file.  Oppenheimer
Like mr.  Nichols, I gave him or someone
else from the AEC access to the file.
These are very
serious allegations.
it is your intention
to insinuate that
Is Dr. Oppenheimer
disloyal to the United States?
I always thought
and still think that he
was loyal to the United
States of America.
I believe this to be true and will read it
until I see convincing evidence to the contrary.
Believe it or not, is Dr. Oppenheimer
a prisoner of security?
We should at least
think about it for a
moment, because the
means justify the ends.
Germany is about to surrender.
Yes.
Mr. Bonger, the enemy is the greatest
threat to humanity, that's our job.
He was dead.  That's right.
Japanese combat
Their defeat seems certain.
Not if you're a GI
ready to invade.
We can end this war.
But how can we justify
the use of this weapon?
We are theorists.
Yes.
We imagine the future and
our imagination scares us.
They will not fear it
until they understand it.
they won't understand
it until they use it.
When the world discovered
the terrible secret of Los Alamos,
Our work here will bring about a
peace humanity has never seen.
A peace based on a
form of international peace
The cooperation that
Roosevelt always expected.
A step forward?
Two years and a million dollars.
It is difficult to determine
the price in your city.
Not exactly.
Only from accounts.
Free rural deliveries.
In the first year, 80
children were born.
This year ten are born a month.
Checks on lands that do not
comply with the general restriction.
Clearly general.
Upside down
Let's go
Everybody keep your heads down.
That's what war is like.
Two suicide bombers.
I need an appointment.
September.
July.
That's great, guys.
August.
July.
Stairs
I need my brother
Frank goes to the desert.
He leaves politics behind.
He's been working with Mars for two years.
What do we call the test?
The animal of my heart.
God for three.
What?
Really
You insisted on bringing
your brother Frank.
A known communist.
Former communist
You brought in a
known ex-communist.
The most secret and important
American defense project.
I knew my brother
could be trusted.
Absolutely yes.
And you felt that your judgment of
who the team can be trusted was correct.
Everybody keep your heads down.
Everyone ready?
Hope you learned something.
We learned that we should
have been much further away.
I will solve the problem
Quickly
We need Washington
in the morning.
We will give him a date.
You're a long way
from Chicago, Leo.
If we don't act now, they'll
use this thing in eastern Japan.
We had set up a meeting with
Truman, but someone screwed it up.
You met the Minister of War.
The fact that we built it
does not mean that we
have to decide how to use it.
History will judge us for this.
We have prepared
a petition in Chicago.
I... I'm not telling you to.
Tell me your worries
and I'll let them go.
My worries?
Germany is defeated.
Japan cannot survive on its own.
How do you know?
You put us in this situation.
You and Einstein with your letter to
Roosevelt saying we can build the bomb.
Germany, I believe
That's not how
weapons are made, Cillit.
I hope you will have to help me.
Stop at a meeting.
Lawrence during a meeting.
Is not you
You are a big science salesman.
You can convince
anyone of anything.
Even about yourself
Excuse me
A firestorm in Tokyo
kills 100,000 people.
Mostly civilians
When we do these things and
no one objects, I fear for America.
Pearl Harbor and three years
of brutal conflict in the Pacific.
It gains too much favor
with the American public.
Is it enough to see
the target bomb?
An aerial bomb may not do as
much damage as the Tokyo bombs.
What are we assuming?
20,000 or 30,000 dead
in a medium sized city.
However, don't underestimate the
psychological impact of an atomic explosion.
A 10,000 foot pillar of fire.
Lethal effects of neutrons
from a kilometer in all directions.
From a single device dropped
from the little-known SP-29.
The atomic bomb will be a
terrible revelation of divine power.
If true, it will be certain.
World War II will be over.
My parents came home.
Military targets.
But none of them are big enough.
Possibly a vital war facility
with workers housed nearby.
And we can give a warning
to reduce civilian casualties.
They would send everything
they have against us.
I was about to
get on that plane.
But if we advertise it
and it doesn't work..,
We will destroy the
possibility of Japan's surrender.
Is there no way to show Japan
the bomb and offer surrender?
We intend to show it
as clearly as possible.
Twice
Show the power of weapons
once and the other to
prove that we can
make it until they give up.
We have a list of 12
places to choose from.
Sorry, 11.
I took Kyoto off the list.
Because of its cultural
importance to the Japanese people.
My wife and I spent
our honeymoon there.
It's a wonderful city.
Let me make
things easier for you.
which, according
to my intelligence.
I can't share it with you,
the Japanese don't give up.
Under all circumstances.
Successful and total occupation
of the main islands soon after.
Many lives will be the longest
of Americans and Japanese.
The use of the atomic bomb
in Japanese cities saves lives.
If we have a moral advantage.
What do you think about this?
If we use this weapon
without warning.
our allies will
see it as a threat.
We will find ourselves
in an arms race.
How often can we
be with the Soviets?
Secrecy will not prevent the
Soviets from joining the atomic world.
We were told they
didn't have any uranium.
You have been misinformed.
The Russian bomb is imminent.
After the war the program
must continue at full speed.
Minister Simpson, if I may.
Not all project
scientists agree.
In fact, this may be a good time
to consider other points of view.
If you will speak as soon as possible
this project will not be disturbed from
the outset by some scientists of
questionable judgment and uncertain loyalty.
One of them just tried
to see the President.
We need these guys now,
but as soon as we can, we
need to remove this
scientist from the program.
Don't you agree, doctor?
If a Russian bomb is needed,
perhaps we should invite
the best scientists to Trinity.
President Truman has no
plans to raise expectations,
to be included in
Stalin's atomic project.
Inform him of our discovery
and present it to him.
as a way to win the war.
he made no promises
that could not be kept.
However, the Potsdam peace
conference will be held in July.
The last chance for President
Truman to give a speech of this kind.
Can you give us a
working bomb by then?
Absolutely yes.  We'll test
fire before the conference.
Ground floor.  The observation point has
10,000 meters to the north, south and west.
Where do we start from?
South 10,000.
Base camp is 10
miles south of here.
There is another hilltop
lookout 20 miles away.
Is that so?
Your lines are already here.
The Air Force has requested
a lightweight line for its B-29s.
Which B-29?
Our bombs in the tower.
They want to use the test
to verify the safe distance.
It's risky
But it's not as risky as
dropping someone on Japan.
and they hoped we were
right about the blast radius.
It's a little surprising.
We shoot 15.
The 15?  This is the 15th.
15.
with Frank and Kistiakowsky
at the Southern Observation
Point, we will all be
assigned to base camp,
sunset or fire observations.
Pay some attention to the eyes.
The safety distances
depend on your calculations.
It's literally time to defend
your science weapons.
And the radiation cloud?
It should settle within two to three
miles in the absence of strong winds.
Vacuum measures in progress.
But we need good weather
for visibility so it should be good.
All out
You are 15 at night.
It's a difficult term.
If someone does something,
he speaks right away.
Can you survive the blast test?
It was not possible
Is there anything
else that can stop us?
What's going on, huh?
I will send a message
He worked for us.
Take it to the street
Robert.
Rick Land.
Three years, 4,000
people, $2 billion.
So it won't come out.
We're both done.
Three kilotons, I think.
Less things?
I don't understand
what happened.
And what did Fermi mean
by atmospheric ignition?
There was a moment
when it seemed like a chain
reaction of the atomic
bomb could never stop.
Ignition of the atmosphere
And what was Fermi
still doing in side bets?
Let's call it gallows humor.
Are we saying that if we push this button
we have a chance to destroy the world?
In more than three years of research,
nothing has led to this conclusion.
It's just the most unlikely.
How far?
The chances are almost nil.
Almost none
What do you just want from the theory?
Zero would be fine.
An hour and 58
minutes behind us.
Optimal.
Load.
Military parties left zero.
They go this way.
Throw me the keys.
Spin the cars
Ready for the emergency.
After the photo shoot.
Everyone, get on your cylinders.
Twenty minutes
Winds.
Gentleman
Arriving
Now.
In glass
Blocks UV rays.
Block the glass.
I had a base of 10.
This is fire
Robert.
Try to work in the world.
What does it mean?
If the detonator is still charged,
the voltage will drop by one volt.
If you push that
button, you break it.
I will start
Everyone down
Don't fold until you see
what works in the hills.
Then watch the explosion it
causes on your eyeglasses.
I will keep it here.
Create a detonator.
Are you in favor of
these two explosions?
Do you think I exist?
Yes.
These things are
heavy on your heart.
Thirty seconds
Give me your rate.
I have a match, I have a match,
I'm in.  I have a game, Quattro.
Nine.  Eight.  Seven.  Six.
Five.  Four.  Three.  Four.
Three.  Two.  One
And now I'm Conde,
destroyer of worlds.
It worked
No dollar interest.
Continues
I'm fine like this, Kisti.
AND.
Yes, six
Give me the vase immediately.
HI.
Hi Cyst
What?
Charlotte.
Charlotte, go on.
I do not know
Can I help you with the cheese?
kittens?
If they had flown it very high, the
explosion would have been just as powerful.
With all due respect,
Dr. Oppenheimer, we've got you covered.
Real vase holder,
stolen for a short time.
A brief description
would be an exaggeration.
He was talking about a powerful
new weapon that was stolen.
I hope we will use
it against Japan.
That's all
Where we gave them
an Ace is to play hands.
You are a six pack.
About CO in the Pacific.
If anything happens, Washington.
Before.
When you will be informed.
Naturally.
To the best of my knowledge.
What would the Japanese give
up if they knew what awaited them?
I do not know
Everything is here,
this is the petition.
How is this possible regardless of
Japanese?  Not signing an article?
Many people are like that.
Many people.
Pydrode
The fact that we have
established this link any other
right or responsibility
to decide how to use it.
And no one else.
But they are the only ones who know.
I explained the passages in the
various points of view of the congregation.
But what is your opinion?
When this is used, the
battle will become clear.
Perhaps all wars will
become unthinkable.
Until someone makes
a bigger connection.
I thought they would call.
Very fast.
And this is the sixth.
Charlotte?
Triggers?
Anything?
Charlotte?
Trumpet on the radio
general?
I am proud of you
and all your people.
It went well
Apparently it exploded
with an explosion.
Everyone here feels pretty good.
It's been a long journey.
I think it was one of the
smartest things I've ever done
That's when I chose the
director of Los Alamos.
we asked for
two billion dollars.
the greatest scientific
gamble in history and we won.
The world will
remember this day.
it is too early to tell
What are the
consequences of a bombing?
But I bet the
Japanese don't like it.
I'm honored.
I am proud of what
you have achieved.
I wish we had time to
use it against the Germans.
Doctor Oppenheimer.  Doctor
Oppenheimer.  It's beautiful.
Image.  The inmates need help.
Dr. Oppenheimer, I'm honoured.
Mr. President, please.  Thank you.
16 minutes.
How does it feel to be the
most famous man in the world?
In the world?  You helped save
the lives of many Americans.
What we did in
Hiroshima... in Nagasaki.
Sure, sure, sure.  Your invention has
allowed us to bring our children home.
It wasn't my invention.
You are on the cover.
Jim told me you were concerned
about the Soviet arms race.
Yes, it is.  Now we have
a chance to make sure
International cooperation and
interest in the field of atomic energy.
Did you know when the
Soviets would have the bomb?
I don't think I can give you...
Never.  Never.  Never.
Mr. President, Russians have
excellent physiques and rich resources.
Abundance?
Yes.
I do not believe.
Well, don't put everything
they've got into it.
I heard you left Los
Atoms.  What should we do?
Return it to the Indians.
Dr. Oppenheimer, if what he
says about the Soviets is true.
We have to build Los
Alamos, not close it.
Mr. President, I feel like
I've flattened all my hands.
Do you think they care who built
the bomb in Hiroshima and Nagasaki?
They want to know
who posted it.  I did it.
Hiroshima is not about you.
Doctor Oppenheimer
Don't let crying bring me back.
Robert saw that the
handshake had captured him.
out of nowhere, and the moment
I met him, I was fully embraced
his father's fame and used
his profile to influence politics.
Can you say "Dr."?  In
the years following the war
Did it have a major impact
on US atomic policy?
I think it's great.
We know that's what they mean.
Really?  We will ensure that
the isotopes we personally deal
with are not to eliminate any
opposition to their expulsion.
Can you check out the beer?
You are building atomic weapons.
I was the speaker, but the opinion
of the scientists was unanimous.
Meanwhile McCarthy was on the rise
because he knew he was vulnerable.
His brother was blacklisted
from all universities in the country.
The crewwoman works on
the railway and lays the rails.
Like Chevalier,
he's gone into exile.
But all this did not
stop Robert's progress.
The GAC recommends arms
control instead of the hydrogen bomb.
Truman was shocked
when he rejected their advice.
I miss Richard more
than he can bear.
I'm glad you didn't live to
see what the fuss was about.
The birthday boy arrives.
Take it off
Have fun with him.
Robert my son and his
girlfriend the most beautiful
words for me the father of
the atomic bomb, that is...
Suspicious.
What do you think, Lewis?
I guess I had to wrap you up.
in the world.
What does Fukes mean
to the rest of the world?
Fukes.  Fukes class
Honey, you didn't hear me.
The Fukes class.
They are British scientists
Formed an explosives
team at Los Alamos.
It turned out that he was…
... as good as him.
God. I'm sorry.
When the truth about Fukes emerged,
the FBI increased its surveillance of him.
He knew his phone was tapped.
He fell all over the place.
Destroyed
But never stop
saying what you think.
A man of faith.
And maybe he thought that
fame could really protect him.
Eisenhower had another
chance when he took office.
He took it.
America and Russia can be
compared to two scorpions in a bottle.
Each can kill the other, but
only at the risk of his own life.
There are several aspects
of politics about him.
Modern scientists blame
me, but how could I protect it?
Too secret to discuss.
Honesty is the only medicine.
Washington authorities should start
with the country of American media.
This is the last straw
for Roberto Sotomayor.
So he had to lose
his security class.
And with it his reliability.
But how can they do it?
He was a war hero.
He had already told
everyone about his past.
He would prefer
not to wet them all.
How did the Board get access
to Oppenheimer's FBI file?
Could it have been Nichols?
No, I can't imagine that.
Whoever it was, at least if I was
the storm that burned a person.
From the White House or
from my desk, to the AEC.
You see it there, right?
I've worked all
my life to get here.
Now from all over the country,
Canada and the United States.
They will put me back in my place.
flat shoe salesman.
Lewis, we can win.
I think we can take the sun off
the grass, but you did your job.
It was a bitter bill.
Will Hill's testimony
prove us right?
Hill will be fine.
I don't know him, but he was
their son by Silveridge in Chicago.
Robert has never been forgiven for failing to
support the petition against the bombing of Japan.
This photo was taken
31 days after the bombing.
Almost all the inhabitants of
the street for almost a kilometer,
burned immediately
and violently.
The Japanese talked
about people wearing stripes.
clothing in which the
skin is burned in strips.
Many thought they were lucky
They emerged from the ruins of
their home with only minor injuries.
But they died anyway.
They died after a
few days or weeks,
due to the rithium-like
rays contained within it a
large amount emitted at
the time of the explosion.
Did you read that
link in the newspaper?
British physicists worked
It was not the final
act of WWII, but
the first act of this
cold war with Russia.
which physique?
I think you know him.
Patrick Blackett.
He may not be wrong.
Stimson is telling me that
They chained the
essentially defeated enemy.
Robert, you now
have all the influence.
Please encourage them
to continue my super quest.
Anything can and
will happen, Edward.
Why?  It's not a good
use of our resources.
Do you really believe it?
Wow, Robert Oppenheimer,
the sphinx, your atomic guru.
Nobody knows what you believe.
Six
Once again our Program Director
is Dr. J. Robert Oppenheimer.
I hope he has arrived and that we
here will look at your work with pride.
Today, however, this pride must
be tempered by deep concern.
If atomic weapons are to be added
to the arsenal of the warring world,
then the day will come when people
will curse the name of Los Alamos.
I'm sorry I was wrong.
Wait, forget it.
Seems auspicious.
Here is Oppenheimer.
What's the title?
J. Robert Oppenheimer, Hayfight.
And the United States won.
This will work
Those were your
words the other day.
We had to go back.
But how do you know what
Time magazine will write?
Henry Luce was a friend.
Sit here and I'll tell
you how it's done.
But you were always in front.
Survival in Washington.
I still wanted to know
how to do something.
Exact.
What did you say about Borden?
Why were you caught
with a knife in your hand?
I found out that Borden
keeps a knife for you.
Depends on how much
effect Borden can have.
Tell him
Did I say something funny?
Borden, Borden, Borden.  When
we all know they are made of straw.
It probably appears
in the princely state.
And then you acknowledge
it before Congress.
But more useful than the center.
How many?
Maybe it's too good, Robert.
That was six years ago.
You know, they're
really vindictive.
Patiently saying that it is…
It was pretty obvious to
Slamka that he was neutral.
Wakes up!  This is trash!
It's always been
straw and you know it!
Wake up, you will
have to fight him.
It wasn't Nichols or Hoover,
one of Truman's men.  It was you.
You gave the file to
Borden and you uploaded it.
Oppenheimer.
You convinced him... Borden!
He didn't give me
anything convincing.
Don't rush to
use the whole file.
Write your results.
Send them to the FBI.
Of course the material is very
extensive, but there is nothing new.
Your results will be listed.
And it will be necessary to answer.
Hoover will pass
them on to McCarthy.
Oppenheimer is too slimy
for the compliant clown.
I talked to Hoover about it.
Hold McCarthy.
He is in contact with the AEC.
A test
Negative.  There is no
court.  It cannot be given
Oppenheimer.
You can't torture him.
We must systematically
destroy Oppenheimer's credibility.
and we will never again talk
about matters of national security.
And then?
We will shut you down.
Out of the spotlight.
A simple bureaucratic procedure
has a nice approval.  To be healed.
Submit your allegations to the FBI.
Hoover will send them to the AEC.
You have to move.
You are writing an indictment.
But tell Oppenheimer his security
clearance doesn't need to be renewed.
However, give him
a chance to object.
As you can see, Robert, it hasn't
been signed yet.  Can I keep it?
NO
If you decide to object,
do not include it in the copy.
When you object and trust me, I
will appoint a board of directors.
Of course they will count.
prosecutor
Name and surname
WEAVING?
RogerRob
Oh.  Oh.  Rob will have security
clearance to review Oppenheimer's file.
Just like great advice.
There won't be a defense attorney.
The closed case concerns the so-called defamatory
information contained in your accusation.
No public, no journalists,
no burden of proof.
No burden of proof.
We are not prisoners.
Eye of Len
What did you say?
That's how it's played.
Forgive my naivety.
Amateurs seek
the sun, let's eat.
Power remains in the shadows.
But, sir, you are now
out of the shadows.
Yes, that's why it should work.
Tell him you
resigned this morning.
This will help you.
And then Hill in the afternoon.
Hill will help us.
As you can see, Robert, the
situation is not on your side.
Can I keep it?
NO
If you decide to appeal,
they'll need to send you a copy.
Take my current
chauffeur, sister.
I won't sell my
lawyers for this.
Of course not.
But don't take too long.
I can't keep Nichols for a day.
I'm sorry it has
come to this, Robert.
I think this is wrong.
Nichols wants you to find him
so he can record everything.
Stross wants me to leave.
Stross knows he can't do it.
He was about to plead
guilty to the charges.
you will lose your job.
You will lose your reputation.
We will lose the house!
Robert, we have to fight.
I cannot represent you
as the Council of the EC.
I'll call Lloyd Garrison.
He has the best.
But I have to warn you.
It won't be a fair fight.
Did you mention microfilm in your
interview with Boris Paš in 1943?
NO
Touch 11.
Thanks for my paragraph.
You never said the man at the
consulate is an expert in using microfilm?
I am sorry.  I am sorry.
I'd like to know it,
What document does
Mr. Robb and can we get a copy?
The document is
confidential, Mr. Garrison.
I think we should go back
to first hand information.
First hand
Is it me Roger?
Recorded interview.
My client is sitting here
potentially lying to himself.
And all this time
you had a precedent?
Nobody told your client to
twist his previous answer.
It happened 12 years ago.
Can we listen to this recording?
You're not allowed,
Mr. Garrison.
You have made a small pre-cut.
Please please please.  Is this
case about prison or the truth?
If this is true, where is the statement?
Where's the witness list?
Mr. Garris, this is
not a trial because you
know very well.  Trial
rules do not apply.
We are dealing
with national security.
Yes, sir.  With all due respect, I don't
understand what national security is.
prevents the prosecution from
providing us with the witness list.
Joanne, you know my words.
Either it's in the transcript
or it's not accepted.
I already explained how I
created a story filled with Recocan.
So why would anyone make
up such an elaborate story?
Because I was an idiot.
Why lie?
Obviously with the intention of not
revealing who your intermediary is.
Your friend, Paquon
Chanaali, is a commissioner.
Is he still your boyfriend?
Yes.
Dr. Rami, thank you for coming.
How did the accusation come about?
Tell them they passed the law.
What did he say?
He didn't come down to them.
But Frost told him that
you and Ruth Dohmen
have been in a
relationship for years.
He was persuasive the entire
time he watched them in Pasadena.
Lawrence said Richard
died of a broken heart.
Mr. Surd, what
kind of heart is this?
Broken heart
Richard never learned.
as long as he proves it.
I do not know
Dr. Rabbi, what government
positions does he currently hold?
I am the Chairman of the
General Advisory Council.
I am a member of the EIC
committee and I am Dr. Oppenheimer.
How long have you
known Oppenheimer?
I have known him
very well since 1928.
Well enough to speak of
her loyalty and his character.
Dr. Oppenheimer is a
man of honorable character.
And it is loyal to the
United States of America.
friends, institutions
that are part of.
Eat food
who's this?
There is nothing
to be afraid of.
After the Russian
atomic bomb test
Lawrence turned to you
about the hydrogen bomb.
You'd better ask him.
What's up?
What will you buy?
Was Dr. Oppenheimer always
against the hydrogen bomb?
No, he was thinking about the
future of the merger program.
at the expense of our
low-quality fission program.
But it turned out
that was not the case.
In case you can do both.
Suppose this counsel doesn't feel
the sense of fulfillment it does have.
testimony here, Dr. Oppenheimer
was absolutely right.
Should he be clean or not?
Why are you doing
all this against a man?
The Dr proved it with his
own hands.  Openheimer
Check your card.
We have the atomic
bomb and the whole series.
We have the whole
series of superbombs.
More of what you want
My friends
But I've known
Minister Stoltz for years.
I feel the need to express
my warm support to him.
Louis de Chon for
science and scientists.
But right now, if
there's nothing...
Senator, I'd like to ask again.
we have a list of witnesses.
And I remind the
candidate that you are not.
always have this
information in advance.
Dr. Hill will be
here after lunch.
Mr. President, the
next scheduled witness,
Dr. Lawrence, it
appears to be colitis.
We'll go with William
Borden instead.
Mr. Borden, please have a seat.
Mr. Borden, when he
learned of the investigation...
Dr. Oppenheimer, have
you come to any conclusions?
I did it
The time has come to
express these conclusions.
Letter from the Federal Bureau
of Investigation to Mr. J. Gopover?
That's right
You discussed writing
the letter before writing it
A letter with someone from
the Atomic Energy Commission?
I will not do that
You actually remembered that
letter when I was in front of you.
If so, could you
be very nice to me?
Dear Mr. Hoover, The
purpose of this letter...
I'm sorry, I'd
apologize if I could...
What is the purpose of the delay?
You just have to read the letter.
Mr President, this is the
first letter I have seen.
And here I see at least one
declaration of the type you speak of.
I don't think anyone
wants it on the record.
These are allegations
that did not exist before.
which have come to light and
were not part of Nichols' prosecution.
These are allegations that I
do not believe belong here.
The witness wrote this
initiative letter of him presented
evidence that had already been
presented to the commission.
His conclusions are a
valid and positive testimony.
the results of his friends, Dr. Oppenheimer.
It is a statement that applies to both parties.
How long has the consultant
been holding this letter?
I don't think I need
to be subjugated.
cross-examination
by him, Mr. Garrison.
Mr. Garrison, since we're
on the board of directors
They read the letter, wouldn't it
be better to put it in the minutes?
Go on.
Dear Mr. Hoover, The purpose of this letter
is to express my views based on the following:
long-term study of the
available categorized
evidence, it is very
likely that J. Robert
Oppenheimer is an
agent of the Soviet Union.
The following
conclusions are justified.
One, from 1929 to 1942, with the
most most likely, J.
Robert Oppenheimer
A communist staunch enough
to feed the Soviets information.
Second, it's more likely that he's been
working as an espionage agent ever since.
After the third, most
likely, he moved on.
Soviet directive affecting
US military policy.
Sorry Robert.
Does anyone want to tell the
truth about what's going on here?
We will now hear
from Dr. David's Hill.
Dr. Hill, does he want
to make a statement?
Okay thanks.
I've been asked to
testify about Louis Straws.
he held high-level government
positions for many years.
and is known for his seriousness,
industriousness and intelligence.
The opinions I have to
express are my own, but
I think much of what I
say will help indicate that.
why most of the
scientists in this country
He preferred that Mr.  Slamek was
completely alien to the government.
You mean the hostility of some
Scientists directed to Mr.
straws
Because of his commitment to security,
as demonstrated in the Oppenheimer case?
Negative.  Because of his personal
grudge against Dr. Oppenheimer.
Book!  Book!
It seems that most of the scientists in
this country are Robert Oppenheimer.
He has been washed and tested for
expressing his honest opinions of him.
Dr. Bush, I thought
I was performing.
Service to my country
when I approached this case.
No parliament should
judge in this country
because it has expressed
the strong views of him.
If you want to try this
case, you should try me.
Friends, forgive me if
I'm angry, but I'm upset.
Dr. Hill, we have already learned
that Mr. Straws will not sue.
He didn't even attend the
hearings against Dr. Oppenheimer
The Oppenheimer affair was
initiated and accomplished
largely through the
hostility of Louis Straws.
Oppenheimer got the men talking
about Straws' attitude towards shipping.
Norway and isotopes a Straws never
forgave him this public humiliation.
Another discussion between the
two centered around their differences.
in deciding how the elderly
contribute to national security.
The straws turned it into
a personal security system,
To destroy Oppenheimer's
effectiveness.
And Straws managed to find a
couple ambitious
men who disagree
He was jealous of Oppenheimer's behavior
and prestige in government circles.
I always thought
and still think that he
is loyal to the United
States of America.
I believe it and I will leave it until I
see the truth that is convincing for others.
Believe it or not, is
Dr. Oppenheimer a security risk?
In many cases that I have seen,
Dr. Oppenheimer will intervene.
in a way that is extremely
difficult for me to understand.
I completely disagree with him
on many points and I disagree with
him the actions honestly seem
confusing and complicated to me.
At this point, I feel like I want
to see the life interests of this.
I understand the countries in their
hands better and therefore trust them more.
Thank you sir.  Well thank you.
I am sorry
Did you shake his hand?
I could have spit in his face.
I'm not sure the border
will appreciate that.
Isn't he nice enough for you?
You are all very nice gentlemen.
Gray needs to see what Rob is
doing.  Why doesn't he stop him?
And are you shaking
the towers again?
You have to stop being a martyr.
Under current AEC guidelines,
does Dr. Oppenheimer check?
According to my interpretation
of the Atomic Energy Act,
Not when I hired Dr. It's open,
If I was on the committee, I
wouldn't have checked it today.
Sure sure.  Thanks, General.
That's all.  But I don't think so
I wouldn't exonerate any
of these men, that's all.
Dr. Oppenheimer
bore no responsibility.
selection or selection of the
opinions of the class, right?
Negative There is none
And you don't want
to leave this forum
today without a
questioning suggestion
His fundamental allegiance
to the United States of America
State-run Los Alamos?
It is not possible.  I hope I haven't
convinced anyone otherwise for a moment.
Thanks General.
You shouldn't keep them waiting.
Will arrive.
Do you want it here?
A fool or a teenager would
dare to acknowledge it.
someone else's relationship?
And you don't have a lawyer.
Kitty and I are adults.  We went through
fire together.  It will all be fine.
Would you describe your view
on communism as pro-neutrality?
against the Communists.  I have
nothing to do with communism since 1936.
Since I met Robert.
That's all
The record shows that he
did not question Oppenheimer.
A neutral and impartial
adviser to the Gray Board.
The prosecutor who used
all of them was questioned
tricks of a rather
sophisticated legal education.
Now that the gray council has authorized
the prosecution, you are charging.
If I were on the gray
board, I would protest.
the tactics of a man who
really was a prosecutor.
A man nominated by Louis
Straus, not the Council.
who was he?
How come?
who was?
Roger Roberts
Mrs. Oppenheimer.
Did he have a Communist
Party membership card?
I'm... I'm not sure.
I'm not sure
Naturally.
Certain?
I think the act of joining
the party probably
required sending money
and receiving postcards, right?
Yes.
I am sorry
Yes?
That was a long time ago.
Mr. Robert couldn't make
it long enough to forget it.
Not exactly.
Do you return the
ticket or tear it up?
A card I had forgotten existed.
Communist Party membership card.
I have not the foggiest idea.
Is it possible to distinguish between
Soviet communism and communism?
When I was a member I thought
there were definitely two things.
I was thinking about the
United Communist Party.
The state takes care
of our internal problems.
Now I don't believe it anymore.
Everything is interconnected
and spread throughout the world.
And I believe it
since I left the party.
Sixteen years ago.
Seventeen years ago.
my fault
But you... Sorry, eighteen.
18 years ago.
You realize your
husband is contributing.
To the last national anthem
of the Spanish Civil War?
The last civil war since 1942.
I knew Robert donated
money from time to time.
Did you know that this money
goes to Communist Party channels?
Do not you think?
Excuse me?
This means through the channels
of the Communist Party, right?
Yes.
Then I don't think this
is the same thing the
husband has nothing to do
with the communist party?
You don't have to answer yes or no.
You can answer however you want.
I know thanks.
This is your problem.
It is not expressed correctly.
Do you understand what I mean?
Yes.
Why do not you answer?
Because I don't like your statement
that it has to do with communism.
Except that Robert
never had anything.
In collaboration with
the Communist Party.
I know you gave money to
Spanish refugees.  I know.
intellectually interested
in communist ideas.
Two types of
communists. Ordinary
intellectuals and communists.
Here's what I couldn't answer.
I didn't succeed either.
Robert, you can't win.
This is a kangaroo court.
predetermined result I
exposed myself more.
I had my reasons
He's right about one thing.
I'm not sure you
understand, Albert.
NO.
I left my country and
never spoke to him.
You have served
your country well.
If this is the reward he's offering you,
maybe you should turn your back on him.
Oh shit.  Shit.  I was
not out of this country.
Then tell him to go to hell.
Interesting, Leon.  No more
briefing hearings.  This is a process.
About the hearing?
He doesn't want to tell everyone
that you initiated the hearings.
Nothing can prove it.
We are not in court sir,
there is no burden of proof.
It is true.  They are not prisoners.
Just deny it.  Why did he come
here to destroy me?  What's the goal?
Do people need a reason to
do the right thing in their opinion?
I told you.
Up and down the courthouse
He blamed me
from the first call.
I don't know, but Oppenheimer said it
would be the last time I would see him.
Oppenheimer knows
how to manipulate him.
He straightens his elbows.  He prayed
that night while you were a scholar.
they thought they could
understand how he used his work.
They will never think
that he is so naive.
Doctor, during your work
on the hydrogen bomb,
Yes, certainly.  But he kept
working anyway, didn't he?
Yes, because it was worth
exploring and not preparing a weapon.
Are you saying it was more
of an academic field trip?
No, it wasn't an academic
thing.  The point is, you could have
built a hydrogen bomb.  It
was a matter of life and death.
Until 1942 you actively supported
the development of the hydrogen bomb.
Did you print what
I was working on?
Support and work on it.  Yes.
When did these moral
doubts get so strong?
did you actively oppose the
development of the hydrogen bomb?
When was the US policy proposed?
The state must do
these things at any
cost, whatever the
balance between the two
firearms and atomic
weapons as part of our arsenal.
What moral qualities
do they have with this?
What moral qualities does he have?
Yes, it's true.  Oppenheimer
wanted to have an atomic bomb.
He wanted to be a man who
could move the world.  He
says the nuclear chain is
to put it back in the bottle.
Well, I'm here to tell
you that I know one.
If J. Robert Oppenheimer could
do it all, he would do it again.
You know you never said that.
He feels sorry for Hiroshima.
He would do anything.  Why?
Because to him is the most
important man who ever lived.
We used the atomic
bomb liberally.
In fact, Dr. Badger argued
that in choosing a target
Dropping an atomic
bomb on Japan, right?
Yes
So did you know, did you know, that
by dropping an atomic bomb on a target
you killed thousands of civilians
with one assassin wounded.  It is true?
Yes, it's true.
Not as much as it seems.
How many people died?
Seventy thousand
Seventy thousand from Hiroshima and...
One hundred thousand from both.
Every day of bombing.
Yes, it is.  One of the
weeks and years to come.
It is estimated that there are between
fifty and one hundred thousand.
At least two hundred
and twenty thousand dead.
Yes.
This is the reason
for the moral scoop.
Horrible.
But did you testify to me that the
bombing of Hiroshima was a success?
Technically it was a success.
Technically very successful.
It's right next to us and we,
even as humans, can't go this way.
We are acting.
You are against rollover
Thermal nuclear weapons in
Japan due to moral concerns?
You said I would.
If I was against
dropping the nuke.
Bomb Hiroshima
for moral reasons.
We expressed ourselves... I know.  A
thousand, a thousand, a thousand, a thousand.
I wanted... I see you
I should have made our arguments against
his release, but I did not support them.
So, after three years of working
day and night, he made a bomb.
Then you squared
off against the tool.
The Minister of War asked me
what the opinion of the scientists was.
I gave them
counter-opinions and opinions.
You supported the study.
You had no problems
with the plan.
supported
I didn't mean "supported".
You helped select
the target, right?
I've done my job
I had no political
position at Los Alamos.
I did whatever was asked of me.
Then you wouldn't marry a
hydrogen bomb, would you?
That's not what I
asked you, doctor.
The GAC reported that she left
after the broadcast and the target said.
A super bomb
should never be built.
What do I mean, what do I mean?
I thought you knew what I meant.
Are the Russians doing
nothing to increase their power?
If we did it, they should too.
Our efforts would only encourage their
efforts, just as they did with the atomic bomb.
Just like the atomic bomb.
In 1945 there was no moral
school, in 1949 it was plentiful.
Oppenheimer, when are you here?
Did he develop strong moral
beliefs about the hydrogen bomb?
When it was clear to me that whatever weapon
we had available we would tend to use it,
Martyr J. Robert Oppenheimer, I
gave him exactly what he wanted.
He remembers Trinity, not
Hiroshima, not Nagasaki.
You should thank me.
It is not so
Do we still have enough votes?
Or it could be the
pinnacle of my career.
the biggest public
humiliation of my life?
It's about the whole sentence.
Don't draw.
Well then take the press.
Dr. J. Robert Oppenheimer, this
Council, based on his testimony
From him and many
of his current and former
colleagues, that you
are a loyal citizen.
However, in light of your
continued associations and
disrespect for this
country's security apparatus,
with your somewhat
disturbing behavior
in relation to the
hydrogen bomb program.
and the incredible lack of honesty
in this committee and in some of your
responses we voted two to one to deny
the renewal of your security clearance.
Written opinion
complete with dissent
Evans' report will be published
by the AEC in the coming days.
That's all
Council member.
Robert.
Do not say that
Don't buy sheets.
It's official?
Unexpected problems arose.
Yes, was I rejected?
I'm afraid so, sir.
Naturally.
Who are those who resisted?
There were three of them,
led by a junior senator.
Massachusetts and a
man trying to make it.
I don't like what you
did to Oppenheimer.
What is his name?
Kennedy.
John F. Kennedy.
When you let them talk or get
involved, will the
world forgive you?
not gonna happen
We will see
I am sorry
Please.
You told me I'd be fine.
I didn't have all
the facts, did I?
Here is the truth
President Eisenhower pinned the
Medal of Freedom to my chest last year.
because I've always done
the right thing for this country.
They don't want
me in the toilet.
No problem
Maybe they should invite
Oppenheimer over for him.
Maybe they will.
I told you he's turning the
scientists against you one by one.
Me, starting with Einstein.
I told you about it, Einstein.
I said near the pond.
You know it, but you know it, sir,
no one knows what they are saying.
it is impossible that they
have never talked about you.
It's impossible that they
talked about such a thing...
It's more important than I know.
Okay thanks.
The man of today
He once organized a reception for
me.  He actually gave me an award.
Yes.
You all thought I had lost the
ability to recognize what had begun.
So the award wasn't really
for me.  It was for all of you.
Now it's your turn to face the
consequences of your success.
And one day, when they've
punished you enough,
you will need salmon
and potato salad.
Thank you peach
Self...
Oh Frank.  You are
happy, I am happy.
I'll turn around and
say all is forgiven.
Remember, it won't be for you.
It will be for them.
Help me.  Help me.
When I came to you
with these calculations,
we thought we could set off a chain reaction
that would destroy the entire world.
I am in the world
What happened?
I think we did.
I think so.