[ocean waves crashing]
[atmospheric music playing]
[woman] Do you dream of a better life?
A life that you could never afford?
Aeon offers a time donation program
which compensates generously
for every donated year of your life.
[inaudible dialogue]
The procedure is minimally invasive
and performed daily in our clinics.
Get your DNA test done today.
We'll find
a matching time recipient for you.
[applause]
More than 200,000 donors
have already donated their lifetime
and thereby made their dreams a reality.
EVA
AGE 21
We at Aeon believe in this.
If you give your time,
life will give something back to you.
Choose your dreams.
[inaudible dialogue]
And remember, your age
only makes you more beautiful.
Donate your time and start a new life.
Your time. Your chance. Your choice.
[man] Minimum age 18.
DNA compatibility required.
Aging process takes two to three days.
Possible side effects.
Headaches, exhaustion,
disorientation, emotional strain.
For more information, visit aeon. legal,
or talk to your time donation manager.
[pop music playing on TV]
Fifteen years?
I was actually thinking
more like three or maybe five.
Look, Denys. This is just an offer.
As you can see, the sum
rises exponentially with more years.
If you were to donate
15 years of your life,
Aeon would pay you 700,000 euros.
[speaking Arabic]
[in English] I mean, I just turned 18.
[man speaking Arabic]
[in English] I just think this is
all a bit too much right now.
Mr. Bondar, how long
have you been waiting for your visa?
Since Deny's was born?
Let me be real with you for a second.
You're probably not gonna live
to see that happen.
You're gonna die in this dump
or get deported. So will Denys.
[indistinct background chattering]
[man] But with 700,000 euros,
you can get your whole family
out of here, completely legally.
That's enough capital
for you all to get citizenship.
[speaking Arabic]
[man in English] Your father wants
to open a shop, right?
Uh, yeah.
How long would you have to work for that?
Fifteen years wouldn't be enough.
[Mr. Bondar speaking Arabic]
[woman speaking Arabic]
[in English] I did it myself...
[Mr. Bondar speaking Arabic]
...when I was around your age.
In my case, it was five years.
That was enough to pay for university.
If you want something better for you,
for your family,
then this is the ticket
that will win the lottery for you.
[woman speaking Arabic]
[in English] And what
do I tell my girlfriend?
Well, you marry her
and get her the hell out of here.
[man laughs]
[Mr. Bondar speaking Arabic]
- [woman] Mm-hmm.
- [in English] Here.
[Mr. Bondar speaking Arabic]
[tense music playing]
[indistinct chattering]
♪ I can see clearly now ♪
♪ The rain is gone ♪
[wind chimes jingle]
♪ I can see all obstacles in my way... ♪
[in English] Hey.
I was just about to call you.
Yeah, sure you were.
Are you still on the field?
You do know how important today is?
Erika, Relax. I was at Denys Bondar's.
He was about the throw away
the opportunity of a lifetime.
Max...
Should I waste my time at some reception
instead of taking care of my donors?
Don't push it.
You better hurry.
- ♪ It's gonna be a bright ♪
- ♪ Bright ♪
- ♪ Oh, bright ♪
- ♪ Bright, sunshiny day ♪
- ♪ It's gonna be a bright ♪
- ♪ Bright ♪
- ♪ Oh, bright ♪
- ♪ Bright, sunshiny day... ♪
[man groans]
- [device chimes]
- [door lock buzzing]
[man 1] Take it easy.
There is nothing inside.
[man 2] Be quiet.
♪ Well, look all around you... ♪
- Would you look at him?
- [reporter] And in other news...
[girl] I want one like that.
Show me. Show me!
♪ Look straight ahead ♪
♪ Nothin' but blue skies ♪
♪ I think I can make it now ♪
♪ The rain is gone ♪
[demonstrators chanting]
Aeon, fuck yourself! Aeon, fuck yourself!
Fuck you, asshole!
MY TIME BELONGS TO ME
Stay out of people's lives, asshole!
[chanting] Aeon, fuck yourself!
Aeon, fuck yourself!
- ♪ It's gonna be a bright ♪
- ♪ Bright ♪
[woman] Asshole!
Turn around!
♪ Well, look all around you ♪
♪ There's nothin' but blue skies ♪
♪ Blue skies ♪
♪ Look straight ahead, nothin' but blue... ♪
There you are.
[device chimes]
I already sent it to you.
Fifteen years!
Quit bragging. You're still really late.
[host] This is where one researcher,
in particular, stood out.
With their latest optimization
in DNA matching...
[Max] Hey.
...Dr. Mortensen and his incredible team
have made life that much easier
for our donor scouts.
And now a big round of applause
for our next Aeonian of the Year.
Donation manager extraordinaire, Max Toma!
Congratulations, you bastard.
Get your ass up there.
276 years brokered,
and the quarter isn't even over yet.
But what really speaks to Max's ability
is his empathy and sincerity.
Donors who were advised by Max always said
they'd be willing
to come back to Aeon a second time.
Well done.
[gentle music playing]
And now, the woman
we've all been waiting for.
The incredible genius
behind the chrono transfers,
our CEO, Sophie Theissen.
[audience cheering, clapping]
Hi!
Max, we're all very, very proud of you.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
[Sophie] Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart...
died at age 35.
What incomparable musical treasures
were forever lost to us
due to that untimely death?
Let's imagine for a moment
that he had lived to be 80,
120, or even 150 years old.
Or how about Friedrich Schiller,
Frida Kahlo,
Nelson Mandela, Marie Curie.
What more could they have achieved
in a world where it's no longer age,
and instead, the person who decides
how long they'll contribute to society?
Therefore, I'm happy to announce
that, starting right now,
we will include any current
and future Nobel Prize winners
in our database of recipients.
As I stand before you today,
the first 15 scientists
have already received their donation.
They're currently recuperating
in our Berlin Chrono Clinic.
Professor.
They're ready for you now.
[Sophie] There, our doctors and therapists
are in the midst
of preparing them for their new lives
so that they can continue
their groundbreaking research
for many years to come.
Together with Aeon,
in the service of progress.
Sponsored by the Lucy Theissen Foundation.
[audience cheering]
[gentle music playing]
[woman laughs]
Take it all in.
It's perfectly normal to get emotional.
I know it's hard to believe,
but your body is now young again.
I just don't know if I feel comfortable
getting undressed in front of you anymore.
Honey, I'm still the same person.
Hello. Please take a seat.
Well, I can see
the rejuvenation was a success.
We can turn back the clock,
but we still can't
make it stand still forever.
And so, we'll keep researching
until, finally, it won't be age and death
in charge of us but the other way around.
The final big step
towards absolute freedom.
And not just for the top 10,000
but for all people on this planet.
[audience cheering, whistling]
How do you feel?
I can walk again.
It's incredible.
- [tense music playing]
- [body thuds]
[woman shrieks]
[people clamoring]
[people shouting]
[tense music intensifies]
[shrieks]
[man grunts]
[woman] He executed all 15 patients.
He spared our nursing staff
and the relatives.
This was a targeted terrorist attack
by the Adam Group.
The police have already launched
a massive manhunt.
No success so far.
Adam's already claimed responsibility
for the attack.
Time donations create a system
that suspends the principle of equality.
Those who make lifetime a commodity
also make people a commodity.
They reduce human beings to cattle.
That's what the people did
who had to die in Berlin today.
Anyone who steals other people's time
will be executed by us.
Nobel Prize or not.
Turn that off.
We're gonna hunt them down and...
[monitor chimes]
How the hell could this happen?
[man] The guy got himself hired
as a nurse months ago.
I'm Nowak,
your new head of operations in Berlin.
His predecessor
already cleared out his desk today.
Sixteen years with the Berlin Police's
counter-terrorism unit.
First thing I'll do is
run a background check
on every German employee to make sure
you don't have another mole around.
I've already given the order
for all employees worldwide.
It might be helpful if, in the future,
I had the authority to...
In the future, I won't be involved.
I have to prepare a statement.
["Starry Night" playing]
[dishes clattering]
Well, this is very romantic,
but my husband will be home any minute.
[Max] Really?
I hear he's the jealous type.
- Extremely unattractive men often are.
- Mm.
- I compensate in other ways.
- I already read the news.
- Employee of the Year.
- [lighter clicks]
[Max] Maybe we can afford a place
by the lake soon.
Are you crazy? We haven't even
paid off this apartment yet.
[chuckles] So what?
Just call that bank consultant
that loves you, and get us another loan.
You said he has a crush on you, right?
A little one.
Honey, think about it.
A house by the lake.
This is our life.
We shouldn't have to wait
till we're retired to enjoy it.
Our kids would love it too.
Our kids, huh?
You heard me.
We should probably tackle that part first,
don't you think?
The food needs another seven minutes.
You can do it.
♪ Starry Night I gaze upon ♪
♪ Lovers that have come and gone ♪
♪ But you hang around a little more ♪
♪ You do everything I ever wanted to ♪
♪ I was always too afraid ♪
♪ I know through it all
We still remained ♪
♪ This home
Never had a fire burn this way... ♪
[moans]
[breathing heavily]
[moaning]
[Max moaning]
[both moaning]
[moaning intensifies]
♪ Is this really happening? ♪
[music fades]
Try to be nice to him.
I'm always nice.
[woman] You guys are crazy! Elli!
[laughs]
You really didn't
have to do this, sweetie.
[Elena chuckles] The supermarket
is on the way anyway, Mom.
Are there really no shops left?
First, they closed down all the shops.
Next, they'll ban meat altogether.
Best thing that could happen
to your cholesterol.
Yeah, yeah.
He's smoking again,
and he thinks I don't notice!
Remember Rudi? Uh, colleague of mine.
Slim and trim. Never smoked.
No meat. Now? Dead.
Heart attack in his early sixties.
Great argument, Dad.
Not everyone can have genes
as good as yours.
[father] Now you say it's the genes.
Then how come the poor
keep dying earlier and earlier,
and the rich keep getting
younger and younger?
Is that also thanks to genes?
It's for the same reason the poor
have a higher standard of living
than they did ten years ago.
Mm-hmm. And what if I wanna be 20 again
to enjoy my high standard of living?
Could you arrange that for me,
Mr. Employee of the Year?
Sure, if you can find a compatible donor.
And what would that cost me?
Oh, I forgot.
It costs more than you can make
in a lifetime.
At least if you have an honest job.
Animals are no longer slaughtered,
but humans are sucked dry.
Many who were "sucked dry"
are better off today.
Instead of living in the ghetto,
they live in Neukölln or Prenzlauer Berg.
They have jobs and families.
I mean, if they have nothing left
but their youth,
you really wanna stop them
from profiting off it?
All right, that's enough.
- Both of you.
- Yeah, yeah. I'll shut up.
Stefan!
[sighs]
[Elena] I don't agree.
His entire life and career,
he paid into his health insurance.
And now he has to pay
for his medication himself.
You know how unhealthy
your father's lifestyle has been.
Now he has to face the consequences.
Seriously?
[scoffs] Why do you always end up
taking his side?
I'm on your side.
Always. You know that.
Well, it would be nice if you said that
to your father sometimes.
"Yeah, Dad, my husband's no saint,
and Aeon isn't exactly Greenpeace."
"But other managers
screw over their donors all the time."
"At least my husband makes sure
that they're compensated fairly."
"He also busts his ass every day
to pay off a huge loan
because his wife works
in a community hospital
for a minuscule salary."
So, I'm supposed to tell him
all that next time I see him?
I better write that down, then.
Or you could just say, "I love him
despite him being a small cog
in a capitalist system."
I love him
despite him being a small cog
in the capitalist system.
I love you too.
I know.
[pensive music playing]
What is that?
Shit. It's our building.
[tense music playing]
Stop! You can't come through here.
- [Max] Elli!
- Go on! Get back!
We live here.
[both breathing heavily]
Shit.
[indistinct police radio chattering]
It's only stuff, okay?
The insurance company will handle it.
It's our home.
[woman] Your apartment
was completely destroyed.
According to the last data
transmitted by the fire detector,
the fire wasn't caused
by faulty wiring or anything like that.
It was definitely an open flame.
Probably a candle.
Fuck.
I'm sure I put out the candles
before we left.
Unfortunately, your insurance won't budge
in this case. It's considered negligence.
So they won't pay out anything.
What are we gonna do?
There's not a lot we can do.
Your bank will demand
the mortgage you owe.
The entire sum.
[Max] Uh, that's almost 2.5 million.
How are we supposed to pay that?
All our money was in the apartment.
[woman] Unfortunately, they're going to
have to claim your collateral.
- [Max] What collateral?
- [somber music playing]
[woman] You didn't tell him?
[Max] What?
Tell me what?
I put up something else
as collateral back then.
I'm a match.
You... you put up your lifetime?
The bank advisor told me it was risk-free.
Worse comes to worst,
we could just sell the apartment.
I don't believe this. How can anyone...
And you never thought
to tell me about this before?
- I wanted the apartment for us.
- [Max sighs]
For our family.
No, we're gonna find a way to fix this.
It's... I'm also a match.
I already looked into that, Max.
According to Aeon,
there's no match for you in the database.
- But I've donated before.
- [woman] I know.
But apparently, that recipient
recently passed away.
[somber music playing]
Elena is the only one
who can still donate.
Two and a half million. That's like...
forty...
forty years.
[tense music playing]
There has to be something we can do.
[woman] Unfortunately,
I don't see any other way.
[rain pattering]
[unsettling music playing]
[woman] Elena Toma?
- You're gonna need to come with us.
- She didn't do anything.
Sir, step back, please.
A writ of execution
has been issued against you.
We've reason to believe
that you're planning to leave the country.
We just went to see our lawyer.
Just a precautionary measure.
My colleague will escort you
to our vehicle.
[Max] What? Hey!
Elli?
We'll fix this, okay? We'll fix this.
I'll find a way.
[officer] Watch your head.
[unsettling music continues]
[Max] Ms. Theissen?
Uh. Remember? Max Toma?
Donation Manager of the Year.
Of course. How are you?
I need a loan. Two and a half million.
I know that's a lot of money,
but I can work it off.
The bank's trying to collect
40 years from my wife.
We've tried everything we could
to pay it off, but this,
it's just too much.
So your wife is having a donation
legally enforced on her.
Is that what you're saying?
Yes, 40 years.
To be honest, you're our last hope.
Send me your documentation.
I'll see what I can do for you. Okay?
[indistinct chattering]
[man] Our customers
need to feel 100% safe with us.
Otherwise, the whole business is at risk.
We've already taken countermeasures.
And as far as our business is concerned,
we sell a product worldwide
that's never been seen before,
and the quarterly profits
are reflecting that.
[woman] And you've invested
the entirety of those profits
into research
and other philanthropic projects.
We're talking about lost dividends
to the amount of 23 billion euros.
And that's just last year.
Research is what made this company
what it is today.
Yes, that may be true,
but we've now perfected the procedure.
"Perfected"?
How the hell can we say we perfected it
if donors and recipients
still need to be DNA compatible?
We're still wasting
way too many valuable resources
looking for suitable donors.
That some people will never find.
[pensive music playing]
A minority
with a rare genetic disposition.
I mean, can we really justify
spending this much
on questionable research
that only covers a tiny niche?
And one more thing...
The shareholders are worried that
because of this, Ms. Theissen,
you might be a bit too biased.
As opposed to you?
[pensive music continues]
[footsteps approaching]
You ready?
[Max] She promised.
Sophie Theissen promised
she'd get back to me.
[sighs] Max.
I've been trying to reach her office
every day for weeks. Every day.
Welcome to Aeon.
Luna Ackermann.
We're here to see a patient.
Elena Toma. I'm her lawyer.
Her donation is in two hours.
I can't let her see any visitors
until after the procedure.
Look, I work over at headquarters.
I just wanna see my wife.
For enforced donations, you have to wait
until after the operation.
You're sucking 40 years from her,
and I'm not even allowed to see her?
Regulations. I'm sorry.
"Regulations"? You asshole! Her life
will be over after you're done with her!
- I wanna see her now!
- Max.
This is getting us nowhere.
Luna, that's all I ever hear from you.
Why are you even here, huh?
Fuck!
[unsettling music playing]
- [Luna] Max. Max!
- [man] Hey, stop! I said stop!
[panting]
[music fades]
Elena?
- [tense music playing]
- Elena!
Oh!
[Max grunts]
Elena! Elena!
Let go of me!
I just wanna see my wife! Let go of me!
You need to calm down right now...
[grunting]
...or else my colleague
is going to hurt you.
Hey, please! This isn't necessary.
The man just wanted to see his wife.
That's all. Please let him go.
He'll be calm.
[breathing heavily]
[Max groaning]
[Sophie] Why were we finally able
to stop the climate crisis?
Because the top 5%
decided to invest into green technology.
Because the prospect of presumably living
in this world for, hopefully, much longer,
completely changed
their perspective on the climate.
When we change
our perspective of this world...
[Max sighs]
...we can also change the world
as a result of it.
[ethereal music playing]
[beeping]
You, Ms. Elena Toma,
hereafter referred to as "the debtor,"
have had an attachment of assets
issued against you.
The seizure shall be levied
against the time assets of the debtor.
As decided by the court,
the amount shall be 38 years.
In accordance with section 863
of the Civil Procedure Code,
after the procedure
is performed by Aeon Inc.,
the seized amount shall be
immediately paid out to the creditors.
The People's Republic of China
has long been advocating
for an international ban
on time donations.
What do you have to say about that?
It's innovation. You can't stop it.
Uh, but what you can do is
enforce the responsible handling
of innovative technologies.
And that's where I think
this resistance is coming from.
[breathing nervously]
[door opens]
[breathing heavily] No. No!
No! Stop! You can't do this!
Let me go!
Help me!
[whimpering] Help!
Help!
[breathing heavily]
You have to help me. Please.
Please help!
You have to help me, please!
[breathing heavily]
[air hisses]
[device chimes]
[brooding music playing]
[machine beeps]
[brooding music swells]
[hip-hop music playing]
[indistinct chattering]
[baby crying]
[Max] We can't afford
anything better right now.
- [siren wails in the distance]
- [hip-hop music playing]
[Elena] It's already starting.
[breathing nervously]
[children chattering]
[somber music playing]
[gasps, panting]
Hey. It's okay. It's all right.
[Elena crying]
[somber music continues]
[device buzzing]
[Max] "Got some good news
from the very top. Erika."
Unless I'm somehow mistaken, this comes
from the desk of Sophie Theissen herself.
I've been working here ten years,
and I doubt she knows my name.
So, what does it say?
Congratulations, you've been promoted.
Senior donation manager.
- You'll have your own team and everything.
- Wait, that's it?
What do you mean?
You're making more than me now.
Almost a thousand more a month
and a 35,000 euro bonus on top of that.
You think I wanna spend
one more millisecond working here?
- Hey. Everything set up for the meeting?
- Hi.
- Hey, how are you?
- Hi. Good to see you.
[panting]
Ms. Theissen?
- Ms. Theissen is busy right now.
- She knows me. She...
Hey. You promised you'd help me.
If you care about your future here at all,
you'll turn around and walk away now.
[ominous music playing]
[gentle music playing]
[dog barking]
[indistinct chattering]
[keys jingling]
[ethereal music playing]
Elli?
[indistinct chattering]
[music fades]
Best I could do.
I love you so much.
We'll get through this.
I can't do this.
Look at us.
This is crazy.
I love you.
- Regardless...
- Of how old I am?
What is this anyway?
Pity?
What? No.
Then what? You feel guilty for me?
Come on now.
Your life goes on.
I paid the price, not you.
I didn't ask for this.
Leave me alone.
Leave me alone!
- Elli.
- Just leave me alone.
[Elena sighs]
[door opens]
[door closes]
["Gravity of Sin" playing]
[sighs]
[grunts]
[sobbing]
[groans]
[distant siren wailing]
Rough day?
["Gravity of Sin" continues]
Need a pick-me-up?
I'll give you a really good deal.
Fuck off.
You don't have to be
such a dick about it. Asshole.
- [man shouting]
- [bottle shatters]
[alarm wailing]
[Elena groaning]
[Elena crying]
["Gravity of Sin" continues]
[woman] Fortunately, we were able
to stop the bleeding.
But we're still waiting
for the results of the hematogram.
Why would you withdraw 40 years at once?
That's incredibly irresponsible
and reckless.
You should've stayed
at the transfer clinic a few more days.
Especially after a procedure that serious
and given her condition.
What condition?
[doctor] Elena had a miscarriage.
It's unfortunately very common
with time donors.
You were pregnant?
[ethereal music playing]
[ethereal music continues]
[Elena] There's just no point.
You belong with me,
no matter how old your body is.
Max, this isn't just about
some gray hair or wrinkles.
We wanted to watch our kids
grow up together.
They'd have kids of their own.
We'd play with our grandchildren one day.
And we wanted to grow old together.
Both of us.
But now I won't be able
to do any of that with you.
You still have
your whole life ahead of you.
[Max sighs]
[Stefan sighs]
[ethereal music playing]
[mother sobs]
[mother sobs] I'm here, Elli.
[car door closes]
[mother crying]
[sighs]
You don't have to come in.
[sniffles]
It can be reversed.
I know who the recipient was,
and I'll find a way
to make them reverse it.
How? They didn't break any laws.
That's how it works, isn't it?
Your stupid system.
Fuck the system.
[ethereal music playing]
[children chattering]
[man] Give me those
and two of the other ones.
[girl] No problem. Mommy's got everything.
Thanks.
[mysterious music playing]
[indistinct chattering]
[lighter clicks]
[Max] You really shouldn't do that.
Stunts your growth.
Ha ha. What do you want, asshole?
Where did you get it done?
You're not fooling me with that baby face.
Aeon didn't do it.
Relax. I'm not gonna report you.
I just want your contact.
[unsettling music playing]
[robotic voice] We have received
the 30,000 euros.
Dr. Berg will expect you
in one week's time.
As soon as you've crossed the border
into Lithuania,
you'll contact him
via an unregistered burner phone.
You will then be given
the coordinates to the clinic.
Those will be valid for exactly six hours.
If you don't show up,
our agreement is void.
[indistinct chattering]
[female newscaster] Ever since
the attack that claimed the lives
of several Nobel Prize laureates at
an Aeon clinic in Berlin a few weeks ago,
Lilith, the leader of the Adam Group,
has been on the very top
of every international most wanted list.
As of now, we have no information
on her whereabouts.
However, one of our reporters
was able to make contact with her,
and she's agreed to be patched in
from an undisclosed location.
[man on TV] You've claimed
that your acts of terrorism
are simply a continuation
of dedicated lobbying.
Are you not simply trying to justify
these needless acts of violence?
We are a wake-up call.
If more people would take a stand
against grave injustice,
groups like Adam would not be necessary.
And thankfully,
more people are joining us every day.
[radio host 1] Convoy on standby.
Sophie Theissen
is now leaving the building.
[male host 2] In the United States,
prison sentences can now be
legally settled via a time donation.
Is that not preferable
to incarcerating an offender for years
at the taxpayers' expense?
[Lilith] What Aeon is trying
to pass off to us here
as a public service
is actually a perverse privatization
of the justice system.
How do you think this will affect
the future verdicts
when de facto profits are to be made
from long prison sentences?
[male host 2] People well-versed
in the bible associate your name, Lilith,
as well as that of Adam,
with the wrathful God
of the Old Testament.
Don't you think you're playing God?
[Lilith] We kill every chrono recipient
until this horrible practice
is terminated. It's as simple as that.
[male host 2] The number of time donations
in the last year has more than doubled,
despite all your
terrorist activities and threats.
And it hasn't stopped me either.
Which is why you're also
right on the top of our list.
LAZARUS CEMETERY
BERLIN
[woman] Can you wait here, please?
I wanna be alone.
[man] As you wish.
[pensive music playing]
[tense music playing]
[tense music subsides]
Help me! Help me! Help!
[both grunting]
[tense music playing]
[woman grunts]
[both grunting]
[woman straining]
[electrical pulsing]
[woman groans]
[tense music continues]
[paint spraying]
[Max grunts, pants]
[breathing heavily]
[woman] Probably a stroke.
- Preexisting conditions?
- Not in his file, at least.
But his donation was only
three months ago.
It probably hasn't sunk in for him yet
that he isn't 30 anymore.
I'll take it from here.
- Theater 2 has just become available.
- You don't have to.
- Elli, you need to take it slow.
- [groans]
Your shift is almost over anyway.
Okay?
[whispers] Okay.
[Max] Elli.
Elli, we need to talk.
- Oh, Max.
- You have to come with me right now.
- Listen to me.
- What for?
Let it go, please.
You have to accept the situation.
What if I've found a way?
[pensive music playing]
Just trust me.
One last time.
[mysterious music playing]
CAR SERVICE E-CONVERSION
Here. Put this on.
Come on.
[mysterious music continues]
This is Sophie Theissen.
The woman who stole 40 years from you.
And now we're taking them back.
[male officer] I'll start here.
Are you gonna do that side?
- [Nowak] Thanks. I owe you one.
- [male officer] No worries.
They think it was Adam?
Well, that's pretty conclusive evidence.
And you? What do you think?
Usually, they just kill their targets.
Kidnapping is new.
What else they got?
According to traffic surveillance,
there was a car from Berlin Cars
at the cemetery, around the back.
Booked via a fake account
that can't be traced back to anyone.
However, that same account
has been used before at Tempelhof Field.
I went and checked our database.
And guess who just happened
to enter the field
at that exact time using an Aeon ID.
- Have his work phone traced.
- I think we can skip past that.
He's Employee of the Year.
He's not stupid.
But as long as you have a face,
you can't hide forever.
Well, you're not as stupid as you look.
Have you lost your damn mind?
[Max] It's the only way.
No!
This is crazy.
I've got everything set,
but we need to get out of Germany now.
I packed you some clothes.
You'll have to leave your phone here too.
I'm not doing this. Absolutely not.
Well, then what? Huh?
We just live like this?
You run yourself down as a doctor
for a few more years until you drop dead?
[somber music playing]
What are you going to do
after the operation?
Kill Theissen and run?
We'll start over.
Away from here, by the ocean.
Max, we aren't kids anymore.
If they catch us,
it's not just my life that'll be over.
Yours would be too.
Yeah.
[pensive music playing]
[Max] I guess you shouldn't have
blown me off, huh?
You're right.
Our lives are over either way.
So, should I go to prison for this woman,
or are you coming with me?
[tense music playing]
Should we inform the local authorities?
What for?
- [explosion]
- [gas hissing]
[man 1] Clear!
- [man 2] Clear!
- [man 3] Clear!
[man 4] Clear.
[man 5] Clear!
[man 3] Gonna check on the gallery.
- All clear!
- [man 4] Okay. Moving down.
Back to position one.
We'll find them.
You can save it with the platitudes.
I've been at this longer than you.
Shit!
["Line Them Up" playing]
Your new life.
You still surprise me sometimes.
[Max chuckles]
I surprise myself.
Should work everywhere but airports.
Erika?
Seriously?
[laughs]
ROSTOCK HARBOR
["Line Them Up" continues]
If the police knew about this...
[music fades]
This'll take some time.
Coffee?
Do you know the story
of how Max Toma met his wife?
He was assigned to her
as a donation manager.
But in the course of making the sale,
they fell head over heels in love
and got married.
Hmm. How romantic.
Yeah.
Until their apartment suddenly burns down,
and they're drowning in debt.
I know we're not dealing
with criminal masterminds here.
These are two people
in a desperate situation.
Well, if you were Elena Toma,
how do you think you'd feel?
If your life was stolen from you
and given to some billionaire
because you forgot to blow out a candle.
Nobody forced this woman
to mortgage 38 years of her life
on a luxury apartment.
"Your time. Your chance. Your choice."
They wouldn't be the first
to fall for something like that.
That suddenly gives them the right
to kidnap someone?
Take the law in their own hands?
What about us?
Illegal software,
off-the-record operations.
The richest woman in Europe
gets to play by different rules?
Our job is to keep the Theissens safe,
not achieve world peace.
If you have a problem with that,
then what are you doing here?
Touché.
In the end, it's always about money.
The coffee.
The nice company.
What about you?
I started working as a bodyguard
for Sophie Theissen over 30 years ago.
I owe her a lot.
Apparently, a lot more
than first impressions would imply.
Chronologically, I'm 64.
Sophie Theissen needs people
she can trust implicitly.
And I guess the rejuvenation treatment
is just an added perk.
[chuckles] Well, at least now
you can stop quietly sulking
that your superior is younger than you.
- That's a load off my mind.
- [laughs]
[Max] Hey.
I'd already resigned myself
to the fact that my life was over.
Our life.
And then you come strolling back,
telling me there's hope.
[typing]
[pensive music playing]
[Nowak] Zoom in there.
[computer chimes]
Well, fuck me.
Fuck.
[tense music playing]
[girl clears throat]
We won't hurt...
We won't kill you
if you keep your mouth shut.
[whimpering]
[muffled scream]
[grunting]
- [Max sighs]
- [tool clicking]
Okay.
[game chiming]
You're already better than Daddy.
- [mother] Very pretty.
- [father] Let's try it like this.
- Emilia. Emilia, look.
- Oh, you're so good.
Don't go too far, okay?
[man on PA] All passengers, please prepare
passports and documentation.
Mommy, Daddy!
- Look at the pretty lights!
- Uh-huh.
[man on PA] All passengers, please...
[father] That's enough.
Come back and finish your drawing.
Come on, honey.
[woman on PA] Dear passengers,
we will shortly arrive
at Klaipėda, Lithuania.
We ask all passengers
with destination Klaipėda
to return to their cars...
Is that for us?
Shit, I don't know.
Who else would it be for?
We still have the passports.
Those won't help us
if they check too closely.
So, this is it, then?
[Emilia's mother
speaking Lithuanian, laughs]
continues speaking Lithuanian]
[Emilia's parents speaking German]
[tense music playing]
KLAIPĖDA TRANSIT PORT
LITHUANIA
[indistinct chattering]
[indistinct radio chattering]
[dog barking]
[tense music continues]
- Passport, please.
- Yes.
Yes, passport.
[dog barking]
[indistinct radio chattering]
[officer] What's in the back?
Um, uh, a bathtub from Germany.
[officer] And where are you going?
[breathing heavily]
[whimpers]
I'm going to Vilnius.
Okay, we'll check.
Drive through.
- [indistinct chattering]
- [device chimes]
[indistinct radio chattering]
[unsettling music playing]
[dog barking]
[baby crying]
[indistinct radio chattering]
Your passport, please.
[baby coughing, crying]
[door lock rattling]
Uh, how do I open this again?
Push, then turn to the right.
[truck approaching]
[muffled whimpering]
[truck engine humming]
[muffled] Help me! Help me!
[muffled moan]
[officer] What's in here?
[muffled screams]
[truck engine revving loudly]
[truck departing]
What's inside?
Bathtub, I think.
You think?
Tell him you're just the driver.
I... I'm just a driver.
[officer on phone] Sir, I'm gonna need you
to open the whole box.
Sir, did you hear me?
Everything okay here?
He looks a little nervous.
Why are you so nervous?
[baby crying]
All right, have a good trip.
- Hey.
- [car engine starts]
Just take a deep breath.
Just smile and tell them
you're not used to this.
I'm just not used to this.
Not used to what?
Being threatened by a gun.
[tense music playing]
How many times have I told you?
Stop pointing that thing at people
for no reason.
We're sorry, sir. You're good to go.
Okay.
- [Emilia breathes heavily]
- [Max sighs in relief]
[mysterious music playing]
[baby crying]
It's all right, Emilia.
Everything'll be okay.
Can we go now?
Your phones.
Phones!
- [baby crying]
- [mother shushing]
I'll just get the phone, okay?
It's all right.
- [baby crying]
- [mother shushing]
I'm sorry.
- [air hissing]
- [baby crying]
[mother speaking Lithuanian]
- [mother speaking Lithuanian]
[ethereal music playing]
We had no choice.
Yeah.
[phone chimes]
We crossed the border.
We should check on her.
She's not doing well.
We can't stop now.
They'll call the police.
We need to take side roads.
And then?
Wait for the doctor to contact us.
[music fades]
What do you want from me?
We're just gonna take back what's ours.
Then we'll let you go.
You can have whatever you want.
My mother will pay it.
Your mother?
Sophie Theissen.
You are Sophie Theissen.
What? I'm...
I'm Marie Theissen, her daughter.
[chuckles] No.
She's lying.
My mother keeps me out of the public eye
for reasons just like this.
SOPHIE THEISSEN DAUGHTER
[Max] Daughter. See?
This is Theissen's daughter.
She died of progeria over ten years ago.
That was my older sister Lucy.
Listen, my mother and I
have always looked alike.
- But after this fucking donation...
- Shut up!
Did she have any ID on her?
Driver's license, anything?
Yes, only it's in my purse.
That was left at the cemetery,
and she knows that.
- Nice performance you put on though.
- No. No. Please. Please!
My mother will give you anything!
Honest to god. She'll give you... Please!
- [Marie whimpers]
- [taser crackling]
We gotta make sure it's her.
[breathing heavily]
How?
Call Aeon to find out
if we've actually got the right one?
So her people can track us down?
That's exactly what she wants us to do!
Theissen would say anything
to save herself!
We're sticking to the plan.
What is the plan?
Why hasn't this Dr. Berg contacted us?
What if it's a scam,
and they just wanted the money?
How long are you going
to keep her in there?
She's dehydrated and hypothermic.
We need to find a warm place to hide.
[keys jingling]
[ethereal music playing]
[Elena] Why isn't anyone here?
The tourism industry collapsed
when the Baltic States
left the European Union.
We've got the hotel to ourselves.
Theissen's used to it.
[Elena] Ha ha.
Well, it sure beats that hotel
you booked us that time in Tuscany.
[Max] Ha ha.
[chuckles softly]
It really hurts.
[footsteps approaching]
Thanks.
- Watch what you're doing.
- We don't have to be assholes about it.
You're the one who sold 40 years
to my mother, aren't you?
[sighs] Quit playing.
You know better than anybody
that it was enforced.
Don't let her get to you.
I'm against donations, too, you know.
What happened to you
happens to so many people.
Look at the refugees that go missing
from the camps outside the EU borders.
Even children!
They're sold by their own parents.
Not to Aeon
but to illegal Eastern Bloc clinics
so that third-rate celebs and influencers
can rejuvenate on the cheap.
Are you trying to make me feel guilty?
- You of all people?
- No.
I'm trying to tell you
that I'm on the same side as you.
I've been trying to convince my mother
that what she does...
Bullshit!
Please. You've got to believe me.
Please don't.
I won't say another word. I promise.
Hey! Hey!
Whose side are you on here, huh?
Whose side?
Yes! I'm doing this for you.
For you!
We don't even know
if you kidnapped the right woman.
[sighs]
Even if it is her daughter,
then she's probably compatible with you.
First-degree blood relatives
are almost always a match.
We can still use her.
"Use her"?
Uh, she can just get it back after
from her mother.
They can sort it out themselves.
It's not our problem.
The consequences of what we're doing here
are absolutely our problem.
Oh, okay. So we let her go.
I mean, it's just your life.
She still has hers.
Maybe she wants a child.
[unsettling music playing]
[sighs]
You've changed.
- So have you.
- [footsteps retreating]
[exhales]
[sighs]
[Marie breathes deeply]
Is there any running water here?
I'd like to clean myself up.
Please.
[water running]
[water stops]
Wait a sec.
- [restraint snaps]
- [Marie] Thanks.
My mom just wanted to help Lucy.
That's how the whole thing started.
She was researching cell aging
and made groundbreaking discoveries.
But she couldn't find
a match for Lucy in time.
[Max sighs]
[water running]
[metal rasp]
[grunts]
- [Marie whimpers]
- [Max groans]
[tense music playing]
[Max panting]
[tense music intensifies]
No, no, no, no.
[Marie panting]
[mysterious music playing]
Damn!
No. [panting]
Come on.
[breathing heavily]
[water gently splashing]
[phone dialing, line ringing]
[woman] Hello? Who is this?
[whispering] Kaya?
Kaya, you've gotta help me.
No, no, no. No. [whimpers]
Oh shit.
[whimpers]
[tense music playing]
[tense music subsides]
[breathing heavily, whimpering]
[grunting]
[whimpering]
Help!
Help me!
- Help!
- [Elena] Grab this.
With both hands.
[Elena grunting]
[gasping]
[Elena straining]
[Elena grunts]
[Marie breathing heavily]
Thank you.
- [Marie whimpers]
- [Max grunts]
Leave us alone.
- Are you sure?
- Look at her.
[soothing music playing]
[plastic crackling]
[phone chimes]
[spraying]
Did you hear from the doctor?
Mm-mm.
[Max sighs]
What happened with Theissen?
She said she wanted to clean herself up,
and I didn't wanna be an asshole.
Of course not.
Are you angry with me?
No. Why? Should I be?
[sighs] After everything
I've done for you?
For me? What about what I need?
Are you interested in that?
Yeah, right.
I'm not doing this for you,
for us, or our child.
I really don't know what you want from me.
She didn't have the operation scar.
[scoffs]
Th... that's what's bugging you?
The skin regenerates
during rejuvenation. It's normal.
Elli, she... she's manipulating both of us
by acting all innocent.
You know what went through my mind
when I saw her going under?
If she dies, then it was all for nothing.
She's my only chance.
What if we have the wrong person?
I don't think I want to know.
[tender music playing]
And that scares the hell out of me.
Elli, you were the wrong person.
You didn't deserve this.
We...
we still have our lives ahead of us.
["Starry Night" playing]
[Max kissing]
[moaning]
[music intensifies]
[Nowak] We got them.
We located them.
Finally.
Burner phone
with dynamic service provider.
It always takes a while.
They're still in Lithuania. Near Šumskas.
That's at the border of Belarus,
130 kilometers from here.
Then we can start immediately.
The reinforcements are here.
[tense music playing]
Let's go!
[tense music intensifies]
You sure we don't need
combat helicopters too?
[tense music fades]
[gun cocks]
[both gasp]
[man] Easy now.
[Max breathing heavily]
If you have any weapons,
you better tell us where they are.
- Under the pillow.
- [chuckles] Classic.
Yeah.
Who are you?
Aeon?
On the contrary.
Sorry to interrupt.
Fuck.
What do you want?
[Marie whimpering]
Hey. Please. Don't kill her.
Please.
Why would we wanna kill Marie Theissen?
[tense music playing]
What if the Tomas aren't intimidated
by our little private army?
I'm getting Marie out of there alive.
I don't care how.
So we'll be digging
a couple of graves today.
Deep in Lithuanian no-man's-land.
You think I would do that?
I'm wondering if I could do it.
Whether I could live with those ghosts.
It isn't easy.
I never wanted a longer life.
I just wanted to be fit for my job.
Youth is...
It may sound tempting,
but youth alone doesn't
make your life better or happier.
Just longer.
And also full of ghosts.
When you've worked
in the private sector for so long,
you sometimes forget why you started.
I know a trick.
It's called anchor.
Any time I start to doubt, I do this.
It reminds me
of the reason I started doing this.
For justice.
What about you?
For money?
For youth?
Sophie Theissen?
We're here to free an innocent woman.
After that, you'll buy me a drink.
[chuckles]
You don't give up, do you?
All right, then. One drink.
When this is done.
[groaning]
[man] Okay.
[tense music playing]
[panting]
[Marie whimpers] Please.
Let me go.
- I've never had a donation.
- I know.
But I'm afraid
this is much bigger than you.
My wife was forced to make a donation.
We're the victims here.
I know your story, Max.
Textbook career,
prestigious job, great salary,
employee of the year.
Always benefited from the system.
And then, all of a sudden,
your house burns down.
Just when Sophie Theissen
urgently needs a donation.
And your own recipient, Max,
just happens to die
in a motorcycle accident
so that only Elena remains as a donor.
So many tragic coincidences.
What?
W... what are you saying?
You were supposed to be
Elena's donation manager.
Isn't that how you two met?
[Marie whimpers]
Sophie Theissen already knew back then
that Elena was a possible donor.
The only match she'd ever really found.
You were supposed to convince Elena.
Instead, you married her.
[Marie whimpers]
[Lilith] Too bad for Sophie Theissen.
How is she gonna get access
to Elena's lifetime now?
[Marie whimpers]
The apartment that was much too expensive
for the two of you?
The bank that nevertheless
gave you the loan?
But only if Elena
put up her lifetime as a collateral.
Then a little fire,
and the two of you are so deeply plunged
into financial misery
that she could simply take your lifetime.
And now the two of you
wanna do exactly the same with this girl,
the only Theissen
with a bit of a conscience.
It was a mistake.
I didn't know we had the wrong person.
Really? After spending two days with her?
Or you just didn't wanna see it?
You are no better.
You're killing innocent people.
"Innocent"?
- [Marie whimpers]
- Hey. Hey! Hey!
[Elena grunts]
[tense music playing]
Finish what you started. Kill her.
Wha... what?
What?
You were prepared to take
40 years of her life.
Obviously you decided some time ago
that your life is worth more than hers.
That's just sick. I won't do it.
Stop. This is madness.
[whimpering] I've never done anything.
Exactly. What did you ever really do
to stop your mother?
There's only one bullet,
so no funny business.
[gasping, whimpering]
- [guns cocking]
- [Lilith] Your life or hers.
Make your choice!
[tense music intensifies]
[whimpering] Please! Please! Please don't!
Please. Please.
[Marie whimpering]
[Marie groans]
[gasps]
[tense music subsides]
[Marie gasps, whimpers]
Most people become pacifists
when forced
to pull the trigger themselves.
But if it's doctors in white coats
arranging it for you,
few have a problem with it.
[phone buzzing]
[Lilith] That's why Aeon is so successful
and so dangerous.
What?
[man] Dr. Berg has shared
the location of his clinic.
Valid for six hours.
You're gonna miss that appointment,
I'm afraid.
[man] Sophie Theissen
will be making an appearance soon,
and she'll wanna talk to you.
Our source is telling us
make sure she comes in with you alone,
without her guard dogs.
Is that clear?
We're just the bait.
You wanna kill Sophie Theissen.
And make a martyr of her?
No. We'll take her with us,
provided you don't make a mistake.
[vehicles approaching]
- [tense music playing]
- [guns cocking]
Come on.
[guns cocking]
You've got this.
[door hinge squeaking]
[man] Get down!
On the ground now!
[Max] Marie Theissen is alive.
If nothing happens to me,
nothing will happen to her.
[man] Down on the ground!
I wanna talk to Sophie Theissen.
Nobody else.
Sophie Theissen.
If he fucks it up?
Plan B.
Sophie Theissen leaves either with us
or not at all.
Judas will take care of that.
[unsettling music playing]
My wife's youth suits you.
Mr. Toma,
I understand that you feel
that what happened with your wife
was an injustice.
From your point of view,
I can absolutely see
why you did what you did.
My daughter is innocent.
More than anyone else in this.
I assume you don't want
to hurt innocent people?
Only if I'm forced to.
[Sophie] Good.
I'm prepared to pay you
for your wife's years a second time.
Ten million.
That's more than anyone in your position
could hope for.
You can start a new life with that.
And maybe you'll even find her
a new donor.
I have one.
I'm Donation Manager of the Year.
[gun cocks]
I know how those conversations go.
How you list all the advantages
of donating like it's a big win for them.
All the while knowing
you have the upper hand.
That you're holding all the aces.
And those poor suckers
sitting across from you...
only had their lives.
We have your daughter,
and you have my wife's 40 years.
If you give those back,
then we don't need Marie anymore.
If you don't,
then we'll have no other choice.
Your call.
How do I know that Marie's still alive?
That she's well?
She's not doing well.
But she's still alive.
You can go see for yourself.
In person.
Sophie Theissen is not
entering the building without me.
The very minute any other person
goes through that door,
my wife pulls the trigger.
Then we'll call Marie on the phone
from out here.
Forget it, guys.
I know who I'm dealing with here.
People who will do anything,
burn down houses, arrange accidents.
This deal is going to go down
exactly the way I say.
All right, I'll come in.
Good.
I will not lose Marie as well.
[Kaya] Just one question, Mr. Toma.
You wanted to talk
to Sophie Theissen directly.
How did you know
she was going to be here in person?
[whispers] Say something.
You idiot, just say something.
It's a trap, Sophie!
Fuck!
[tense music playing]
[whispers] Do it.
- [gunshots]
- [Nowak grunts]
[Marie gasps]
[Nowak grunts]
Sophie!
Make sure she's dead.
- Fire!
- [guns cocking]
[Kaya] Fire!
Fire!
[tense music playing]
- [gunshots continue]
- [breathing heavily]
[Max groans]
[groans]
- [breathing heavily]
- [gunshots continue]
Elena.
[Max grunting, groaning]
- [man 1] Get down! Get down!
- [man 2] Come on! Come over this way!
[indistinct shouting]
[Lilith] Max, do you...
- [Max coughing]
- [high-pitched ringing]
[muffled groaning, coughing]
[man] I'm behind you.
I've got you covered.
[Max grunting]
Sorry.
[gun cocks]
[Max] Please. Let me see my wife.
[indistinct shouting]
[brooding music playing]
[gun cocks]
[man] Keep your heads down and stay here.
[gunshots]
[Max grunts, groans]
[panting]
[Elena] Max!
[Max panting]
[Elena] Behind you!
[both grunting]
[man screaming]
[man unsheathes knife]
[screaming]
[grunts]
[both grunt, groan]
[Max groaning]
[Max panting]
[Elena panting]
[Max] Hey.
- You all right?
- I'm okay.
Yes. Yes.
- Thank God.
[distant gunshots]
Wait.
[blade rasps]
- Careful.
- [Elena] Quick.
Okay. Okay. We're going right now.
- Marie!
- Come on.
Go ahead.
Marie! Come on. Let's go.
- [Marie gasps]
- Hey! Let's go!
- You wanna die here? Come on.
- [Marie whimpers]
Let's go! Let's go. Hurry!
[Elena] Hey!
[Max] This way. Come on.
[Elena] Come on.
[Marie] Fuck.
[gun cocks]
I'm outta here.
[Marie breathing heavily]
- [Marie grunts]
- [gun clicking]
[whimpers]
Shit!
[Marie gasps]
[Marie screaming]
[Elena grunts]
- [Max] Hey!
- [Marie screams]
[loud thud]
[Max] Enough!
[tense music playing]
[Max breathing heavily]
[car engine starting]
Okay.
[somber music playing]
[indistinct chattering]
[man 1] All right.
That's it. Let's wrap it up.
Moving out.
- [indistinct chattering]
- [line ringing]
[man 2] Come on, men.
- [man 3] Did you check the basement?
- [man 4] I checked the whole area.
[phone buzzing]
[indistinct chattering]
It's not far from here.
We almost killed her.
She would have shot me.
But we know she isn't Sophie Theissen.
You said she's also compatible.
She can get it back from her mother.
Her mother is dead.
Marie had nothing to do with it.
If we do this, we'll be just like them.
Do you wanna be better than them?
Or do you want our life back?
We wanted to have children.
[sighs]
Elena, she's innocent.
Our child was innocent too.
Theissen took it from us.
Theissen burned down our home,
had your recipient killed.
We need to go public with that.
Will that get my years back?
Will it?
There's gotta be another way
to fix this, Elena. It's just not right.
I can't see one.
[unsettling music playing]
I can't do this anymore.
We're taking her to a hospital.
[tense music playing]
Get out, please.
You can't be serious.
Get out.
Elena, come on. Let's talk.
Get out!
Get out.
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
[ethereal music playing]
[parking brake clicks]
[truck engine humming]
[ethereal music continues]
[air hissing]
[Marie] No! No! No!
[crying] No!
No! [coughing]
No!
No! No!
[Marie coughs] No! No!
[crying] No! No!
No!
[Marie crying]
[ethereal music continues]
[man 1] Move it. Come on, people.
Let's go.
Hey.
[man 2] Come here. Move. Move.
Move. Move!
[man speaking Lithuanian]
[in English] These two boys
are going to the doctor.
The others can wait for now.
[man 3] What about the girls?
[ethereal music continues]
- [man 4] The doctor will see you now.
- Thank you.
[car engine starting]
[ethereal music continues]
Hello. Are you okay?
[whimpers]
[ethereal music continues]
REFUGEE CAMP ŠKLÈRIAI
LITHUANIA
[Marie whimpers]
[Marie crying]
[music fades]
[indistinct chattering]
Luckily, you were faster
than your colleague.
He was not my colleague.
Are there any leads yet?
We need to find those people
as soon as possible.
Not my problem anymore.
What does that mean?
I'm done hunting down people for you.
I'm done burning down homes for you.
I'm done arranging fatal accidents.
I'm done here.
We've known each other half our lives!
Lives end eventually.
[dark music playing]
[breathes in deeply]
[exhales]
[Sophie] Hi, sweetie.
[moans]
[gasps]
[Marie crying]
[Marie] Why?
[whimpers]
They said that you'd be compatible.
We are so close to reaching our goals.
I'm gonna need all my strength for that.
I'll do everything I can
to find a donor for you.
I promise, sweetie.
It's only a matter of time.
- [sighs]
- [footsteps retreating]
[ethereal music playing]
[ethereal music continues]
[music intensifies]
[dramatic music playing]
[cocking guns]
[Max] To buy someone's time
is just another way
of taking someone's life.
I know this now.
I've been part of this system.
As long as Aeon exists,
as long as illegal clinics exist,
this injustice will remain.
The time to fight is now.
If not for us, then for our children.
[dramatic music playing]
[intriguing music playing]
[ethereal music playing]
[mysterious music playing]
[music fades]