This is the 22nd century,
the land renewed.
The air and water pure again.
The conflicts of the past are gone.
It is a new Earth.
New peoples and new customs.
In some places, bizarre savagery.
In others, advanced cities.
Everywhere new challenge
and new adventure.
And this is also the story
of Dylan Hunt.
Lost in 1979
in a suspended animation accident.
Over a century and a half later
in the year 2133,
he was found and awakened by
the people of this city called PAX.
Peace.
The one place on Earth which
escaped the final conflict
of the 20th century.
The one place on Earth
where civilization did not perish.
Dylan Hunt is one of them now.
Leader of a PAX Science team
exploring a much changed world.
Part of the PAX dream
of rebuilding on Earth,
a new and wiser civilization.
Their mission is mankind.
Rebirth of...
planet Earth.
Dylan Hunt, log report
to the PAX Council.
Per instructions,
we were escorting Pater Kimbridge
on a survey
which has confirmed
that Central California
is now an inland sea.
Population along the shore
is a handsome racial mixture.
Illiterate but intelligent.
Although the land remains fertile,
famine is common.
Their primary need
from us is education
and agricultural techniques.
With those facts determined
we headed homeward
when the ambush occurred
They were Kreegs.
That mutated form of human
capable of understanding
only machinery and warfare.
It was clear that
they recognized who we were
and wanted us alive.
Possibly because they've heard that
underground subshuttle tubes
honeycomb the earth
and that only we of PAX,
know the secret.
Slowing our progress was
the age of Pater Kimbridge,
his rapid exhaustion.
Each of us in turn tried
to divert the Kreeg vehicle
while the others moved
Kimbridge nearer and nearer
a subshuttle tube entrance,
where we hoped to escape.
There he is, over there.
Team, switch to XY tranquilizers.
Our standard hypos
aren't stopping them.
Message received,
we're reloading.
Isiah, divert them.
Isiah.
That thing is from your century?
Yeah, we call them automobiles.
It's fantastic
that it's still running.
It's a late 1970s chassis with
a converted wood gas fuel system.
There.
No, get the Pater.
Dylan, don't.
Keep down.
They won't try to take us
alive anymore. Go ahead.
Isiah.
Lock it. Hurry.
Looks bad.
He's alive.
Hurry, it's still here.
Team 21, arriving in four minutes.
You'll have a medical team
standing by?
And an operating room.
You say you saw signs of
still other Kreegs out there?
Perhaps a whole expedition?
Affirmative, suggest you cut off
tube power at that point.
We can't get let them
get hold of a subshuttle.
Agreed. Power is terminated.
- How is he?
- There's definite heart damage.
You can close the medikit now,
I've done all I can with it.
And with your mind?
Try.
He's slipping away. He's dying.
Isiah, please..
Ah, let the savage pray.
It'll help as much as
anything I can do here.
Concluding log report.
If Kimbridge dies,
the responsibility's mine.
And our return to PAX
has made the burden no easier.
To me, Kimbridge is PAX.
Its grace, its warmth,
its dreams of helping Earth
rebuild again.
He is the man who discovered
my body in suspended animation.
Whose skill brought me to life again.
Whose wisdom helped me to understand
that the best of my own
20th century is not dead.
That Earth is still my home,
it's people still my people.
Dylan, Baylok needs you.
Pater Kimbridge
is coming out of surgery.
Dylan.
How is he?
Well, the bullet sheared of a section
of the pulmonary artery.
He can last only a couple of days
without bio-plastic prosthesis.
Now, the only surgeon qualified
in that is a Dr. Rabans who--
He's in the eastern
Mediterranean area.
How far is he
from a subshuttle station?
Uh, two weeks at least.
There's a slim second choice.
A Dr. Connor who trained under Rabans.
Jonathan?
But he disappeared on a team mission
about a year ago.
We've made attempts
to locate him, of course.
- Where was he last seen?
- Back the way we came,
several hundred kilometers further on.
Our equipment's waiting
at the subshuttle.
Log entry 324.
As the first PAX team available,
we are headed for what seems
our best chance
of finding Dr. Connor alive.
Hope that the Kreegs are moving
in another direction by now.
Our destination is
an unexplored region out of which
have come stories of
a strange Amazon society.
Where males are bought and
sold like captive animals.
Women's lib.
Or women's lib gone mad?
Officer Smythe,
you call Dr. Connor "Jonathan."
How well did you know him?
I mean, did you know anything
not on the tapes
that might be useful to us?
He did once mention he'd heard of
some plant mutations in that area.
He was interested
in the medical properties
of any new plants,
found after the Great Conflict.
That could explain how he got
separated from his team.
That's our one hope.
He became separated
and was captured by those women.
The tapes list several reports
of men being taken captives.
Hands bound, led by a rope
around the neck.
Pater Kimbridge
has only 60 hours left.
Just finding Jonathan in that time
is once chance in a thousand.
There's one way we can
cut those odds a little.
We're going to split the team.
Baylok and Isiah
will take the subshuttle
to the old power station
that's listed in the diagrams.
It's near the heart of the area.
Hopefully near a main village
or a town of some sort.
You'll immediately
identify yourselves.
Try to explain to them
who and what PAX is.
And why they have a lot to gain
and nothing to lose
by co-operating with us.
As you say we will do, my friend,
but, to split the team--
Yes, isn't that--
It'll give us two separate
and different shots at our objective.
If yours doesn't work, ours might.
You'll drop us in part of the way
near a place where
we can pick up some horses.
We'll carry no weapons
and just one transceiver.
We'll ride into
the Confederacy of Ruth.
Where you'll tell the first women
that we meet
that you've heard of their
system of female dominance
and that you believe in it.
What makes you think
they'll accept that story?
I'll be proof. Your captive,
as described in the tapes.
Bound and led in by the neck.
You. Have Partha send out
a second team.
I want this field ready tomorrow.
You're on your own HS.
Who are you?
I've come to join your Confederacy.
I brought a male captive
from my country
to prove I agree with your beliefs.
What do you know of the women of Ruth?
I subscribe to your principles.
Female dominance is
the natural order of life.
- Eyes down.
- Stop that.
Eyes down.
He hasn't been properly trained.
But he looks healthy enough
to bring a good price.
I challenge your ownership.
But--but it's obvious that I own him.
You saw me ride in with him.
I've just challenged you
for this male.
Will you fight for him or not?
But there's no reason to fight.
I have come in friendship. I--
He is my property!
He was your property.
Uh, there's another man
from my country, miss.
Uh, Jonathan Connor.
He came here about a year ago.
I've explained to you,
the rule here is silence.
But, perhaps this friend of mine
and myself can help you.
We can be a value to you.
You have men pulling wagons,
ploughing fields.
This friend of mine knows how to train
horses to do it better, faster.
Or even oxen.
Why? You Dinks are
more easily trained.
You take care of yourselves,
you grow your own food.
Why should we bother with animals?
That's the second time
you've mentioned training.
What kind of training?
We don't geld our males
if that's what worries you.
It would make them too fat and lazy.
But if you break the rule
of silence again,
I'll make an exception in your case.
This way, Dink, follow me.
- Greetings, Marg.
- Fine day, Bronta.
Villar.
Another outsider?
You haven't enough of them, Marg?
I'm putting this one up for sale.
His manners are tricky.
Eyes down.
Hands don't show much heavy labor.
That'll affect the price.
Eh, but his lines aren't that bad.
Teeth are good, eyes clear.
Couldn't you use a new breeder
at your place?
No spirit.
No, he came along too willingly.
If you can get a breeder price
for him, all the better.
Now listen carefully, wherever
you're from, you're a Dink now.
Untrained, but still a Dink.
The rules are made simple
so that even a male
can understand them.
Show obedience at all times
and you'll find happiness
in service to the community.
As long as your behavior warrants it
you'll be protected, fed, clothed,
relieved of all the responsibilities
that your sex finds
so difficult in life.
It's a mutant group named Kreegs
and they're dangerous.
Silence.
Look, I'm trying to help you.
Your Confederacy may be attacked
any time now.
This is not a chaotic,
male-dominated society.
We are fully capable
of protecting ourselves.
Remember, you'll keep
eyes down and keep silent.
Look, I must have
the answer to one ques--
Silence!
One question!
And then I'll obey all your rules.
I thought Marg said he had no spirit.
Well?
I have a friend who disappeared
in this area about a year ago.
If he's alive and he's here,
I must find him.
Is there something about
this particular Dink we'd remember?
Was he unusually large or small?
Deformed somehow?
No, but his name is Jonathan Connor.
The only name a Dink owns
is the one his mistress
chooses for him.
That is, if she cares
to give him a name at all.
Now, eyes down.
And silence.
I'm looking for someone--
I have to find an outsider who--
Baylok, Isiah, what happened?
Well, how did you get here?
What happened? Tell me.
Dylan, please, your voice is angry.
You, on your feet!
C'mon, get on your feet.
Get over there.
I have a buyer interested in you.
First sale today.
A team of outsiders recently captured.
You'll find this one well trained.
As powerful a field Dink
as you'll ever see offered.
Examine him as close as you like.
He's a bargain in strength
and stamina.
Look at these shoulders.
Look at these back muscles.
Well, if he's as strong as he looks,
- I'm interested.
- Wow!
- Yeah, I'll bid for him.
- And I.
Baylok.
- Wait.
- Go away.
What have they done to you?
What's wrong with you?
Listen, look up at me.
Try to look into my eyes.
- Look into my eyes.
- Please, don't hurt me.
I won't hurt you.
Try to meet my eyes.
Try.
It's your friend, Dylan.
You're an Esper, shut out all of this.
Concentrate on what's inside you.
Your eyes, keep them on mine.
Keep them on mine.
It's just the two of us.
Our eyes, our contact.
Dylan...I'm frightened.
Why?
Have they operated on you in some way?
O-or given you an injection
of some kind?
No. No, nothing medical.
Well, were you given something
to drink then?
No. Water.
Food. Isiah and I...
...we both...ate the food.
Something, so--something in the food.
Do--don't eat the food.
D-don't eat. It contains something.
Don't, please, go away.
Leave me. Frightened.
Drug induces fear.
T-terrible fear. Fear.
Six and six, done.
Can I get six and seven?
- Seven.
- Can I get six prime sheep
and seven bushels?
I bid a ram.
A ram! Six prime sheep
and eight bushels of grain.
Do I hear nine?
- Kyla.
- No. I won't go that much.
Let's see the other one of the pair.
Get him.
Nine bushels, Bronta. Remember,
he might have breeder capacity.
If you like 30 pound babies.
Are you certain
he's completely trained?
He's trained.
My bid stands.
That's too high for me.
Sold to Delba.
Another eight bushels for this one?
No, he'd last about two days
in the field.
They're up as a pair.
You take both of them or neither.
How about that one instead?
The outsider?
That's prime breeder stock
if I'm any judge.
Yes. I like him.
He'll be offered as breeder stock
tomorrow after training.
All right. I'll take him
and I'll reserve this one.
Not so fast, Delba.
I need a breeder too.
He's got spirit.
I may bid for him myself.
I hope training
won't affect him too much.
We'll want him tested, Villar.
- Agreed?
- Agreed, you'll see him tested.
Thank you.
I told you that west section
was arable, Merlo.
Then next month, we'll do
even better, mistress.
The door.
An outsider.
I'm lost. I'm trying to--
Go back the way you came.
We want no outsider female ideas
in our Confederacy.
I've seen more hospitality
from savages.
What do I have to do? Fight you
just to get simple directions?
That is your right, of course.
You challenge me?
Yes.
I want some directions.
And I'm damn well gonna get them.
Mother!
There, there, there, there. Don't cry.
Mother.
I'm sorry. i-I didn't see
the children. I'm sorry.
Come by the fire.
It must have been cold out there.
It's all right.
You see, we're not unkind.
Conduct yourself properly
and I'll leave your hands
free tonight.
Now, eat.
Eat!
I must find him tonight, please.
I can't explain--
There's nothing you can do
until the morning.
All new captives must be kept
overnight in the compound.
Do you enjoy the music?
That was my great-great-grandmother's
strike harp.
It's lovely.
Then the other man I described?
Connor?
You can ask about him
in the village tomorrow.
When you challenge Marg
to win back your captive.
But why do you have customs like that?
Challenging, fighting.
Because women don't deceive
themselves like men.
Male societies reward
deceit and cowardice.
Here, as in nature,
the strong have the best mates
and households.
In nature, the female
is always dominant.
When that natural order is reversed,
men become the same vain,
quarrelsome little seed carriers
who lied and postured and drove
the whole world into destruction.
We'll be at full strength
tomorrow sundown,
Commander Soldier.
Position units.
One to attack each female household.
Their males, they will not fight.
No, Commander Soldier,
the woman do something
which make men fear their own shadow.
Yes.
Commander Soldier, sir.
Sub-units ready to inspect.
Well...
Have you seen him?
Jonathan Connor? If you worked
here at the village last year
you must have seen him.
He's about 35 years old,
5'10" and he--
No, no. No, I've never seen him.
Pretend to be asleep.
- Hmm!
- Quiet, quiet.
- I'm looking for an outsid--
- Back to the compound!
You remember that rule of silence?
It's still in effect.
Not one word.
We're getting some horses
and you're gonna help me
find my friend--
There, you look more like one of us
for your challenge tomorrow.
Beautiful, mistress.
The Dink extract wasn't always
used on the men here, was it?
In the beginning, it was given
only to troublesome males
but over the years,
our women have begun to depend on it.
It's in a gruel that
Marg delivers everyday
to most of the other households.
Which makes it impossible for
anyone to learn Marg's formula.
The secret's been in her family
since our beginning.
But by using it so much now,
it's slowly destroying
our Confederacy.
Not one household in five
had a child last year.
Pity, he didn't respond
to the extract.
He would have made you a nice profit.
Delba wanted him badly
as a breeder. Bronta, too.
Are you certain you saw him
eat the gruel?
How long have I been running
this compound, Marg?
Do you think I can be tricked?
He tricked me, Villar.
I didn't think he had any spirit.
Delba's right about one thing.
Excellent lines.
None of which changes the law.
He must be trained or exterminated.
Please, please, don't hurt me.
Hurt you, little man?
I have more interesting things
in mind for you.
Come out here, Dink.
Eyes down.
Damn, your whole--
What did you say to me?
He's fighting it.
More than any we've had
here in quite a while.
Yes.
Has Marg's outsider been sold yet?
No, Delba.
Good.
...sold to Carlotta.
Next we have an outsider captive
of exceptional spirit.
His resistance to training
promises a good breeder.
I'm not so sure I'm putting
him up for auction.
That's unfair. I've just ridden
all away in to bid on this one.
You agreed to auction him,
Marg. Bring him up.
Don't be shy, Dink,
you'll get used to it fast enough.
Look at the spirit on this one.
- Are you ready, Delba?
- Yes.
Stop.
I'll do any testing that's done.
He's still my property
until he's sold.
Hold on, Villar.
This is Harper-Smythe.
She's here with a challenge.
That Dink is my property.
I captured him and brought him
to the Confederacy.
I challenge any claim you have on him.
You've received
a properly issued challenge, Marg.
Either give up the property or fight.
I'll fight.
Harper-Smythe, over there.
Fight, Marg.
You won him fairly.
Marg is offering you friendship.
We feel no shame here
after we've done our best.
At her age and with his spirit,
we'll have little ones about soon.
I'd give half my fields for a baby.
What do you expect of your males?
If you drugged your rams and
stallion, it's the same way.
Are you still peddling
that nonsense, Treece?
The human male
is an unstable creature.
Who can easily be controlled
by any real woman.
Unless she's afraid
he'll end up by dominating her.
I'd like to see the male
who could dominate me.
Perhaps that's exactly
what you'd like.
Secretly.
Stand still for your mistress, Dink.
Dylan, it's me. Harper-Smythe.
Everything's all right now.
Come closer, everybody.
Harper-Smythe is looking
for another Dink
who came here about a year ago.
Yes, I'd be interested in buying him.
He was a medical healer in my country.
About 34 years old.
Brown hair, hazel eyes,
intelligent features.
I've bought most of the outsiders
in the last few years.
You're welcome to come and
look for him at my household.
That's true. Marg does own
most of the outsider Dinks.
And you can easily visit
the other households from there.
Why not stay with me?
Welcome home, mistress.
You see the order,
the tranquility of our system?
I certainly think there's some
sense in female dominance.
But I don't agree about the drugging.
The extract has its strongest effect
in the beginning.
But as they become accustomed
to it, why, they're content.
Why they're--they're even happy
with it.
The Dink you're looking for?
- You've more in the house?
- Yes.
Perfect contentment.
They take great pride in their work,
their responsibilities.
- Is he here?
- No.
There're many in the fields,
of course. They come at sundown.
Welcome home, mistress.
Another busy day, Gorda?
Thank you.
Not a brain in his head,
but he's a comfort.
I'm sure.
Until yours adjusts to training,
you might find Gorda
much more helpful and amusing.
Oh, no, thank you.
Your room is this way.
Dylan...
This way.
Pater Kimbridge is still
not responding to the heart machine.
Repeat, Kimbridge critical
with 15 hours of life at most.
Please confirm
your understanding of this.
Fifteen hours, message understood.
Team 21 out.
Do you understand?
We must find Jonathan.
Must find...Jonathan?
Dr. Connor. Pater Kimbridge is dying.
Dylan, you're drugged.
Keep fighting it.
Fighting.
Trying.
So much fear.
- Fear of you.
- We mustn't be--
Help.
Help me!
Dylan...
I want to help you.
You're frightened you won't please me.
That's how the drug works.
See?
You do please me.
Does this help, Dylan?
Does this make you less frightened?
Yes.
Doesn't this prove there's
nothing to be afraid of?
Help me.
This...this makes you happy?
Yes, Dylan.
Mm, Dylan, Dylan,
we--we have to find Jonathan.
No, Dylan, no.
Jonathan?
Jonathan.
Jonathan, do you recognize me?
I'm not drugged.
Who's he?
My team leader.
Here's an antidote to Dink extract.
Mix it with water when you
want him to be himself again.
We came here to find you.
You're needed urgently at PAX.
Urgently?
Pater Kimbridge needs heart surgery
in the next 15 hours or he'll die.
Drink it all.
Or you'll displease your mistress.
The damage to the heart
requires bio-plastic surgery.
- Dr. Rabans?
- Can't be reached in time.
If you could just escape
to the subshuttle station...
Marg would miss me immediately.
I'm due in the cooking shed.
After she bought me, I was put to work
where she makes the Dink extract.
Even drugged, I could recognize
simple distilling equipment.
And once I recognized the process,
I avoided eating the gruel
until my mind began clearing.
Who--who are you?
You'll be all right in a minute.
The extract is from a mutated plant
which produces
a fear fascination syndrome
on the central nervous system.
The antidote was
easy since it's similar
to compounds isolated in the 1960s
in biochemical warfare labs.
You're Dr. Connor.
Yes, it's Jonathan.
You've been drugged.
I know.
- You gave me something?
- An antidote.
Listen, we've got to get you
back to PAX.
I know about Kimbridge.
But there's no way I can leave now.
Or maybe there is one way.
Harper, you must tell Marg that
you want to trade him for me.
She wants him.
Everyone in the household knows it.
Maybe we ought to tell him
what she wants him for.
I know, I remember parts
of what happened.
Parts?
Marg, usually oversees
the gruel shipments
to the other households.
If you can get her distracted
from that
she won't notice I'm gone.
- I'll try.
- Good.
This Dink may just have
a surprise for her.
Get her occupied and
I'll leave with Harper.
As a woman, she can take me
anywhere without questions.
What in the devil kept you here
if you weren't drugged?
I've been accumulating
a supply of the antidote.
Waiting for a chance to get it into
the gruel they send out from here.
In that way, it would reach Dinks
in almost every household.
Do it. I mean, on your way out.
With her help, it oughta be easy.
Tell PAX that I'll look
for Baylok and Isiah and--
Marg.
What are you doing in here?
He's the one I was looking for.
This one?
I saw him from the window
and called him in.
Yes, he is a handsome devil, isn't he?
I paid quite a price for him.
I'm sure.
I wonder, could we make an exchange?
That is if mine interests you at all.
Well, it would hardly be
an even exchange.
Mine's extremely well trained.
But you are my guest, so I agree.
You're very generous, Marg. Thank you.
Dylan, you're to go
with the household mistress.
You belong to her now.
- You handled that well, Harper.
- You think he'll be all right?
Marg can be dangerous.
It probably depends on how well
he understands female psychology.
I don't think he knows
the first thing about it.
Perhaps.
But you can never be sure
about us Dinks.
- Excellent, Gorda.
- Thank you, mistress.
Does the mistress wish something
done with this ugly one?
No, I may want him after I see
the gruel wagons loaded.
Get up!
How dare you sit with me.
Oh. Oh, I'm sorry, mistress.
I--I'm--I'm so used to sitting
with my wives when they take--
Silence!
You've had no permission to speak.
Yes, mistress.
You said wives.
Did you have several wives
at the same time?
I only had 14.
Some had more.
Fourteen?
Huh! Well, you must've used
them for many duties.
- Cooking, weaving, field work?
- No, no, mistress.
Our wives are used only
to please us and to bare children.
Gorda, you're being a nuisance.
Get out! All of you, get out!
Typical male vanity.
Fourteen wives is totally ridiculous.
A male hasn't lived who could
properly see to just one of us.
Well, you found that
to be true, didn't you?
I've had 41 children in
the last five years, mistress.
You're lying.
The male creature is unable
to produce children in those numbers.
Your bodies as feeble
as your intellect
and just as unreliable.
But, mistress,
the males in my country
are trained from childhood
in certain practices
which...make us different.
Practices?
What are they? Show me.
Oh, well...
Well, first, I need strength.
And then, of course,
we would require a quiet place.
Gorda.
Gorda!
Yes, mistress?
Have this food brought upstairs.
And tell Partha
that he'll be responsible
for the gruel shipments today.
Come.
Four pots.
Ship to the village later today.
Gorda, have you seen your mistress?
She is upstairs
and has asked for wine.
- May I hurry there, please?
- And the outsider who--
He is with her, mistress.
May I hurry, please?
All right.
Wine, does that mean anything?
It's kept for guests, mainly,
Marg rarely takes any.
They're almost finished making
the gruel.
Mm, it's the proper color.
Well, get out.
Out!
You've tricked me before.
If you're lying about
any part of this...
Eat! Stop dawdling over your food.
Mm, good.
Wine is necessary?
A proper wine is most important
to the ritual, mistress.
'Course this isn't exactly
the right kind--
No, please don't.
It's all right, Dink.
I just wanted to sure of something.
Get up and eat.
You frighten me, mistress.
Nothing will work if I'm frightened.
I'm not angry with you.
See?
I'm quite...pleased with you.
While you're in my quarters,
you may take certain liberties.
You are permitted to look up at me.
To speak freely.
And...touch you as necessary?
Of course you can touch me.
Just why do you think you're here?
All right.
Now we begin.
- This will be for you.
- I don't care for any wine.
Oh, but this is necessary, mistress.
We must... join
in chemical conditioning.
Conditioning?
Oh, you must drink it, mistress.
My body has been trained
from childhood to be excited
by the action of wine
on your biochemical structure.
All of it, mistress.
Our chemical configurations
must balance.
Now...
The first test.
That's strange.
I should feel our balance beginning.
Do you feel any balance yet?
I seem to feel something.
I definitely feel something.
Yes, it's beginning.
But it's only a shadow
of what it should be.
We'll need a...second assimilation.
All of it, mistress.
Balance is critical at this point.
The entire place could be cleaner.
How long has it been
since the equipment
had a thorough going-over?
And I've other complaints, too.
The fires are built wastefully,
requiring too much fuel
for too little heat.
The gruel is far too thin.
Altogether, you've been careless
in a number of things.
But I'm sure you'll try harder now.
I'll say nothing of this
to the household mistress.
Just this once.
- Partha.
- Yes, mistress.
I need some exercise.
He'll ride with me.
Two horses.
You...promised...we'd be balanced.
I know I'm balanced
because I feel balanced.
Perfectly, perfectly!
Perfectly? Not quite.
Our bio...our bio...you-know-what's
are nearly there, pussycat.
See here, Dink. You may not call me...
What did you call me?
Pussycat
Pussycat.
You don't talk like
a proper Dink-Dink.
You certainly don't act like
Dink, Dink.
Dink.
What shall I name you?
Already got a name.
Say hello to Rip.
Rip?
Rip Van Winkle.
Born February 3, 1944, Fire Creek,
Colorado, in the good old US of A.
Colorado?
Mm-hmm.
What do you think of that, my girl?
I know I'm balanced.
Why aren't you balanced?
Well, it...because it takes a while
at my age.
Born 1944, that makes me
189 years old.
How 'bout that?
Marg of the Confederacy
trapped in the clutches of
a 20th century male chauvinist pig.
Mm. Who's willing to admit
that females in charge is no more
upside-down than our system was.
Women's lib. Men's lib.
What do you say
we dump 'em both, Marg?
People's lib.
Are you for people's lib?
I'm for balance!
Please.
What a lovely word.
I don't think we need
any more of this, Marg.
We're there.
No more words.
I think we're ready for
a little nonverbal mutual...
respect.
Marg, it's Kreegs!
Get out of here!
Outside!
I am going.
You, come!
Pardon me.
Shoot him!
Partha!
What are you doing?
You're being foolish.
I'll give you all the food
you can carry.
Just leave this household as it is
and I will be able to continue
to supply you any time you come here.
Yes. Your land very rich.
We want the secret.
Secret?
Yes. How you turn men
into frightened rabbits.
You offer farm goods
when you have that?
Gorda.
Did everyone get the gruel last night?
- What?
- The gruel!
- Did all the Dinks eat the gruel?
- Stop that!
Yeah, I guess they did.
Come on.
I tell you, there is no secret.
You lie!
Move!
- Move!
- There is no secret!
Our males know life is pleasant here,
their needs are cared for.
You lie to a manly soldier!
Now tell!
Why do wagons come here each day?
From here, what do they take?
You do not fear me.
Soldiers.
Bring other female.
What can we do?
Do?
There are only six of them.
Look how many there are of us.
This female has also lied.
I'm sorry.
I hoped you'd seen them and escaped.
We show reason to fear.
Fight! Fight or they'll kill you!
Well, come on!
Careful, my friend.
Harper!
Harper! Are you all right?
You were doing very well
without our help.
Marg, are you sure you're all right?
They fought for me.
My Dinks fought for me.
Because they're no longer drugged.
We'd all be dead if they were.
Know every household
has fought like this.
It's happened over
the entire Confederacy.
Connor, we need you. I just spoke
to Pax, Kimbridge is hanging on.
We almost made it to the subshuttle
last night.
Well, there's still a chance if we can
make the subshuttle fast enough.
Gorda, we need two fast horses!
You can use the medikit here.
Here are 200 horses!
Come on! Connor,
Baylok, Isiah, get in!
HS, help with the injured,
I'll be back for you.
It's agreed, then?
All our households will try it
without the extract?
Agreed.
But it won't be the same.
Imagine a household
with undrugged males underfoot.
Chattering, making mischief.
And children, perhaps.
It's true, Isiah, there were
millions of cars in my century.
All over the world.
HS.
Any word yet?
Yes, I just received a message that
Jonathan reached surgery in time.
- And the Pater will be all right?
- Yes.
Oh, that's good news.
For you, friend.
No thanks, tiger.
So you'll be staying on?
I'm almost sorry
I can't stay on, Marg.
I'm not.
You're the worst of everything
that's vile in the male species.
She laughed at me
when I told her about the 14 wives.
Your 41 children.
Your...secret ritual.
I've never felt so demeaned,
so insulted, so--
Hungover?
Come back, Dylan Hunt.
On equal terms?
On balanced terms.
- Men.
- They have their place.
Here's Dylan now.
Pater, it's good to see you
looking so well again.
He'll be running with our young people
in a few weeks.
Harper-Smythe tells me you've had some
most unusual experiences.
Oh, yes, Pater. Did she mention that
I was her Dink for a while?
As a matter of fact, she didn't.
I don't think we should tire the Pater
with too many stories.
Oh, I want to know.
It sounds very interesting.
No, actually not. Dylan was drugged,
he hardly knew what was going on.
Actually, most of it's
beginning to come back to me, HS.
Oh, except the part with you,
that's a total blank.
Were you a good mistress??
Not nearly as good as Marg, I'm sure.
Marg?
I don't think we should tire
the Pater with too many stories.
The 22nd century,
a reborn planet Earth,
a thousand new adventures.
This has been one of them.