Previously on Ghost...
- We'll break into his crib.
- Pardon me?
I need every document
he has on me.
Effie Morales,
you are under arrest.
What the fuck?
Hey, y'all got
a fucking warrant?
Are you her lawyer?
You're not being arrested
for drug dealing, Effie.
- Then what fucking for?
- Attempted murder.
That's the bitch
that tried to kill me.
You think Weston Holdings
is a giant Ponzi scheme--
you're right.
You guys are fucking criminals.
Remember I know about
your drug business.
You met with Lucas Weston?
I also accepted
a campaign donation.
It was him.
He killed papi.
Take a look at this.
Now he's gone,
and I ain't got nothing.
If Davis or Cane Tejada
or Tariq St. Patrick
find out
that I'm informing on them,
we both know I'm dead.
The feds are building
a RICO case
against you and the Tejadas.
Saxe is a fucking mole. Shit.
I found out last night that
Saxe is working with the Feds.
And you just let him walk on
out of here?
I'm worried
it'll fuck with your release.
I have a target on my back.
I'm sorry, but I can't ask
for protection for you now.
Theo, put the fucking gun down!
- It's over.
- Please, for me.
You'll be fine, brother.
We both free now.
I know where Tasha
and Yas are.
And if I die,
that information does, too.
This is Davis MacLean.
Please leave a message.
Yo, what the fuck?
I called you, like,
1,000 times.
Effie just got roped up.
I'm headed to the office now.
Why the fuck
would Saxe have this?
What the fuck you doing here?
Your ex-bitch, Lauren,
that bitch still alive.
Hell, no, nigga, that can't be.
I just saw her
snitch-ass mean mugging Effie
while they put cuffs on her.
You set her up.
Nigga, why the fuck
would I set up Effie
knowing that shit'll
come back on me, Cane?
Because you like acting
like you fucking T'Challa.
But you'll always be the punk
who let pussy get in the way
of what needed to be done.
Listen, my nigga, Lauren wasn't
gonna say shit, all right?
Everything was fine
until your dumb ass
started doing stupid shit.
Effie wouldn't
have got arrested,
and we wouldn't have
a fucking RICO right now.
This is all
your dumb-ass fault.
- Dumb-ass fault?
- Yes.
Okay. Fuck you,
because every bad thing
that's happened in my family's
been your dumb-ass fault.
You know,
since I met your family,
you've been obsessed
with me, and I peep that.
- Okay.
- That's why you fucking
with Effie
to try to get back at me.
You wanna be me, my nigga.
I understand that.
Listen, you left shorty
in pieces, all right?
I had to pick up those pieces,
so you can't be mad at her
for fucking with a real nigga,
but I appreciate you.
Thank you so much, 'cause you
sure did leave shorty thirsty.
Fuck.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Fuck y'all doing?
What the hell is this about?
It's about Effie.
- Fuck.
- She got arrested.
The girl we used as bait
for the Feds?
Yeah, I need you
to help her out.
Yeah, she could burn all of us.
All right,
I'll take care of it.
You do that.
Come on.
- You okay, Money Mayweather?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Sure it's the last thing
you wanna see
after last night, though.
That's for sure.
Yeah. Appreciate you
letting me get out of there
before the cops came, too.
Hey, I answered
all their questions.
They know Theo acted
on his own.
I don't think there'll be
any legal fallout
for either of us.
My brother...
stupid motherfucker.
Saxe deserved a bullet,
no doubt.
But that should have been
my bullet, not Theo's.
I mean, losing
your brother like that,
there's no fucking words.
Any luck finding
Tasha's address?
Saxe probably
never even had it.
That rat knew that we were
onto his double-crossing ass.
He probably left
that voice mail
as a-a Hail Mary
to save his ass.
Yeah, he probably did.
I did come across
some shit, though.
Looked like a...
like a photo of a police report
signed by Whitman.
Did it look like this?
Yeah, that's
exactly how it looked.
Fuck.
This is Whitman's case file
on Monet.
Wait. So you stole it
or something?
It was procured
on Monet's behalf.
I kept a copy as leverage
against her unpredictable,
murdering ass.
Leverage?
It proves Monet
had motive to do dirt.
You don't want to know what.
Now, if Saxe knew I had this,
the Feds know, too.
This could fuck us.
Okay, what are you doing?
Hiding this shit
so it doesn't fuck us.
The Feds ask about Saxe,
you don't know nothing
about him, a'ight?
Ain't that the fucking truth.
I better get
on this Effie thing
before the next fucking crisis.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's true.
Aah!
Attorney.
Attorney, attorney,
attorney, attorney, attorney.
I need a fucking attorney.
Can y'all hear me now?
Attorney.
Please escort Miss Morales
to holding.
You can call an attorney
when it's your turn
in the phone line.
You're too kind.
Well, this isn't working.
I know.
I thought we'd get
through to her by now.
It's been hours.
Oh, it's Medina.
Yeah, me too.
All right, thanks.
NYPD checked
their security cameras.
Theo Rollins intercepted Cooper
in the parking lot.
All while Davis
was in his office
with a rock-solid alibi.
That's bullshit.
Davis and Rollins
could have planned it that way.
And if they knew Saxe was here,
they probably made him
before we raided the warehouse.
Fuck,
that timeline makes sense.
That's why we came up empty.
He was feeding Saxe bullshit.
I fucking warned him,
the stupid asshole Saxe.
Back the fuck off, Blanca.
Blanca, show some respect.
Saxe was one of us.
Saxe was up to his eyeballs in dirt.
Let's not pretend
that he's some kind of hero.
I mean, how does catching
a bullet wipe his slate clean?
Saxe sacrificed
his life for us.
Without him,
there would be no case.
Without his testimony, we lose
a vital link to St. Patrick.
Then give Effie Morales
everything you got.
Recomb through the St. Patrick
and Tejada files
for connections.
If she doesn't flip,
we're fucked.
Cane.
Cane!
You a narc?
What the fuck
are you talking about?
You know Lauren was alive?
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- Shut the up, my nigga!
Effie covered
for your incompetent ass.
- You was there.
- No, I wasn't.
You really think
I'm stupid, huh?
Okay, when Effie showed up,
she knocked Lauren out
and drove off without me.
Whatever the fuck happened that
night is between them, not me!
The Feds roped up
Effie last night.
- Oh, my God.
- Lauren ID'd her.
Fuck!
You got to be
fucking kidding me!
What are we gonna do?
I think I need to go
to the hospital first.
Yeah, you do that.
Fucking psycho.
Ma, it's me.
What's that?
A letter
from that lawyer Saxe.
Why would he send you
something?
" Monet, If you're reading
this, that means I'm dead.
"No matter who pulled
the trigger,
"the person I hold responsible
is Tariq St. Patrick.
"Ever since Tariq
came into your life,
"your family's been
falling apart.
"Want to know why?
Tariq has been working
with the Feds."
- Man, fuck outta here.
- Wait.
This is
some lying bullshit, Diana.
You don't know that.
Shit.
Right here Saxe says, "Tariq
set me up to get arrested."
Do you even think
that's possible?
Tariq told me
to have my product
in the lockers on the roof.
That's why they came after me.
Well, shit, we better
not do anything
till we know for sure.
This could be
a fucking setup, D.
Go do what you do.
Find out what you
need to find out.
A'ight, bet.
What the fuck happened to you?
Cane went fucking Suge Knight
on my ass
'cause he found out Lauren was
alive and Effie got arrested.
He thinks I'm up to it.
Yeah, me and him
was just throwing hands
at Davis' office
about the same shit.
But why? I get why he came
for me, but you?
Look, I don't know man.
You know Cane.
That nigga's crazy.
You knew.
You knew about Lauren.
That's how you knew Effie
and I were behind it.
I mean, yeah, I knew
about fucking Lauren, bro.
But why the fuck would I tell
the motherfuckers
that just tried to take her out
that she's still alive?
'Riq, I tried to save Lauren.
How many times do I have
to tell you that?
Now Effie got arrested,
and you know her.
She only cares
about number one.
Yeah, that's why we need to be
careful with our next move.
'Riq, there is no fucking
next move.
After that shit you pulled
with CrashCoin and the Feds?
Bye-bye, Weston Holdings.
Bro, the shit needed
to be done, all right?
Stop bitching about it.
Tell Obi that we're not gonna
make the quota for now
so he doesn't merc our ass.
Okay. How?
All right, fine, I'll do it,
but do something, bro.
Keep your eyes
on Weston Holdings.
Do something.
'Riq, can I please just have
one day off?
Just one, okay?
Me, my Xbox, and some Twitch
babes in a hot tub, just once.
Listen, I understand
you're in pain, bro.
But what the fuck happens
when your shady-ass uncle
pulls a moves to back us
out of our deal?
What the fuck do we do then?
Fine.
When I'm discharged,
I'll go see him.
You are discharged.
Just a little scratch.
You'll be fine.
Lauren, why you ghosting me?
Effie got roped up.
Are the Feds coming
for the rest of us?
I need you to let me know.
Hit me back ASAP.
Where's Dru?
Hello to you, too, Evelyn.
Dru ain't here.
What do you wanna talk about?
There's a video
of Dru floating around.
Know anything about that?
- Do I look like I'm on YouTube?
- Stop lying, bitch.
Have you lost
your fucking mind?
Cut the bullshit.
I saw the video.
It was a confession.
Look, Dru already told you
he don't know
what happened to Gordo.
I know you took Frank from me.
- You admitted that.
- I didn't admit shit.
I told you what Lorenzo wanted.
And now Lorenzo's dead.
Yes, he is.
You saying you had something
to do with that?
You know I didn't.
I told you I didn't want a war
with the Tejadas.
I told you that!
But you don't even seem
to be grieving him.
Why the fuck are
you here, Evelyn?
I'm coming to you as a mother.
My Gordo is missing.
I don't know
whether he's dead or alive,
somewhere needing my help.
Can you imagine that?
I don't know what to tell you.
Stop. Just stop.
Forget the rules of this
fucking game for one second.
What if this was your son?
I just wanna know
what happened.
I just--Can you help me?
Look...
I had no beef with Gordo.
Last time I checked,
him and Dru were good.
I granted you grace for Frank.
But I promise
you will not get away
with taking my son from me.
"Granted"?
"Grace"?
"Get away"?
Sounds like a fucking threat
to me, Evelyn.
And I'm sure
you don't wanna do that.
Evelyn.
Fuck.
They know Dru killed Gordo.
That's the last fucking thing
we need.
They're not gonna stop
till they find you.
This is my mess.
I'ma handle it.
We gotta take 'em out.
All of them.
Whatever you do, just make sure
this doesn't come back on us.
Look, we just--we got heat
on us right now, all right?
We gotta stop the Wall Street
operation for now.
But our other distro--
What the fuck?
Our other distros
are solid, all right?
For now.
It is not
your first misstep, Tariq.
Ajebutter playing at gangster.
Look, I don't want you
at my neck.
I just need some extra time,
and I promise the quota
will be met.
Why would I deny myself
the pleasure
of watching Noma kill you?
I'm hoping she makes it slow,
really takes her time.
Listen, man, whatever it is
that you need,
I can get it for you, a'ight?
I promise.
What I need only
Noma can get me.
What makes you so sure?
You know how of much of a
resourceful motherfucker I am.
Shh, shh, shh.
Let me go!
Her influence is the only way
my family in Nigeria
can get green cards.
Why would I betray her
to help you?
Because I know what it's like
to want your family
so fucking bad
that you'll do
whatever it takes
to get to them, all right?
Look, if I get you
these green cards,
will you please stall Noma out
for me?
You have 72 hours.
Thank you.
So them green cards
is payment
for boosting your numbers.
Yeah, yeah, the boost helped,
but the raid on the Russians
didn't put me over AVH.
Sounds like a you problem.
Not if my continued association
with you
puts my campaign at risk.
Yeah.
So I'm gonna need
a bigger bite of the apple,
- my young brother.
- What do you mean?
I'm giving you
five bands a week, come on.
Yet you're still fucking
holding out on me, Tariq.
Come on, man.
There's rumors that
Weston Holdings is doing dirt.
You know anything about that?
I mean, they on the up-and-up.
Who told you that?
You know, you hear things
here and there.
Look, man, the Westons
wanna put me on a payroll,
and I need to know
what I'm working with
before I can agree to anything.
Do you understand
what I'm dealing with?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Well, if you know something,
then fucking tell me.
Look, trust me,
Weston Holdings is legit.
All right?
You gonna give me
these green cards or what?
I'll see what I can do.
Thank you.
Lying motherfucker.
Hello?
Hey, Harp, you finally
answered--thank you.
Listen, I know
you've been avoiding me, babe,
but please just hear me out.
So I told Rashad
about what you do, Herb,
and he did some digging.
I have a contact
at Weston Holdings
I've known for a long time.
The kid is a lying liar
who lies just like his father.
I can read him like a book.
Now, he insists
they're on the up-and-up.
So I have a hunch
there's something wrong there.
I'd say you have
good instincts.
I've been watching
Weston Holdings
for a while now.
The numbers just don't add up.
Well, how have their activities
gone unnoticed by the SEC?
Powerful lobbying.
Frankly, I'd say that
they paid the right person
to look the other way.
Like Congressman
Rick fucking Sweeney.
That would explain
why my many letters
have gone
completely unanswered.
Look, I have the evidence,
and no one will listen
to what I have to say.
Until now.
With me behind you,
they'll have to listen.
I'd be a fool
if I didn't recognize
your motivations here, Councilman.
You think this might be
a winning issue
for your campaign.
Taking down Wall Street
on behalf of Main Street
ain't a bad look,
but it's also
the right thing to do.
This could be dangerous, Rashad.
Are you sure?
Of course.
Okay.
I don't need
Tariq's help, okay?
You're wasting your time.
Cane asked me to come as well.
Given the circumstances,
hear me out.
If they charge you, you'll
be facing attempted murder.
Most likely lose and get time.
Question is, how much?
Normally I avoid no-win cases,
but we're all on the line here.
"No-win"?
That's your pitch?
You'd rather I sugarcoat it?
I'd rather someone
go to bat for me.
Smelling like
the bottom of a bottle,
I'm not so sure you're it.
If you don't like a gift horse,
I can give you a referral.
I have someone, but some bitch
keeps cutting in front of me
in the phone line.
Can't contact them.
And the, uh, deputies
let it happen?
They say they don't see it,
but they're lying.
Then they're in on it--
a tactic they use to, uh,
pressure you into cooperating.
That's not illegal?
It's unethical
but legal as fuck.
Tell you what--I'll have a word
with the captain on my way out.
My, uh, parting gift.
Thanks.
Does Tariq--
Never mind.
Stay calm. Stay calm.
It's all gonna work out.
Stay calm.
- What's going on?
- Not here.
Not here.
Everyone, let's give
the agents some space.
Conference room, now.
Why are we being accused
of running a Ponzi scheme?
- It's not possible.
- I don't know.
All I know is
that when the agents showed up,
Uncle Lucas just dipped.
Which one of you
snitched to the SEC?
Nobody snitched, all right?
We made a deal with Lucas.
Where is he anyway?
God, he slipped out.
Left me to hang.
You're not gonna
turn me in, right?
That depends.
Did you have an escape plan
with Lucas
in case shit went sideways?
If we did, trust me, this isn't
the way it was supposed to go.
- I wanna know.
- Dad, they don't know shit.
Keke, where the hell is Lucas?
I-I don't know, Robert.
I'm in the dark
just as much as you are.
Oh, bullshit.
I know you two were fucking.
You don't know what the fuck
you're talking about.
Trace is an idiot.
This is Lucas' fault.
I know because I saw
something off in the books.
So these accusations are real?
Yeah.
When I asked Uncle Lucas
about the discrepancy,
he said that he
would handle it,
but he made me swear not
to tell anyone, not even Keke.
She's telling the truth.
Oh, dear God.
We're gonna have
to call the lawyers
and the board of directors.
We need to find Lucas.
Fuck you.
Agent Young reported back.
He thinks if we use
the interview surveillance,
it might spook him.
That's dicey territory.
I'm nervous to play
our hand that way.
It's from Saxe.
What? How?
"Dear Jenny,
so that happened.
"Tough break, huh?
"This isn't your fault.
"I knew what I was getting into
when I agreed to help you.
"I arranged for this in case
something like this happened.
"There's so many things I wish
I could have said to you.
"I realized pretty late
in my life
"how much I wanted
my own family with you.
"It wasn't just the sex,
but it wasn't not the sex.
"I also had feelings.
"And as much as you tried to
deny it, I know you did, too.
"So my last gift to you
is freedom.
"Let the white whale go.
"I won't let it take you down
like it did me,
"because from where I am now,
I can play just as dirty
as they do."
So you two really were...
But I'm not letting
this fucking go.
I'm gonna bury Davis,
the Tejadas, and Tariq,
every single one
of those fuckers.
- Shit.
- Davis.
I'm busy.
We have an offer
for your client.
Ms. Morales
declined my services.
Smart, since you
would've conflicted out.
You should really think
about making a deal with us.
We know you asked Saxe to pay
off a member of the parole board
to get Theo Rollins
released early.
I had no knowledge
of a payoff, okay?
But getting Saxe to help
my brother
certainly didn't work out
for Theo.
Saxe would still be here
without Theo.
And whose fucking fault
is that, huh?
I don't know why Theo
did what he did.
Talk to the NYPD.
They know I'm not responsible.
See, I'm not so sure
about that.
We reviewed
the surveillance footage
of you and Saxe meeting
with Diana Tejada.
From the attorney's room?
Nice.
That violates privilege.
Not if you don't record audio.
Do you recall the meeting?
We talked to our client
and left.
How about when you spilled
coffee on Saxe?
'Cause it looked like
you slipped Diana a note.
I don't recall.
See, we think
you made Saxe as our CI,
and you fed Diana false
information to give Saxe.
Then you had Theo, who already
took the weight once for you,
kill Saxe.
What'd he have to lose, right?
He was dying anyway.
- Fuck you!
- No, fuck you!
You may not have pulled
the trigger,
but Saxe's blood
is on your hands.
I dare you to take that
to a grand jury
after I sue the fuck out of you
for harassment.
If you're looking for someone
to blame Saxe's death on,
look in the fucking mirror.
You think RSJ blew the whistle?
I don't know. I think
he just wanted his money.
But we only got one option, B.
Gotta find Uncle Lucas
and take him out.
- He gotta go.
- Okay, wait. What?
We're not killing
my uncle, 'Riq.
It's the only way.
Didn't you say that family
was more important
than drugs and money?
I can't do that to my family.
All right, but what
about my family, huh?
My trust fund
would've covered them
when they got out of WITSEC.
Now that shit is gone
'cause of your fucking uncle.
So now what?
Listen, he has nothing left
to lose, Brayden, all right?
And you know he'll rat
on our fucking operation
to cover his dirty ass.
Now you freezing up.
Listen, bro, you chose
to live this life!
Now live by the fucking rules
one time!
- Here we go.
- Please, bro!
Here we go with that "one foot
in one foot out" bullshit.
So what the fuck is it?
What is it, bro? What is it?
I don't want
to end up like you.
What the fuck
do you mean by that?
Listen, 'Riq,
I saw you change, okay?
That person that I met
at Choate a few years ago,
that's not who you are anymore.
All right.
I went through life.
I grew up, bro.
I had no fucking choice.
Yeah, I know
it's not your fault,
but I-I just don't want
to be able to knife Bash
and act like it's no big--
Listen, I kill
because I fucking have to!
To protect us!
You hear that?
Us, bro!
I don't want to be someone who
could kill their own father.
I never said I fucking did
that shit, all right?
Shut the fuck up saying that.
You didn't have to.
I'm just being real
with you, 'Riq.
There's no being real
with you, my nigga.
You a hypocrite.
I need to know one thing
from you, and that's it.
Are you gonna step up
for this family?
Because that's
what you called it.
So what are you gonna
do for this family?
Even if I wanted to,
I don't even know where
the fuck Lucas is--he's AWOL.
You got access
to your family's properties,
the money,
and all of the a-fucking-bove.
Find him and take him out,
because it's either him or us,
all right?
Our assets are frozen?
Whoa, how the fuck
do our personal finances
fall under SEC's purview?
There's talk
of criminal charges.
- Against who?
- Us.
If they did it to the Madoffs,
they can do it to the Westons.
Robert, if there was ever
a time to let Lucas hang,
it's now.
You've been willfully blind
long enough.
You said everyone loves Lucas.
You act
like you wanna fuck him.
- Come on.
- That's disgusting.
That was the Klonopin talking.
Oh, just Klonopin, Mom?
Not now.
No, Dad.
Mom's right.
Fuck Uncle Lucas.
He left us holding the bag.
Yeah, and we have no idea
where he is?
Nope.
Mom sent me to his apartment,
thinking Uncle Lucas
would open the door
with some emotional blackmail
from his favorite niece.
You mean his only niece?
Okay, the place was empty
like he planned on leaving
for a while.
I mean, can't we track
his spending?
His accounts are linked
to Weston Holdings
anyways, right?
Nope. No, that's the best part.
Our dear Uncle Lucas has been
moving money for weeks.
You know, small transactions,
so undetected,
but totaling several mil.
He's probably partying it up
in the fucking Maldives,
for all we know.
Nothing's been proven
against him.
Wake the fuck up, Robert!
He's running
because he's guilty!
He's still my brother!
I can't just throw him
under the bus!
Well, I'd do it to Skids
in a heartbeat.
Ah! Trace,
I swear to fucking God.
Hey!
Who the fuck is that?
What now?
Can I help you?
Yeah, we're looking
for Robert Weston.
Sir, we'd like to ask you
a few questions.
We have an escort.
I'll have my attorney
meet us there.
Lead the way.
Dad, you don't have to do this.
If not me, then who?
Brayden, sometimes
doing the hard thing
is the only thing we can do.
You're all gonna want
to hear this.
Hello, you still there,
Mr. Weston?
Yeah, I'm still here,
Agent Medina.
Please call me Lucas.
All right,
I've looped my team in.
Go ahead.
Well, my attorneys
have informed me
that the SEC is investigating
a Ponzi scheme
at Weston Holdings.
They seem to think
I've gone on the run
because I had something
to do with the Ponzi,
but that's not it at all.
So you went into hiding
because you're afraid
the person responsible
is gonna come after you?
Well, not just them.
You see, the thing is...
not only do I know
who's behind the Ponzi,
but I-I also have intel
on a drug ring
operating
within Weston Holdings.
And when I reached out
to the DEA, they--they told me
you were the agents
I should be in touch with.
We are.
What'd you have in mind?
Protection and immunity
from these false
Ponzi scheme allegations.
This fucking scumbag's lying.
Lucas and Robert Weston are
at the top of the food chain.
He's involved.
Even so, his intel
could be the evidence
we need for your RICO case.
Lucas, this is
Assistant District Attorney
Jenny Sullivan.
If you want me to cut through
red tape for immunity,
I'm gonna need a taste before
we can agree to anything.
Look into CrashCoin.
I'll be in touch.
If Lucas' intel pans out,
we get the whole drug network.
Now we just need someone
to flip on the bodies.
If we tell Effie that we're
taking down the drug ring
and offer her a lifeline
if she flips on the murders.
What's with the luggage?
Unlike you,
I don't have lawyers, liquid,
or white privilege to protect
me, so I just--I have to go.
Running is my best option.
For how long?
A year?
Ten?
Is this what you want?
Yes, Brayden.
All the sacrifices
that my parents made
to send me to school, what,
so I can go hide in Toronto,
work at a McDonald's with a
fucking bull's-eye on my back?
- I'm serious, Keke.
- I am too.
Look, my parents
are good people.
- You're a good person.
- I'm not.
I'm literally a part
of a fucking Ponzi.
I'll be crucified
once this gets out.
Okay, then why get involved
in the first place?
Look, when I started, Lucas,
he--he's the only one
that believed in me, okay?
He--he listened.
He treated me like an equal.
But he was
just fucking using me.
Okay, so then why protect him?
If you don't turn him in,
he's gonna turn you in first.
Look, even if I knew where he
was, I'd have to come forward.
I can't fucking do that
to my parents.
If I make this all go away
without letting anyone know
you were a part of it,
will you tell me?
I promise I won't betray you
like he did.
How are you gonna do that?
You just trust me.
Please.
Mami, ¿qué te pasa?
What the fuck?
- Guillermo, watch her.
- Oh, my God!
Gustavo.
Open the door!
Hurry up!
It's locked.
I'm so sorry.
Gordo...
I'm sorry.
I didn't have a choice.
It was your mother.
She wanted Lorenzo dead.
It was Monet.
No.
All good?
Yeah.
She say anything?
Yo.
I've been texting and calling.
Haven't heard from you
since I got out.
Yeah, I know.
I've been dealing with a lot.
- What's up?
- You tell me.
I got arrested because you
told me to use the lockers.
Ah, look, I ain't know
there was cameras up there.
I ain't been up there in,
like, a whole semester.
Then why the fuck would you
send me up there, Tariq?
Because you needed help.
You know Stansfield is hot.
You gotta do your
due diligence--come on, now.
That ain't fair.
Noma has a photo of me.
My family needed me.
Listen, Noma had a picture
of me and my family as well, D.
That's why when I figured out
Saxe was a CI,
I put together a plan,
and I protected you.
So you're not working
with the Feds?
Did you just ask
if I was working
with the fucking Feds, D?
After what they did
to me and my mother,
you really think I would
fucking work with the Feds?
You're bugging.
- I'm sorry.
- What the fuck, yo?
I said I'm sorry.
Look, Monet just got my head
all fucked up.
I need to get away from her
and get out the life.
'Riq, can you just
slow down for a second?
If I transfer outta state,
where would that leave us?
Look, just put yourself first,
all right?
- After this Effie shit--
- I'm not Effie.
I know that,
but it doesn't matter.
I just--I don't have it in
me no more,
and I really need
to take this call, D.
Okay.
- Yo.
- When were you gonna tell me
that Rashad Tate
blew the whistle to the SEC?
Wait. Tate did what?
Fuck. All right, I'ma fix it,
I promise.
You better.
Shit.
Come on.
"Lorenzo Tejada"?
Why would papi's prints be
at the scene of Zeke's murder?
Papi told Monet IG killed Zeke.
Uh, hello?
I'm talking to you, Dru.
Could papi have had something
to do with Zeke's murder?
What? No, absolutely not.
But it would explain
the prints.
And if Monet found out
about it, then--
How, Dru? From who?
Fucking Tariq.
Why else would he have
that file?
Yo, Tariq told Monet
about papi,
and then she gets Gordo
all wound up
and convinces him
that papi is responsible
for Uncle Frank's murder.
Evelyn said Monet
wanted Lorenzo dead.
Monet is fucked up, okay?
But that's a lot even for her.
Dru, you said it yourself.
Papi told Monet IG killed Zeke.
She didn't believe him.
She knew it was a lie.
- What the fuck, Cane?
- You fucking knew.
That's why papi
let you call the shots,
'cause you knew he killed Zeke.
But why the fuck
would papi kill Zeke?
That doesn't make sense.
It was a mistake, all right?
He thought
he was shooting Mecca.
And you think Monet
had papi killed?
I thought it was
a real fucking possibility.
When I brought it up to her,
she threatened to kill me.
And if she'd kill Cane...
Dru, what's stopping her
from killing us, too?
Hey, I knew y'all was coming,
I'd have ordered more food.
What's up?
We know
about papi's fingerprints.
What fingerprints?
See, that's that lying
bullshit again.
What the fuck is wrong
with you, Dru?
I fucking killed Gordo for you.
I killed the entire
Castillo family for you,
all so you can lie to my face
about who killed papi.
It was Kai and Gordo.
Shut the fuck up!
I'm so done with your lying
bullshit, Monet!
Uh-uh, Dru.
You shut the fuck up.
This is my fucking house.
- What the fuck, Cane?
- Don't, okay?
'Cause part of me
never wanted to believe
you was evil enough
to kill our father.
But why not?
You're fucked up.
I've lied, stole,
dropped bodies for you, Monet.
I've done everything you wanted
me to do, and what you do, huh?
Turn your back on me
for this nigga Tariq?
You really let this nigga
walk in here
and ruin our fuckin' life?
That's what
this is all about--Tariq?
- He feeding you all these lies?
- Ma, this ain't about Tariq.
You know it's the truth.
Well, so,
if this is the truth...
that means y'all giving Lorenzo
a pass for killing Zeke?
It was an accident.
You should know that--
How the fuck you know
it was a accident?
Your papi ain't even want you
in the house
because he knew
you was a nosy bitch.
And he didn't send you
to Stansfield
because he loved you.
And the minute he could,
he fucking had your dumb ass
out there slinging.
And look where that got you.
Don't listen
to her lying-ass mouth, Di.
Yo, y'all fucking
making Lorenzo
to be some kind of saint,
when he set you up, too, Dru.
He wanted me to believe
that the Guaps killed Zeke,
and that's why he had
IG jump you.
All this fucking
family-first bullshit,
and this motherfucker
ain't care nothing about Zeke.
All his memorial bullshit was
only lies to cover his ass,
even though he saw how losing
Zeke was fucking killing me!
I would've did the same thing
for any of you!
Are you even listening
to yourself?
Do you hear yourself?
Ma, you took
our father from us.
You killed him.
Did you even think about us?
Fuck, no, you didn't,
because you only think
about your damn self as usual.
- Shut the fuck up, Diana!
- No, you shut up!
You need to hear this!
Let the bitch go.
Let her go, Dru.
Let her go.
Let that bitch go.
This whole time you made--
no, this whole time
you made me feel worthless,
saying what happened to Zeke
was my fault, but it's you.
It's you that kill everything
good in this family--
first Zeke, now Papi.
You know what?
If anybody should be dead,
it's your ass, not them.
- I should be dead?
- Yes.
Get the fuck off her.
Don't you ever put your
fucking hands on me again.
Get the fuck out of my house!
I don't need
y'all motherfuckers.
It's all there.
I've had eyes on him all day.
Your boy Brayden
went into that building
a few minutes ago.
All right, bet.
Thanks, Pinky.
Sure.
You boys play nice now.
Keke fell for you.
Guess I underestimated
your charm.
Leave Keke out of this.
Look, I can help you.
Just sign this letter taking
legal liability of the Ponzi,
and then we get you
out of the country.
Spare me the "knight
in shining armor" bullshit.
You're no better than I am.
In fact, you might be worse.
This isn't about me.
You have
the fucking resources, Lucas.
Just sign the letter
clearing the rest of the family
and then set yourself up
in a non-extradition country,
where you'll be protected
from the Feds
and anyone else
who come after you?
What if I get bored?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Why would I give
all this up
to go live
in some Third World shithole?
Because despite everything,
my dad still thinks
you're worth protecting.
Your dad.
Oh, what a nice guy.
I think that's
why I dislike him so much.
Look, I stole a few mil
from some pigs
fattening their already-fat
wallets--big fucking deal.
Some would call that justice.
Uncle Lucas, can you please
just listen to me?
I-I am listening to you.
I am not scared
of your ghetto-ass friends.
When are you gonna
fucking get it, Brayden?
I hold all the cards.
White collar is a nuisance.
Drug dealing, that's
a whole different story, B.
Okay, but even
if you turn Tariq and I in,
the Feds are still gonna
fucking come after you.
What's the point?
Not if I pin the Ponzi
on Robert and Keke.
They go down
with you and Tariq.
See, that's the difference
between me and you.
I'm never gonna take the blame
for something I can easily pin
on someone else.
Oh, my God!
Number 40.
Are you fucking crazy?
You can get in serious trouble
for this shit.
Relax, okay?
These motherfuckers
don't record audio.
We good.
Plus, Davis said
we can chop it up.
If you start acting funny,
you gonna blow my cover.
What's up, baby? I thought
you'd be excited to see me.
Why? Because we fucked once?
Wow. Don't do that, all right?
'Cause I remember
it being a whole lot of times.
It doesn't matter.
Why are you here?
Listen,
they won't go easy on you
if Lauren points you out
in a lineup.
You think
I don't know that already?
So flip on Tariq.
Put the blame on him, Effie,
'cause they don't want you.
They want him.
Now, I've already figured out
exactly what you can tell 'em,
so he takes all the weight.
I ain't even built like that.
So you gonna go to prison?
You risk us all going away
for this nigga Tariq,
and I'm the one right here--I'm
the one that's got your back?
I didn't ask you
to have my back.
It ain't about you.
It ain't about Tariq.
It's about me making
a choice for myself.
What the fuck, Effie?
This ain't the time
to play hard, okay?
Now, this can work out for both
of us if you just listen.
There's no us, Cane, and
I'm not playing anything.
Get the fuck out of here.
My real lawyer will be here
in a minute.
Fuck you.
Fucking finally.
What the fuck you gonna do?
Pop me in the wide open, 2-BIT?
I should...
since you still owe me, nigga.
But as my man
Warren Buffet says,
sell when a competitive
advantage changes.
I got a letter
from that white lawyer.
- From Saxe?
- Yep.
He knew I had beef
with your pop,
so he sent me
some valuable information.
I'm thinking 100 bands
on top of what
you already owed on your tab.
What the fuck?
Listen, I ran through a lot of
my liquid already, all right?
I could give you some weapons
and some--some--some product
on top of that.
But I don't know. There's
not much I can do right now.
The plug got us diversifying
the fucking portfolio.
And I want the keys
to your ride.
Nigga, what?
You can take mine.
That's gotta be worth knowing
where Tasha's holed up.
It's a offer
you can't refuse...
unless you want somebody
to shoot your moms.
What the fuck are you talking--
Here.
Hello.
Tameika, somebody
knows Tasha's location.
Tariq, that's impossible.
Your mother's whereabouts
are sealed.
Look, even if it wasn't true,
sending some extra protection
over there wouldn't hurt, right?
If it gives you peace of mind,
I'll call the Marshals' office
in the morning.
Tameika, I need it
to happen now.
Please.
Okay. Okay.
I'll put the call in now.
All right, thank you.
Where is that child?
You know it's not safe
for you to be letting her
run around like you do.
Yes, I know, Mama.
I just want her to have
as normal of a childhood
as possible.
Oh, girl, please.
That ship has sailed,
young lady.
You know,
I don't always like to hear
your criticism.
'Riq.
It's you.
- I missed you so much.
- Shh.
Just wait till Big Mama
and Mama see you.
Shit.
All right, just stay down
and be quiet, all right?
Just turn around.
Hey, ya, fellas.
Shit.
Well, Mama, if you are
so worried about it,
please go ahead
and get Yasmine, then.
Yes, I will do just that,
because it seems like
I'm the only one around here
who gives a damn.
Really?
Okay, Mama.
Tommy?
Hey, Tasha.
Yas, wait right here.
Tommy, what the fuck
are you gonna do--
shoot me with Yas
and Big Mama right outside?
Don't worry. I got a silencer.
They ain't gonna hear nothing.
Look, I-I don't--I-I mean,
how did you even find me?
Your buddy Monet Tejada--
she dropped me a message.
Maybe she trying to get
on my good side,
or maybe
she finally figured out
that your son is
the fucking seed of the Devil.
Please, don't do this, Tommy.
- Too late, Tasha.
- You don't wanna do this.
Don't do this.
Tommy, please.
- Tommy!
- 'Riq?
Tariq, what the fuck
is you doing?
Okay, look, stop.
This battle between us
has gotta end.
Put the guns down.
Tommy, look at me.
We're the only family
we got left.
Fuck out of here
with that family bullshit.
Family don't snitch
on each other.
They don't kill each other.
They don't turn on each other.
None of us wanted that shit,
all right, Uncle Tommy?
Now, I love you,
but I'll put a bullet in you
to stop you
from killing my mother.
You think you finally
gonna kill me, huh?
Well, you killed your father,
so pulling the trigger on me
ain't gonna be nothing to you.
No.
Shit.
Tameika.
Easy, Tariq.
You have a head injury.
Looks like someone hit you
on the back of the head.
Estelle called the Marshals.
They found their people dead
and you lying
on the floor unconscious.
Estelle said a man broke in.
She heard him
threatening Tasha.
Did you know the man?
What?
Tameika, where's my mom?
What happened
to my mother, Tameika?
I'm sorry, Tariq,
but Tasha is missing.
But your sister
and grandmother are safe.
The authorities are searching,
but they don't have any leads
to her whereabouts.
It's possible whoever
was threatening her took her.
I'm so sorry, Tariq.