Excuse me, can you tell me
this, where Delmare Berry lives?
He ain't here.
Go on inside, baby.
He's a friend of mine...
Well in fact, he wrote his
address down...right here.
Here.
You can see that's Delmare's writing.
I sure had a hard
time finding this place!
- That's his writin'.
- Like I said, he's a friend.
My name is John Rambo. We served
on the same team together in Nam.
I don't know if he
ever talked about me...
I've got a picture of us together.
Somewhere...
This junk in my pocket!
Here...here it is.
That's me, that's Danforth,
Westmore, Bronson, Ortega,
and there's Delmare, right in the back.
We had to put him in the
back because he's so big,
if we didn't, he'd take
up the whole picture!
Delmare's gone.
- What time will he be back?
- He died.
What?
Died last summer.
Died how?
Cancer. Brought it back from Nam.
All that orange stuff
they spread it around.
Cut him down to nothing. I
couldn't lift him off the sheet.
I'm very sorry.
Morning Amy! How are you doing, girls?
- Great, thanks.
- Alright this morning?
- Andy!
- Howdy, Will!
- Good morning, Dave!
- Hi, Sheriff!
Gonna take a bath this week?!
Morning!
You...you visiting someone around here?
No.
You know, wearing that flag on that
jacket, looking the way you do...
you're askin' for
trouble around here, friend!
- Headed North or South?
- North.
Jump in, I'll make sure you
head in the right direction, huh!
- Where you heading?
- Portland.
Portland is South, you said
you were headed North.
You got some place I
can eat around here?
There's a diner about
30 miles up the highway.
Is there a law against me
getting something to eat here?
Yeah, me.
Why are you pushin' me?
What did you say?
l said why are you pushing me,
I haven't done anything to you.
First of all, you don't ask the
questions around here, I do. Understand?
Secondly...we don't want
guys like you in this town.
Drifters.
First thing you know
we got a whole bunch
of guys like you in
this town. That's why!
Besides, you wouldn't like it here...
It's a quiet little town.
In fact, you might say it's boring!
But that's the way we like it.
And I get paid to keep it that way.
Boring...
Portland, straight ahead!
If you want some friendly advice...
Get your hair cut and take a bath.
You wouldn't get hassled so much!
Hope this ride helped you out!
Have a nice day, huh!
Where the hell do
you think you're going?
Hey, I'm talkin' to you, goddammit!
Let's see some I.D.!
All right, you're under arrest!
You hear me? You put
your hands on the car.
Now you put your hands on
the car, and you spread'em.
Are you gonna put
your hands on that car?
How you do it, you
decide, right now!
Put your legs back.
Back!
You try to be nice to some people!
Well, what do we have here, huh?
What would you be
carrying a knife like this?
Hunting.
Don't be a wise guy! What
do you hunt with a knife?
Name it.
- Hi, Will.
- Lester.
Harry, buzz us in, will ya?
Hey, talk about your
sorry looking humanity!
Just another smartass drifter.
- Morning, Arthur.
- Morning, Will. What do you got?
I want you to book
this gentleman for
vagrancy, resisting arrest,
carrying a concealed weapon.
He says he uses it for hunting.
Huntin'? What do you hunt, elephants?
See if you can clean him up a
little. He smells like an animal!
Hey, Mitch...Mitch!
Yo!
Escort this young man downstairs.
Yes, sir.
Right this way, partner.
Right here.
That's it.
OK, here we go.
You know, it looks
like it'll take old Leroy
about 10 years to paint this hall!
Why don't you paint it your damned self?
Come on Leroy, sling that paint, boy!
Mr. Ward!
Would you take this for me, please?
Name?
Your name?
Your name!
Name!
Hey...you're lookin' to trouble?
You came at the right place, buddy!
Oh, wait a second.
You got three seconds
before I break your face in!
He means it.
Yeah, I do.
What do you know about that?
Old Harry here is a soldier!
Rambo...
John J.?
You're gonna talk to me.
I promise you're gonna
talk to me, soldier.
I'm starting to dislike you.
A lot.
I'm gonna run a make on him.
Put his name in the Teletype.
Just roll it across.
Roll it across!
Push it.
It won't work that way, it'll
only smear. Roll it across!
Look, you son of a
bitch, if you don't put your
goddamned hand down
there, I'm gonna break it off!
- Put it down, goddammit!
- Art, what the hell's going on down here?
Nothing I can't handle.
He won't let us print him well.
Leave the ink on your hand!
Just what is your problem, huh?
Listen, hardass! As
things stand right now,
you're facing the ass end
of a 90 day incarceration!
Plus a 250 dollars fine, which you
don't look to me like you can pay!
At 10 o'clock tomorrow morning,
you're going up in front of that judge.
And you think we're tough!
We're gonna make you
look more presentable
for your courtroom appearance.
Between now and then, you can
just impress the hell outta me
by doing exactly as you're told.
Clean him up.
All right, Preston,
I want you to go
over there and get that
hose ready, alright?
Holy shit, look at this!
What the hell's he been into?
Who gives a shit?
All right, put your hands on
top of your head and turn around.
Oh, Christ! We should report this
to Teasle, Gault! Look at that!
You just do what I tell you.
Gault, what the fuck was that?
Well, the Man said "clean him up".
Clean him up!
Hey, Preston, don't forget
to get him behind the ears!
How'd you like that, huh?
What's the matter, Mitch?
Don't you like water sports?
All right, hurry it up, it's time for
my coffee break. Alright, sit down!
Sit down!
Damn it, that boy's
hard to get a hold of!
That's OK, Ward, don't worry
about the soap, he's tough.
Just shave him. Dry!
All right...
How blind are you? Can't
you see this guy's crazy?
Can't you see I don't give a shit?
- Yeah, I can see that.
- Yeah, that's better.
See there, I knew that you...
We're just going to shave
you partner, take it easy!
Take this, Mitch.
Don't move...
I don't want you to cut your own throat!
You son of a bitch! Come on!
What the hell is...
Art! Art!
Hey, you can't...
I'm gonna kill this asshole!
Art, don't shoot!
Don't shoot, there's people down there!
All right, get help! I'll go after him!
Get outta the way!
Son of a bitch!
Lester, this is Will.
I'm right on his tail.
He's just east of Smith's farm,
headed towards Chapman Creek.
I know you can hear me!
You're finished!
You've gone as far as you're gonna go!
D'you hear me?
Mitch!
Lester!
He's up there behind the draw.
Mitch, get Orval on the radio.
Tell him to get out here with
his damned dogs right away.
And tell him to bring the Dobermen!
lt's gonna rain, we'll need
dogs that can hunt on sight.
Lester, tell Paul to get
out to the lumber camp
to get the helicopter up here.
If they give him any shit, tell him to
site him for obstruction
right on the spot.
We'll get him!
No problem.
Go on, Hooch! Thunder, lets get him!
Come on, sweethearts!
Let's go get him, babies!
Won't be long before he's
stuffed and mounted, huh Will?
Make him into a bear rug!
Didn't we go hunting here up last year?
Yeah, I got a couple of bucks last year!
Hey Mitch, up the hill!
Get those hounds away from me,
Orval! I don't trust those bastards!
Keep moving, my dogs can
eat and run at the same time!
He's going straight to the top.
Isn't that supposed to be dangerous?
He's just dumb!
Hey, you're spoiling the scent.
Let my babies do their job!
- This is no good.
- Why?
There were three of us in
the cell block down there!
He went through us like
we weren't even there!
Oh, come on!
We've got him, go ahead, he's trapped!
Art, Art! This is Teasle, he's
heading for Chapman's gorge.
Chapman's gorge! Head him off!
There he is! On the cliff!
Son of a bitch!
What the hell's going on?
What are you doing? We're
just supposed to spot him!
- Hold it steady.
- I can't! We're in a thermal draft!
He's stuck there, he can't go any place.
If you don't ride this thing right,
I swear to God, I'll kill you!
Sheriff to Galt! Come in Galt.
Hold it steady, you son of a bitch!
Galt, come in, goddamn it!
Get closer and hold it steady!
Galt, talk to me, damn it! I
want to know what's going on!
I got him...easy now.
There he is!
Over there, dummy! Come on!
Hey, soldier boy!
Galt, I'm tellin' you to get on this
radio! What's going on up there?
I don't want him dead, Galt,
I want him alive! You hear me?
Art, come in!
Art Galt, come in!
Helicopter, come in, goddamn it!
Christ, look!
Jesus Christ, gimme the binoculars!
Oh no, no, no! Shit!
I can't figure it...How did he fall out?
Does it matter?
Let's nail this sucker's
ass...He can't be far!
Will!
Looks like he wants to turn himself in!
There's one man dead. lt's not my
fault. I don't want any more hurt.
Freeze!
Stay right where you
are and give yourself up!
But I didn't do anything!
I'm warning you, boy, don't make
a move, I'll blow your head off!
I didn't do anything!
Cease fire! Cease fire!
Ward, goddamn it, cease fire!
I think we hit him. Let
us get down there. Move!
Sheriff to base, come in.
Go ahead, Will.
Lester, we're down in the gorge.
Galt's dead, alright? Where the
hell is that goddamned chopper?
He won't come, Will. Says
there's a storm heading your way.
I don't give a goddamned
what's on its way.
I want that chopper back here right now!
I don't want Gault's
body out here all night.
Listen, Will. You sure picked one
hell of a guy to mess around with!
Just came over the
Teletype a few minutes ago.
John Rambo is a Vietnam vet.
He's a Green Beret, Congressional
Medal of Honor! Guy's a war hero!
Jesus, that freak?!
I knew there was
something about that guy!
I double checked it, Will.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to do what I
told you to do, goddamn it!
Get that chopper back here now! Out.
Green Beret!
War hero!
- That's great! That's just great!
- Shut your mouth!
What the hell's the
matter with you guys?
He's one man...wounded!
Those Green Berets...they're
real bad asses.
Why don't you let the
State Police handle this?
Look. Look at him...look at
him! That's Art Gault, boy!
He and I were friends when your
momma was still wiping your nose!
Now he's dead. He's dead!
Because of that psycho out there!
Now you listen boy,
you listen to me good:
I'm gonna get that son of a bitch...
and I'm gonna pin that Congressional
Medal of Honor to his liver!
And I'm gonna do it,
with you, or without you!
We're closin' in, the
scent's getting stronger.
All right, keep your eyes open!
It's gonna storm...it's all we need now!
Will, c'mon, let's get out of
here before it gets too dark.
What's the matter, you
afraid of the boogie man?
You goddamned pansy!
Put your gun down, I'll
show you who the pansy is!
Knock it off! Ward! Ward, move out!
The fight is out here! He's
out there waiting for you.
Mitch, get on your feet and move!
Go find this guy for Chrissakes!
Keep your eyes open!
- I'll see you later, Ward!
- Shut up, Mitch.
There he is!
Let them dogs loose, Orval!
Go get him sweethearts!
Here's your dinner!
Cease fire!
Goddammit, I'm hit!
Jesus, he's got a gun..
It's not him, it's a
goddamned scarecrow!
No scarecrow that
shot Orville, he's close.
Kill him! Go get him!
Go get him, Maggie!
Mitch, Ward, come here!
Shingleton, you cover us.
Look at his leg!
Mitch, get your belt. Make
a tourniquet around that.
We got to get this guy to a doctor!
Goddamnit, get your belt on that
fast! Where's the first-aid kit?
I left it in the car.
Shit!
- Where did he get that gun?
- It's gotta be Art Gault's gun.
- He's outta ammo...
- How do you know that?
Because whatever killed Orval's
dog was no bullet, that's how!
Hurry up! Orval, listen
to me, now listen!
You have to stay awake, all right?
You have to release that
tourniquet every 15 minutes.
We'll be right back! We go
get him now, he's outta ammo.
Get him! He had no right to shoot
my babies. Get the son of a bitch!
- Let's go!
- Go get him!
All right, now listen up!
We're right on top of him.
We're gonna form a
skirmish line, 50 feet apart.
Keep moving, there's no way
outta here, except through us.
OK, let's do some huntin'...
Huntin'? We ain't
huntin' him, he's huntin' us!
Spread out. Spread out,
dammit! I said 50 feet!
I hate this!
Will, it's Mitch!
Who is it?
- What's goin' on?
- Shut up!
He's got Ward. Spread
out, I'll go this way.
Will! Over here!
Who's firing?
I got him!
Shingleton, follow me!
Will, help me!
Help me, Will!
Balford? Where the hell are you?!
Shingleton, over here!
Shingleton, where the hell are you?!
I could have killed'em all.
I could have killed you.
In town you're the law,
out here, it's me!
Don't push it! Don't push it, or I'll
give you a war you won't believe!
Let it go.
Move back, you guys, move back!
How bad is the situation?
Captain, we need some...
That's the only good thing about this,
is the business you're doing in town!
Reporters are drinking the place dry.
You look like you're
ready to keel over, Will.
Why don't you go
home? It's my problem now.
Your problem? Listen Dave,
don't give me any of your
horsehit about jurisdiction
in this one, you understand?
- Should I step outside?
- Just finish up what you're doing.
Somewhere in this rugged mountain
countryside, possibly above the snow line,
shrouded in mist, the
fugitive John Rambo, is hiding.
Units of the state
police along with local
members of the National
Guard are now being mobilized.
What still remains
unexplained by local authorities
is just how and where
the former Green Beret
came into possession of the weapons
with which he allegedly
killed one deputy sheriff,
and tried to kill 6 others.
Only their skilled training
in police enforcement
techniques saved their lives.
And word now is that
the fugitive will be
in custody in a matter of hours.
Maps, Will.
Will, there's something
I think you oughta know.
I'll talk to you later, OK?
What is it, Lester? What is it
for Christ sake, spit it out!
Well, I was just talkin' to
Mitch, and he was sayin' that
Gault and a couple of deputies
were...a little hard on the guy.
Assholes!
It doesn't make one goddammed bit
of difference, Dave, and you know it!
If one of my deputies...gets
outta line with a prisoner,
then the prisoner
comes to me with it!
And if I find out it's like he
says, I kick the deputy's ass!
Me, the law! That's
the way it's gotta be.
People start fuckin' around with
the law, and all hell breaks loose.
Whatever possessed God in
heaven to make a man like Rambo?
God didn't make Rambo.
I made him.
Who the hell are you?
Sam Trautman. Colonel Samuel Trautman.
We're a little busy this morning,
Colonel, what can I do for ya?
- I've come to get my boy.
- Your boy?
I recruited him, I trained him, I
commanded him in Vietnam for 3 years.
I'd say that makes him mine.
I wonder why the Pentagon would
send a full bird Colonel to handle this?
The army thought I
might be able to help.
I don't know in what way.
Rambo's a civilian now, he's my problem.
I don't think you understand. I didn't
come here to rescue Rambo from you.
I came here to rescue you from him.
Well, we all appreciate
your concern, Colonel.
We'll try to be extra careful!
I'm just amazed he allowed
any of your posse to live.
Is that right?
Strictly speaking, he slipped up.
You're lucky to be breathing!
That's just great!
Colonel, you came out here
to find out why one of
your machines blew a gasket!
You don't seem to want to
accept the fact that you're
dealing with an expert
in guerilla warfare.
With a man who's the best.
With guns, with knives,
with his bare hands.
A man who's been trained to
ignore pain, ignore weather.
To live off the land...
To eat things that would
make a billy goat puke.
In Vietnam, his job was to dispose
of enemy personnel, to kill...period!
Win by attrition. Well,
Rambo was the best!
OK, Colonel, now you've
got us all scared to death.
What do you and the Special Forces think
I oughta do about your psycho out there?
Let him go.
- Do what?
- For now.
Defuse the whole situation, defuse him.
Provide a little gap and
let him slip through it.
Then put out a nation wide
APB. In a couple of weeks,
you'll pick him up in Seattle or
someplace, working in a car wash.
There'll be no fight and
nobody else will get hurt.
I do my own work. I don't
figure the best way to do that is
to close my eyes and then hope
he gets picked up in Seattle!
If you send your people in
there after him, they'll get killed!
You know, we're just a small
hick town Sheriff's department,
Colonel, but we're
expected to do our duty
just like our heroes
in the Special Forces.
In Special Forces, we teach our
people to stay alive in the line of duty.
No shit, I never thought of that!
You want a war you can't win?
Are you tellin' me that 200 men against
your boy is a no win situation for us?
You send that many,
don't forget one thing.
What?
A good supply of body-bags!
Trautman!
I don't know which side
you're on, Trautman...
I still think you came out
here just to cover your ass.
But if you're serious about taking
Rambo out clean, follow me...
State police calling John
Rambo. Acknowledge.
State police calling John Rambo.
Come in please. Acknowledge!
If you're listening, Rambo, here's
your situation: you are surrounded.
Every possible exit has been blocked,
every highway, every
road, every fire break.
You have our word that
your services to your
country will be taken
into consideration.
And you'll receive fair treatment.
Just respond, we can
work everything out...over.
Anything?
- He took a radio off one of my deputies.
- Then he has to be listening.
If I was in his position,
I'd try to pick up
some information. Maybe
catch some cross talk.
Of course, he's listening.
He's not gonna break radio silence.
No, not for us, but he
might do it for you, Colonel.
He's your boy, isn't he?
Maybe you can talk him into sparing
all our lives by giving himself up.
I can try.
At least, we'd get a
radio fix on his position,
if you don't mind
setting him up for us...
Setting him up for you?
It's like bringing the
pigeons to the cat!
Thanks for bringing your people out.
Any time, Will.
C'mon, Bobby, put the
magazine away, will ya?
Pay attention. I mean we
may only get one crack at this.
Company leader calling
Raven. Come on Raven.
Company leader calling Raven.
Company leader to
Raven. Talk to me, Johnny.
Company leader to identify Baker Team:
Rambo, Messner, Ortega, Coletta,
Jorgensen, Danforth, Berry, Krakauer.
Confirm.
This is Colonel Trautman.
Talk to me, Johnny.
They're all gone, Sir.
- That's him, get on it.
- Rambo. Are you alright? Over.
Baker team, they're all dead, Sir.
Not Delmare Berry, he made it.
Berry's gone too, Sir.
How?
Got himself killed in Nam...
Didn't even know it. Cancer
ate him down to the bone.
I'm sorry, I didn't know.
I'm the last one, Sir.
lt's good to hear your voice,
Johnny. It's been a long time!
Look, John, you've
done some damage here,
but they don't want any more trouble.
He's north-west!
That's why I've come.
I'm gonna come in
and fly you the hell out.
Just you and me. We'll work this
out together. Is that fair enough?
Where'd you come from, Sir?
Bragg.
I tried to get in touch with you,
but the guys at Bragg
never knew where to find you.
Well, I haven't been spending
much time there lately,
they've got me down in DC.
I'm shining a seat with my ass.
I wish I was back in Bragg now.
We'll talk about that when you come in.
I can't do that, Sir.
Well, look, John, we can't have
you running around out there,
wasting friendly civilians.
- There are no friendly civilians.
- I'm your friend, Johnny.
I was there with you, knee
deep in blood and guts.
I covered your ass more than once!
Seems like bailing you out of trouble
is becoming a lifetime job for me!
There wouldn't be no trouble
except for that king shit cop!
All I wanted was something to eat.
But the man kept pushin', Sir.
Well, you did some
pushin' on your own, John!
They drew first blood, not me.
Look Johnny...
Let me come in, and get
you the hell outta there.
They drew first blood...
Rambo! Are you still reading me?
Company leader to Raven!
Rambo, acknowledge!
He's all finished, Colonel!
We've got a real good fix on him now.
Come first light, I'm gonna put
every man I got upon that ridge.
Then we'll get him my way!
Goddammit.
Goddammit!
Come on, move it!
Let's go!
Does this guy got a gun?
There's the guy the
cops are shootin' at!
I see him over there,
I'll get him, I'll get him!
Don't shoot!
This way! Let's go!
There he is! Come on!
Now we got him!
Yes, I know exactly where it is.
Now listen to me very carefully.
Surround the area with every
man you've got, but don't move in.
I repeat: don't move in!
Don't do anything till I get
there! And no shooting!
I don't want him dead, I want him alive!
Keep firing!
Come on guys, shoot!
Come on!
You guys are great!
- All right, Steve.
- Yo!
I want you and Bruce,
head around these trees,
go to the front of that mine.
Screw that Clint, but
I ain't goin' up there!
No way!
- Brandon?
- What?
- I want you to go into that mine.
- No, not me!
What do you mean, not me?!
Look, I do this part time, I
didn't come here to get killed.
He's probably just waitin' for us!
What's wrong with you, Clinton?
Rambo! This is
Lieutenant Clinton Morgan.
National Guard leader.
And I'm giving you just
3.0 seconds to come on out.
Who's got the rocket launcher?
- I do.
- Come here, Earl.
Right!
Rambo! This is your
last chance to come out.
Maybe we should wait.
Earl, this creep is a killer!
Besides, I'm in charge
and I say we blow it up!
Now fire that thing! Just let
me get outta the way first.
Give that man a cigar!
Bull's eye!
- Where the hell are they?
- Up the hill about 500 yards.
Move in a little closer,
just like Iwa Jima.
I don't believe it! Idiots!
All right, one more for
''Soldier of Fortune''!
Soldier of Fortune?!
Dammit, what the hell do you
think this is, some kind of a circus?
Get the hell outta here!
Clinton, Jesus!
Didn't you get the word, Clinton?
I told you people to
wait until I got up here!
Well, he was shooting at us, Will!
Come on! I wasn't taking any chances.
What a mess!
We have to dig his body
out of there right away.
You can't get a dozer up here,
you're gonna have to find
somebody to dig him out!
lt's your mess, Clinton!
You clean it up.
Will, come on...I gotta be back
at the drug store tomorrow!
You'd better get started
right away, Clinton!
Shit!
Buried in a hole by a bunch of
goddamned weekend warriors!
Thought you said he was
the best you ever trained!
However he may have ended up,
there was a time when
he was very special.
'Special', my ass! He was just
another drifter that broke the law.
Vagrancy, wasn't it?
That's gonna look real good on
his gravestone in Arlington:
''Here lies John Rambo, winner of
the Congressional Medal of Honor.
Survivor of countless
incursions behind enemy lines.
Killed for vagrancy,
in 'Jerkwater', USA.
Don't give me any of
that crap, Trautman!
You think Rambo was the only guy
who had a tough time in Vietnam?
He killed a police
officer, for Christ sake!
You're goddamned lucky
he didn't kill all of you...
This character! He
comes waltzing in here,
full of all kinds of good advice.
And wished we'd let that
goddamned maniac go on the loose,
so we could save our own asses!
Well, we saved our asses, Colonel!
And we didn't let him go on the loose.
The best man lost!
And he doesn't like it!
- How you doin', Will?
- Hold my calls.
Colonel?
Have a seat.
Oh miss, can you do this again, please?
- Oh sure!
- And for my friend...?
A shot of wild turkey.
If I was out of line before,
I just want to apologize.
None of that makes much
difference now, does it?
No, I guess not.
I suppose...
I just feel...
Like you were...cheated
outta your chance?
I wanted to kill that kid.
I wanted to kill him so
bad, I could taste it.
Doesn't sit well with that badge.
It can get confusing sometimes...
In Vietnam, you can bet that Rambo and
I got pretty confused. But we had orders.
When in doubt...kill!
But what the hell, you're a civilian.
You can go home to your wife,
and your house and
your little flower garden.
You're under no pressure
to figure all this out.
And what about you, Colonel?
What did you figure
out from all of this, huh?
I mean what would you have
done with him if he came in?
Would you wrap your arms
around him to give a big sloppy kiss?
Or would you have blown his brains out?
I couldn't answer that
until I met him face to face.
Well, there it is.
Just as well we never
got a chance to find out.
Drive!
Don't look at me, look at the road.
That's how accidents happen!
- What's your name?
- Cathcart, Robert A.
All right, what do you
got in the back, Robert A.?
M60.
- OK, Robert A., get out of the truck.
- I don't got no beef with you!
Go home! Move, go home!
Want to turn that up?
What's your story, Steamboat?
Looks like somebody
pulled the plug too soon...
That Rambo guy? He's on the loose again!
Shit!
Hey Will, it's Rambo! He's still around!
- Holy fuck!
- Get out there right away. Move!
What the hell is going on?!
- Watch yourselves!
- They're all gonna blow!
Attention, all civilians!
For your own safety, please
evacuate the streets immediately.
Remain indoors until you
receive further instructions.
I repeat: this is a police emergency.
Please evacuate the streets immediately.
They found Rambo's body...
As a matter of fact,
he stole an army truck
and blew up a gas station
on the other side of town.
The kid is resilient.
Why don't you forget what you're
thinking and clear out while you can?
Get the fuck outta here, Trautman!
You take your advice with you.
When I talked to you
earlier this afternoon,
you knew he was still alive, didn't you?
I suspected it.
Sure...Sure, that's why you
stuck around. You trained him.
You taught him how to get
out of places like that cave.
But he's not gonna
get out of this place!
Teasle, you and all your men
couldn't handle him before,
what makes you think
you can handle him now?
Because God knows what
damage he's prepared to do.
You're gonna die, Teasle.
Everybody dies!
There's only one man in this
room that has half a chance.
That's not because
I'm better than he is.
But it's because he trusts me.
See, I'm the closest thing
to family that he has left,
and that may be all the edge I need.
Jesus Christ, where do
you people come from?
This is my job Trautman,
this is my town!
And I'm not giving it up to you,
or to Rambo or anybody else!
Now you just stay the hell outta my way!
- Get a little closer!
- I can't!
lt's too goddamned hot!
Will, it's Lester, do you copy, over?
Come on, let's go! Will, this
is Lester, do you copy, over?
Listen Will, we've got some serious
problems. The highway's been cut off.
The truck's out here, but
we couldn't find the body.
I repeat: no body,
it's totally burnt out.
Preston, get those people outta here!
Move them back to the south side.
We don't know how many gas
tanks there are under the pumps...
Go ahead...go ahead!
Go ahead, you crazy
son of a bitch, finish me!
Rambo!
Rambo, don't do it!
Listen to me, Rambo!
You have no chance.
Drop your weapon.
We're gonna order a chopper
in and fly you back to Bragg.
Hold your fire!
Hold your fire! Hold your fire!
Think about what you're doin'.
The building's perimeter's
covered. No exits.
There's nearly 200 men
out there and a lot of M16s!
You did everything to make
this private war happen.
You've done enough damage!
This mission is over, Rambo.
Do you understand me?
This mission is over!
Look at 'em out there.
Look at 'em!
If you won't end this
happen, they'll kill you!
Is that what you want?
lt's over, Johnny. lt's OVER!
Nothing is over! Nothing!
You just don't turn it off!
lt wasn't my war. You
asked me, I didn't ask you!
And I did what I had to do to win,
but someone wouldn't let us win.
And I come back to
the world, and I see all
those maggots at the
airport, protestin' me, spittin'.
Callin' me baby killer
and all kinds of vile crap!
Who are they to protest
me, huh? Who are they?
Unless they've been me and been there,
and know what the
hell they're yellin' about?
It was a bad time for everyone,
Rambo. It's all in the past now.
FOR YOU! For me,
civilian life is nothing.
In the field, we had a code of honor.
You watch my back, I watch
yours. Back here, there's nothing!
You're the last of an elite
group...don't end it like this.
Back there I could fly a
gunship, I could drive a tank,
I was in charge of a
million dollar equipment!
Back here, I can't even
hold a job parking cars!
Where is everybody?
I had a friend, who
was in the Air Force.
There were all these guys, man.
Back there were all these fuckin guys!
Who were my friends!
Back here, there's nothing!
Remember Dan Forest?
Wore this black headband.
I took one of his magic
markers, and I said:
"If found, you mail this to Las Vegas",
'cause we were always
talkin' about Vegas,
and this fuckin' car. This so
great '58 Chevy convertible!
He was talkin' about his car,
he said we'd get cruised
till the tires fell off!
We were in this bar in
Saigon, and this kid comes up,
this kid carrying a shoe shine box.
And there, he says:
''Shine please, shine!''
I said no, and he kept askin',
yeah, and Joe would say 'yeah'.
And...I went to get a couple of beers.
And the box was wired.
He opened up the box...
Fucking blew his
body all over the place.
He's laying there and
he's fucking screaming,
there's pieces of him all over me!
And I'm trying to pull them off, you
know...my friend! It's all over me!
I got blood and everything and...
I'm trying to hold him
together, I put him together
the fucking entrails keep coming out!
And nobody would help!
He's saying, sayin', ''I want to
go home!'' just calling my name.
''I wanna go home, Johnny,
I wanna drive my Chevy!"
I said: "Why I can't
find your fuckin' legs."
''I can't find your legs!''
I can't get it out of my
head. lt was seven years.
Every day it hurts.
Sometimes I wake up and don't know
where I am. I don't talk to anybody.
Sometimes a day.
Sometimes a week.
I can't put it outta my mind...
Ripped and Fixed By evgeni99