I'm Nick Fury.
Been riding a desk for the past six years
trying to figure out where
our future enemies are coming from.
Official S.H.I.E.L.D. activity.
Never occurred to me
they would be coming from above.
(GASPS)
You say this thing looked like Coulson?
Mmm. Talked like him, too.
Shapeshifters.
TALOS AS AGENT KELLER:
We can't trust anyone.
Not even our own men.
Now I stand before you
as my true self.
Without deception.
I just wanna talk.
My people lived as refugees, homeless.
- SOREN: Talos!
- Soren.
And the handful of us that are left
will be slaughtered next.
There are thousands of us
separated from each other.
This is just the beginning.
- (GUNSHOT)
- (GROANS)
(SOREN SCREAMS)
They won't be safe here.
They need their own home.
(CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
Varra. Welcome.
Thank you, Fury.
I'd like you to meet someone.
This is Gravik.
Gravik.
His parents were killed
in the last stand against the Kree.
He escaped from behind enemy lines,
piloted a ship all on his own.
He is smart, Fury. Knows how to survive.
We could use someone like him.
He's a child.
Only to human eyes.
Just talk to him.
(FURY SIGHS)
Gravik. Sorry to hear about your parents.
They died a brilliant death.
I'm sure they did.
This work here...
you know it's very dangerous.
I'm not afraid.
I can see you're not.
I wanna thank you all for...
For joining me.
I know it's been a...
It's been a rough journey.
We went looking for a home,
found nothing but violence.
And hate.
All of us have lost someone.
Or everyone.
And our entire species
is scattered across the galaxy,
but for those of you
who braved the journey here to Earth,
you did so for one reason.
This man.
This man that I trust.
You know I don't use that word lightly.
Thank you, Talos.
(SIGHS)
My friends, ever since...
Let me rephrase that.
Almost ever since I met Talos,
I believed that humans
and Skrulls can help each other.
The world is facing a serious threat.
And I could use your help.
It would mean putting on a new face
and keeping it.
This is the promise.
While you work to keep my home safe,
Carol Danvers and I
will find you a new one.
Who'll be first to take the pledge?
Thank you, Soren.
You have a courageous mother, G'iah.
(SKRULLS MURMURING INDISTINCTLY)
You keep your word...
I'll keep mine.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(WOMAN YELLS INDISTINCTLY)
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
(MAN YELLING AND SOBBING)
What are you doing?
Let go of me.
I'm an American!
I'm an American! I'm an American!
(GRUNTS)
I'm an American!
(WOMAN SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN
OVER PA)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(SIGHS)
They've gone.
You hear anything from G'iah yet?
No, nothing. Not yet.
(CLEARS THROAT)
When me and my mama used to
take these long train rides to Detroit...
You know, train travel back then
wasn't nowhere near this elegant.
Comin' out of Alabama,
we always had to ride in the colored car.
It was hot, sweaty.
Bathroom didn't work half the time.
And we couldn't go in the dining car.
So, we brought fried chicken, white bread,
deviled eggs, and pound cake in a shoebox.
(CHUCKLES)
Mmm. Half hour after the train pulled out,
that chicken be gone!
Smelt way too good to wait.
On these long rides,
me and my mother would make up games,
pass the time.
"Tell Me Somethin' I Don't Know."
That was one of her favorites.
One time she said, "Tell me somethin'
I don't know about you and Suzie."
Me and Suzie had a standing game of doctor
we'd been playin'
behind Old Man Jackson's barn.
Suffice it to say,
I wasn't about to tell her about that.
So, I made up something crazy like,
"Me and Suzie
saw a bullfrog with polka dots."
(LAUGHS)
My mama just smiled.
Even though I'd lied through my teeth,
the mere fact that I did that,
told her everything she needed to know
about me and Suzie.
Mmm.
Well, you wanna go a few rounds?
Sure.
Tell me something I don't know
about the destruction of Skrullos.
You know everything
there is to know about it, Fury.
Name of the game
is Tell Me Something I Don't Know.
We were overpowered by the Kree.
We held 'em off for as long as we could.
When we couldn't hold 'em off any longer,
the million of us that were left, we fled.
FURY: Interesting.
Tell me something I don't know
about the Skrulls that fled.
Um...
They're here.
Who's here?
All of us.
Wait. Whoa, whoa, whoa!
You're tellin' me there's a million
Skrulls walking amongst us right now?
Have you lost your reptilian-ass mind?
I sent out the call
and every Skrull that isn't
in Emperor Drogge's colony, they answered.
You lied to me!
Hey, we were being hunted
across the universe.
I had two choices,
I could let my people be annihilated
or summon 'em here to Earth.
- What would you have done?
- This ain't about me!
Oh, right. But you're fine using us
as your spies and your errand boys,
long as it's on your terms.
The host gets to set the terms
of the visitation.
What happens
when the host disappears, huh?
'Cause you were gone!
And I didn't think you were coming back,
I really didn't.
And even when you did come back,
there was no talking to you
about anything real.
Your boots barely hit Earth.
(SNAPS FINGERS)
And, "Oh, it's too heavy here, man.
I gotta go up to my space station."
You've been up there for years!
You knew how to get
in touch with me, Talos,
and you didn't
because you didn't want me to know.
My hope...
My hope is that with your help...
Skrulls and humans can coexist,
here on Earth.
Human can't coexist with each other!
You've been here long enough to know that!
We've been at war with each other
since we could walk upright!
There is not enough room or tolerance
on this planet for another species!
(WOMAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN OVER PA)
Matter of fact,
neither is this train compartment.
I think this is your stop.
(WOMAN CONTINUES ON PA)
Oh, my God.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
Elizabeth.
Were you there?
Yeah.
How did it happen?
It happened quickly.
Don't you be one of those bastards
who gives me a platitude
when I'm looking for the truth!
That one, over there.
You know what he told me?
He told me that
my nation owes me a debt of gratitude.
But he won't even tell me where
on Planet Earth my daughter was killed.
So apparently, facts are not included
in the debt I'm owed.
She died in Moscow.
We were there trying to stop the attack.
Someone set a trap.
- For her?
- No, for me.
Someone wanted to hurt me...
so they hurt her.
Oh.
So, you're the reason I'm taking
my daughter back home in a box.
I'm sorry
I couldn't protect her, Elizabeth.
You're Nick Fury.
Maria believed in you.
She would've followed you
to the gates of hell and back.
(SIGHS)
Look, I don't know
what Maria died for out there.
But whatever it was,
don't let it be for nothing.
NEWSCASTER: Developing Story at this hour.
Several bombs exploded today
at an annual celebration in Moscow,
killing at least 2,000 civilians.
One suspect is currently in custody,
identified as a leading member
of the online fringe group,
Americans Against Russia.
The UK Prime Minister
was quick to denounce the attack,
while the NATO Secretary-General says...
(READING)
Despite the outpouring of condemnation,
all signs point towards
imminent retaliation from Russia
for what the Kremlin regards
as an all-out declaration of war
by the Americans.
They're all saying
we had something to do with Moscow.
Well, I call bull on that.
There's no way that Moscow attack
was committed by Americans.
This has got false flag
written all over it.
How did you know Fury would be there?
I didn't.
Well, not to a certainty. But I hoped.
I wanted to see how much of him was left.
And?
He's just vapors. Old.
You know,
I could've killed him if I wanted to.
You don't punish a man
by givin' him what he wants.
You just get me to the Council meeting.
I wanna see their faces
while Moscow is still burnin'.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
You, wait.
Uh, yeah, that's not happening.
Gravik.
If I'm not out in an hour,
shoot him in the head.
Members of the Council.
Seems someone didn't get
the suggested attire memo.
Well, I also didn't get a formal
invitation, Mr. Secretary-General.
But I'm sure
that was just a curious oversight.
Madam Prime Minister.
Hello, Shirley.
I trust I speak for the group when I say,
we are all happy to have you with us.
Please sit.
GRAVIK: I see you,
all dressed up in the man's finery,
drinking the man's wine.
Playing the man's game,
using the man's fork and knife.
Better to behave as a human than as a dog.
Well, I quite like dogs.
In fact, I prefer 'em.
Dogs aren't hypocrites.
And they don't lie.
They don't lock each other up in cages.
They don't pimp, poison,
and they don't go out of their way
to degrade and destroy their own habitat.
A naive reading of human history.
It's the only reading of human history.
Are you done?
Perhaps we should get on
with what we came here for.
SHIRLEY: A prudent suggestion, sister.
Recent acts of terror
in cities across the globe,
most notably in Moscow,
severely undermine the stability
that this Council seeks to preserve.
The purpose of tonight
is to determine what punishment, if any,
should be meted out on the individual
who has imperiled us all.
You murdered over 2,000 innocent humans.
Children.
And yet,
you don't seem remotely remorseful.
What the hell gives you the right
to disobey this council?
What gives me the right?
(SPEAKS SKRULL LANGUAGE)
(IN ENGLISH) I think it's a war.
I think it's a war!
Hmm?
And unlike the last war each one of us
around this table fought in,
I'm not gonna lose this one.
Humans are doomed to self-destruction.
Long before we arrived on this planet,
they were destined to consume themselves.
So, for anyone flinching
at the thought of innocent deaths,
let me assure you,
we're only hastening the inevitable.
SERGIO: And what happens
if the Avengers return?
You don't think I thought about that?
Put your faith in me.
And I promise,
your loyalty will be repaid.
Well, Madam Prime Minister...
We need to streamline
our chain of command.
Democracy is fine for peacetime,
but whilst at war,
we need a single commander
whose war power is total and unchecked.
My God!
Therefore, I nominate Gravik
to the post of Skrull General.
SERGIO: Traitor!
You were in on this with him
the entire time!
Seat yourself down, Sergio.
I'm not done yet.
Who do you think you're talking to?
I'm the commander of NATO.
I can mobilize a million troops
at the snap of a... (GRUNTS)
Shall I remove him, Madame?
Oh, I don't think
he'll be any more trouble.
(GAGS)
(COUGHS)
All those in favor of Gravik
as our new general...
will submit.
I fear each one of you
has forgotten our history.
We did not end up homeless refugees
because we were unwilling to wage war.
We ended up homeless refugees
because we were too willing.
I do not support your coup.
I will not support your war.
And I do not submit.
If I had another 100 like you,
I could take on the universe.
You go in peace, sister.
You'll not be harmed.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
- Shirley.
- It's Gravik.
The Council just voted him General.
He has control of our people
and our future.
If there's anything I can do...
Yeah, set up a meet
between me and Gravik. Public place.
Talos, he will kill you.
Yeah, thanks for the faith.
You don't understand.
Gravik has changed.
So have I. Soren's dead.
I know.
But if you can't keep it together,
you will not walk out alive.
Shirley, set up the meet.
Just tell him
I wanna talk about my daughter.
(ALL CHEERING)
Thank you, sir.
Without you, this wouldn't be possible.
(INDISTINCT)
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
You don't have it.
Harvest wasn't there.
ROSA: Then it's back to scavenging.
Our DNA selection
remains extremely limited.
PAGON: I'll send out teams.
ROSA: I was told this phase
would be over.
So was I.
Gravik has given me multiple locations
for the Harvest, all of them empty.
Our fearless leader isn't always right.
Perhaps I misheard you.
Do you need anything else, Dr. Dalton?
Yes. Your absence.
(ROSA SIGHS)
REPORTER: In this stunning sign
of just how seriously it regards rumors
of American involvement
in the Moscow attacks,
the 27 EU heads of state,
plus the British Prime Minster
have all but commanded Washington
to account for itself
at this emergency security summit
here in London.
MAN: Colonel?
Colonel Rhodes?
Colonel, are you denying
that two of your citizens,
Mr. Nicholas Fury and Miss Maria Hill,
were present in Moscow
at the scene of the attacks?
We are aware of allegations
that Mr. Fury and Miss Hill
may have traveled to Moscow.
Which, if true, it would've been in
their capacity as private citizens, so...
Do these photos suffice as confirmation
of that fact, Colonel Rhodes?
(CHUCKLES)
Respectfully, Prime Minister,
I can't take the authenticity
of Russian-supplied photos at face value.
However, I will be more than happy
to have them analyzed
at our facilities at Langley.
(SCOFFS)
How do you explain
Mr. Fury's presence in Moscow?
Uh, alleged. Alleged presence, madam.
(WOMAN SCOFFS)
If Slovakia rolls its eyes at me
one more time,
I'm gonna put on the suit
and carpet bomb it.
PAMELA: Why are you here, Colonel?
You are not a Head of State.
Surely, President Ritson
is aware of the seriousness
with which his international partners
regard this allegation.
Well, I'm here as a courtesy,
Madam Prime Minister.
President Ritson has a pretty busy day job
running the most powerful country
and military on the face of the planet.
He doesn't just hop to when summoned.
Not by France,
not by Italy, not by the UK.
Now, while we are sensitive
to your concerns,
until such time as you can present
an actual shred of evidence
to back those concerns up,
I'm afraid sensitivity
is all you're gonna be getting from us.
All right?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
- Rhodes.
- FURY: Nice suit. Armani?
(SIGHS) Brioni.
(WHISPERS) Fury.
Pretty expensive for a government salary.
Yeah, well,
my other suit's made of titanium
so this actually constitutes
considerable savings.
We need to meet. ASAP.
Great. Tell you what,
let me just finish mopping up
this globe-sized bucket of steaming hot
kaka you tipped over yesterday
and then, we can get a drink. Sound good?
You sound frustrated.
What's the matter? Croatia talking crap?
Slovakia.
Well, carpet-bomb their ass.
Burner's Tavern, one o'clock.
Do me a favor and try not to pop off
a nuclear holocaust before you get there.
(SIGHS)
Should I be worried about poison?
You should be worried
about spending the rest of your days
in the Siberian retirement community.
Yeah, don't let the relaxed ambiance
fool you.
I'm this close to handing your ass
over to the Russians.
Forgetting your rank here, Colonel Rhodes?
You do not wanna be playing
"mine is bigger than yours"
with job titles right now, Fury.
Trust me, I'm the last friend you've got.
Are the Russians
really tryin' to pin this on me?
Your face is all over CCTV footage.
I was there trying to stop the attack.
Oh, well, excellent job at that,
by the way. 2,000 dead so far.
Number will probably triple
once they clear all the rubble.
Meaning you not only set the stage
for World War III,
but you simultaneously flipped
all of our allies to Team Russia.
How well do you know your security detail?
I know they're catching bullets first
if I get shot at.
(CHUCKLES) What do you mean
how much do I know about 'em?
What if I told you they were all spies?
Spies for who, the Russians?
Well... non-state actors.
You know, global reach,
borderless operations.
- HYDRA?
- Yeah.
If HYDRA was a bunch of green guys
who could shape-shift into your daddy.
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
So, how long have you known about them?
About 15 years ago,
I was part of an eyes-only,
top-secret presentation.
It was about
a shape-shifting alien species
that had sent a few of its light ships
crashing down to Earth.
The Pentagon was concerned
that they might get into their heads
to invade us one day from the inside.
That invasion is real. It's happened.
That's... That's not possible.
Yeah, that's what I thought, too,
but it's true.
And here's the crazy part,
we're being invaded and we can't even tell
who the invaders are.
Moscow was just the beginning.
Maybe we should call our friends.
No, no, no, we can't jump the gun on that.
You know, we get them
in a fight with the Skrulls
and next thing you know,
they find themselves duplicated
and turned into terrorists.
Fury, this isn't...
This is my war, Rhodey.
I need you to back me on this.
(SIGHS) I... I can't do it.
Ain't no "can't" in our business.
There's only what you can do
and what you will not do.
You're right.
I should've said, I'm not doing it.
I just spent
all the political capital I had
in getting Maria Hill's body
back from the Russians.
Are you really talking to me
about politics right now?
I'm here as an envoy
of the United States government, Fury.
The job is political.
I remember when your job
was protecting the planet.
We protect the planet
by protecting our seat at the table.
Are you forgetting who helped you
get your seat at the table?
Oh, so I owe you now? Is that it?
We owe each other.
Men who look like us don't get promoted
because of who our daddies know.
Every ounce of power
we wrestle from the vice grip
of the mediocre Alexander Pierces
who run this world was earned in blood.
So let's make the power mean something.
Help a brother out.
Car's outside, Colonel.
Colonel Rhodes will let you know
when he's ready to go.
RHODEY: The car is for you, Fury.
They'll escort you outside,
then you're goin' to the airport.
Oh. I'm sorry.
I didn't know I had travel plans.
I made 'em on your behalf.
Have you even listened
to a word that I've said?
Yeah, I have. The world is on the line.
The enemy is a million times
more dangerous than HYDRA,
but they can only be vanquished by you.
Alone.
And you want me to make the power
mean something by helpin' a brother out.
But you should know better than most.
The reason we wrestled this power
from mediocre men who don't look like us
was not simply to turn around
and hand it to mediocre men who do.
The point of this power
is to be uncompromising,
to be unsparing,
to be able to sit across
from a man we greatly admire,
with whom we share an entire professional,
personal, ancestral history with
and to tell him without any reservation,
that he's fired.
That's what this moment right here,
right now is about, Nick.
(SCOFFS)
(CHUCKLES)
(COUGHS)
They sent you to fire me?
Nobody sent me. I volunteered.
And not to put too fine a point on this,
but that mess that you created in Moscow
that resulted in getting
one of our best people murdered,
you earned all this smoke, brother.
Move.
- (GROANS)
- Are you seriously under the impression
that just because you strip me
of my titles, I relinquish my DNA?
Careful, Fury.
- (BONE CRACKS)
- (GROANS)
RHODEY: And you wonder why you're out.
I'm Nick Fury.
Even when I'm out, I'm in.
(WHEEZES)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Yes,
and now that the door is unlocked,
what does that tell you
about me and doors?
Who are you?
I'm above your pay grade. Where is he?
Thank you.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Where is your safe house?
- Speak!
- SONYA: Didn't your mother ever warn you
you could lose an eye
by beating your meat like that?
(LAUGHS SARCASTICALLY)
What are you doing here?
Oh, I'm taking over.
(MAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) I've thrown everything at him
and he hasn't said a word.
What makes you think
you can get him to speak?
Oh, I can be quite persuasive.
Oh, before I forget,
where is the escape hatch in this dump?
Why do you need to know that?
Oh, just a hunch.
Oh, wonderful. Okay, make yourself scarce.
MAN: What are you looking at?
Alone at last. Now, shall we do this
the easy way or the other way?
I'm gonna break these chains.
And then, I'm gonna break
every bone in your body.
(CHUCKLES) The other way it is.
(SCREAMING IN PAIN)
(GRUNTS)
Mmm.
Well, now that's confirmed,
let's party, shall we?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(TYPING)
What are you doing in here?
Checking the progress
of our newest recruit.
He'll be ready for a face before long.
He's loyal.
GRAVIK: Loyal.
You know, I remember
when you first came to me, G'iah.
The daughter of a failed General.
I thought to myself, what kind of coward
sends his daughter to do what he wouldn't?
But you know, then I realized that kind of
coward just doesn't have it in him.
Our man on the inside located Brogan.
Let's go then.
You're wasting your time.
I'll never talk to you.
Well, that's very brave,
but everyone talks
when their blood starts to cook at 160°C.
It's a biochemical imperative.
The smart ones
start talking earlier than that.
You a smart one?
(GRUNTS)
Right, I didn't think so.
Go ahead, put it in my arm. I don't care.
(BROGAN GROANS)
(SIZZLING)
(GRUNTS)
(YELLS)
(SCREAMING IN PAIN)
SONYA: Tell me the location
of Gravik's compound.
I swear I know nothing. Please!
I'm afraid, sorry, dear heart,
I can't work with nothing.
I need to know where Gravik is,
and where he'll be.
I don't know, I swear.
Gravik keeps everything a secret.
And what secrets doesn't he keep?
He's building a machine.
What kind of machine?
I think it's to make us stronger.
GRAVIK: You wait in the car.
- Keep the engine running.
- Mmm-hmm.
Who's helping you?
I don't know what you mean.
Who's leading the science?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Some married couple.
What's their name?
I can't, please. Gravik will kill me.
I'm terribly sorry,
but if I don't get a name,
- Gravik won't get the chance to kill you.
- (GROANS)
Please.
Dalton.
The name's Dalton.
You see,
that wasn't so terribly difficult, was it?
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(SILENCED GUNSHOT)
(MEN CHATTING INDISTINCTLY)
(MEN GRUNTING)
Sounds like your lift is here.
(GRUNTS)
Listen, I'm just gonna go
and check around back.
Cool. I'll come with.
No, no, no. You stay here.
They might come out with Brogan.
Yeah.
You're a smart lady, G'iah.
How very Dostoyevsky.
(MAN GRUNTING)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
PAGON: Gotcha.
You're all right.
I've got him. Let's go.
What'd you tell 'em?
Nothin', just lies.
Nothin'?
Just lies?
That's all, I swear.
GRAVIK: Take him to the car.
- (BROGAN GRUNTS)
- Keep driving.
How did they find our safe house?
(BROGAN BREATHING RAGGEDLY)
(BROGAN PANTING)
(BROGAN GRUNTS)
(SIRENS WAILING)
GRAVIK: Pull over.
(GUN COCKING)
(BROGAN GRUNTING)
Did we make it home, Pagon?
Almost there, bro.
(BROGAN GRUNTS)
(BROGAN PANTING)
(GUNSHOT)
(BODY THUDS)
(GRUNTS)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO)
(SIGHS)
Aren't you forgetting something?
Better?
Almost.
("TRY A LITTLE TENDERNESS"
BY OTIS REDDING PLAYING)
All you got to do is, man,
hold her when you wanna
Squeeze her, don't tease her,
never leave her
Get to her, got, got, got to try
a little tenderness, yeah, yeah
You got to know how to love her, man
Don't be surprised, man
You got to squeeze her,
don't tease her, never leave
You got to hold her,
brother, something, man
Try a little tenderness
yeah, yeah, yeah
You got to grab her gently, man
Don't bruise her, no, no
You got to love her, tease her,
don't squeeze her
You got to try, na na na na na
Try, try a little tenderness, yeah
Watch her groove
You got to know what to do, man
Take this advice
You gotta love, squeeze, don't tease