GAJANG RESTAURANT
Why is no one controlling the area?
Why are you so late?
Come this way.
Hey! Hurry upstairs!
Hey! Damn it!
Seonga!
Seonga...
AMBULANCE
SHADOW DETECTIVE SEASON 2
-You're here.
Yeah.
It seems like a gas leak caused the fire,
but we need to investigate further
for exact details.
Hey, don't let cars come in here.
Hey, Officer Kang. Come here, you punk.
- Yes, sir.
- Hey.
What did Son Gyeongchan say
when he got here?
About what, sir?
I said, what did Son Gyeongchan say
when he got here, moron?
What was Lee Seonga doing here?
He says he doesn't know either.
But he's her partner!
Lee Seonga's call records.
Look them up and send them to me, got it?
- Yes, sir.
- Get going.
- Run, you punk!
- Yes, sir!
Don't cross the line!
Move your car!
The leading suspects
of the serial theft case
that has been occurring recently
in the Geumo redevelopment area
have been revealed to be
runaway teenagers, to the shock of many.
Mr. Woo, who is charged with confining
and assaulting these runaway teenagers,
has been reported to have died from
a gas explosion earlier this afternoon.
Onto the next news.
Today is the third day
of local election campaigns.
Lee Youngho, candidate
for governor of Youngseo Province,
paid a visit to the Geumo dockyard.
Candidate Lee's goal to turn Geumo
into the greatest port city in Asia...
You're here.
Yeah.
They said she had a brain contusion
from the shock of the explosion.
They don't know when she'll wake up.
We'll have to wait and see.
She'll wake up soon enough.
She's strong.
Take good care of her.
Why...
Why did you tell me to stop her?
You told me to stop Seonga
from digging into Woo Jangik's case.
Why was that?
See you.
Chief Baek,
the problem of runaway teens
and serial thefts in the area is serious.
Do you have a solution?
Yes, we created a task force
for runaway teenagers and--
An individual who had been in conflict
with a runaway teenager died
from a gas explosion.
Where are you with the investigation?
I heard a police officer
was seriously injured.
- How is the officer doing?
- Yes, it's quite an unfortunate incident.
We are thoroughly investigating the fire,
and the injured police officer
is recovering quickly.
I'd like to ask Director Choi Dohyung.
Do you have anything to say
about the problems with delinquent teens
that have persisted recently
near the Geumo redevelopment area?
The foundation...
will be announcing a plan
to build a shelter for runaway teenagers
and a vocational education center.
However...
I don't think it's right to label children
with words like "delinquent."
So, please.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Ask the children
what they want to do in the future,
not what they did in the past.
Please!
Director Choi.
Director Choi!
Are there any other measures being taken?
We are doing our best to prepare them.
Hey. You're Hana, right?
Excuse me?
You're from that runaway fam, aren't you?
Behind the serial thefts.
How's that kid, Doyoon, doing?
What else did you do there?
Did the boys make you
engage in prostitution?
- Let go!
-Take your hand off her!
What are you doing here?
Asking something like that
to a minor without parental consent is
a serious violation of her human rights.
Hana, go inside the room.
- Who are you?
- Team Leader Yeon.
Chief Baek.
Team Leader Yeon Juhyun of
the Women and Juvenile Affairs Division.
Director Choi.
I think we'll get some good attention
if we get a picture of you and the kids
along with the foundation's plan.
That isn't necessary.
That's enough.
You can do that later.
Let's call it a wrap for today.
Sure. Let's go.
Thank you.
By the way, I think Team Leader Yeon here
will have a lot to do
with your foundation from now on.
Hello, sir.
I'm Yeon Juhyun
of Geumo's Women and Juvenile Affairs.
I'm Choi Dohyung.
I guess I'll have to bother you
from now on.
It would really be an honor to help
a legendary officer such as yourself.
Detective Kim.
This is Lieutenant Kim Taekrok
of the Women and Juvenile Affairs.
Hello, ma'am.
Goodness.
You haven't shown up in so long.
I thought you were dead.
Take a seat.
So who's this?
I haven't seen him before.
Yes, he's a very successful man in Seoul.
He's even on TV sometimes.
Really?
I'm sorry.
I don't watch TV besides soap operas.
It's all right.
- We'll have the pollock soup.
- Sure.
I know all about
what kind of a man Kim Taekrok is.
I've been meaning to call.
I know.
You're not one not to reach out
when you clearly knew I was back.
How have you been?
From what I heard,
you've been through a lot.
Kook Jinhan, was it?
Were you close
with the dead chief investigation officer?
Close? No, we were just work colleagues.
I don't even want to think about it.
Okay.
You'll be retiring soon.
Forget about all the complicated stuff.
I thought you hated leaving the force,
but I guess life is good after retirement.
It is.
I sleep comfortably, eat comfortably,
and poop comfortably.
You're busier than that.
- Doing good deeds.
- Oh, not at all.
There's one thing nice
about being back in my hometown.
Sitting down with Kim Taekrok
and having a drink.
Here.
Right.
I heard you were close to the detective
who was injured in the explosion.
Well...
I've known her since she was little.
I should've paid more attention.
You still haven't fixed
that habit of blaming yourself?
It's not rare for police officers
to get hurt or go crazy on the job.
Still, they all live on somehow.
Taekrok.
Jinseok is doing well too.
You know he got married, right?
He opened up a barbecue restaurant
in Yangpyeong last year.
His wife is really nice,
and I guess business is going well.
He looked really happy.
He worked hard on rehabilitation,
and now you can barely notice
he has a limp.
That's good.
He asks about you every time I visit.
He says he's moved on.
How much longer are you--
Dohyung. Try this pollock soup.
It's nice and spicy. It's good.
Stay in touch.
I let it slide when I was far away,
but not anymore when I'm close by. Okay?
All right. Hurry up and get inside.
Taekrok.
The past is the past.
Move on and only think
about the future, okay?
You and I, let's put down
the heavy load off our chests now.
Let's live an easy life, all right?
Sir, take good care of him.
Sure.
See you.
What do you think?
I think the fire was started
to get rid of the traces.
See the hole here?
The light shining through?
They put something in here
to get to the control panel
and reset the passcode.
This is the work of a professional.
Petty thieves don't even touch
these things.
They don't know what's inside,
and it takes too long to unlock it.
It's a significant risk.
Then they were already after
what was inside the safe.
Yes, this was what they came for.
If the thing Woo Jangik
is looking for was in his safe,
someone else took it.
Hey, who was that earlier?
I don't know.
I didn't get a look at his face.
He ran away as soon as he saw me.
It felt like he knew who I was.
Darn. Is this gonna be another headache?
Dongbum.
Please keep what happened today
a secret from Taekrok.
Taekrok doesn't know about this?
Well...
I just want to tell him myself.
Well, all right.
I'll get going now.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Thank you for today.
- It's nothing.
This is where all the dirty interests
were connected together back then.
It feels like something's going on again.
It's all in the past.
-Detective Kim.
- Take your hands off this case.
Sir, what took you so long?
What about Detective Lee? Is she okay?
You should at least tell me
what's going on. We're family!
Family?
We're a community.
A community of neighbors.
I don't want to be family with you.
Just close the door.
You really...
have never met
with Chairman Jang in person?
No, I haven't.
So,
why did Chairman Jang kill Kook Jinhan
but let you live?
Isn't it strange?
CIVIL AFFAIRS
NOEUL GOSHIWON
INMATE VISITOR LOG
INMATE: SEO GWANGSU
KIM TAEKROK, KIM JUNGSOOK, KIM TAEKROK...
POLICE OFFICER PERSONNEL RECORD
PERSONAL DETAILS REPORT
SEOKYUNG DAILY
ARSON CULPRIT... REVEALED TO BE INNOCENT
WHO IS THE DETECTIVE THAT SAVED HIM?
NO CALLER ID
Yes?
There are no life-threatening injuries.
Yes.
I think I will have to keep looking
into how much Detective Kim Taekrok knows.
Yes.
POLICE OFFICER PERSONNEL RECORD
Taekrok.
Seonga.
What are you doing here?
You ruined everything.
I guess nothing has changed.
Chief Kook.
Everyone around you
gets hurt and experiences pain.
Right?
No.
He's right.
No one can be happy around you.
Do you get it now?
It's all your fault.
You're to blame for everything.
Do you get it?
MISSED CALL, OFFICER GONG
Wait, Detective Kim.
What took you so long?
You didn't answer your phone either.
Hey, what's going on?
Chief Baek ordered Homicide
and Women and Juveniles
to gather right now.
Come on. I'll be on my way.
HANYOUNG DAILY
WHAT TO DO WITH THE CRIME HAVEN,
GEUMO REDEVELOPMENT AREA
Please sit.
I can tolerate a lot of things,
but this, I cannot.
"Geumo Police lacks presence."
I won't let Geumo Police Station
be treated like this.
Not under my leadership.
As of right now,
Homicide and Women and Juveniles
will act under joint investigations.
Back from the start.
From children to adults.
Go through everyone, dead and alive.
Take care of the runaway teenagers
and find the arsonist at once.
Did the results come back? Is it arson?
Yes, we have
the identification results back.
And it's almost certain that it was arson.
I'll begin the briefing
on the Hoyong-ro office explosion.
The case overview.
I organized it according to time, date,
and location, as you see here.
We analyzed camera footage from the area.
But we haven't been able to find
any leads besides that.
And when we asked around
people in the neighborhood,
they said they had seen big thugs
go in and out of the victim's office
and that they hadn't seen them
since their last visit.
The victim is Woo Jangik,
age 39, as you can see here.
If you look at these pictures,
there is a timer, a high-capacity battery,
a heat cable, and a needle.
This here is the predicted diagram
of the explosive device.
The culprit cut the hose
so that gas would slowly fill up
from the bottom.
And he stuck a needle
to the dial-type timer.
It starts ticking down.
After a certain time,
it makes contact
and the heating wire catches fire.
Did Woo Jangik die from the fire?
The autopsy report isn't out yet,
so we don't know the exact cause of death.
That means he could have been murdered
before the gas explosion.
That's possible.
All right. Homicide, look through
all the security camera footage
nearby Woo Jangik's office
and report back to me.
-Yes, sir.
-Yes.
What is Women and Juveniles going to do?
We plan on starting a fresh investigation
on all the runaway teenagers
who were involved
in the recent theft and arson.
All right.
What are you all doing? Get to work.
Lieutenant Kim.
Take Officer Gong
and go to the runaway fam hideout
at the redevelopment area.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll be outside.
Yes, all right.
Detective.
I trust that you already know this.
Just because the two teams are cooperating
doesn't mean you're back on Homicide.
All procedures and processes
of the investigation
happen under my orders.
I'll keep that in mind.
Gosh, she's so charismatic.
Seeing how you can't say anything
back to your team leader,
the rumor must be true.
What are you talking about?
Didn't you know?
I heard your team leader went to the chief
and asked to have you on her team.
DON'T JUST WATCH GEUMO BECOME A SLUM!
CONTINUE WITH REDEVELOPMENT!
Is this it?
-Hey.
- Yes?
I have to stop by somewhere.
Go take a look at the hideout
and get back.
By myself? Do you have any plans?
- It's none of your business.
- Excuse me? Detective Kim.
-Sir.
- What?
Thanks.
-Here.
- Thank you.
Our team is done
securing the whereabouts of the kids
in Hana's runaway fam.
- Okay.
- Now,
- we'll proceed with witness investigation.
- Wait.
- They're not suspects?
- Excuse me?
I mean, the teenagers have
the clearest motive
to do it in this situation.
They set the office on fire
because they kidnapped their friend.
Not until we have evidence.
Hey.
How did it go on our end?
Did we secure all CCTV footage?
Yes, we've secured all the footage
from the nearby security cameras.
I'm watching it
from 12 hours before the explosion.
What? Hold on.
I think I just saw something.
Can you rewind it just a little?
Okay.
No, just a little bit more.
Yes, this person.
Team Leader Han.
YOUNGSEO WELFARE FOUNDATION
Yang Gitae...
The fourth floor. Up there.
Get up there. Run.
NOEUL GOSIWON
Ah!
THE REQUIREMENTS OF LOVE
CAN THEY FALL IN LOVE WITHOUT THEM?
Kimchi.
Sour kimchi.
Is the lady okay?
Yeah.
She'll be back on her feet soon.
Hey, is there anything else
that you can tell me
besides what you told the police?
Even the tiniest detail would help.
He was the only one who listened
to what I said and believed me.
To tell you the truth...
These punks are being so loud.
Hey, I think he just had ramyeon.
- Take this hoodie, will you?
-Yes, sir.
- Gitae, come over here.
- I don't want to.
Come here as you're told, you punk.
Hurry and catch him.
What are you looking at?
You're dead when I catch you!
That night, before we went into the office
of the man who confined us,
I saw someone wearing a black hoodie.
A hoodie?
If something really is missing,
that person must be the culprit.
Let go of me.
-Yang Gitae. You listen up.
-Hold still.
You're being arrested for arson
and the murder of Woo Jangik. Got it?
What bullshit is that?
It's not me. Fuck! You brainless pigs!
What did you just say?
You brainless...
Hey, cover the security camera.
What? Don't cover it.
You little shit.
Hey. What did you just say?
- Wait. It hurts so much.
-What did you just say?
What? You piece of shit.
Come here, you goddamn piece of shit.
Fuck you.
It hurts, doesn't it? You son of a bitch.
I didn't tell the police
because they might say I made it up.
But it's true.
Did you see the person's face?
Hey, what's up?
Yang Gitae has been arrested
as the arson suspect.
-It hurts.
-What are you talking about?
On the day of the incident,
he was filmed near Woo Jangik's office.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
He's still going through a retrial,
but he has a history as an arsonist
who set a homeless person on fire.
I'm sure.
The two of you
must get along well.
This was faster than I expected.
It's all thanks to Team Leader Han.
No, we did it together.
- By the way...
- Yes?
What happened to his face?
His face... When we were bringing
him outside, he fell on the stairs.
He kept resisting, so we lost our grip.
It's true.
He lives in the same apartment
as Lieutenant Kim Taekrok?
Yes.
Hmm.
Let's begin.
What did you bring him in for?
He was filmed on the security camera
near the victim's office
the night before the incident.
So we brought him in.
- Do you have evidence?
- What?
Anyone?
He's not the culprit just for being there.
- Is this how you do your job?
- Detective Kim.
A word, please.
He didn't do it.
What did the suspect say
when you arrested him?
I mean, he couldn't explain
why he was there at that hour.
I'm sure it was that jerk.
I have a strong hunch about this, Chief.
You investigate based on hunches?
Why do you keep trying to cover for him?
Seonga's laying there injured.
Don't you feel the need
to destroy whoever did it?
Or what, is there another reason?
- What?
- I mean, the way you're acting right now.
You're the one who was on the phone
with Seonga right before she got injured.
The former arsonist who was on the scene
ten hours before the incident occurred
is also someone close to you.
They're all connected to you, aren't they?
It's been concluded
that the arson murderer wasn't Yang Gitae.
He's going through a retrial right now.
The fact
that he's going through a retrial...
means that he hasn't been acquitted yet.
Right.
All right, settle down.
We're not suspecting you of anything,
Detective Kim.
You know that investigating one
with a history is a must.
This may simply be a formality,
but he is a close acquaintance of yours,
so I hope you don't interfere.
You understand what I mean, right?
Gitae.
It's you, right? You did it.
Hey, did you kill him
before you started the fire?
I have a right to remain silent.
You idiot.
The right to remain silent?
You think that's going to help you?
Be honest.
You went to Woo Jangik to make
a quick buck because he looked rich.
But he didn't welcome you,
so you killed him
and started the fire. Right?
I have nothing to say.
You think Kim Taekrok will have your back
because you live in the same apartment?
Is that it?
- Hey, you need to wake up.
- We're family.
What kind of family?
A community.
A community of neighbors.
- How does that make you family?
- We are family...
Yes. Did you get it restored?
This isn't easy.
It's at the top on the difficulty scale.
Hurry. Things have changed.
There's not much time.
I'm trying my best...
Hello?
This old man. Jeez!
I thought you quit smoking.
You know
why Yang Gitae was there, don't you?
Are you not going to tell me?
- What is it you want to hear from me?
- Anything.
The reason you're not doing anything
even while Seonga's hurt
and Yang Gitae is arrested.
Just one thing that I can understand.
Get off the case if you're going
to get emotional while investigating.
I saw someone in a black hoodie
when I stopped by Woo Jangik's office
last night.
When?
Around midnight.
Was that Yang Gitae, too?
I saw someone wearing a black hoodie.
The punk who did that to Seonga.
I'm going to catch them no matter what.
Whether it's Yang Gitae...
or anyone else.
These analog dials
are rarely used these days.
You know those terrorists
you see on international news?
Even they use digital timers.
Improvised explosive devices like this
are all digital.
If the maximum on this is 60 minutes,
it must have been set up
right before the explosion.
if you adjust the dial, it could be
60 hours, not just 60 minutes.
That means it can be set to ten hours too.
Yes, in theory.
I guess places that sell these
aren't common.
It'll be difficult to get
something like this on the internet.
Maybe you can try
the industrial tool complex...
If I ask around, I might be able
to find out where it was bought.
Right.
I should go tomorrow.
And...
- don't tell Taekrok I came today.
- I got it. I won't tell.
What's this?
This. It's...
I was asked to catch
someone's wife cheating.
Isn't that illegal?
You cops ask me to do worse.
Thank you.
- See you.
-Yes.
Yes. I'm ready.
I restored it as you asked,
but is this for real?
It's going to be chaos if this gets out.
Are you sure this is okay?
Right. We do handle it.
We sold one just a few days ago.
Do you remember what the person
who bought it looked like?
Well... just an ordinary person.
How did they pay for it?
In cash.
I give ten percent discounts.
You wouldn't happen to have
a security camera here, would you?
Why wouldn't I?
What kind of store doesn't these days?
Then could I take the footage?
It's already been taken.
By who?
The police came and took it
before you came.
I mean, which police...
How would I know?
They asked for it saying they were police,
so I did.
Hey, where's the evidence list?
Excuse me?
Where's the evidence list
to Woo Jangik's case?
The Woo Jangik case...
The evidence list...
Here.
LIST OF ITEMS FOR ANALYSIS
What? Is this it?
Yes.
What about footage from the tool shop?
I'm not following.
I managed the evidence this whole time,
and there was nothing like that.
All right.
These are from the last ten years.
There are juvenile crimes
involving theft and arson.
They're in such disarray, aren't they?
I'm sorry about that.
Anyway, please organize them,
starting with the ones
that are most relevant to our case.
I will.
I'm surprised.
The colleague you're most fond of
got hurt.
The acquaintance you were taking care of
was accused of arson.
You seem too calm, given the situation.
I'm not in Homicide anymore.
What more can I do?
Seonga will wake up,
and Yang Gitae will be freed.
Yes, well...
I'm glad you think that way.
I heard you were the one who recognized
Yang Gitae on the security camera footage.
Yes.
I could hardly tell
because the picture was too blurry.
How did you recognize him right away?
I was really impressed
by an article I read.
About the arsonist who was vindicated
thanks to the detective
who put him behind bars.
You have a good memory!
Anyway, please keep it up.
Sure.
Seonga.
Guess what I did.
I investigated a target.
The target...
was Taekrok.
Ah!
Slow down.
I was starving to death.
I like white soup better, but still.
This is so good.
Don't you resent Taekrok?
It's just me in here.
Are you aware?
Still, what can I do about it?
He said he'd have it resolved soon,
so all I can do is wait.
It's not like he'd ask me
such a favor without good reason.
I have a favor to ask.
Still, it was risky this time.
He should have done it himself.
Don't you think so?
Picking the lock and installing a spy cam
is a piece of cake.
I was just unlucky getting caught.
Spy cam?
A spy camera?
Taekrok didn't mention that to you?
Maybe it got burnt,
so he got nothing out of it.
Darn it.
That's no good.
You're going to tell me
I'm crazy when you wake up,
but I have to see for myself
what Taekrok is hiding.
He was still at the office when I left.
Why do you ask?
It's nothing.
Okay.
NOEUL GOSIWON
GEUMO POLICE STATION
ACHIEVEMENT AWARD, YEON JUHYUN
POLICE JUDO CHAMPIONSHIP
I heard
your team leader went to the chief
and asked to have you on her team.
Team Leader Yeon recognized his face
in the footage and pointed him out.
HOW TO PREVENT DEMENTIA
1. NO DRINKING, NO SMOKING...
WOMEN AND JUVENILE AFFAIRS
INVESTIGATION TEAM
One more thing.
That person.
There was something weird about them.
Something weird?
This.
Isn't that weird?
But...
That lady...
Goodness, Hana.
...did this with her finger.
That lady's also a cop, right?
- I'm Yeon Juhyun.
- Right.
NONHYEON-DONG WOMAN
MURDER CASE
SHOOTING AT ABANDONED GEUMO TRANSMITTER,
1 OFFICER DEAD
CANDIDATE LEE YOUNGHO'S
FIRST CAMPAIGN IN GEUMO
YOUNGSEO DISTRICT OFFICE'S
CHIEF PROSECUTOR...
DONATION 10 MILLION WON
GEUMO POLICE STATION CORRUPTION
FORMER CHIEF IN PRISON FOR TAKING BRIBES
This is it, right?
-Yes.
- Okay.
SHADOW DETECTIVE SEASON 2
Modify by Blue-Bird™