DECEMBER, 1999
GEUMO CITY
-Wow.
The hero of Geumo Police.
What are you talking about?
You caught the guy before the MIU did,
so that makes you a hero.
Don't get cute with me, man.
He was acting all high and mighty
when he first came down
to catch that escaped prisoner
but ended up getting schooled by Taekrok.
By the way, I heard that guy is
just as crazy as you are.
-Maybe we should pit him against you.
-What?
You know.
That's why we call you Taek the Dog.
Didn't you know?
-Everybody calls you that.
-Taek the Dog.
We caught the guy
without much trouble thanks to you.
You should do a little sightseeing
while you're here.
It must've been a hassle dealing with us.
Well, not really.
It happens often with the MIU
since we travel all around the country
and stick our noses
into the cases of the local cops.
I guess so.
I won't beat around the bush.
I very much like the way you investigate.
Would you like to work with me
by any chance?
Think about it.
OCTOBER 2000
SEOUL
Hey!
Stand back!
-Put the knife down!
-Drop it!
Stay back, you fucking pigs!
Drop it!
Hey! Fuck!
Put the knife down!
He has a hostage. Stay back!
-Don't come closer!
-You bastards!
-Get lost, fuckers!
-Hey!
Please help me!
-You sons of bitches!
-Put our weapons down!
Please save me.
Let's calm down and talk about this.
SHADOW DETECTIVE SEASON 2
Dohyung shot his gun again.
I created BST with members from the MIU.
Let's be safe today too.
We never know when or how we'll get hurt…
That guy.
He held a university student hostage
and slit her throat before.
If Squad Chief Choi hadn't shot him,
the same thing could
have happened to that girl.
So why the hell do we even have to worry
about getting punished for using guns?
Calm down. The disciplinary action will
just be a pay cut if I get one at all.
It's fine. I'll take care of it.
Right. Let's stop worrying tonight
and just drink away, okay?
-Be safe!
-Today too!
Come up with something else.
It's always the same...
Come on. What else could be
more important to us than this?
Right. Dohyung.
I've been thinking about this for a while.
What if we form a group? Just us guys.
BST, for Be Safe Today too.
BST. What do you think?
-That sounds so lame.
-It's nice.
-Good, right?
-I like it.
Be Safe Today too.
It's good, don't you think?
-I like it. It's decided, then.
-Let's do it!
-BST!
-Good? Good!
All right. Be safe!
Today too!
Hey, Jinseok.
What is it?
What's this?
For your mother's surgery.
We all pitched in a little.
I know you all don't get paid much.
I can't accept this.
Hey, kid, I ought to…
We're supposed to help each other
when in need. Take it.
Take it.
Thanks, Taekrok.
BST
You and your obsession with BST…
What? It's nice.
Be safe today too.
Maybe the situation got serious
because the guy he shot sued him.
HOMICIDE TEAM 2
Squad Chief Choi
got suspended for three months.
What the hell? That isn't right!
For fuck's sake, that's too harsh.
Those damn higher-ups.
Hey, man.
Taekrok, are we just supposed
to sit back and watch?
Dohyung received a three-month suspension.
NOEUL GOSIWON
Should I proceed…
with Kim Taekrok?
All right.
Kill it.
In order to protect ourselves…
In order to protect ourselves
we should help each other.
…we should help each other.
We're ready.
LEE SEONGA
Listen carefully.
This is very important.
DETECTIVE KIM TAEKROK
Goodness, Detective Kim.
To what do I owe the pleasure of you
calling me at this hour?
You sound at ease.
I don't think you should be.
I'm not sure what you mean…
Ah...
I heard Seo Gwangsu turned himself in
and made some ridiculous accusation
about me working for Lee Youngho.
Did you put him up to it?
Do I take it you aren't concerned
since Won Jaegu has your back?
Think however you will.
How much longer do you think
you can get away with this?
By the way, Detective Kim.
Be careful.
That might get you into big trouble.
You're the one who should be careful.
I've seen plenty of guys like you get
stabbed in the back for trusting people.
What is it?
Are you any different
from Team Leader Han?
Aren't you the reason
Team Leader Han ended up like that?
Tell Choi Dohyung.
You.
The Geumjeong Society.
I'll be ending it all.
Kim Taekrok left this behind.
PETITION
EXCESSIVE USE OF FORCE
PETITIONER: KIM TAEKROK
"Squad Chief Choi Dohyung is
a police officer of great dedication,
who always puts the safety
of his team members and civilians first."
Come on, stop reading that. Jeez.
Give it here. It's just that I'm touched.
You're doing this on purpose, right?
Stop messing with me.
I'm just thankful, that's all.
I didn't get disciplinary action
thanks to you.
How did you manage to get over 100 people
to sign on such short notice?
It wasn't me.
It was the boys who did everything.
By the way, you might have
gotten on the bad side of the higher-ups.
Aren't you worried?
I don't care.
-Kim Taekrok!
Thanks to Taekrok,
we're all safe again today. All of us BST!
Didn't you say the name was corny?
When did I say that?
How about we all go for a drink tonight?
-Yes.
-Sounds good.
All right, let's go.
Barbecue on me. Prime beef.
-Choi Dohyung!
-BST!
SEOUL METROPOLITAN POLICE AGENCY
CONSTITUTIONAL ORDER, LOYAL SERVICE
I URGE YOU TO CANCEL THE SUSPENSION
PETITIONER: KIM TAEKROK
Excuse us.
-Is Detective Lee Seonga here?
-Who are you?
-Is Detective Lee Seonga not here?
-What is this about?
Seonga, someone's here for you.
I'm Lee Seonga.
We're from the provincial police agency.
You're going to have to come with us.
For what?
We're investigating
the murder of Woo Jangik
and Team Leader Han Giyong's suicide.
-Who are you people?
-What am I being investigated for?
There's proof that you had been
following Team Leader Han Giyong
at the time of his disappearance.
-Still, this is too sudden.
-This isn't right.
You should follow protocol.
-You know that.
-What are you doing?
Cooperate.
As of today,
Homicide Team One is disbanded.
Chief, what do you mean...
Be quiet!
Detective Lee will be investigated
following protocol.
But Chief--
Also,
you'll be appointed to another department,
Detective Son Gyeongchan.
That is all.
Chief Baek,
you can't just disband a team like that.
-Please…
-Listen carefully.
Choi Dohyung will be
going after you with full force.
We knew this would happen.
What on earth are you doing?
You've been ordered to stop
all internal investigations.
I told you to return to headquarters
as soon as you recover.
Detective Kim Taekrok told me
that I should have taken on
the responsibility myself.
You stop here…
and go back to your post.
I can't do that.
That is what your father
would want for you.
What I want…
is to prove that my father
didn't die from a car accident,
but that he was murdered
by the Geumjeong Society.
POLLING BOOTH
BALLOT BOX
With turnout for the
local election at 18 percent as of noon,
it already seems quite certain
that Candidate Kim Jinsun
will win the election.
Director Choi Dohyung
voted alongside Candidate Kim Jinsun
and urged citizens
to actively vote for the community.
Meanwhile, the campaign headquarters
of the Future Freedom Party
and the Upright Country Party
seem to be at odds with each other
while citizens continue
to visit voting booths...
-Taekrok.
-...to cast their precious votes.
OCTOBER 2003
You jerks. Do you take me for a joke?
If I tell you to do something, you do it.
You don't get any say in it!
The operation getting canceled
doesn't make any sense.
It's been postponed, not canceled.
If we miss our chance today,
we won't catch that drug ring.
Are you under pressure
from the prosecution again?
What did you say?
Cops aren't lackeys to the prosecutors!
You asshole. Who the hell
do you think you're talking to?
This is the shitty reality
Korea's police officers have to face.
Powerless against those above and below.
What do we do now?
How did it go?
What if they catch onto us and run?
Tonight,
we'll give them a quick raid
with just a few of us BST guys.
That's right.
What are they gonna do if we catch them?
Let them go?
You're right. Let's go.
Yes, let's go.
-Jinseok.
-Yes?
-Make sure Dohyung doesn't use his gun.
-Okay.
What did you just say?
We're out here without approval.
If you want to get punished
and have me as your boss,
then be my guest and shoot away.
You brat. Stop talking nonsense.
That's my head…
Over there, they're coming.
-Get ready.
-Hey, get ready.
Go in.
You bastards!
That bastard…
What the hell? I told you not to use it!
-Step aside!
-You punk.
-Stop.
-Let go, damn it!
Step aside!
Fuck!
Hey!
I'll go around!
I heard from an old colleague
that Kim Taekrok came to see him.
It seems like
he's visiting old BST members.
I'll look into that.
The party welcome assembly is in two days.
Make sure you take care of it quietly.
Yes, sir.
Who are you? I don't recognize your face.
My name is Yeon Juhyun.
Here, hold onto this.
Taekrok will be in touch.
Where's Taekrok right now?
He didn't tell me.
He's worried about you a lot.
What happened to Detective Lee?
Are they still investigating her?
I can't get in touch with her
and I can't look into it.
It's driving me insane.
I know how you feel.
For now, let's trust Taekrok and wait.
Didn't Kim Taekrok tell you?
I have nothing more to add.
You should leave.
I'm going to ask you something else.
Back in 2005,
while conducting
a joint investigation with Chief Baek,
a detective at the Inspection Department
died in an accident.
What does that have to do with me?
That detective…
was in pursuit of the Geumjeong Society.
Why did you kill him?
I stopped by on the way
to Candidate Kim's campaign headquarters.
I heard you weren't coming today.
I didn't want to get in the way
when today isn't about me.
How thoughtful of you.
Oh, right.
Did you get a chance to look over
the policy proposal I sent you?
Ah.
You mean,
the bill to strengthen the police force?
Yes, I read it but…
Perhaps you approached the matter
a bit seriously…
It's a bit radical too.
Also, we're in no rush.
Sir.
I know well enough
why the party recruited me.
My recognition, reputation, and image
are all things you need.
But I want to discuss
what the people want from me.
-If the party doesn't support that--
-In due time.
Let's trim the edges and ease up a little.
They say they have to amputate
Jinseok's leg.
My goodness.
Why did you stop me?
I could have shot him.
Why did you stop me? Tell me!
-You punk!
-Calm down, sir!
I'm sorry about earlier.
I would have stopped me if I were you.
But is this right?
We have to walk on eggshells
with the higher-ups
to catch scumbags like that.
We can't even use guns properly
at the scene.
Is this right?
Seonga.
Hey.
Those bastards
kept you in there for hours.
Has Taekrok reached out to you?
Please answer the phone.
Hello?
Mr. Cha.
Assemblyman Lee Youngho
would like to see you.
You remember this thing
you used to say all the time?
In order to protect ourselves,
we should help each other.
Taekrok, let's just pull out.
Whether it's his mom's 60th birthday
or 70th, Park Chunkyu won't be coming.
All right?
It's been a week since you ate or slept.
You'll die keeping this up.
Yeah?
Okay, all right.
Squad Chief Choi
has Park Chunkyu's location.
-Is this it?
-Yes!
We got him
just before he was about to run.
You fucking asshole.
How dare you, you scumbag?
You son of a bitch!
Get him up.
Hold him.
-Hey, what's going on?
-You goddamn scumbag.
What do you think you're doing?
Let go of me!
I got it, so let me go!
Why did you stop me?
BST took a hit,
so we have to pay him back.
Taekrok, you're the one who said
we should help each other.
-Isn't it?
-All right. Let go.
-God damn it, let go!
-Taekrok.
Isn't this why you made the BST?
All right, let go.
We caught Park Chunkyu.
That's good.
They say they won't pay for it
saying it's all my fault.
Don't worry about the hospital bill.
BST will take care of it.
And after that?
How do I make a living?
My mom's surgery?
And who'll pay for my sister's tuition?
Fuck, I should have just…
I should have just died.
Then my family would get compensated.
What the fuck is this?
What am I going to do?
Bye. See you at the station.
Why did you do it?
You just stood there and watched.
Are you talking about Park Chunkyu?
How could you say that
after seeing Jinseok like that?
You should have stopped them.
Me?
Why?
What?
Isn't the BST about protecting each other?
Taekrok.
We're going to have
a lot more power from now on.
With that power,
we can do a lot of things.
That's what we wanted.
No.
This isn't what I want.
SPEECH
EVERYONE, PLEASE REMEMBER.
THE POLICE NEED TO BE STRONGER…
We've been waiting at the location
you mentioned yesterday.
But he still hasn't shown up.
Keep looking out for him.
We can't lose him.
Why don't you step out
for a moment, Attorney Choi?
Yes, sir.
You don't look so well.
You must have more worries
than you expected.
I'll get straight to the point.
Secretary Cha.
I'm going to get out.
To Choi Dohyung, you are simply a tool.
Yes, I know.
I know what you're thinking.
Things will be harder for me
even if I do get out.
But, Secretary Cha…
you can achieve what I couldn't.
You have to do it yourself.
Me?
All I want is to destroy Choi Dohyung.
What…
do you need me to do?
Someone asked me…
an amusing question yesterday.
LECTURE HALL
A NATIONAL HERO! WE WELCOME CHOI DOHYUNG
TO THE UPRIGHT COUNTRY PARTY.
The PR Department
has prepared some questions.
What made you decide
to start a career in politics?
As you may know,
I was a police officer almost all my life.
And during my service,
I witnessed countless innocent civilians
and police officers get killed or hurt.
I thought somebody
would have to change it.
Number 2938. That's the car, right?
Kim Taekrok showed up.
Get him.
And why does that somebody
have to be you, Mr. Choi?
Not only did you disregard orders
and make a private organization,
but is it true you also assaulted
the criminal due to personal feelings?
Who took the lead in this?
-Who's responsible for this?
-It's me.
Creating a private organization,
going on an unauthorized operation,
and assaulting Park Chunkyu.
I took the lead in everything.
DISCIPLINARY COMMITTEE
I'll take responsibility for everything.
The committee has
decided on the following.
Sergeant Kim Taekrok. Three-month
suspension and demotion of one rank.
Superintendent Choi Dohyung,
three-month pay cut.
COLLECTIVE EFFORT FOR SECURITY
PEACEFUL SOCIETY
Are you really going to
return to Geumo like this?
-It's for the best.
-No, it isn't.
You're simply running away.
Fine
That could be it.
Because I don't run away.
I'm the kind that knows
how to take responsibility.
It looks like
all preparations are ready.
I'm surprised
you don't seem nervous at all.
Do I seem that way?
Yes. It's as if you've always been here
from the beginning.
This is something
I've dreamed of for a long time.
Starting tomorrow, it won't be
a dream anymore, but a reality.
And a year later,
you'll be an assemblyman yourself.
Yes.
As it should be.
Drop your weapons.
We'll see you tomorrow, then.
Please don't worry about tomorrow
and have a good night's sleep.
I will. Thank you.
Goodbye then.
-What?
-I think we've been tricked.
Some of the boys have been captured.
What are you talking about?
BE SAFE
TODAY TOO!
BE SAFE TODAY TOO! FROM AN OLD FRIEND
OLD FRIEND
Why did you tell the higher-ups about BST?
Did you have to?
You were the one who made it,
so why did you end it like that?
I shouldn't have formed BST
in the first place.
I started something
I couldn't take responsibility for.
COLLECTIVE EFFORT FOR SECURITY
PEACEFUL SOCIETY
YOUNGSEO WELFARE FOUNDATION
In a shocking turn of events,
a group of men caught yesterday
for armed robbery with illegal weapons
turned out to be former police officers.
Police say they will investigate the case,
saying they found evidence
of their involvement
in the death of a homicide detective
at Geumo Police Station a few days ago.
It seems that the guys who were caught
yesterday gave up info about the hideout.
We should have been careful.
Tell the others not to step foot
in Geumo for the time being.
Yes, sir.
But the Youngseo Provincial Agency
summoned Chief Baek for an investigation.
Don't worry about that.
Chief Prosecutor Won Jaegu will take
care of it before things get out of hand.
Yes, sir. Understood.
What has the police shown us so far?
You keep protecting your own,
and there are allegations everywhere!
We'll be investigating
the evidence being tampered with
alongside the Lee Youngho case.
So, with that in mind,
hand over Chief Baek to us.
Now, hang up!
What is all this?
NO CALLER ID
Did you get them?
Are you…
Kim Taekrok?
They'll be looking at the same photos
at the Inspection Division
of the Supreme Prosecutor's Office.
What?
Do you know who I am?
How dare you threaten me?
Choi Dohyung,
whom you left Lee Youngho for,
will crash and burn today.
Make the right decision.
PROSECUTION SERVICE
All right. Let's get back on track.
What do you mean?
Wasn't I being sent
to the Prosecutor's Office?
I'm not sure what happened exactly,
but the Chief Prosecutor backed out.
I guess you were trying to
cut a deal with them.
Give up on that and cooperate.
You're the one who should be careful.
I've seen plenty of guys like you get
stabbed in the back for trusting people.
You saw the news, right?
Yes, I did.
The issue with the police
broke out just in time.
The party sees this as a good opportunity.
Why don't you announce
that you'll uncover the truth of this case
at the welcome ceremony today?
It aligns with your cause
and people will pay attention.
I'm not sure.
Not much has been revealed yet.
Isn't it too early to say that?
The party chair actually wants you
to lead the special investigation team.
He really expects much from you.
An investigation team?
Yes.
The detective who uncovered
the Geumo redevelopment scandal last year
happened to come by and suggested it.
The party chair really liked the idea.
That detective agreed to be part
of the investigation team too.
That detective…
Detective Kim Taekrok.
I heard you knew each other well.
You'll have no problems working together.
It will really make the perfect picture.
Like a hero appearing
in the midst of chaos.
Ah.
-You have a guest, ma'am.
-Oh.
Let me excuse myself for a bit.
CANDIDATE 2 KIM JINSUN
CHIEF PROSECUTOR WON JAEGU
NO CALLER ID
Kim Taekrok.
Are you trying to play games with me?
What's next?
You're the one who started this game.
I'm just trying to end it.
You're just as I expected, Kim Taekrok.
I was right.
I knew that if I had Kook Jinhan
give you a lead, you'd go after him.
Even when I arrested Chairman Jang,
his associates didn't get revealed.
At that time,
Assemblyman Lee Youngho of this region
was the only one who faced charges.
What if 0121 represents
Assemblyman Lee Youngho?
That means large-scale acts of corruption
in the political and business realms
are taking place right here in Geumo.
I knew that if I gave you
the hint and provoked you,
you'd take care of it on your own.
So don't tell me what to do, you scumbag!
What are your orders?
In the name of Geumjeong Society,
we must eliminate him.
Do I kill both Kook Jinhan
and Kim Taekrok?
Just Kook Jinhan.
That's it?
That's why you let me live?
Yes.
You ought to be grateful
that I even let you live.
Now it's too late. You crossed the line.
Yes.
I'm going to cross that line
and go all the way.
I'm going to catch you no matter what.
SHADOW DETECTIVE SEASON 2
Modify by Blue-Bird™