Detective Kim.
You've come all the way to the end.
Is it though?
Stop doubting everything.
But, Detective Kim...
what's left after all this?
An old cop full of regrets and pain.
I'm just an old cop...
full of regrets and pain now.
Hyeonseok!
Taekrok...
Hey, you...
-I'm sorry.
-Yeongdu!
Yeongdu!
Seonga!
Jinseok!
Yeon Juhyun!
Are you all right?
Do you think all the choices you made...
were the right ones?
Back then,
I didn't have a choice.
Jiu!
Dad!
When did everything start to go wrong?
I only wanted to live a normal life.
I shouldn't have become a cop
in the first place.
That's when it all began.
SHADOW DETECTIVE SEASON 2
Here.
The bloodstains found
in the Geumjeong Society's car
were found to be from Team Leader Han.
Also, a fisherman spotted the car
close to where
Team Leader Han's body was found.
There is circumstantial evidence
that it was deleted
on Chief Baek's orders.
The Youngseo Provincial Police
summoned Chief Baek because of it.
They can't hold him for long
with only circumstantial evidence.
Choi Dohyung wouldn't let Chief Baek
just stay there.
What about Director Kwon?
Gyeongchan's digging into the guys
who got caught yesterday,
so we should have something soon.
At seven o'clock tonight,
once his initiation ceremony is over,
Dohyung will have political authority.
We'll stop them somehow.
Yes, go ahead.
I checked
their recent financial transactions
and they sent bundles of cash
a few times to one car rental company.
So I looked into it.
They operate illegal taxis
throughout the Gangnam area
and secretly sell cars
with fake registrations too.
Who's the owner?
I'll send you his information right now.
Why aren't you eating?
Why did you ask to see me again?
Last time,
you said you didn't know anything.
You know, you're at fault too.
You should have told me
that it was about your father.
I see you did a background check on me.
I'm also a father to a daughter.
It truly is unfortunate.
Just...
Just get to the point, please.
It's simple.
The man who killed your father.
I can help you catch him.
But you have to do one thing for me.
What do you want?
The man who did this to me.
All you have to do is take him down too.
Choi Dohyung.
The leader of the Geumjeong Society
is Choi Dohyung.
Hey. Where is it?
The second floor.
Hello.
-We're with Geumo Police.
-What?
Taekrok.
You're the one who said
we should help each other.
It's been a while.
Yes?
I sent you
the information you asked for.
Why do you need a disciplinary report
from 20 years ago?
There's something I have to check.
DISCIPLINARY REPORT
NAME: KIM TAEKROK
Team Leader Yeon,
I told you to stop looking into...
HE IS SUSPENDED FOR 3 MONTHS
AND DEMOTED BY ONE RANK.
HE FORMED AN ILLEGAL PRIVATE ORGANIZATION
WITHIN THE SPECIAL INVESTIGATION UNIT...
The only one who's made it out alive
from all this chaos.
Kim Taekrok and Choi Dohyung.
There's definitely
something between the two.
That explains why he killed Kook Jinhan,
but kept Kim Taekrok alive.
The ones who won't be swayed
and will catch Choi Dohyung
are just me and you.
At least the two of us
share the same goal.
ILLEGAL PRIVATE ORGANIZATION (A.K.A BST)
LIST OF CARS
Look, I only did what they asked me to do.
All these fake registration vehicles,
illegal cars, and loans.
Director Kwon managed all of them.
All I did was send money
to the merchants' association
when he told me to.
If I give you this,
you'll let me go, right?
All I did was trust Dohyung
and do whatever he told me to do.
Use this list of cars
and catch Director Kwon with the police.
-Yes, sir.
-Also...
Take him to the station.
Taekrok.
Let's go.
2023 YOUNGSEO WELFARE FOUNDATION
DONATION RECORDS
Director Kwon got the funds,
then the money was laundered
through business transactions.
Then it was donated to the foundation.
Choi Dohyung used this money
to operate the Geumjeong Society.
FRESH MEAT RESTAURANT
HWANG JINSEOK
Records of Choi Dohyung's corruption.
There should be something else
before this.
Did you talk to the director
of the inspection department?
Yes. Once I have the evidence,
the agency will be on it.
This was taken
near the scene of the accident
as Detective Yeon Sanghoon was dying.
The man who killed my father...
was Chief Baek?
Yes.
I believe
a witness at the time stated that...
the vehicle was black.
Choi Dohyung must've taken care of it.
You'll find the details of the witness
who was bribed inside as well.
This should be enough evidence
to get a reinvestigation started.
The chief of the inspection department
is on the move again.
Rumor is there's going to be
an extensive internal investigation
starting with Yeon Sanghoon's death.
Who started this?
As far as I know,
it's Detective Yeon Juhyun.
What brings you here, Team Leader Yeon?
Was it really you?
Did you...
kill him?
Are you the one who killed...
Detective Yeon Sanghoon?
Yeon Sanghoon? Who's that?
And why would you say I killed him?
December 22, 2005.
You killed Detective Yeon Sanghoon
by performing a hit-and-run with a car.
You even bribed the witness
to tamper with the case.
Is that right?
I don't know
what on earth you're talking about.
Why would I do such a thing?
So why did you do such a thing?
Why did you do it?
Why did you kill him?
Did Detective Yeon Sanghoon too persistent
in chasing the Geumjeong Society?
And what's a Geumjeong Society?
You must have been very close to him,
seeing you're acting this way.
But I don't know him.
You might not know his name,
but you'll remember his face.
And this is a picture that was taken
near the scene of the accident.
That's your face, right?
I'm not sure.
I don't understand
why on earth you're being like this
with some old pictures.
So they're just old pictures to you.
The inspection department
will take this case up to headquarters.
I'll see you there.
Did you check the pictures I sent?
Yes. What are these?
It's evidence
of how Choi Dohyung funded his crimes.
Go investigate the businesses on the list.
And make it quick.
All right.
By the way, is it really true?
What is?
I heard the real culprit
of Yeon Sanghoon's murder was found.
And Chief Baek is the suspect.
Lee Youngho is the only one
who would give
that kind of evidence to Yeon Juhyun.
That old fox.
I heard from the attorney
and it seems like
Chief Baek is very anxious.
If he decides to act out to save himself
or says something by mistake...
The initiation ceremony is today.
We have to stop him no matter what.
Won Jaegu, how dare you betray me?
Is Judge Kim
the one in charge of warrants?
Yes.
Neither Kim Taekrok nor Lee Youngho
will stop here.
The Geumjeong Society cannot suffer
any more losses.
There needs to be a sacrifice.
LIEUTENANT KIM TAEKROK
Yes.
Okay. I have something to discuss anyway.
I checked the car owners,
but they weren't connected to Geumjeong.
Another dead-end.
-How many cars do we have left?
-More than half.
-Think we'll catch him within the day?
-We have to.
After the initiation ceremony,
Choi Dohyung will have gained authority.
If we catch Director Kwon then,
he'll slip away.
Then everyone will be in danger.
Including us and Taekrok.
Let's do whatever we can.
Okay. Let's do it.
Where did you get the evidence
that it was Chief Baek?
I got it from Lee Youngho.
What?
Why on earth...
When did you find out Choi Dohyung
was the leader of the Geumjeong Society?
Did you come to hesitate
when you found out...
that it was Choi Dohyung?
No.
Choi Dohyung seems to think so.
Last year, and then at the safe house.
He didn't kill you.
Team Leader Yeon.
Also, when did you find out...
that the BST you two made together...
was related to the Geumjeong Society?
Okay.
I understand you resent me for it.
Do not judge how I would feel.
If I had dissolved BST back then,
Geumjeong Society simply wouldn't be.
If I had done that,
your father wouldn't have died
at the hands of the Geumjeong Society.
I'm sorry, Team Leader Yeon.
There's no need to apologize.
I don't hold any grudges against you.
What angers me is that...
you're involved in this investigation.
Okay.
Anyway, you can't work with Lee Youngho.
He's only taking advantage of you.
You have no right...
to give me such advice.
You have no right.
The Upright Country Party and Kim Jinsun,
the Youngseo governor-elect,
have expressed their willingness to set up
a special investigation team
under the leadership
of Director Choi Dohyung
to thoroughly investigate
the current corruption scandal.
The investigation team is composed
of highly reliable professionals,
including incumbent detectives
and Director Choi Dohyung,
who has recently joined our party.
The specific plan of action
will be announced at 7 p.m.
during Director Choi Dohyung's
initiation ceremony.
Director Choi said he will announce...
You said that Chief Baek's arrest warrant
was rejected?
Yes, sir.
I didn't know
he'd take care of it so quickly...
Choi Dohyung is playing
every single one of us.
And where the hell is Secretary Cha?
I can't get a hold of him.
I'll look into it.
GEUMO CORRUPTION SCANDAL
INVESTIGATION TEAM SET UP...
Choi Dohyung, that scumbag.
Yes.
It must have been tough.
No, sir. Thanks to you, I'm over the hump.
But what will our next move be?
We'll talk about that in person.
Yes, sir.
Did you find it?
Here!
Right. It's 9221 from the list.
Good job, kid.
Yes, that's the guy. Okay.
I found it. It's me who did it. I did...
-Yes, Mr. Gu.
-Hey, we found it.
He just made a right on the intersection
at Geumo University of Education.
Okay. The intersection
at the University of Education.
Okay.
Yes?
Where are you?
Did you know Chief Baek was released?
All right, I'll look into it.
It was just recorded,
-so he should be in the area.
-Okay. Let's go that way.
Sure.
NO TRESPASSING
KEEP OUT
You look concerned.
Are you worried that I might abandon you?
Ah.
Of course not.
Thank you for handling the matter
so quickly.
Come have a drink.
Yes, sir.
It's been a while
since we had a drink just the two of us.
Yes, sir. It has.
I've come this far all thanks to you.
Now, our heyday,
the age of the police is finally arriving.
I will continue to do my best
until the end.
You've served your purpose
more than enough.
Where is Chief Baek right now?
There's a mountain cabin
owned by the Geumjeong Society.
He must have gone there.
I'll text you the exact location.
You and I.
We're no more than dogs to them.
But...
do we...
...have to live like this?
Scumbag.
Please understand.
This way,
we'll be able to cover everything up.
Just how many cops have you killed so far?
And you still say
what you're doing is for the police?
I shouldn't have trusted you
as he warned me.
It seems Kim Taekrok...
saw right through you.
Shit.
He sent Yeon Juhyun the location.
I'm also on my way.
Okay.
THE ADDRESS IS 47, SUAM-RO,
PANBONG-EUP, GEUMO-SI
-Hey.
-Taekrok.
Secretary Cha is dead.
And he sent an address
to Team Leader Yeon.
LIEUTENANT KIM TAEKROK
The person you are calling...
Put down your gun.
Your father's murderer
lies dead before you.
How does it feel?
Was it you?
The one...
who made the order to kill my father.
Choi Dohyung...
...was it you?
Why?
Why did you kill him?
Why did you kill so many police officers,
so many of your colleagues...
...and my father?
You can ask your father yourself.
Don't resent me for this.
It's nothing personal.
Choi Dohyung!
You relentless punk.
Stop.
Fine.
Shoot me.
Can you do it?
Do you still not understand?
It's the useless sense of justice of yours
that made you the pathetic mess you are.
You live alone
in that petty little studio of yours,
and you can't live
without those psychotic pills.
You've always been like that.
A weak-minded cop
trapped inside the trauma
that he brought upon himself!
Dad!
Let's stop this.
No!
No. No!
Detective Kim!
Please.
Please!
No, please!
You scumbags!
Now, this makes a better picture.
A detective kills the leader of BST
to avenge her father and commits suicide.
I will arrange it that way.
It's time for you to go, sir.
Okay.
Wrap things up.
You're up.
What were you dreaming about?
Did I say something?
You said you weren't wrong this time.
What are you going to do when you retire?
Retire?
Is that too far into the future?
10 years will fly by in no time.
Is there anything you want to do?
There's something I don't want to do.
Running like hell.
If I retire...
I'm never running again.
Chasing people.
Or being chased.
Right, there's nothing
as exhausting as that.
But, Taekrok.
Now's not the time.
You still have to run around
like your heart will burst.
Promise me that you will.
Well then, I'll get going now.
Hyeonseok.
I'll see you again.
Tomorrow's too soon,
and 30 years would be too late.
At a reasonable time.
See you, Taekrok.
We will now begin the initiation ceremony
of Director Choi Dohyung
of the Youngseo Welfare Foundation.
Please give a big hand for Director Choi!
A NATIONAL HERO! WE WELCOME CHOI DOHYUNG
TO THE UPRIGHT COUNTRY PARTY.
UPRIGHT COUNTRY PARTY
Thank you, everyone,
for taking the time to come here today.
Especially the reporters
who are here today,
I thank you in advance
for the favorable articles.
Today, it feels like
I'm back on my first day on the job
as a police officer donning my uniform.
Up until now, you've given me
the undeserved title of a hero
and sent a lot of love and support my way.
To be honest,
I've been ashamed of myself
for not being able to change anything
as I watched Korea
become blighted with crime.
We need to strengthen our police force,
so they can catch criminals
without concern.
That way, they can focus
on the safety of our citizens.
Please remember this.
Only a strong police force
can protect innocent citizens.
Now, I begin anew as a politician.
I will become the Choi Dohyung
who will meet your expectations
with clean and transparent politics.
Just like the first promise I made
the day I became a police officer,
I, alongside the Upright Country Party,
vow to protect the safety of Korea
and the peaceful daily lives
of the people...
Choi Dohyung!
You...
are under arrest for murder!
It's a pistol!
Superintendent Woo Hyeonseok!
Lieutenant Bae Yeongdu!
Superintendent Kook Jinhan!
Those are
the names of the officers you killed.
Detective Kim Taekrok.
What is the meaning of this?
Will you take responsibility
for your current actions?
It's all over, you bastard.
Over here. This way.
Come this way.
Thanks to
the tenacious efforts of a detective,
a massive crime cartel has been revealed,
involving political and business circles,
as well as the police and prosecution.
POLICE
The accusations
raised at the initiation ceremony
are being revealed one by one.
Many are in shock as it was revealed
that the armed force
made up of former police officers
was identified as the Geumjeong Society
led by Choi Dohyung.
Former Assemblyman Lee Youngho
is making the case
that he only committed the crimes
because he was threatened by Choi Dohyung.
But with new evidence
through additional investigation,
it seems that he will be facing
heavy punishment.
Youngseo District Court also issued
a search and seizure warrant
on the Youngseo Welfare Foundation
for a thorough investigation
of the accusations aimed at Choi Dohyung.
The Upright Country Party stated
they are aware
of the public's view on the matter
and will actively cooperate
with the investigations.
YEON SANGHOON
KIM TAEKROK
Where are you off to?
You won't tell me where you're going?
We're family.
NOEUL GOSIWON
Yang Gitae.
Go see your mother.
You're done with your retrial.
All right.
Live your life to its fullest.
Detec...
Taekrok!
You'll come back, right?
Did you come to see me in these?
Have I told you before?
The toughest but happiest time
in my entire police career
was my days
in the Mobile Investigation Unit.
Back then, we had no idea
we'd end up like this.
What are you hoping to hear from me?
Do you want me to beg for forgiveness?
No, you don't have to do that to me.
All I did was catch a criminal.
Because that's what I do.
For over 30 years,
I thought
that I didn't belong in this uniform.
But at this point,
these are all I have left.
I'll get going.
Kim Taekrok.
Do you think this is the end of me?
You'll come to regret this.
Eat well.
And live well.
SUPERINTENDENT WOO HYEONSEOK
MAY YOUR SOUL REST IN PEACE
TAEKROK
6 MONTHS LATER
-Hey.
-I don't want to.
You're going to regret this!
I didn't even say hello!
Will you be quiet inside the station?
Gosh, this is aggravating! What?
-Pipe down.
-Quit it, will you?
-Sit here.
-Okay, here.
-I'll sit down myself.
-You'll regret this!
-Where's your team leader?
-Hey, now!
-Dongbum!
-Mr. Gong!
What are you doing here?
-There's been a mistake...
-Bring me your team leader.
-Where is he?
-Settle down and tell me your names.
Hey, kid. Don't you know who I am?
And who could you be?
Goodness. Your team leader lives
in Geumo Apartment, right?
Yes. And?
Kid! I went to the sauna
with your team leader!
How could you go to the sauna...
-That's not right.
-Yes, I know that.
-Hey.
-Dongbum, you can't be lying.
Alongside your team leader,
I put the Geumjeong Society behind bars!
And put Choi Dohyung behind bars too.
I did that, man!
He did do all that.
Stop with the nonsense.
Just sit down and...
Hey, she's here. Seonga's here.
-Dongbum!
-Hello.
This is the Team Leader
of Homicide Team One, Lee Seonga.
You scared me.
Team Leader Lee. Look.
Isn't this too harsh?
We received a tip-off
for illegal wiretapping,
so we brought them in.
He's saying it's illegal, Seonga!
No, I can't let this one slide.
Hey, I helped you guys
and Taek the Dog so much.
How could you do this to me?
-Where's Son Gyeongchan?
-Dongbum!
Mr. Gu, hello.
What's going on?
He's a sergeant now.
Sergeant Son Gyeongchan. He was promoted.
You little... Then what about you?
I transferred to Homicide. Impressed?
You should be trying to talk things out
instead of yapping like that.
It's embarrassing. This is why
I didn't want to work with you!
You said you'd help your mom's business
once the retrial was over.
What are you doing
at an illegal mercantile agency?
-What did you say?
-Dongbum, you're making things worse!
-Hey!
-Come on, hands off!
Fine. It's Trust Planning,
not a mercantile agency.
-That's right.
-Mr. Gu!
Just close up shop, all right?
Then I'll take the help you gave us
into consideration and be lenient.
-Hey, come on.
-Huh?
Dongbum! The manager position
at the studio is vacant.
I'll write a recommendation letter.
That would solve things!
You do that!
Get back here!
POLICE
JIU, I GOT THE POSTCARD YOU SENT ME.
MAY 2, 2024
WITH LOVE, DAD
KIM TAEKROK
KIM JIU
OLD Chief Constable!
There's trouble at the village
foreman's house. Come quick.
SHADOW DETECTIVE SEASON 2
Modify by Blue-Bird™