I didn't know
that there were other situations
besides police work that require running.
That there were other things to catch
besides criminals.
YOUNGSEO HEAVY EQUIPMENT SCHOOL
FORKLIFT, CRANE, EXCAVATOR
The breakdown is 25 points
for clearing the course
and 75 points for excavating.
Mr. Kim Taekrok.
If Mr. Kim Taekrok isn't here,
we'll move on.
- Mr. Kim Taekrok...
- Yes!
Sign here, please.
KIM TAEK
GRADE AND RESULTS
FAIL
Wasn't this your... third try?
TECHNICAL SKILLS QUALIFICATION EXAM
FAIL
The third time's the charm.
If you still didn't, you won't ever.
This is why I told you
to prepare for reinstatement.
Hey, that hurts.
Darn it.
Just go and unclog the drain.
You're the manager. Go and act like one.
Fine. It always gets clogged.
Can you use an excavator to unclog...
NOEUL GOSIWON
RECIPIENT KIM TAEKROK, VITAMIN
LEE YOUNGHO
THE FUTURE FREEDOM PARTY
...Candidate Lee Youngho!
Even when I arrested Chairman Jang,
his associates didn't get revealed.
Assemblyman Lee Youngho of this region
was the only one who faced charges.
That means large-scale acts of corruption
in the political and business realms
are taking place right here in Geumo.
...it seems.
There has been an accident
in the Geumo Inner Beltway...
GEUMO POLICE WILL CHANGE FOR THE BETTER
SHADOW DETECTIVE SEASON 2
This is awful.
How can I go about living like this?
We'll make sure to catch the thief.
For now, come this way.
Take the victim to the station, please.
How could this happen?
You think they're the same ones
from the last case?
Yeah.
They didn't even try to open the safe
and just took whatever they could find.
They're bold, but it doesn't seem
like they're professionals.
Judging by the footprint,
it should be around 230 to 240 mm.
Could they be women?
Or they could be kids.
Or both.
If they really are minors,
should we call Women and Juvenile Affairs?
Let's do a bit more digging.
This was filed with us, after all.
Okay.
Jeez. This has been
going on for over a year now.
The town's getting depressed.
Taekrok should be there
when we get back, right?
Probably.
It's already been a year and a half.
By the way, Detective Han...
"Team Leader Han."
All right. "Team Leader Han."
Look at him.
It doesn't make sense.
He definitely smells fishy
but doesn't get investigated.
He even buttered up the new chief
and got himself a promotion.
On the other hand,
Taekrok was pressured to go on leave.
Does that make sense to you?
Let's just think of it
as him taking a break.
But still.
He was studying how to operate excavators.
That didn't feel right to me.
He should be on the scene
as a homicide detective.
- Women and Juvenile Affairs?
-Yes.
You'll be joining the Women
and Juvenile Affairs Investigation Team.
BAEK SEONGIL
Are you surprised?
Yes, well...
It's not like I have a say in the matter.
I've read your employment history,
and it seems you've been through a lot
in the Homicide and
Special Crimes Investigation Unit.
You should end your career
more comfortably.
I mean, Women and Juvenile Affairs
could be difficult in other ways.
But at least you won't be
getting stabbed or shot at.
Well, sounds good.
And it should be good
for performance evaluations,
so it might help you get promoted.
You should at least be a captain
before you retire.
It would make your juniors
and I feel at ease.
Is that the only reason?
Should there be other reasons?
Right.
Detective Kim.
Sincere congratulations on your return.
AFTER GEUMO'S CORRUPTION SCANDAL...
REDEVELOPMENT REMAINS A PROBLEM
What do you mean
there's no vacancy for Taekrok?
I know. I was shocked too.
But it's not like I can go to HR
and cause a scene.
We're losing a team member
since we're powerless.
WOMEN AND JUVENILE AFFAIRS
INVESTIGATION TEAM
We really didn't take her money!
Why don't you believe us?
Lying isn't going to help you.
Are you a parent?
Where's your team leader?
- I'm sorry.
-All right. Now, get out of here.
She's not here at the moment.
- Taekrok!
- Lieutenant Ham. Look at you.
I'm having a baby.
The team leader is on a business trip,
so you'll see her tomorrow.
Do you know her?
No, I don't.
I guess it's because she was assigned
while you were on leave.
She's from the police academy
and is pretty good.
Follow me.
This will be your desk for now,
and once I go on maternity leave,
you'll have all this space to yourself.
About our team leader.
You remember the mass assault case
of a mentally handicapped high school
student in Seoul five years ago?
She dug into the case for over three years
until the perpetrators became adults.
Apparently, she even received
death threats from the parents.
But she didn't stop, and in the end,
they all got prison sentences.
She's super tenacious.
But...
But what? What's wrong?
I'm worried that
you two might not get along.
She's the exact opposite of you.
She hates breaking rules and procedures.
I hate that too!
Oh...
Looks like you've gotten
quite shameless with age.
But how did you end up here?
This is quite a huge leap from Homicide.
Things are completely different here.
- Different how?
- You need more brain than brawn,
more heart than muscle.
That's what you'll need the most.
Just make it simple.
So...
- She means you have to hold it in.
- My gosh.
To put it simply,
you've got to have a "service mentality."
Gosh, you know this well.
But who...
Hello.
I'm new here to the Women
and Juvenile Affairs Investigation Team.
I'm Officer Gong Haneul!
Oh, you're Taekrok's partner.
-Hey, what...
- He looks reliable. Right, sir?
FOR THE SAFETY AND HAPPINESS OF CITIZENS
Are you going to start smoking again?
That's so harsh. You just got back.
Are you really joining
Women and Juveniles?
Why don't you talk to the chief again?
It's fine. Who cares where I spend...
my last years?
Oh.
That's Detective Choi Dohyung, right?
Yeah, it is.
I heard he was moving
to Geumo after retirement. So it was true.
Uh, the Seoul Investigation Unit...
Or was it the Mobile Investigation Unit
back then?
Weren't you on the same team then?
Really? Were you close?
- Ooh.
- See ya.
He doesn't brag, does he?
He's not like you.
It's weird he doesn't talk
about his time in the MIU.
I think that's all you should know.
- Then, I'll put that in the record.
-Yes.
Let me ask you the next question.
The book that you wrote
about the Eunsan serial murder
was made into a movie,
which was a huge success.
You must be so proud of it.
On the contrary.
- What?
- The fact that the movie was a success
means that a lot of people still live
in fear of violent crimes.
Since I was in the forces myself,
I'm not proud. I'm ashamed.
And that must be why you set up
a welfare foundation
in your hometown of Geumo.
That's very admirable.
- Right.
- Yes.
Admirable, my foot...
Why are you even writing that down?
Don't put any grand reason behind it.
It's only right that I give back the money
I made by selling victims' stories.
I just noticed that
the detective is very shy.
I think you're right.
For goodness' sake.
Go ahead and ask him.
- So this next question is for you, Chief.
- Sure.
Geumo Police
promised to offer full support
for the foundation
Detective Choi Dohyung established.
Tell us about it.
I was deeply impressed
by the detective's noble cause,
but, most of all, it was
to make it up to the citizens
who would have been disappointed
with Geumo Police
regarding recent incidents.
Make sure to write this down
and put it in the article later.
So he won't go back on his words.
All right.
Yes. I'll make sure to write it down.
Goodness, I guess I'm in trouble now.
Hello. Yes, sir. We should go
golfing sometime soon.
I'll make a reservation
at someplace private. Yes.
Take care. Bye.
Hello, Detective Kim.
So how are you adjusting
to Women and Juveniles?
I think it would have been better
if you came to work under me.
I mean, it sounds better
than those kids who don't know anything.
Don't you get tired of living like that?
Excuse me.
Aren't you Detective Choi Dohyung?
You are. My gosh!
It's an honor.
I'm Team Leader Han Giyong,
of Homicide Team One.
I see.
But what brings you here?
Doesn't Detective Kim Taekrok work here?
Yes, but he's been transferred to
the Women and Juvenile Affairs Division.
I ran into him just now.
Do you want me to get him for you?
No, it's all right.
I wanted to see him since I was here.
I'll contact him myself.
Well then...
- Take care, sir.
- Sure.
They know each other?
- Look who's here.
- My.
- Hello.
- It's nicer than I expected.
- Here you go.
You didn't have to bring anything.
You told us to get this one.
Now it looks like you're settled down.
I hope you get a lot of business.
Thanks. Dear, this is nice.
Hey, I heard Taekrok got assigned
to Women and Juveniles.
Didn't he flip out about that?
He was calm about it, surprisingly.
But I don't get why
he's not doing anything.
He's not the Detective Kim I knew.
Look at this kid.
You only worked with Taek the Dog
for a month, so what do you know?
By the way, I've been curious.
Why do you call him Taek the Dog?
I told you before. He's like a dog.
I know that, but why?
Well, we didn't give him that nickname.
It was the mobs. Because he never
lets things go once he bites.
Now, he's old and weak.
But back in the day, once he got mad,
nobody would be unscathed.
That's what I don't get.
I really considered him my role model.
But now he's in Women and Juveniles,
where he clearly doesn't belong.
Don't you think so?
Come on, he deserves a break.
He'll hit 60 soon.
Retirement's right around the corner,
and he's still out in the field.
And I'm just out of words when I see him.
He spent 30 years in the force, get it?
But then after what happened to Jiu,
he got panic anxiety.
Still, he managed to keep himself
going, with meds and a strong will.
So I thought he'd be fine
until retirement.
Then, that entire mess happened last year.
-What do you want?
-To play a game.
What kind of game?
It's very simple.
Look back on your past.
Hyeonseok!
This game will not end
until one of us dies.
No.
No. Hey...
And after all that happened to him,
there's no way he'd be fine,
not even for Taek the Dog.
I mean, I think I'm actually impressed
that he even came back to the force.
- We should get going.
- Why? Let's have some of this together.
We'll be back.
We have places to investigate.
You know, there are a lot of thefts
these days. So take care.
All right, thanks.
You take care of the old man, okay?
Of course. We'll see you.
Bye.
Detective Kim! I mean, Taekrok.
Let's go get some gukbap.
-I'm busy.
- Where are you off to?
To figure out what to do after I retire.
- Excuse me?
- I should find myself a place
and move out of that studio like you did.
But I miss that place.
I'll see you tomorrow, sir!
24-HOUR PATROL AND CCTV
FOR CRIME PREVENTION
You think we'll find anything?
What was that?
It looks like someone went inside.
Stop the car.
Hey, remember what happened yesterday?
Hey, the kid's here.
Hey.
- This is it?
- He said he was being generous.
You sure he wasn't lying?
- You can usually tell right away.
- He wasn't.
Fucking shit.
Should we find new dealers?
What?
Over there.
Should I call for backup?
They're kids. Why would we need backup?
Kids these days are scary. Wait...
You're not the least bit careful.
Looks like there are five or six.
No doubt they're minors.
They must be some sort of
runaway family or something.
What's that?
What the fuck?
Hey kids, that's dangerous. Put that down.
- Who are you?
- We're police.
What are you doing here?
Hana, get ready to run.
Bullshit.
Run!
Hey, you all right?
I told you we should've called backup!
Don't be so dramatic.
Go get them. Come on.
Hey!
Damn it.
Hurry up, dumbass!
Hey, this way.
Fuck.
Split up!
Shit.
I ran a background check on the girl.
What, she's a minor?
So she ran away from home.
Why keep a kid like her
in the interrogation room?
You could've given her a warning
and sent her home.
She's likely involved in the serial theft
that's been going on recently.
Plus she was in a dangerous environment.
Do you know how many people
we have to call here
to investigate a kid for a criminal case?
Parents, social workers...
Just send her home and tell her
to come back tomorrow.
Never mind. Just hand her over
to Women and Juveniles here.
We have a detective right here.
Hand her over to him.
What an ass.
What should we do?
Didn't you hear
what your team leader said?
Send her home.
You should have seen
the situation yourself.
So let's send her home safely.
Why did you run away from home?
What's it to you, lady?
Hana was in a dangerous situation.
Please take good care of her.
All right.
Hey, come on.
Hana.
What?
This is my contact info.
LEE SEONGA, HOMICIDE TEAM 1
GEUMO POLICE STATION
Call me if you need to.
Hey.
I would rather die than get help from you.
Then live a proper life, kid!
It doesn't make sense for you
to quit school to make money.
What on earth will you become?
So you're acting like my dad
after you put him in prison.
Don't you think that's funny?
What else would a criminal's kid become?
I'd probably end up the same way.
Hey, Seonga.
Lee Seonga!
What were you doing there?
I went by a real estate agency.
I'm looking into getting a small apartment
with my retirement pension.
I can't keep living in a studio.
Is that why you didn't see me once
while on leave?
You were busy planning your retirement?
About Hana.
I'm going to keep an eye on her,
so please do the same at Juvenile Affairs.
Why do you care so much?
You don't have to do all that.
So why did you care so much about me?
You saw the cop jump off, right?
-It was just...
- He's a damn lunatic.
I totally freaked out. He jumped...
- Stop playing.
- You're joking.
Hey. The cops didn't follow you, did they?
This isn't some movie.
-Coward.
- Hey, are you all right?
Where is it this time?
Over there next to the church.
You know it, right?
Go in past midnight. Not from the front.
There. Take the alley
and go through the back door.
- Okay.
- I hope they've got good stuff this time.
I have to get a new phone.
The camera broke.
- Me too.
-I want one too.
-Me first.
-What are you talking about?
There are better things to spend money on.
Let me get one this time.
Feeding your face costs twice
as much as everyone else.
Don't be such a pig.
-Am I the only one who eats?
-You eat up everything.
Shit.
Hey, fatso.
Don't point it at the window, dumbass.
- Anything?
- Nothing.
What about you guys?
Nothing.
Shit, this is driving me crazy.
Let's get out of here.
- Leave?
- Hurry up.
What are you doing? Hurry up!
Hey. What are you doing? Let's just go.
Hang on.
Hey.
Who the hell are you?
You fucking bastard.
You piece of shit. Fucking prick.
What are you, bastard?
Let's get out of here.
Woo Jangik, that jerk, had to call me
out here in the middle of the night.
Damn.
Hey, Mr. Kim! Grab that kid.
Get him!
You got transferred to Juvenile Affairs.
How did you know that?
Just because I'm stuck here
doesn't mean I've gone deaf or blind.
How much longer will this go on?
What do you mean?
How long do I have to be
the world's greatest traitor
while you rot away in the background?
The ones who did this to us
are still out there.
Is this all we get
for me turning myself in?
It's been more than a year
since Chairman Jang died.
What have you been doing all this time?
Do I have to do anything?
Let me know if you need anything.
They say the first snow
is coming early this year.
GEUMO DETENTION CENTER
CIVIL AFFAIRS
-Are you not going to tell me?
-It wasn't us.
Like hell it wasn't! You keep
talking back and won't call your parents.
-It wasn't us.
-Stay still. Be quiet!
-You're here.
- Yeah.
- You're here.
- Hey.
They were driving around last night
in a car they stole.
I feel bad since they're kids...
but they're outrageous. What should I do?
What do you mean what should you do?
The good ones always come
to their senses on their own.
And if they don't?
They end up like you.
Ending up like me is a good thing.
Do you think of all crimes like that?
Standing by and watching
rather than educating,
punishment rather than rehabilitation?
Detective Kim, this is our team leader.
Ms. Yeon!
Oh.
This is Detective Kim Taekrok.
I'm Yeon Juhyun.
It's an honor to have someone
so famous on my team.
Famous?
I mean, the Geumo corruption cartel,
a cop killer, and... What's his name?
Chairman Jang?
Although he did kill himself.
Anyway, even the crime broker.
I heard they were all caught,
thanks to you.
Doesn't that make you
the hidden hero of Geumo?
But, Detective Kim.
Whether you're a hero or a villain,
as long as you're working for me,
you can't be late.
If you start breaking
little rules like this,
eventually, you'll go too far.
Yes, well.
I'll keep that in mind.
Then, let's go to your first assignment.
- Come with us.
- Yes, ma'am.
Let's go. Follow me.
School violence!
Let's prevent it!
Let's prevent it.
School violence!
Let's prevent it!
They took my laptop
and anything that was worth a dime.
- Will you be able to catch them?
- Yes, we'll do our best to catch them.
Are these all the security cameras here?
There's more...
...but they've probably been broken
for a while.
So, the security cameras are broken...
Do you know what's upstairs?
I hear a man is running
an investment company or something.
I wonder if they took anything from him.
Goodness.
Hello.
- Who are you?
- We're the police.
There's been a burglary downstairs,
so we came by to check
if you had anything going missing.
No, we're fine.
Sir. Just a second.
Everything's okay, right?
That's what I said.
Let's go.
Okay.
What?
This is Hana's.
The girl we saw yesterday?
Yes.
Then this probably has to do
with those kids from last night.
Yes, I stopped by the office
after I went to the hospital,
and the police came by.
Darn it.
Did those brats start talking?
-Gyeongchan.
- Yeah?
Here's where Hana's phone
was last located.
It was indeed the redevelopment area.
Juvenile Affairs is trying to find
the rest of the kids. What do we do?
- Let's call for backup on our way there.
- Sure. You can go.
Good luck, sir.
He still hasn't talked yet?
Damn it.
It's within 50 meters from here.
Should I wait for backup?
You go that way.
Seonga!
Jeez...
Forget everything else.
Just tell us where the flash drive is.
The one in the safe.
And we'll spare your life, all right?
We really don't know anything.
Fuck! Do something about it!
Do you want to spend
the rest of your life in a wheelchair?
Hey, hold down his legs.
Hold him!
- Hold down his legs.
- No!
Still not talking?
Go on, start talking!
-No.
-Hey. Move. Let go!
- Hey...
- What?
You bastards...
Get up.
Get up!
What? You want some?
Stop moving around.
We'll take the kid.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
She pretended to be tough,
but now she's crying like a baby.
You were worse back then.
Mr. Woo Jangik.
Do you admit to assaulting and threatening
two minors while imprisoning them?
Imprisoning, assaulting...
Jeez, I was just talking to them.
According to the order of what happened,
Mr. Woo is the victim.
Since a group of them broke in at night
and inflicted injury,
it's trespassing and special assault.
Then why did you say everything was fine
when we visited?
I was embarrassed
about getting beaten up by kids.
Do you think that makes sense?
- Yes.
- Wait a second.
Mr. Woo simply didn't want
to make things worse.
Isn't it better to let them go
after giving them discipline
than handing them over to the police?
Discipline?
Having gangsters assault teenagers.
You call that discipline?
When we settle with the perpetrators,
we'll keep that in mind...
Who are you calling perpetrators?
-Sure. Keep up the good work.
-Yes. Take care.
Investigation without detention,
obviously.
The lawyer used to be the presiding judge
at Geumo District Court.
Even if we detain him,
he'll file for a review of legality.
Then we'll have to let him go anyway.
Did you find out anything about that jerk?
Of recently, he's Geumo's biggest spender.
He's buying up all the buildings
around the abandoned redevelopment area.
The more I think about it,
the more suspicious it seems.
What is?
Everything. Moving to Geumo
when he has no family or friends here,
then investing a huge amount of money
in the redevelopment area.
He must be filthy rich.
What?
This is where all the dirty interests
were connected together back then.
It feels like something's going on again.
It's all in the past.
- Detective Kim.
- Take your hands off this case.
What?
Do you have evidence?
If you're going to make forced assumptions
without any evidence, don't even start.
What are you talking about?
You're unnecessarily empathizing
with this Hana kid.
You can't investigate objectively.
All right.
Lee Seonga.
Seonga!
Hey.
- Yes?
- You stop her.
Get her hands off this case
no matter what.
Got it?
All right.
Hello.
That's bad for your health.
You'd be surprised if you knew
just how much sugar is in that tiny cup.
Use the coffee machine.
The coffee beans are really good.
By the way, Detective.
How did you feel back then? When...
When you found Chairman Jang's body
after he killed himself?
Satisfaction?
Emptiness?
Or...
just sadness?
What do you think?
Me?
Ah...
I think I would've been really angry.
Because I should have put him
behind bars myself
but wasn't able to.
I was relieved.
Since then,
I've been able to sleep soundly.
You little punk, I told you guys
to go ahead and drink without me.
You came all the way here.
Just come with me.
Let's go in.
WE DO NOT TURN OUR BACK ON ANY REQUEST
MIDEUM PLANNING
Jeez!
That kid really brought him.
Nice.
Goodness. You're here, Taekrok.
- You call him like that?
- Hey!
Why aren't you in the studio?
I've got a life too, you know.
Taekrok. Let me fill your glass.
- Congratulations on your comeback.
- Congrats, my foot.
-I ate too much.
- And congrats on making your position.
Thank you.
Hey, how's business?
Do you have any customers?
Gosh, you're just clueless.
There's no such thing as a recession here.
The never-ending inflation in Geumo
suddenly just plummeted
when the redevelopment stopped.
That was actually good for me.
Because of that, a ton of couples
are getting divorced because of money.
What on earth is your specialty?
I do everything they ask me to do.
- Then fill my cup for me.
- Here, kid.
Fill your own damn cup.
- Don't be so harsh.
-Right.
-I wanted to give up, you know?
-You still passed.
When I heard you passed the police exam,
I was so surprised.
I thought, "Gosh, the police must have
really hit rock bottom."
When I heard you were an ex-cop,
I thought of giving up the exam.
Hey.
Let's go for a smoke.
Me?
Top me off, sir.
I thought you quit smoking, Detective.
I have a favor to ask.
GEUMO POLICE STATION
Hello, Team Leader Yeon.
What brings you here, Sergeant Lee?
Ah...
- I was wondering what happened to Hana.
- Hana?
She's currently being investigated.
Once we wrap things up,
a social worker will be taking her. Why?
Could I have a word with her?
Yes, go ahead.
Thank you.
You...
Hey, lady.
Why do you keep worrying about me?
When I was like you,
there was a grown-up who did that for me.
I felt less lonely back then.
Is it...
the man who drove me home with you?
That's right.
He was the only one who listened
to what I said and believed me.
Then...
will you believe me too?
It's true
that we've been stealing this whole time,
but we didn't steal anything
from that man's office.
Really.
Okay.
I believe you.
Hana,
we have to go now.
Let me give you my card again...
I have it.
The one you gave me before.
YOUNGSEO WELFARE FOUNDATION
Did you have a nice chat?
Yes. Thank you.
It's nothing.
So what's going to happen to her now?
First, she'll go to the hospital
to get a few checkups.
And then, following her wishes,
she'll be entering a youth care facility.
They'll investigate her during her stay.
And if there's evidence
of prior domestic violence,
we will take follow-up measures.
- It's a good thing, right?
- At least,
she won't be out in the streets anymore.
Oh, right. I read Hana's statement,
and there was something off about it.
- What...
- She said that the kidnapper
kept telling her to give him
the flash drive in the safe.
- Excuse me?
- The theft case you've been investigating.
None of them had a safe robbed, right?
That's right.
The kids never touched any safes.
Exactly. Hana wouldn't have lied
about something like that.
Sir. Just a second.
I think this needs to be looked into.
I'll be on my way.
Up until now,
the kids never touched any safes.
If the thing Woo Jangik is looking for
was in his safe,
someone else took it.
I need to go see him again.
Then summon him to the station
for questioning.
- Or go with me.
-There's no time for that.
No matter how much I think about it,
Woo Jangik isn't a typical businessman.
I think there's a connection
to Chairman Jang
who was after the redevelopment.
That's a bit of a stretch.
There's nothing definitive.
Forget it.
Hang up if that's all you have to say.
- Lieutenant Kim.
-Yes?
The Sanyong-dong sexual assault case.
Where's the victim's statement?
Just a second.
Women and Juvenile Affairs.
Seonga is on her way
to Woo Jangik's office.
I tried to stop her,
but she doesn't listen.
Lieutenant Kim?
- What, is there an emergency?
- We'll talk later.
-Yes, sir?
- Where are you now?
Woo Jangik's office.
I have to look into something.
Hey!
I told you not to worry about it.
Listen to me. Don't go in there.
Detective, what on earth is this about...
Seonga!
SHADOW DETECTIVE SEASON 2
Modify by Blue-Bird™