2 YEARS AGO
To the ten direction's Buddhas
The profound and stainless Dharma
And the liberated Sangha,
we sincerely go for refuge
With great love and kindness...
There are always good temples
in famous mountains.
Now that you've prayed to Buddha,
it should work out this time, sir.
It should.
It's right there.
The perfect location
to start the port city project.
Kook Jinhan, is it?
Can we really trust him?
He's the kind of man
who'd do anything to complete a mission.
That's why Chairman Jang recruited him.
Like you said, this must not fail.
We'll take care of those who control Geumo
before this year ends.
Hundreds of billions of won
will be at stake.
We have to get rid
of those maggots in advance.
Also, Assemblyman Lee.
As I told you last time,
once this is taken care of...
All right.
You'll be nominated for the by-elections
the year after I become governor.
All right.
SHADOW DETECTIVE SEASON 2
Team Leader Yeon.
Are you all right?
Hold on.
Wake up.
This is your last chance.
You walk out that door, and you die.
What choice are you going to make?
Stop.
Mind your manners.
Nothing good comes out
of being rambunctious.
Don't you agree, Assemblyman Lee?
I heard you even sent people to find me,
so I came rushing to see you.
Did you call the cops on Hwanju?
Let's talk inside.
Team Leader Yeon.
LEE SEONGA
Call an ambulance over
to the safe house. Right now.
Team Leader Yeon.
Team Leader Yeon!
Yeon Juhyun, wake up.
Yeon Juhyun!
And Secretary Cha?
Did you kill him?
Of course not.
You don't put down a dog
when you still have use for it.
You were the one who taught me that.
AUGUST, 2005
JOINT INVESTIGATION HEADQUARTERS
Juhwan.
It's illegal to detain and torture
an incumbent police officer
to extract a confession.
Illegal...
These were all found
at his father's house.
Hey, Choi Dohyung!
You're the ones who did something illegal.
I told you to wipe the drug gang out.
Instead, you stole the drugs
and sold them!
All right. Detective Choi Dohyung.
From now on, you'd better choose
your words carefully.
Or else I'll rip the uniforms
off your men's backs.
You vile police scum.
"You vile police scum."
You've been holding that
against me all this time?
All right.
What is it that you want?
I want to see how far we vile police scum
can go when you give them power.
Is that nonsense how you cajoled
Chief Baek into taking your side?
Chief Baek is also a cop
who was just exploited by you.
All I did was do what you taught me.
I'll take responsibility for everything.
There's no need for my men
to get involved.
Please.
Why? Trying to play the hero?
What did you say their name was?
He called it the Geumjeong Society.
Right, the Geumjeong Society.
An organization founded by a bunch
of maggots trying to band together.
I'll spare you.
That little playtime of yours.
How about I make it come true?
What the...
-Why are the lights...
-Hey!
Let go of me!
Given the number of offenses
and quantity of narcotics
found in the possession of the defendant,
the court finds it necessary
to enact a commensurate punishment.
The court will now read the verdict.
The defendant is hereby
sentenced to three years in prison.
No. I didn't do it, Your Honor.
Drugs? I didn't do it, Your Honor!
Now that the union leader's
out of the way,
your brother's construction
shouldn't be disrupted for the time being.
It's good to see the prosecution
and police cooperating.
Thank you.
Sir.
About the national convention
next month...
Hey. Don't rush things.
I'm aware.
I've prepared everything
for your political debut, Prosecutor Lee.
Thank you.
As for the police personnel,
all you have to do is what's written here.
Just the chief investigator of narcotics?
I thought you were trying
to get rid of the commissioner.
I'm thinking of swapping the arms
and legs first, so they don't notice.
Okay. I see. Good.
- I'll see you soon.
-Yes, sir.
Had it not been for me,
the two of you wouldn't be anything.
On the contrary.
All that you enjoy now
was possible thanks to us.
All right.
I admit you were quite useful for a mutt.
But that doesn't mean
you can bite the hand that feeds you.
So...
Now, what?
Are you going to destroy me?
Would that even be possible?
Above me are the ones I paid off,
and below me are the ones who paid me off.
If I'm finished,
you'll be nothing but dust.
I know this.
Half the people who rule this country
are connected to you.
You know that
and yet, you still do this?
Only because I don't have what they do.
What?
Fear.
I do not fear either dying or living.
But those involved with you probably are.
Because they have so much to lose.
When the sun comes up,
all you will be is a criminal
who traded drugs and incited murder.
There will be no one left to cover you.
Yong Hwanju was arrested.
Also, I looked into it.
Chief Baek personally asked
for cooperation from Narcotics.
In that case, Chief Seo Gwangsu
should be getting investigated soon.
We've been able to locate the car
that took Team Leader Han through CCTV.
We're tracking it now.
We'll let you know if anything comes up.
We finally meet.
Although not under pleasant circumstances.
Thanks to your decisive action,
Team Leader Yeon will live.
Thank you.
Team Leader Yeon's father, Yeon Sanghoon.
Does he have anything to do
with the Geumjeong Society?
Yeon Sanghoon died chasing after them.
It was when we were finally
about to see progress
in the investigation.
It was written off as a simple
hit-and-run, but I'm positive.
That the organization Yeon Sanghoon
and I were chasing was behind it.
But back then,
there was nothing I could do.
After a long time, I became the director
of the Inspection Department,
so I decided to go after them again.
I told Team Leader Yeon Juhyun
the truth, too.
The only thing that was
in Yeon Sanghoon's last report
was that picture.
I failed once again.
I wanted to make sure
Sanghoon's death wasn't in vain...
By using his daughter?
I doubt that was what
Yeon Sanghoon would have wanted.
If you really cared about him,
you should have taken
on this responsibility yourself.
Instead of getting his daughter involved.
Detective Han's car passed by this?
Yes, an hour ago.
But it wasn't caught
on the security camera up ahead.
Yeah?
Let's go that way. Over there.
Okay.
NOEUL GOSIWON
What happened to your face?
It's nothing.
What brings you here at this hour?
I'm in need of your consolation.
It was a really long day.
You'll be cleared of the charges soon.
Don't worry.
This is the first of many.
It'll happen a lot more often from now on.
So why did you choose to walk
this exhausting path?
I can say the same to you.
I heard from a colleague in Narcotics
that he saw you.
What a small world.
You told me last time.
That you had some unfinished business
to take care of.
Was what happened today related to that?
Wait. Stop the car.
- What?
- Stop the car.
That's it, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Get him out.
Don't you need my help?
You remember that thing
you used to say all the time?
That in order to protect ourselves,
we should help each other.
I did?
Taekrok.
Let's stop here.
It's all in the past.
Are you really willing to go further?
Is that more important than your own life?
What's with you today?
I just hate that you're this kind of cop.
Someone who dies
just because of that sense of duty.
You bastard!
I don't want to see that.
If you're talking about Jinseok, stop.
Neither one of us
has anything to be proud of.
I don't regret it.
If you can avoid it, you should.
I said stop.
Whatever you're doing now,
don't regret it later.
That would be...
useless.
It doesn't matter how small.
Find anything you can!
Yes?
We found a note in his pocket.
It admits to killing Woo Jangik
on Lee Youngho's orders.
Any other belongings?
He only had his phone on him
but there was nothing unusual
in this call history or texts.
I'll get back
as soon as things get sorted.
All right.
Yeon Juhyun. Wake up. Yeon Juhyun!
JULY 11, 2005
GEUMJEONG?
Chief Baek turned
his back on Lee Youngho.
We lost our lead witness, Team Leader Han,
and Yeon Juhyun is gravely injured.
How did they find out
about the safe house?
Why didn't he kill me?
JULY 11, 2005
GEUMJEONG?
Your nephew, Yong Hwanju,
has been found to have used money
from drugs for your campaign expenses.
Do you have anything to say?
Is it true that a police officer
from Geumo Station committed suicide,
accusing you of inciting murder?
Were the charges against
Choi Dohyung politically motivated?
Is it true that you ordered
the search and seizure?
- Please say a word, sir.
-Is it all true?
Your youngest daughter studying
in the US is preparing for a recital.
You son of a bitch!
I'm going to kill you...
Do not forget.
We're always watching you
whenever and wherever you are.
Prosecutor Lee Youngho.
From now on, you'd better choose
your words carefully.
Has a candidate ever been put
under emergency arrest
a day before the election?
His supporters in Youngseo Province
are all in huge shock.
As a three-term assemblyman, Lee Youngho
had the trust of the voters of Youngseo.
However, his arrest will likely have
an big impact on the election.
In this case, Kim Jinsun,
who was closely following behind candidate
Lee Youngho's approval rating,
is expected to win the election.
Prosecutor Ahn, this is your chance.
You can't let this get away
if you're thinking of getting ahead.
Yes, sir.
There's the issue of his nephew's drugs,
but the core of this
is him inciting murder.
Make sure to focus on that.
Yes, sir.
Chief Prosecutor Won.
Lee Youngho is only going to keep
using you for trivial things such as this.
When I become a member
of the National Assembly
and achieve what I want,
you'll be with me,
sitting somewhere higher.
FOR A HAPPY YOUNGSEO
CANDIDATE 2 KIM JINSUN
Candidate Kim is entering.
- Congratulations.
- Oh, not you too.
Let's wait until the results
come out tomorrow.
I think you're being too modest.
I recall being shocked
when the prosecution put you
under a search and seizure,
but now I can't believe
what's happening at all.
What a turn of fortune.
Things are finally as they should be.
The timing of it was so perfect
that I thought it was perhaps
divine intervention.
I heard that the party leader
called to congratulate you.
Yes. And they'll invite you
to a formal greeting after the election.
How nice.
The party has great expectations for you,
Director Choi.
They're saying you were of great help
in gaining the support
of the people at the last leg.
I'll have to live up
to those expectations then.
Why did Chief Baek
send Narcotics there?
Did he really betray Lee Youngho?
Team Leader Han was murdered.
What?
Yong Hwanju will soon testify about you.
You have to get away.
I guess I won't be seeing you
for a while again.
I should take one down with me.
What are you going to do?
I think I should do that much
and give them a good blow.
Then I'll be able to face
the guys who died before us.
Among those who retired
from the Special Operation Unit in 2005,
I picked out the ones
whose jobs and addresses were unknown.
PROFILE
NAME: KWON JUHWAN
"Kwon Juhwan."
There's this man whom Chief Baek
refers to as Director Kwon.
He seems to be their enforcer.
Director Kwon?
Is this him?
NAME: KWON JUHWAN
He was a former UDT, then joined
the police through special recruitment
- but was fired after five years.
- The reason?
Violating the Narcotics Control Act.
This ex-spec ops...
Maybe he carried drugs on him?
It's possible if he got his hands
on evidence or foreclosures.
When did he get out?
He was sentenced to three years
but was pardoned as a model prisoner
the year after that.
Find out who the prosecutor
was at the time.
One moment.
- Wait.
- What?
What you just said. It was mentioned
in an article I found last night.
That was around 2005 too.
Drugs, drugs, police...
Drugs, police...
Here it is. Here.
An article from November 21, 2005.
"A final trial was held
for an incumbent police officer
who was arrested last July
on charges of stealing confiscated goods
from the scene of a drug bust
and distributing them to the market.
An official from the joint investigation
team of the prosecution and police
who investigated this case
expressed concern about
the deviant behavior of the officer
in question being misinterpreted
as corruption of the entire police force."
- November 2005?
- Yes.
I found the prosecutor.
Is it Lee Youngho?
PROSECUTOR LEE YOUNGHO
- Yes.
- What's the date?
September 5, 2005.
Lee Youngho caught
Director Kwon stealing drugs.
And now Director Kwon
takes orders from Chief Baek.
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
I'm sending you information
on this guy called Kwon Juhwan.
Look into it thoroughly.
And check if he has any connections
to a member of the opposition party
or Assemblywoman Kim Jinsun.
Hey, send Seonga all the materials
on Kwon Juhwan.
Okay.
Are you going somewhere?
There's someone I have to meet.
So you're Kim Taekrok.
You've got guts coming all the way here
as a mere detective.
You got any cigarettes?
I thought you'd be a bit more formidable.
What?
You're just another pitiful man,
after all.
What? Did you think
I'd be a monster with horns?
That would have been better.
I wouldn't have felt this underwhelmed.
Sure, talk all you want.
This could be your last chance
to be on that high horse of yours.
How much longer do you think
I'll be staying here?
You were betrayed by the ones
you've raised. What can you do now?
What?
Chief Baek. Director Kwon.
You thought you owned them,
but you didn't.
You were just taken advantage of,
then abandoned at the tipping point.
Like Kook Jinhan.
Who is it?
The real boss.
- What difference will it make if you know?
- You have no other option now.
Are you counting
on your drug junkie nephew?
So you were the one behind Seo Gwangsu.
Do you know what happened
because you did that?
Someone else benefited from it.
Both our hard work has gone to the dog.
Congratulations on Director
Choi Dohyung's new beginning.
Congratulations.
You're going to be really busy now.
Let me know whenever you need my help.
You're already helping me a lot.
You wrapped up the search and seizure too.
I almost made a huge mistake back then.
The past is just the past.
What's important is the future.
I have the Chief Prosecutor
to rely on at the prosecutor's office.
Chief Baek is keeping me safe
with the police.
And there's no strategist in politics
as good as Secretary Cha.
I am quite fortunate.
I appreciate the compliment.
We're the ones who are honored.
I'm just coming back
from meeting with Lee Youngho.
The Inspection Department Chief said
it was the last thing he could do for me.
I've been ordered to return too.
Back to Juvenile Affairs at the Agency.
There's no time.
That Director Kwon you found.
I'm sure it's the man
from the picture my father left.
All we have to do is catch him.
If we catch him...
Team Leader Yeon.
The Inspection Department
took advantage of you.
And you almost died for it.
It doesn't matter.
Even if I'm taken advantage of.
If it means avenging my father...
Focus on recovering for now.
I'm on the move.
My father left...
one last report.
You came to turn yourself in?
I bribed Candidate Lee Youngho.
I really was given probation.
I don't know how many higher-ups
he had to talk to in the middle.
Then after that,
you contacted Yong Hwanju,
Cha Kyungpil, and Son Sangwook?
There is one more person.
All right. I'll see you next time.
Yes, sir. Take care.
Right.
- Let's go.
- Yes, take care.
I thought I told you to only bring
Han Giyong out of there.
I'm sorry, sir.
Why did you try to kill Yeon Juhyun?
Didn't Chief Baek report to you?
Do you remember Yeon Sanghoon?
Yeon Sanghoon.
So he's the one causing us trouble?
Yes, sir.
You take this on.
That way you'll earn
Team Leader Choi's trust.
Yes, sir.
Yeon Juhyun is Yeon Sanghoon's daughter.
That's why Chief Baek ordered me
to get rid of Yeon Juhyun.
GEUMO POLICE STATION
INVESTIGATION REPORT
TRANSPORT OF SEIZED GOODS FROM DRUG BUSTS
Yes, talk.
Detective Kim. I looked into it.
There's a commercial
building under Director Kwon's name.
But one of the tenants
of that building is...
Hwang Jinseok.
With the local elections just a day away,
Candidate Kim Jinsun is sure
to win the election
after candidate Lee Youngho's withdrawal.
Someone else benefited from it.
As a result,
- much attention is focused...
- Both our hard work has gone to the dog.
...on the future plans
of Director Choi Dohyung,
who had declared his support
for Candidate Kim Jin-sun.
- Director Choi Dohyung...
-Let's stop here.
Are you really willing to go further?
Is that more important than your own life?
If you're talking about Jinseok, stop.
Neither one of us
has anything to be proud of.
I don't regret it.
He has already made
a political move by winning the nomination
- for next year's by-election...
-To achieve what I want,
I need power.
A 30-year police veteran,
Director Choi solved major cases
such as the Eunsan serial murders...
- Choi Dohyung.
- ...and has the nation's support.
Welcome!
Taekrok.
Long time no see.
I'm all right, Taekrok.
See?
I can even go hiking on the hill out back.
Yeah. I heard you were doing okay.
Then you should have come sooner
to have a drink with me.
We have some good pork.
It was delicious.
Yes.
I would like to keep the party's
welcome ceremony a simple affair.
I'll see you then.
FRESH MEAT RESTAURANT
So...
you already knew
Kwon Juhwan from the start?
Yes, Dohyung hooked me up with him.
Thanks to him,
I was able to get back on my feet so soon.
This restaurant too.
How do Dohyung and Kwon Juhwan
know each other?
They were both members of BST.
Don't tell me you don't remember.
You started it. "Be Safe Today too." BST.
Kwon Juhwan...
was a member of BST?
Yes.
I think it was
after you returned to Geumo.
Dohyung brought him in as a new member.
I thought BST ended after I left.
Dohyung kept it going for a bit.
And then,
I heard it just kind of fizzled out.
- Hey, do you know if...
- Right.
I think he changed the name
from BST to something else.
GEUMJEONG
"Geum" meaning "today."
"Jeong" meaning "safely."
Be safe!
- Today too!
Geumjeong.
SHADOW DETECTIVE SEASON 2
Modify by Blue-Bird™