NO CALLER ID
Hey, friend.
If you keep digging around,
it will be your turn next.
There was yet another friend.
The body found at one of the construction
sites in the redevelopment area
has been identified as Mr. Jang Sungtae.
The cause of death is a fracture
to the skull caused by a fall...
Kook Jinhan and Chairman Jang are dead.
But it doesn't mean it's over.
So, why did Chairman Jang kill Kook Jinhan
but let you live?
Why did they keep me alive?
DEATH HAUNTS GEUMO
ANOTHER FOUND DEAD
CHAIRMAN JANG FOUND DEAD
AT CONSTRUCTION SITE
Are they trying to play another game?
I have to find a way
to survive this cruel game.
STATUS REPORT OF PERSON ON LEAVE
KIM TAEKROK
They could be anywhere.
So, I'll have to be prudent.
I have to investigate them one by one…
until it's truly over.
When I arrested Chairman Jang,
Assemblyman Lee Youngho
was suspected to be involved.
If Assemblyman Lee Youngho
was behind all this,
that would mean that the massive
corruption within the political
and business circles
are happening right here, in Geumo.
LEE YOUNGHO
Lee Youngho.
Is this a hint that Kook Jinhan gave me?
Or will this turn out to be another trap?
I need to be thoroughly prepared.
CRIME INVESTIGATION DEPARTMENT
Small clues will lead me
to smother them out.
I'll investigate to the end…
and eventually find them.
I will
catch
them
no matter what.
SHADOW DETECTIVE SEASON 2
What are you doing?
What are you doing here?
What is all this?
Why are you here?
So you've been preparing
all that by yourself?
Why didn't you say anything?
Forget me.
But Seonga should have known, at least.
She has nothing to do with this.
And neither do you.
What will you do about Team Leader Han?
It's not the time to go after him.
Then...
You weren't here today.
You didn't see or hear anything.
Understand?
YOUNGSEO WELFARE FOUNDATION
I guess they're doing well.
A relief, isn't it?
You're here.
Gosh, what time is it?
I'm not late.
I was told to show up before noon.
You said even that was difficult for you.
What's gotten into you today?
Maybe my time on Earth is nearly over.
Gosh, how could you say
something like that in front of my baby...
It sounds like a threat.
When do you go on maternity leave?
There's still some time left.
Please take good care of him
while I'm on leave.
That night.
I saw someone wearing a black hoodie.
That lady did this with her finger.
Please don't fight each other.
I can't make any promises.
Hey.
It's been a while.
Did you look into it?
Yes. She worked at the same station
as Kook Jinhan.
But they weren't on the same team.
Nothing overlaps.
They probably
never met at the academy either.
Like I said, there's not much to say.
You think?
But before she was transferred
to Geumo,
she'd been on leave for three months.
On leave?
Did it say why?
That's where it gets iffy.
"Personal development."
It is a voluntary leave of absence
you're legally allowed to have, but...
Yeon Juhyun.
She made preparations before coming here.
CIVIL AFFAIRS
-Yes?
-Hello. This is the hospital.
-Ms. Lee Seonga has woken up.
-Yes. I'll be there right away. Thanks.
YOUNGSEO WELFARE FOUNDATION
Detective Choi Dohyung!
LEE YOUNGHO
It's already been a year
since I turned in my badge.
Right.
You're now the director
of a welfare foundation.
My mistake, Director Choi.
Yesterday at the debate, Candidate Lee
stated that he plans on recruiting you
as a crime prevention special advisor...
About that,
I am still discussing
the details with Director Choi.
All right.
Now, why don't we look around
and see how the kids are doing?
Let's go.
Director Choi, it's a relief
to have you back in Geumo
and doing good deeds.
I'm only doing my job.
When you are elected,
please give our foundation
much-needed help and support.
Of course.
You look, well...
better than I thought.
This isn't exactly Hell, you know.
So why did you want to see me?
Do we have any reason
to be seeing each other?
Detective Han...
It's Team Leader Han.
Sure. Team Leader Han.
You must be busy,
so I'll get straight to the point.
Okay.
I want to get out of here.
Smile at the camera.
Give us a big smile.
Make sure everyone's visible, okay?
All right. One, two, three.
Smile a bit more, please.
-Look this way, please.
-We'll take another one.
Let's smile just a little bit more.
Thank you.
We'll wrap things up here today.
Thank you, everyone.
Good luck to you.
YOUNGSEO WELFARE FOUNDATION
Bye, kids!
CANDIDATE NO.1
LEE YOUNGHO
All right. Everyone inside.
The election is around the corner.
But Choi Dohyung setting up the foundation
is making bigger headlines than me.
Have some patience, please.
It's only temporary.
His image as a star detective
isn't going to last that long.
You can't get discharged tomorrow.
Don't push yourself.
I'm fine. I'm better off at home.
No one's there to watch you.
Should there be?
I'm going home because it's home.
Hey, do you even have time to be here?
What happened to the arson case?
Do you have a suspect?
Why aren't you saying anything?
The investigation's still on,
so we'll have someone.
You just take care of yourself.
-What did Taekrok say?
-What else would he say?
"Is Seonga all right?
What did the doctor say?"
He's just worried about you.
You weren't here today.
You didn't see or hear anything.
Get that in your head
if you want to protect Seonga.
I LOVE YOU CAPITAL
Hey, which one of you is Mr. Kim?
-What?
-What the heck?
Where's Mr. Kim?
BELOVED CUSTOMER,
WE WILL BE YOUR RELIABLE PARTNER
I'm about to ask you some questions,
so you'd better answer honestly.
Yes, sir.
Hello.
Who is it?
Excuse me. Is Mr. Park Sangchul here...
That jerk, Woo Jangik.
It seemed like
he was making some kind
of real estate investment company.
There are a lot of people
who sell their personal seals for money.
If he bought those names and made
burner phones and burner bank accounts,
Woo Jangik would've registered himself
as the CEO and shareholder.
Do you have deals these days?
With the redevelopment suspended?
It's still better than last year.
Because outsiders come in
and get the money flowing.
Outsiders?
Yes.
There's a magnate who's been buying up
all the properties around here
since a few months ago.
Allowed me to take a breather.
WOO JANGIK
Woo Jangik made a shell corporation
and was dealing with real estate
near the redevelopment area.
He would meet Kang Seungmo,
President of Yeongseo Bank,
Won Jaegu, Chief Prosecutor of Youngseo,
and Yong Hwanju, nephew of Lee Youngho.
All close acquaintances of Lee Youngho.
They're on a different level
than Woo Jangik.
He wouldn't have been involved
with them for no special reason.
He could be involved in Woo Jangik's
borrowed-name real estate speculation.
CANDIDATE LEE YOUNGHO'S FIRST CAMPAIGN
The plan must have been
to make a huge profit
once redevelopment was renewed.
Is that why he ordered Team Leader Han
to kill the risk factor, Woo Jangik,
with the election coming up?
If that's the case,
there's no reason for him
to take a risk by getting Yeon Juhyun
to steal the USB drive.
Yeon Juhyun…
doesn't work for them.
If that's the case,
then who on earth is she?
It's on the desk.
This is it? Nothing out of the ordinary?
The diner she went to
was near your apartment.
She was there for about an hour.
It's pretty far from her place.
TABLE OF FOOD
Yeon Juhyun's spying on me.
How did you feel back then?
When you found Chairman Jang's body
after he killed himself?
The fact that he's going through a retrial
means that he hasn't been acquitted yet.
Trying to provoke and test me.
It was all because
she was suspicious of me.
…SUSPICIOUS OF ME.
And that suspicion...
is Yeon Juhyun's…
weakness.
He's a former police officer
who's now running
a private detective agency.
And he seems to be constantly
helping Detective Kim Taekrok.
I think we should look into what kind of
information he has when the time is right.
Yes.
We'll have to think about how to use
the data in the flash drive.
Yes, I know.
But they don't have time either.
You have to be careful.
Okay.
TAEKROK
Hana. How did you get here?
The Director brought me.
-Hello.
-Hi.
I'm here to meet
with the hospital's business team.
Hana was worried about you a lot as well.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Then I'll head over to see Doyoon.
All right.
All right then.
I'm glad you're okay.
Being a detective isn't easy, is it?
It's all right.
It's good to see you strong.
I wasn't when I was your age.
I always had my resignation in my pocket.
You did?
I wasn't able to quit because of Taekrok.
He stopped me with all his might.
I can imagine.
He's always the same.
But it feels like he's changed these days.
I thought I knew Taekrok too,
but he feels different somehow.
Why?
Is he hiding things?
He thinks that's the way
to protect his colleagues.
He was like that with Jinseok's case too.
Jinseok?
He never told you about that?
Well...
It's not a pleasant story to tell.
GEUMO POLICE STATION
There isn't anyone around him
that could be identified as the suspect.
And there isn't anyone
who has a grudge against him.
As I've explained so far,
it doesn't seem like
there are any suspects currently,
aside from Yang Gitae.
However,
there's no direct evidence, confession,
or distinct motive
that proves Yang Gitae is the arsonist.
Wait.
You were the one who kept saying
he was the most suspicious so far...
It was because of his arson record.
But after going over the arson case again
which, by the way,
is going through a retrial,
it seemed clearer
that Yang Gitae isn't the culprit.
Chief.
If we investigate him unreasonably
while in our custody,
it may come back at us.
No, sir.
Wouldn't it be okay if you proceed
for now as we look for evidence?
About that,
Team Leader Yeon is right.
It could seem
as if the police are framing him again.
Let Yang Gitae go for now.
Then investigate thoroughly
and find the suspect.
Darn it.
It must have been rough, Mr. Yang.
Mr. Gong Haneul. Is it right
for the police to do this?
-Darn.
-I know.
-You know about my temper, right?
-Yes.
GEUMO POLICE WILL CHANGE FOR THE BETTER
You must be glad
to have your close neighbor
have his name cleared.
So who's the real culprit?
What on earth is it
that he wanted to hide?
I'm curious.
Why do you think that?
-What?
-We haven't got a motive yet.
Why do you think
it was done to hide something?
Ah.
He started a fire.
I mean,
if he just wanted to kill Woo Jangik,
he wouldn't have chosen
such an inconvenient method.
That's good reasoning.
Why don't you go tell
Team Leader Han that?
Hey, it's me.
Are you sure?
With that evidence,
he won't be able to get away with it.
What time do you leave?
Really?
Then...
I'll pick it up by ten.
KANG SEUNGMO / PRESIDENT OF YOUNGSEO BANK
Thank you.
WON JAEGU / CHIEF PROSECUTOR
OF YOUNGSEO DISTRICT PROSECUTOR'S OFFICE
You're here.
Go inside. He's waiting for you.
Yes.
It's been a while, Secretary Cha.
YONG HWANJU / DIRECTOR AT YD GROUP
MATERNAL NEPHEW TO ASSEMBLYMAN LEE YOUNGHO
I must say this villa is
more impressive than what I've heard.
The energy from the site
feels very good as well.
You've made it to the National Assembly.
With Geumo as a stepping stone,
you're now on your way
to becoming the governor.
It should be smooth sailing ahead.
The sail should take you straight
from governor to presidential candidate.
Of course.
There's less than a week left
until he's elected.
If only that jerk, Woo Jangik
didn't make trouble,
we'd already be sailing smoothly.
Anyway...
I'm worried that there's too much noise.
-What do you mean?
-I mean,
the explosion made quite an impact,
and the press is paying attention...
Couldn't you have gotten him more quietly?
Then,
was there a better way to do it?
You said everything he had
was a ticking time bomb.
Enjoy your food.
Take good care of your master.
Director Yong.
The election is just around the corner.
And there are a lot of eyes.
Please be more cautious with your actions.
Fuck.
What about my actions? Tell me.
Speculation, gambling,
women, alcohol, well...
Should I go on?
Have you been snooping around?
That's the problem. I didn't have to.
-Secretary Cha!
-Director Yong.
The way you can help the assemblyman
is by staying quiet.
You ought to have figured that out
by yourself.
Hey.
Do you feel like you're someone
when you act like this?
You...
are nothing but a dog.
You're beneath us.
How long do you think you have
before my uncle puts you down?
Get a fucking grip, man.
Fucking hell.
I'm going home.
Just wrap things up, all right?
-Wrap things up and head home.
-Yes, sir.
Team Leader Han.
Let's go for a drink with Officer Kang.
What's gotten into you, asking to drink?
We haven't thrown him a welcome party,
and you've been working hard.
I'm busy today, though.
So you're not coming back today?
No, I'm not.
All right then. Next time.
Next time.
-Let's drink next time.
-Okay.
Take care.
What are you doing?
Go home.
Yes, sir.
-See you tomorrow.
-Okay.
I was wondering
when I'll be able to meet with him.
No. It's not that I'm getting anxious.
Yes.
Still, there are things
that I've done so far, you know.
No, I didn't mean it that way. Yes.
Okay, then I'll just be waiting.
Yes. All right.
Fucking bastard.
It might not have been exposed,
but there was something going on
between you and Chairman Jang.
You thought I wouldn't know?
Come on.
You've really got the wrong person.
-Are you getting senile?
-Scared, aren't you?
Kook Jinhan's dead
and Chairman Jang's gone.
You've somehow managed to stay alive
by pulling on the right people's strings.
But you're always doing the dirty work
without a reward.
You must be worrying over
when you'll be cut off.
You must be losing sleep over it, right?
If you want to survive,
you can't just hold on to the rope.
You've got to climb it.
DIRECTOR YONG HWANJU
Hello?
Hello, Director Yong.
I'm Team Leader Han Giyong
of Geumo Police's Homicide Team.
Maybe you remember me?
Once while we were golfing, I...
Yes, I remember.
Why are you calling?
You should head to sleep early.
You have a tight schedule tomorrow too.
I should.
Are there any other issues?
What? Is Hwanju causing trouble again?
Why don't you send him abroad, at least
for the remainder of the campaign period?
What are you doing?
I'm getting ready to go home. What else?
Why did you come to work already?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
You can't be. You're in a cast.
Let's have some coffee.
Okay.
EVIDENCE PHOTOS
You're returning
to work tomorrow?
What good is it for me
to stay home?
By the way, what were you doing earlier?
Well, I lost a file, so...
But I thought
you were taking this week off.
What are you going to do with that arm?
I'm going to investigate
the whole arson case from scratch.
Be ready.
LIEUTENANT KIM TAEKROK
Hello?
Let's have dinner.
One more gukbap, please.
Coming right up.
I thought you were after the flash drive.
It's obvious what's inside.
Why would I be curious about that?
For me,
I find this more interesting.
A call made to you
at the same time every day.
I traced the number, and you were right.
The Agency's Inspection Department.
It must be the guy who sent you here.
-What is it you want?
-It's simple.
When they call you today,
tell them you'll expose Kang Seungmo,
the bank president.
And why should I do that?
You're not making some obvious threat
like, "I'll reveal who you are," are you?
Isn't this what you need?
Once the scandal
on the bank president breaks out,
it'll be in your hands.
There must be a reason
you've kept quiet about this until now.
If I bring it to light,
won't that create a setback in your plans?
No, it can't.
You didn't come all this way
to catch a small fry like him either.
It's my treat, so eat up.
Right. Let me make one thing clear.
Don't mess with Seonga to get to me.
If you mess with the people around me
one more time, I won't let it slide.
Do this first.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Finish all of these.
-All of these?
-Yes, all of them.
-Why, you don't want to?
-That's not it.
According to the tip-off
received last night,
it's been revealed that President Kang
has been stealing personal seals
of underprivileged people
such as people with disabilities
and senior citizens living alone
to purchase a large number
of real estate near the redevelopment area
for the past few months.
As of now,
Youngseo Bank has not released any
official statement about these suspicions.
In response, the police revealed
they are investigating
whether there are...
-Sir! You're here early today.
-Mind your own business, kid.
Meanwhile, according
to police investigation...
All right.
...has died from the gas
explosion incident that occurred
in Seonju-eup, Geumo, this past ninth.
Yes, just Bank President Kang Seungmo.
Please trust me on this and do it.
I have a plan.
You won't be disappointed.
All right.
We'll do that.
INSPECTOR HAN JONGSEOK
Ms. Yeon.
Hey, Team Leader Yeon.
What are you thinking so hard on?
-Sign this for me.
-Sure.
Did you have
a hard time sleeping last night?
You look tired.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm looking into where the leak happened.
Still, they haven't found
any direct connection to you,
so there shouldn't be any problem.
Back when I was a prosecutor,
I caught all the punks who thought
that way and put them behind bars.
Being complacent like that
will get you cut off like this.
I understand what you mean, sir.
Why only President Kang Seungmo?
Our deal is over.
Can't you just answer this much?
-Gosh. Hello, Assemblyman Lee.
-Hello.
Yes. Thank you.
You're handsome.
-Yes, thank you for your hard work.
-Sure.
Yes. I'm candidate number one,
Lee Youngho.
Yes, I will create
a new and improved Youngseo.
-Yes, thank you.
-Thank you.
Yes, thank you.
Sir! Please give us a comment
about the suspicion of President Kang's
-borrowed-name transaction.
-That's enough.
There's suspicion that you covered up
Youngseo Bank's illegal loan case...
-Gosh.
-...during your time as a prosecutor.
Is that irrelevant to this case?
-Sir, give us a comment!
-Yes, I understand your suffering.
Thank you. I'm candidate number one.
-Yes.
-I love you.
We love you.
Please vote for candidate number one,
Lee Youngho. It's Lee Youngho!
LEE YOUNGHO
I don't think we'll be able to get
campaign funds from President Kang.
Once the investigation starts,
YD Group's finance team is sure to nullify
all the loan plans for business funds.
Just get to the point.
How much of a setback is this?
-What is it?
-Uncle.
Why only President Kang Seungmo?
The funder.
That's the one thing I want.
Room for just one person.
That's all I need.
Let me know if you need anything.
They say the first snow
is coming early this year.
So why did you want to see me?
All you have to do is take me
to the man at the top.
Then I'll take care of you for sure.
DIRECTOR YONG HWANJU
Hello, Director Yong.
I'm Team Leader Han Giyong
of Geumo Police's Homicide Team.
Uncle. I think I have something for you.
Do you want to hear me out?
SHADOW DETECTIVE SEASON 2
Modify by Blue-Bird™