1 YEAR AND 6 MONTHS AGO
Yes.
I heard you wanted to see me.
Have a seat.
Okay.
How are things at Homicide?
There must have been a lot of talk
after what happened to Chief Kook.
You've been guiding us well
ever since you were appointed,
so I think we're stable
and changing for the better.
All we need to do is catch Jang Sungtae.
Yes, that's right.
But he's holed up somewhere,
so we haven't been able to locate him.
You of all people would know where,
wouldn't you, Detective Han?
I would?
You've probably received a lot
while spying for Chairman Jang.
You must have provided him
with a hideout at least.
Shit, why did he pick a place like this?
What the hell...
Hands in the air!
-What is this? Wait.
- Team Leader Han Giyong?
We're from the Inspection Department.
Punk!
Darn you!
Get him!
Freeze!
Drop the knife.
Drop it, you bastard!
Hey, are you okay?
Who are you all?
Who the hell are you?
Are you okay, Team Leader Yeon?
Don't move, you bastards!
Drop the knife.
I said, drop the knife!
I'm blowing his head next.
Abort.
SHADOW DETECTIVE SEASON 2
I see you're having a hard time
because of that arson case.
It'll be taken care of soon.
It should be.
And tomorrow,
Choi Dohyung's foundation will be
put through search and seizure.
Chief Prosecutor Won
will take care of everything,
but the police should be prepared too.
Yes, sir.
GEUMO HOUSE
-The operation failed.
We were sabotaged.
How dare you risk your life like that?
This is all I learned from you.
What else am I supposed to do?
Yes, sir.
You told me
we should look out for each other.
- You, don't even think about--
- That's why...
I'll just take care of you
until you hit 60.
Let's go.
We'll be in the car, then.
I've explained everything
to the higher-ups.
We'll interrogate
Team Leader Han at a safe house
and move him to the Agency's
Inspection Department tomorrow.
One phone call was enough
to explain all this?
When all the Inspection department
members were injured?
And they were okay with that?
Let's talk on the way.
My mission
is to go after a private organization
within the police.
A private organization?
A group that's been spreading like poison
for a long time now.
We believe that this private organization
is involved in Jang Sungtae's
and Kook Jinhan's cases.
That's why we've been paying
close attention to Woo Jangik,
the realtor who had been buying
the redevelopment district.
Both Chairman Jang and Chief Kook
were after Geumo City, after all.
Was Kook Jinhan
a part of that organization?
We can't be sure.
None of the members are identified.
That's why they chose me,
though I was from Women and Juveniles.
They had to hide
the Inspection department's involvement.
The men who showed up earlier...
We expected there to be armed forces
that work for them.
But this is the first time
I've seen them myself.
But those men earlier
were only after Team Leader Han.
We received an anonymous tip-off
about an employee in our station
trying to cover up the investigation
on the murder of Woo Jangik.
It's Chief Baek.
Chief Baek is controlling them
for Lee Youngho.
You got the closest.
What are you talking about?
To them.
You've gotten the closest to them
than anyone in the Inspection Department.
Things are different now.
They've found out about us.
Why are you doing all this?
What about you?
As a government employee
working for the country,
this is the job description.
RESTRICTED AREA
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Let them through.
Ma'am.
Mr. Han Giyong.
You're currently under investigation
for the murder of Woo Jangik and arson.
Who ordered you to do this?
This is a load of bullshit. Hey.
Are you the one behind all this?
Did you use me to introduce
Chief Seo to Lee Youngho?
Answer me.
Fuck this.
I really must be getting rusty, aren't I?
I got fucking played by Kim Taekrok.
Have you learned nothing
after all the shit you've been through?
Is it that fucking hard
to just lay low and retire?
- You fucking bastard!
-Calm down.
Calm down?
What the fuck
can the Inspection Department do?
Nothing.
What are you doing?
What are you...
Go.
I said go, you prick.
What the fuck are you playing at?
- What are you...
-Go.
-What?
-Runaway if you can, you bastard.
How far do you think you can run?
How far?
Can you make it out of Geumo?
I'm curious.
What would they do
to keep you from squealing?
I know...
everything you've done.
FRIEND, 5:27 A.M.
You scumbag!
I'm really going to kill you!
That was a warning for your friend.
Where are you right now?
So you can lose your cool.
You seem more human now.
That's all just fucking speculation.
You have no evidence!
The death of Chairman Jang and Chief Kook!
What are you going to do
about Chairman Jang?
Just give us the information.
We'll take care of it.
Taekrok.
You don't know what they're like.
All you have to do is testify.
How would you ever guarantee my safety?
Getting investigated under our watch
is the safest choice you have.
This is your last chance.
It's the only way you'll live.
Fuck! This is fucking messed up.
Will you guarantee my safety?
Of course,
as long as you cooperate.
There's not much that I know.
I just did what Chief Baek told me to do.
I'd like you to get rid of Woo Jangik.
You're telling me to kill him?
I don't think I can do that.
Section Chief
at the Youngseo Provincial Police Agency.
And that's just the beginning.
Let's have you reach
the main headquarters.
What? Do you think I'm bluffing?
Geumjeong Society doesn't make promises
it can't keep.
That's all that I know.
Geumjeong Society?
Don't go straight to the station
but go to Dongbum's office.
Secure footage from the cameras
near the scene of the accident.
And track the vehicles
- that got away earlier.
- Yes, sir.
Anything we find out from now on
is strictly confidential.
Understood.
And...
Always be careful!
Yes, sir.
- You too, kid.
- Yes, sir.
Things will get wild starting tomorrow.
It'll be dangerous,
so back out while you can.
You're really hurting my feelings.
I can't.
I've seen too much.
Detective Kim really put
everything on the line.
How can I back out after seeing that?
Yes?
There are no cameras within the vicinity.
I'll look around
the nearby roads again tomorrow.
CCTV FOOTAGE
It's definitely the same person.
The one who was present...
at both sites where Kook Jinhan
and Chairman Jang each died...
The one who was in that car...
The one who killed
Kook Jinhan and Chairman Jang...
I finally found a clue to catch him.
There's this man whom Chief Baek refers to
as Director Kwon.
It seemed like he acts as the enforcer.
Director Kwon and his men
aren't just regular thugs.
Abort.
It seemed they'd received SWAT training.
The picture is complete.
All we have to do is catch them
one by one.
JULY 11, 2005, GEUMJEONG?
"Geumjeong."
Geumjeong Society.
DECLARATION OF SUPPORT
FOR CANDIDATE NO. 2 KIM JINSUN
Today, I have the honor
of welcoming to my campaign
a person beloved and respected
by the citizens of Youngseo Province.
He had dedicated himself to fighting
violent crime in Korea for decades
and now oversees the welfare
and development of his hometown.
Please welcome Director Choi Dohyung.
Hello.
I'm Director Choi Dohyung
of Youngseo Foundation.
YOUNGSEO WELFARE FOUNDATION
In line with our shared aspirations
for the development of Geumo and Youngseo,
I've decided to support
Ms. Kim Jinsun's candidacy.
We will work together from now on
for the underprivileged children,
and in the future, for every child in...
Director Choi Dohyung.
We've received reports
of embezzlement of state subsidies
and the abuse of children
by the Youngseo Welfare Foundation.
We'll have to conduct
an urgent search and seizure.
What are you talking about?
On what grounds are you doing this?
Director Choi, what is going on?
My goodness, you didn't have to
turn the place inside out.
It's the Director's office after all.
If you're done, step outside and wait.
Turns out you can find thousands of faults
with welfare foundations
once you dig into them.
It's not that I'm suspicious
of your intentions,
but we do need to get things straight
since there was a report.
You understand, don't you?
Was it Congressman Lee Youngho
who asked you to barge in
right when I was announcing my support
for Candidate Kim's campaign?
You'd know the answer to that.
Well, think what you will.
It seems that Congressman Lee
is still in control
of Youngseo's prosecution,
seeing as how he has no one less
than the chief prosecutor himself
as his puppet.
I don't think
you have the time for that right now.
I'm aware.
I'm sure you've already prepared
the evidence to malign me well in advance.
So you're aware.
Well then,
you ought to have known better then.
I'll get going now. Ah.
You'll probably be notified
of your subpoena schedule soon.
Chief Prosecutor Won.
GEUMO POLICE STATION
I see.
It seems there were a lot of coincidences.
You just happened
to run into juvenile delinquents
in a place with no security cameras.
And Detective Lee Seonga happened
to be nearby and came over to help.
And Detective Son Gyeongchan
just happened to bring detectives
from the precinct afterward.
We'll search the area again
and submit our report.
No.
I have a more important task for you,
Team Leader Yeon.
Go to Director Choi Dohyung's
welfare foundation
and investigate
for any sign of child abuse.
I guess you haven't heard the news yet.
The place is under search and seizure.
GEUMO NEWS
A HERO IN CRISIS,
WILL CHOI DOHYUNG'S TRUE FACE BE REVEALED?
They're probably trying
to put pressure on him
for announcing his support
for Candidate Kim.
And they're keeping me busy too.
Do you think
Chief Baek caught on that you're with
the Inspection Department?
Probably.
How much...
does he know already?
Still, he won't be able to move so freely.
Since he has to keep
his identity a secret.
There are only two days left
until the election.
If things stay this way,
Lee Youngho will be elected.
Then Geumjeong Society
might go back into hiding again.
Two days.
There's no time.
- Did you look into it?
-Yes.
I looked into it through our guys
at the Inspection Department.
But this is...
It's being handled by the chief
of the Inspection Department himself.
So there's not much I can find out.
Well,
I've been fooled this whole time
since they sent her undercover
as the Team Leader of Women and Juveniles.
But there's one thing you should know.
Tell me.
Yeon Juhyun's father is someone you know.
What?
You met with Secretary Cha
yesterday, right?
Yes.
I need you to give Lee Youngho
a present through Secretary Cha.
- You're here.
- You got anything?
None of these cars are registered.
It'll take days to trace back
the route they used to travel.
I'm back.
How did it go with the hospitals?
I searched from university hospital ERs
to local clinics,
and there were no gunshot wound patients.
Look into anyone who retired
from SWAT teams in the last ten years.
It doesn't matter
whether they retired early or were fired.
If you find anything strange,
let them know.
That's going to be a lot.
Which is why you should get started.
Do you think they're former police?
They're trained. They move differently.
They were exchanging hand signals.
It'll take a while
to look into each of them.
How do we catch them?
We'll have to make them
come out of hiding.
Look at this.
LOCAL ELECTIONS D-2
UNPREDICTABLE ELECTION
FOR YOUNGSEO GOVERNOR
"Predictions on the governor election
of Youngseo Province are in chaos
with Director Choi, who announced
his support for Candidate Kim,
being placed under search and seizure
by the prosecution."
Lee Youngho has taken it too far.
We're going to aim
for Lee Youngho's weak spot
while he's at his most vulnerable.
His nephew's drug scandal
right before the election...
He'll try to stop it no matter what.
If we let them catch a whiff,
they'll show themselves again.
-Hello, sir.
- Hello.
Thank you for seeing me
on such short notice.
Of course.
I was actually
wanting to meet with you too.
Ah, is that so?
I thought I told you.
That I might be of help
to Assemblyman Lee soon.
Well, I heard a rumor
that's entirely different.
A rumor?
The word that the person
who made you approach the assemblyman...
was Detective Kim Taekrok.
Who on earth said that?
A guest has arrived.
Sir, my name is Baek Seongil.
Are you done interviewing the children?
Yes, Director Choi.
Sorry that I can't tell you
the result of the investigation.
I know.
I have a different favor to ask.
What might that be?
If something were to happen to me
and this facility gets shut down,
please make sure
all the children here get somewhere safe.
Why say something like that already?
The charges haven't been proven yet.
The election is right around the corner.
Someone like me without any connections
doesn't stand a chance
against those who suppress him.
What is wrong will be corrected.
Do you trust me?
Detective Kim Taekrok
is very worried about you as well.
All right.
You should get going. You must be busy.
Yes.
Did I say something funny?
No, I'm sorry.
But I couldn't help laughing
at something so ridiculous.
Look here.
You must not know
who put me through all this trouble
for you to come to that conclusion.
It was Kim Taekrok.
I wouldn't have gone to prison
if it weren't for him!
So there really is no connection
between you and Detective Kim?
There was a connection all right.
A rotten one.
That's why you're suspecting me
of being involved with the likes of him
as I am handing over
my precious slush fund.
Don't you agree, Mr. Cha?
You don't seem like you believe me,
Chief Baek.
Words don't prove anything.
You want me to prove my loyalty
toward Assemblyman Lee.
Can you?
I'll prove it
before the assemblyman himself.
Hello, Assemblyman Lee. I'm Seo Gwangsu.
Right, I heard you said
you had to meet with me.
Yes.
I hope this is worth
taking time out of my busy schedule.
I'm sure it will be.
This could affect the result
of the election that's in two days.
Mr. Son here is trying
to get big in the drug business.
I thought he'd be able
to talk to you about business.
Drug business?
Don't pretend you don't know.
I know you made some good money
back in the day.
Oh, dear.
I'm not sure
if there are any dealers left in Geumo.
Tell Lee Youngho
that Yong Hwanju is doing drugs.
What?
You want to hand over his only weak spot?
It's so that Chief Baek will get his men
moving to rid him of that weakness.
Talk to Yong Hwanju
as if you're setting him up
with a buyer in China.
And tell him to bring
a sample of the drug there.
You're trying to shoot
all the birds with one stone.
Gwangsu.
There's no time.
We have to end this with one go.
So why don't you coach us?
Invest in us and look out for us.
If you do that,
I'll take good care of you for sure.
Wouldn't it be a huge disaster
if your opposition
were to find out about this?
- Mr. Cha.
-Yes?
Did you not know about this?
I apologize, sir.
Where's Hwanju?
Tell him to come here immediately.
I haven't been able
to reach him since earlier.
So you're just sitting there?
What kind of idiot are you?
Assemblyman Lee.
To tell you the truth,
I heard something earlier today.
Are you ready?
Yes, the Inspection Department
agreed to dispatch their squad.
I barely managed to persuade them.
The director has been in a bad mood
since what happened yesterday.
This might be your last chance,
for a number of reasons.
Anyway, good luck. I'll get going now.
Yes, Taekrok.
Yes, did you look into it?
Yes. Nothing came out
of Yeon Sanghoon's autopsy.
So they just brushed it off
as a car accident.
They didn't have any evidence.
And there were no suspects.
- But...
- But?
He took a leave of absence
about a month before he died.
A leave of absence? Why?
That's a bit strange.
There's no specific reason.
A leave of absence
without a known reason...
Yeon Juhyun did the same.
Did her father die working on a mission
for the Inspection Department?
Mr. Cha.
Yes, sir.
Prepare to send Hwanju off overseas.
Yes. I'll make the arrangements.
He may be family...
but I've been too soft on him,
that fucking fool.
Don't worry too much.
I'll get things done within tonight.
Perhaps this could be a good thing.
We'll be able to take care
of all the people...
leeching off Director Yong.
And keep an eye on Seo Gwangsu.
He dares to wiretap
the person who introduced him.
He can't be trusted.
Take care of him
if he does anything fishy.
Yes, sir.
What now?
It seems like something went wrong
on Chief Prosecutor Won's end.
What are you talking about?
Why did you bring so many people?
Isn't this too obvious?
Those Chinese bastards can be scary.
Haven't you heard of the Triad?
Did you make sure to bring the sample?
Of course.
It's the real deal.
- I do know a decent buyer.
- You do?
Get a sample ready and wait.
I'll try to set up a meeting for tonight.
You have your gun on you, right?
Yes, sir.
The squad
sent by the Inspection Department
is on standby a minute away from here.
All right.
Tonight,
the tiny ripple made by a pebble
will come back as a tidal wave.
Today,
you placed Director Choi's foundation
under search and seizure.
Was there any evidence
on the embezzlement of state subsidies?
No, not yet.
We're going over the possibility
that it was a false report.
Then are you saying
that this was a political attack
on Director Choi Dohyung
and Candidate Kim Jinsun?
I can't tell you anything further
other than the fact
that the Youngseo Prosecutor's Office
will not be used for any politics.
-Just a moment.
- Won Jaegu, that son of a bitch!
This is Choi Dohyung's doing!
Sir, please calm down for...
It doesn't take a lot to find
Won Jaegu's weakness to control him.
This was a mistake!
Calm down, sir.
This won't affect the election that much.
If things take a wrong turn,
that retired policeman
might win against me.
That won't happen, sir.
- Chief Baek.
- Yes, sir.
Kill him.
What do you think?
Wouldn't that solve everything?
You can't, sir. Director Yong is...
Get out!
- Sir...
- I said get out!
You're right, sir.
It's best to get rid of
the root of the problem.
I knew I'd be able to get through to you.
Can you take care of it tonight
along with Hwanju?
Of course.
This is why you've supported
Geumjeong Society all this time.
Yes, all right.
You might want to play,
but you have to sleep
to wake up in the morning.
- They're here. What do we do?
- Should we dispatch the squad?
No. Wait until they all move.
Yes, sir.
What?
What the hell is going on?
What the fuck is all this?
- Those fucking bastards...
- Where are you going? Hey!
- Good night.
Let's go.
YOUNGSEO WELFARE FOUNDATION
Does he really have to go this far?
Drop your guns!
Hold still!
Are the transfer team here yet?
It seems like they'll be late.
-Go check one more time.
- All right, ma'am.
It seems
that things are getting chaotic again.
Do you...
want me to give you
a piece of sincere advice?
Kim Taekrok.
Don't get too involved with him.
He'll bring you your doom.
Mr. Han Giyong.
Let me ask you something
before you're transferred.
"Geumjeong Society." What does that mean?
"Geumjeong."
What does "Geumjeong" mean?
That...
is for you to find out yourself.
Who are you people?
Are you the police? Where are you from?
Homicide at Geumo station.
Where are you from?
Narcotics at Youngseo Provincial
Police Agency.
How did you know to come here?
We're carrying out an operation
to arrest a drug offender
upon request from Chief Baek Seongil.
Was there a mistake?
What happened?
Where did things start to go wrong?
What am I missing?
So does Geumjeong Society
work only for Lee Youngho?
I don't know much about that,
but the thing Geumjeong Society
deemed the most important
was the organization itself.
What's important to them
isn't Lee Youngho's safety.
It's to keep their organization hidden.
And what do they need to get rid of
to do that?
What on earth are you doing?
So does Lee Youngho now want me dead?
Please understand.
Do you really think this is right?
Do you think it's right
to serve such a master?
The one
that threatens their existence the most
is Team Leader Han.
Please take care of it as planned.
What on earth do you hope to gain
by serving such a man?
What do you think you're doing?
Are you all right?
This is your last chance.
You walk out that door, and you die.
Team Leader Yeon.
Hold on.
Wake up.
What choice are you going to make?
SHADOW DETECTIVE SEASON 2
Modify by Blue-Bird™