6 MONTHS AGO
Within less than a month,
three police officers have died,
and one was put in prison.
On top of that,
the man known to be behind all this
died before he could be investigated.
It must have been murder
disguised as suicide.
So you are as sharp as they say.
Who is this?
The only one who's made it out alive
from all this chaos.
In three months,
you'll be assigned team leader
to Geumo's Women and Juvenile Affairs.
It's up to you to uncover the truth.
Use any means necessary.
Your starting point...
is him.
But why me?
I'm not part of the inspection department.
SHADOW DETECTIVE SEASON 2
Heavy traffic is expected
on Youngseo Boulevard
in both directions.
That's all for the traffic report.
Mr. Seo Gwangsu,
former Chief of Geumo Police Station
who was arrested for accepting bribes
has been released this morning
on probation.
He's out!
You were granted probation today.
Are you satisfied with the ruling?
NEWS Do you have any comments
on the deaths of your colleagues
involved in the corruption?
I cannot apologize enough to you all.
In accordance with the ruling,
I will repent for my crimes
and reflect on them deeply.
From now on, I will serve the community
without pursuing any self-interest.
Do you really not know
about the slush fund?
I have no idea.
Please refrain
from making baseless accusations.
-Thank you.
-Wait.
-Please tell us more.
-What are your plans now?
COURT
The court explained they took into account
the fact that Mr. Seo voluntarily appeared
and turned himself in back in 2022,
the fact that he is deeply
regretting his crime,
and his history of contributing
to the local community.
-Most major roads in Geumo City...
-This is the last one.
-...are experiencing traffic jams.
-Restock on time, kid.
And special attention is required
-on Geumo Inner Beltway
-You eat these every day, that's why.
since there was an accident.
NEW With the ninth
local elections just five days ahead,
in an election poll for governor
of Youngseo Province,
Future Freedom party candidate
Lee Youngho's approval rating
dropped by 3.5 percent
compared to last week.
As a result, the gap
between the approval ratings
of candidate Lee Youngho and candidate
Kim Jinsun of Upright Country Party
is now within the margin of error.
Candidate Lee's election camp
has announced
that Candidate Lee was not involved
in the illegal real estate dealings
of Bank President Kang,
who is a close associate of his.
Nevertheless, it seems
this has affected his approval ratings.
With the election just around the corner,
public attention is focused
on how the scandal
involving Candidate Lee's associates
will affect the election from now on.
-Thank you for your hard work.
-I'm rooting for you.
Thank you. I'm Lee Youngho,
Candidate No. 1.
-Thank you.
-Yes. Take care.
He's out on probation,
just as you planned.
FUTURE FREEDOM PARTY
CANDIDATE NO. 1
-You're here. Hello.
-Hey.
PHOTO
Room for just one person.
That's all I need.
So that one person was Seo Gwangsu.
Please give my thanks to Assemblyman Lee
for putting in the work for my release.
It wasn't a big deal.
My uncle is practically
the President of Youngseo.
Then, I guess that makes you
the Prime Minister, Director Yong.
Apologies.
Don't push it, Team Leader Han.
Sorry.
Show him what's inside.
Prime Minister is a bit too much, so...
"Minister"?
Yes, it's perfect. Minister Yong.
Minister Yong.
That's just what my uncle needs.
And this is but a small fraction.
Really?
Director Yong.
I want to get back on my feet again.
If Assemblyman Lee paves the way for me,
I promise I will pay him tenfold.
NOEUL GOSIWON
Detective Kim!
You might not make it on time today.
Maybe if I step on it...
-What brings you here?
-I'm driving you to work.
-Why?
-Carpooling.
Don't you know it saves gas
and is good for the environment?
Did you send your congratulations
to Mr. Seo Gwangsu?
The two of you are close.
He's busy.
There's no need for me to bother him.
Because his top priority
is sending his thanks
to Assemblyman Lee Youngho
through Yong Hwanju?
Are you late to work
because you were looking into that?
When it comes to my priorities,
the inspection department comes first.
Speaking of which,
let me ask you something.
What is it that they want to know?
If I were to guess, the same thing as you.
First,
we're going to uncover the full account
of everything that happened last year.
And then,
we'll find the one
behind Chief Kook and Team Leader Han.
The one that manipulated the police
and took advantage of us.
We're going to get rid
of the root of the problem.
How ambitious.
It's going to take a while.
If you and I work together,
we might be able to save some time.
Wouldn't your next opponent after
Team Leader Han be a bit too much for you?
Who's the next guy?
What if I refuse to work with you?
Then we'll go after you before them.
For concealing Seo Gwangsu's slush fund
and Team Leader Han's crimes.
Then my plans get revealed,
and the people you're after
will go into hiding.
I don't know about that...
Perhaps, I'll use you as bait
and infiltrate them myself
going undercover.
That's bold.
Think about it.
I'll be in the driver's seat,
and you in the passenger's seat.
I think it's a good partnership.
GEUMO POLICE STATION
Come on, give it a rest.
What?
You're not the only one
who can solve this case.
You're free to leave
if you aren't going to be of any help.
Sir.
-Seokhoon, come here.
-Yes, ma'am.
This is the timing device
found at the scene, right?
-Did you find where it was purchased?
-This can't be bought online.
Detective Son checked tool shops and...
I looked at all the tool shops in Geumo,
but none of them had it.
Look, Gyeongchan.
If it's not found in Geumo,
search the rest of the country.
I'm working on it.
You're not the only one
who knows how to do it.
Hey.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Hello, sir.
-Hey.
PROFILE
Hey, what are you doing?
Excuse me?
Why are you looking into this case,
you little brat?
-Sir, I'm just...
-Hey.
Don't you know victims aren't allowed
to investigate their own cases?
Don't you?
I'm not the victim.
I'm the detective in charge of...
What do you think you're doing?
Now that you mention it,
you never reported to me
when you were digging into Woo Jangik.
You got into this mess
because you ran amok
-without my orders...
-Ran amok?
-What? Did you just yell at me?
-Sir, please.
-I ran amok?
-Are you picking a fight with me?
-Am I running amok? Move!
-Hey, let me go!
Let go. You heard him!
What's wrong with you?
You're making a scene.
-Stand up straight, you punk!
-Sir, let's stop.
You fucking idiot.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
I'm sorry, sir.
Will you come to your senses?
Will you look at that darn brat?
Thank you for the food!
CANDIDATE NO. 1
LEE YOUNGHO
In today's
In-depth Exploration of Current Affairs,
we have Director Choi Dohyung,
who recently retired from the police
and founded a welfare foundation.
Hello, Director Choi.
Yes, hello.
Choi Dohyung is doing a lot
of good work even after retirement.
That's why he's so popular, I guess.
He would've been elected
if he ran for office this time.
-Those children may seem out of control...
-Tell me about it.
-I'll be back sometime.
-Come back again. Thank you.
It needs a lot of attention and support.
You said it needs a lot of attention.
Have you ever thought about
just doing that yourself, Director Choi?
Excuse me?
With the local election coming up,
you've been named the most preferred
candidate for Governor of Youngseo
in a pre-election poll.
Although, of course,
you're not running for office.
That's...
We are aware that there is public opinion
that they wish to vote for you
in the National Assembly
by-election next year.
Do you really not have
any plans on trying?
I'm not sure.
I appreciate the citizens' support,
but I am still lacking in many ways.
Tell Chief Prosecutor Won
to come by the Geumo House tonight.
Yes, sir.
All right. Help yourselves.
Who's next?
Here we go.
Hana.
You got yours earlier.
Are you getting this for Doyoon?
Doyoon didn't come home
last night, did he?
No.
But he went to see his grandmother,
so he'll be back soon.
It's true.
-Look...
-Hey, what's all this?
Hello.
You actually came.
I thought you weren't coming.
You said you would cut ties if I didn't.
I was looking forward to doing that.
Get yourself a plate. They're over there.
They're grilled to perfection.
What's with the barbecue?
A VIP patron of our foundation
sent over some meat.
You're here.
Yes, I invited her.
She should be eating well
to get better soon.
The two of you can talk. I'll go see Hana.
Uncle, I met the guy.
It turns out
getting out wasn't all he had in mind.
He's desperate to go back
to his former glory.
I only did it
to cover for President Kang's vacancy.
Don't think about
bringing him in any closer.
You got him out of there,
so you might as well
get your money's worth.
The resort complex that you promised
in your campaign.
What if we get him to invest in that?
What do you think, Mr. Cha?
How would he know?
He's never even met him.
He's not one to live
under the shadows of others.
It seems strange that
he's groveling to work under you.
You should be prudent.
What the hell do you know on the matter?
Go on home.
Tell him I appreciate the gift.
You're not going to
set a date to meet him?
What's the rush? Take it slow.
Okay.
Sir.
We were the ones who sacked Seo Gwangsu.
Yesterday's enemy can be today's ally.
If we need him, we'll use him.
If we don't, we'll throw him away.
That's how things work in this country.
Still, if he approached Director Yong
with an ulterior motive...
I'm the one who cut off his arms.
If he's up to something again,
I'll end him, then and there.
-Is Chief Prosecutor Won not here yet?
-He just left the prosecutor's office.
You don't have to go to school,
but you have to take the GED, okay?
All right.
-You promise?
-Yes.
Go on ahead.
Oh, right.
What happened to that lady?
Who?
This pork. Jinseok sent them.
He told me to invite you over,
saying you liked pork belly with soju.
He remembers everything.
I feel bad for Jinseok.
He still thinks you resent him.
When the one you really resent is me.
It's all in the past.
It doesn't mean you forgot, does it?
Aren't you the same?
That's the reason you made the foundation.
That's right.
Watching the kids reassures me.
It makes me believe
that I'm doing something
to really protect these kids.
You should just retire early
and help me out.
I'll make sure you can make a living.
Not yet.
I still have things to do.
One thing's for sure.
Neither you nor I
am destined to live comfortably.
You're right.
Well, I saw the news.
It seems like you're going to be busy.
You mean politics?
Are you thinking about running?
Honestly, I'm seriously considering it.
To achieve what I want,
I need power.
Let's drink.
Here.
YOUNGSEO WELFARE FOUNDATION
-Did you look into it?
-Yes.
Team Leader Yeon was on a business trip
to attend a seminar in Seoul.
What time did the seminar end?
At 6:00 p.m.
At 6:00...
The time Hana saw the black hoodie
was around half past 11 p.m.
She had enough time in-between.
But you said
Hana didn't even see the face.
And why would she do
something like that in the first place?
Forget it. I'm hanging up.
The theft case you've been investigating.
None of them had a safe robbed, right?
Hana wouldn't have lied
about something like that.
I think this needs to be looked into.
Kim Jinsun is visiting
Choi Dohyung's foundation tomorrow?
Yes.
It looks like she'll try recruiting him.
All right.
You can leave us, Mr. Cha.
What are you waiting for?
Still, shouldn't you meet again
with Director Choi...
I told you to leave.
Yes, sir.
Let me fill your glass.
Find out how Seo Gwangsu
approached Yong Hwanju.
Yes, sir.
How's life as the chief prosecutor
treating you?
I'm just following along the path
that you carved out, sir.
Right, you should be following
along diligently.
Of course.
You'll have to join
the National Assembly next year.
-Excuse me?
-Why are you so surprised?
You've already met Chairman Hwang.
And it'll be easy to get nominated
if we coax a few prominent assemblymen.
I'm thankful, but...
it feels like you have
a huge task for me in mind.
It's not much.
Does it have something to do
with Director Choi Dohyung?
I'm going to go check on the kids.
Have a seat.
How are you feeling?
Is that all you're worried about?
You knew about Woo Jangik
even before this case, didn't you?
What on earth are you hiding?
I'm not hiding anything.
Is Yeon Juhyun the arsonist?
-What are you talking about?
-Hana told me.
And how she told you about it.
It's not Team Leader Yeon.
You already knew who the real culprit was.
-Stop.
-I understand you're trying to protect me,
but what would you do if you were me?
-Lee Seonga!
-Go on, tell me!
Why are you... Hey!
Drop it.
GEUMO POLICE STATION
Hey.
What are you doing?
You're here.
The arson murder case was transferred
to Homicide Team 3.
-On whose order?
-Team Leader Han...
He's trading it
for the Songan-ri murder case...
-You got the cast-off.
-Hey, did you know about this?
-About what?
-Did you know they took our case?
I'm the one who suggested it.
-We can't take on the case because of you.
-What?
Hey, I'll bring these over.
Jeez.
What happened to the arson case?
Do you have a suspect?
The investigation's on,
so we'll have someone.
I'm working on it.
You're not the only one
who knows how to do it.
Come with me for a second.
Tell me about the tool shops.
BAEK SEONGIL
You asked to see me.
Why aren't you saying anything?
I see you're impatient as ever.
You can't even enjoy your tea.
It's not anything special
to discuss, but...
A lot has happened to you as of late.
A junior of yours has been injured,
and a close acquaintance of yours
was suspected of a crime.
I wanted to know how you were holding up.
I'm good.
You took a leave of absence for a year
and a half due to a panic disorder.
That's not something
you recover from so easily, is it?
Yes, come in.
Chief, there's something
I have to talk to you about.
All right. If you're done,
I'll get going...
Sure.
I heard former Chief Seo Gwangsu
was released yesterday.
Have you reached out to him?
No.
To tell you the truth,
I'm not very happy about it
as the current chief.
I'm working hard to reform the image
of the Geumo police.
And if the former chief,
with his corruption scandal,
were to get involved with someone here,
it would be a huge problem.
You don't have to worry about that.
I mean, he and I aren't so chummy.
-I'll be on my way.
-Sure.
Team Leader Han, take a seat.
-How old are you?
-Fifteen.
Are you all around the same age?
You all look similar somewhat.
-The weather has gotten cold, hasn't it?
-Yes.
Make sure to eat well. I'll see you again.
-Take care, everyone.
-Okay.
-Stay healthy.
CANDIDATE NO. 2
UPRIGHT COUNTRY PARTY, KIM JINSUN
Okay.
How do you think
your visit today will help?
What are your plans?
The kids look like
they'd need winter jackets.
I'll take it as payment for the photo op.
The kids here have the brightest faces
among the facilities that I've been to.
Oh. Don't get me wrong.
I also grew up with nothing,
so I know how terrible poverty is.
That's why I like politics.
There's no other playground like this
for self-made people like yourself and I.
Playground...
Is there a reason I should join you
in that playground?
If you give me your support,
Director Choi,
it's definitely possible to turn around
the tables at the last minute.
You know that
you have that kind of influence.
What do I get...
from doing so?
You didn't move back to Geumo for nothing.
You should have a seat
at the National Assembly.
I will become governor,
and no matter what it takes,
I will bring Youngseo Province
and Geumo City to success!
LEE YOUNGHO
I will make Geumo
the greatest port city in Asia!
Lee Youngho!
When was this?
Right after Seo Gwangsu was released.
...support me until the very end.
I will serve you
even from the lowest places!
A REAL WORKER FOR THE PEOPLE
LEE YOUNGHO
It seems that Yong Hwanju
is a bigger simpleton than we thought.
He'll be easy to control.
Do you think you'll be able
to approach Manager Cha?
I still need more time.
FUTURE FREEDOM PARTY
LEE YOUNGHO
APPOINTMENT CEREMONY OF SECURITY SECRETARY
JANG SECURITIES CHAIRMAN JANG SUNGTAE
Lee Youngho's secretary,
Cha Kyungpil,
also known as Secretary Cha.
He's the heavyweight
who manages everything
that happens around Lee Youngho,
whether public or private.
It would be one of his responsibilities
to look into people
who approach Assemblyman Lee.
If you're right,
Secretary Cha must be watching me already.
What should I do?
Team Leader Han called,
asking to be paid for introducing me.
-When?
-Tonight.
He seems to be in urgent need of money.
Chief, there's something
I have to talk to you about.
Tonight.
Excuse me.
I'm with Geumo Police.
Come on.
I already gave the police everything.
Why do you cops keep bugging me?
You mean the security footage?
Yes, that's right!
I looked into everything you asked.
There's not much, but take a look
at her high school records.
SCHOOL RECORDS
FATHER'S NAME: YEON SANGHOON
FAMILY DETAILS
FATHER:
Will you make me run a background check
on everyone transferred to Geumo?
Do you think I enjoy doing this?
That's what I mean.
Don't you get exhausted living like this?
-She graduated from the police academy?
-Yes.
She's only ever been
in Women and Juveniles.
She's even been appointed
as team leader this time.
FATHER:
But why isn't there any record
about her father?
FATHER'S NAME: YEON SANGHOON
She intentionally omitted
her father's information.
Isn't it strange?
She had records of her father
until high school,
but it's not on her personnel record.
Yeon Sanghoon?
Look into Yeon Sanghoon for me.
See you.
LIEUTENANT KIM TAEKROK
Yes?
The Chief ordered us to assemble, Ma'am.
Yes, I'll be there.
Have a seat.
Listen carefully to what I'm about to say.
We received an anonymous tip-off
about an employee in our station
trying to cover up the investigation
on the murder of Woo Jangik.
Along with evidence that there was
a significant monetary transaction
between Woo Jangik and said staff.
I'm sorry, sir.
Quiet down.
I cannot allow this kind of corruption
to happen again at Geumo Police Station.
Whoever is involved in this matter
in any way,
I urge you to confess
before it's too late.
This is your last chance.
Things are taking a strange turn.
-Hey.
-I'll send you an address.
Tell Team Leader Han to meet you there.
By ten o'clock.
Yes, all right.
And Yong Hwanju?
I'm on my way to see him.
Hm.
KIM TAEKROK
GRAND MALL, 29, HYOYONG-RO,
SEONJU-EUP, GEUMO
He still used to be a cop,
even if he's not one anymore.
Can we really trust him?
Why would he have gone to jail
if he was a good cop?
We need to get
as much as we can out of him.
Be sure to get him hooked
when he gets here.
You're about to be the governor's nephew.
Why are you always talking about money?
It's not like I get paid
for being the governor's nephew.
I should invest some money
so that I can get a nice position.
Those university smartasses
have been sucking up to my uncle
trying to take everything for themselves.
Those fucking pricks.
He's here.
I hear you're the new big man in Geumo.
Not at all.
Mr. Son here
is trying to get big in the drug business.
I thought he'd be able
to talk to you about business.
Hm. Drug business?
Don't pretend you don't know.
I know you made some good money
back in the day.
Oh, dear.
I'm not sure
if there are any dealers left in Geumo.
I haven't been able
to make a move for a while,
but I just shipped some over
from abroad recently.
It's doing better than I thought,
so I wanted to expand.
You're the expert in that area.
So why don't you coach us?
Invest in us and look out for us.
If you do that,
I'll take good care of you for sure.
So how do you bring in
the stuff these days?
It seems a lot has changed since my days.
SEONGA, WHAT ARE YOU UP TO
THAT I CAN'T REACH YOU ALL DAY?
It's me. Is Seonga at her desk?
No. She left to go to the tool shops
early this afternoon,
and she hasn't come back.
All right then.
-Hey, you...
-Careful with the stairs.
You discussed everything
with Gwangsu, right?
-Yeah.
-Take good care of him, okay?
-Bring him home, will you?
-I will. What about you?
I called a driver myself.
Okay. I hope to see you again.
-Sure.
-Good.
What should I do?
Secretary Cha knows that Yong Hwanju,
the junkie, is a liability to Lee Youngho.
If you keep messing with Yong Hwanju,
he'll show up.
I threw a stone at them.
I'll be straightforward.
Why are you trying to get close
to Assemblyman Lee?
Probably the same reason as you.
I want to be close to power
to secure a good position for myself.
Don't be too wary of me.
Who knows?
I might be of huge help to you
and Assemblyman Lee Youngho.
The ripples
will gradually spread out.
How long will it take for
the inspection department to take action?
It will have to be at least 10:00 p.m.
for them to get to Geumo.
Okay.
I'll get Team Leader Han to show up
by then. You take him somewhere safe.
We have to wrap this up within the night.
Or else we might lose
an important witness.
The inspection department is here
on standby.
Is Team Leader Han
supposed to be here by ten?
He is.
You don't think
he caught on to our trap, do you?
He was probably out of it all day today.
He has to get money,
and he has to secure a means to survive.
Okay. I'll be in touch when it's over.
Let me ask you something
now that we're working together.
Since when did you know?
-What are you talking about?
-The fact that Team Leader Han...
...is working under Chief Baek.
You want to be transferred?
Yes, there's a vacancy for a section chief
at a provincial police agency.
And as you're aware,
Lee Seonga keeps digging into things.
If she catches on, me and you...
-But Team Leader Han.
-Yes?
You're the one who failed
to finish things.
So why should I accommodate your request?
SEONGA
Come on.
SON GYEONGCHAN
The one who ordered Team Leader Han
to murder Woo Jangik
is undoubtedly Chief Baek...
JOINT INVESTIGATION TEAM FORMED
TO ERADICATE DRUG GANGS IN SEOUL
LEE YOUNGHO AND YG GROUP'S
WINTER PROJECT TO HELP THE ELDERLY
...for the sake of Lee Youngho.
Chief Baek is plotting
to pin everything on Team Leader Han
and get rid of him later.
Team Leader Han probably realized that
and contacted Gwangsu
to scrape up funds for his escape.
And what if Chief Baek found out about it?
We received an anonymous tip-off
about an employee in our station
trying to cover up the investigation
on the murder of Woo Jangik.
If so, Chief Baek will definitely
eliminate Team Leader Han by tonight.
We need to get Team Leader Han away
before Chief Baek makes his move.
There's something
you have to take care of.
SON GYEONGCHAN
Hey, what's up?
I can't get in touch with Seonga.
I think she's after Team Leader Han.
What are you talking about?
They transferred the case.
Well, they did.
But I guess
she's been investigating on her own.
TAEKROK
TO CHIEF SEO
I'M HERE
THERE MAY BE PEOPLE WATCHING,
COME INSIDE
Darn it.
Your call cannot be connected...
-Hello?
-Lee Seonga is headed over there.
What are you talking about?
Why would Detective Lee...
The target is entering the mall.
Han is here. We'll proceed
with the operation as planned.
Shit, why did he pick a place like this?
What the hell...
God damn it...
Hands in the air!
Hold on. What is this? Wait.
Team Leader Han Giyong?
We're from the inspection department.
What is this?
Don't do anything rash.
You'll have to come with us.
What the fuck does the inspection
department want with me anyway?
-What the fuck is this? Let me go.
-Take him.
-Don't make this hard, just cooperate.
-Let go. Cooperate, my foot!
Shit!
Punk!
Get him!
Darn you!
SHADOW DETECTIVE SEASON 2
Modify by Blue-Bird™