JEWS FORBIDDEN
You!
Come here.
Why haven't you greeted us?
I'm sorry.
The sidewalk is forbidden for you.
Go to the gutter.
- What is it? Are you in a hurry?
- What's wrong with you?
- Come on, do something.
- Right. Dance!
- Dance!
Come on, come on! Dance!
Very well.
What about you?
Dance with him.
Let's clear the street,
so the Jews can dance.
Come on. And you.
Go on.
Faster!
Come on!
Come on, move! I said faster!
Come on, Jews!
- Keep dancing.
- Dance.
Hold it!
You little bastard!
Turn on the lights.
Come on!
Open the door!
Let us in!
Stand up!
You, stand up! Come on!
Throw him out!
Come on, run!
- Hands up.
- How are you?
- You, bandit.
Dead! Dead!
- He's crazy.
- Hands up.
- Want a cigarette?
- Cigarette?
Thank you.
Everything is alright!
He looks very happy.
Everything is alright.
Hands up! Hands up!
It's alright.
Help! Help!
Let go! Help!
At least we got work
in the ghetto.
At least we are still together.
Everybody out!
To the courtyard!
Move, move!
We are workers. We have
employment certification.
Go over there. Hurry.
You.
You. You.
The others, put your clothes on
and come back here.
Bring your things with you.
15 kilos only.
Where are you taking us?
Attention!
Forward march!
Onward!
Turn left!
On the march!
Stop! Halt!
Attention!
At ease.
Turn right!
Step forward.
You.
You. You.
Down on the ground!
Turn left!
On the march.
You! Come here!
Take this! Take this!
Take him away.
Round up only the Jews!
Round up!
Only the Jews.
The Polish keep working.
Dismiss them.
Have you got a plaster?
What are you up to?
What have you got there?
We are allowed to take
food to the ghetto.
Three kilos of potato and bread.
Open it.
- It's only potatoes and bread.
- You're lying. That's not true.
Open it.
Potatoes!
You Jews are all alike.
We offer you a finger...
and you take the whole hand.
If you lie to me again,
I'll kill you. Personally.
- Halt!
Wait. What's going on here?
Take this! Take this!
I'll teach you some discipline,
you dirty Jews.
Do you know why
you're being hit?
- No.
- Do you know why you're being hit?
- Why?
- To celebrate New Year.
On the march!
March and sing!
Sing something nice!
Loud and clear!
Come.
DO NOT PASS
Spread out!
We're being attacked!
Take cover!
Shoot!
Take cover! Fire!
Come on, get out!
The attack was successful.
That building...
Turn around!
Shoot!
Come here.
Be careful with it.
That's it. Be careful.
Throw a grenade!
There's a wounded man over there!
Come.
Watch out! Watch out!
- I'll go get help!
- Hurry!
Come on! Bring the stretcher!
Go back inside!
Are you alright?
There's too much dust.
I'll check this side.
Don't worry.
Be careful!
- Heinrich?
- I'm checking!
Is there anybody here?
- Come on down!
- Alright, I'm coming.
Come on, pile them up.
Throw it.
We have to mark everything.
Come on.
What are you doing here?
Who are you?
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
What are you doing?
I was...
trying to open this can.
Do you live here?
Do you work here?
No.
What do you do for a living?
I am...
I was a pianist.
Pianist?
Come.
Play something.
Are you hiding here?
Jew?
Where are you hiding yourself?
In the attic.
Show it to me.
Have you got anything to eat?
According to them,
it's very important that...
Attention!
- At ease.
Jew?
Please.
What does it mean,
all that shooting?
The Russians,
on the other side of the river.
You just have to hold on
a couple of weeks, not more.
- What's going on?
- We're leaving.
- Are the Russians here?
- Not yet.
I don't know how to thank you.
Thank God, not me.
He wants us to survive. At least,
we have to believe in that.
Here. Take it.
- And you?
- I have another one. Warmer.
What are you going to do
when this is over?
I'll play piano again at
the Polish radio station.
Tell me your name.
Maybe I'll listen to you playing.
Szpilman.
Perfect name for a pianist.
Musician?
Are you a musician?
Do you know...
a pianist called Szpilman,
from the Polish radio station?
- Of course I know him.
- I helped him to hide himself.
Tell him I'm here.
Ask him to help me.
- What's your name?
- Hosenfeld.
What?
Subtitled by Cook Street Subs 2007