What went we out
into this wilderness to find?
Leaving our country, kindred...
our father's houses?
We travailed a vast ocean...
For what? For what?
We must ask thee to be silent.
Was it not for the pure
and faithful dispensation of the Gospels
- and the Kingdom of God?
- No more!
We are your judges, and not you ours.
I cannot be judged by false Christians,
for I have done nothing
save preach Christ through gospel.
Must you continue to dishonor
the laws of the commonwealth
and the church with your prideful conceit?
If my conscience sees it fit.
Then shall you be banished
from this plantation's liberties!
I would be glad on it.
Then take your leave
and trouble us no further.
How sadly hath the Lord
testified against you.
Katherine.
Thomasin.
Come.
I will confess Jehovah with all heart
In secret and in assembly of the just...
I here confess I've lived in sin.
I've been idle of my work,
disobedient to my parents,
neglectful of my prayer.
I have, in secret, played upon my Sabbath.
And broken every one of thy
commandments in thought.
Followed the desires of mine
own will, and not the Holy Spirit.
I know I deserve more shame
and misery in this life...
and everlasting hellï¬re.
But I beg Thee...
for the sake of Thy Son...
forgive me, show me mercy,
show me Thy light.
Thomasin.
Boo!
There you are, there you are.
Where is Sam? Where is Sam?
Where is that little man?
Boo!
There you are, there you are.
Sam.
Samuel!
Thomasin.
Sleep.
All will be well, sleep.
Caleb.
God give you good morrow.
All are still a-bed.
Save Mother.
Tis no ease to rise on a gray day.
The Devil holds fast your eyelids.
- I'll wake em.
- No, let em be.
Thy Mother's not slept a night since...
We can search no more, Caleb. We cannot.
If not a wolf, then hunger
would have taken him yet.
Let's to the wood.
Been a'layin traps for some while now,
even before this new misery.
Within the wood?
Will thou not help thy father?
You and Mother have always
forbade us to set foot there.
Caleb, our harvest cannot last the winter.
We must catch our food
if we cannot grow it.
We will conquer this wilderness.
It will not consume us.
Aren't thou then born a sinner?
Aye, I was conceived in sin
and born in iniquity.
Then what is thy birth sin?
Adam's sin imputed to me and a corrupt
nature dwelling within me.
Well remembered, Caleb, very well.
And canst thou tell me
what thy corrupt nature is?
My corrupt nature is empty of grace,
bent unto sin, only unto sin
and that continually.
Soft now.
We must lay it again.
Was, was Samuel born a sinner?
Aye.
Am I then...
We pray he hath entered God's Kingdom.
What wickedness hath he done?
Place faith in God, Caleb.
We'll speak no more on thy brother.
Why?
He hath disappeared, not one week passed.
Yet you and Mother utter not his name.
He's gone, Caleb.
- Tell me!
- Tell thee what?
- Is he in hell?
- Caleb!
Mother will not stop her prayer.
And if I died, if I died this day...
- What is this?
- I ought evil in me heart.
- Me sins are not pardoned!
- Thou art youngly yet...
And if God will not hear my prayers?!
- Caleb!
- Tell me!
Look you, I love thee marvelous well,
but 'tis God alone, not man,
what knows who is the son
of Abraham and who is not,
who is good and who is evil.
Fain would I tell thee
Sam sleeps in Jesus,
that thou wilt, that I will.
But I cannot tell thee that. None can.
Caleb?
Where are these from?
From Indian Tom and old Slater,
when last they past through.
What did you trade?
Thy Mother's silver cup.
Speak none of this to Mother. None.
She's overwrought already.
I'll tell her of the cup
when her grief has passed.
Let's not speak on this again.
Aye.
Fowler!
Fool of an animal.
Fowler, what's this?
Praise be to God. Make haste, Caleb.
Fie upon't!
- Father, it died.
- The other end.
Father?
Father!
Fowler.
Black Phillip, Black Phillip,
a crown grows on his head
Black Phillip, Black Phillip
to nanny queen is wed
Jump to the fence post...
- Jonas! Mercy! Come hither!
- Black Phillip, Black Phillip
King of all...
Jonas! Mercy!
Black Phillip, Black Phillip,
king of sky and land
king of sea and sand
We are ye servants, we are ye men
Black Phillip eats the lions
from the lions' den.
Black Phillip, Black Phillip,
a crown grows on his head...
Get back! You two, stop that!
Phillip, back!
Heavens bless us!
Caleb, hold the gate.
Caleb!
Get in!
Oh.
I'll have thee quiet.
Wither were you and Caleb this morn?
How could you disappear?
And thee, I told thee to keep
watch of Jonas and Mercy.
I was, and I bade them help me
and they paid me no mind.
- I was a-getting...
- What's the matter with thee, Thomasin?
What is the matter with thee?
Take thy father's rags to
the brook and wash them.
- They would pay me no mind.
- And brush out his woolens.
Help him!
Wee one, it gave me such
a fright to find thee gone.
I will not be left here alone. Dost hear?
A morning's work is well behindhand.
Jonas, leave thy sister be.
- She likes it.
- William.
What, can't a father spend
Godly time with his son?
Jonas!
- Father said stop it.
- Thomasin!
- Stop.
- Stop it!
Each of ya, stop it.
Thomasin, take the twins inside.
No!
Get inside, get inside, get inside.
As you like.
We went to find apples!
In the valley.
I thought I seen an apple tree
in the valley.
Father brought the gun,
for if we glanced that wolf...
Why did you not tell me?
Father wanted it a surprise,
to cheer you, and...
but there were none.
I thought I seen em.
I like you not outside
the farm, even to the valley.
Dost hear me?
Caleb, be a good lad
and get some water for thy Mother.
Stray not from the brook.
Why are you dallying?
What then?
What?
Caleb? Caleb!
Stop it.
I meant no harm in it.
What's the matter with thee?
Come hither.
What's the matter with thee, eh?
Shh.
I've seen no apples
since we went from England.
I would thou hadst found them.
I so wish for one.
Hear that?
Aye.
Who's there?
I be the Witch of the Wood!
Mercy, come out.
I be not Mercy,
I be the Witch of the Wood
and I have come to steal ye.
Hear me stick a-flying through the trees:
Clickety-clackity, clickety-clackity!
- Mercy!
- Clickety-clackity.
Why is't when thou dost a wrong,
I be a-washin Father's clothes
like a slave,
- and thou art playing idle?
- Because Mother hates you.
Spoilt child. I'll tell Mother
you've left the farm alone.
Black Phillip saith I can do what I like.
Devil take your Black Phillip.
It's your fault I can't leave the yard.
I could go to the brook
before you let The Witch take Sam.
- Quiet, thee.
- It were a wolf stole Sam.
A witch. I've seen her in her
riding cloak, about the wood.
- Father showed me the tracks.
- It was a witch.
Aye, it was a witch,
Mercy, you speak aright.
- Thomasin!
- It was I.
Liar.
Twas I what stole him,
I be the witch of the wood.
- Liar! Liar!
- I am.
List not to her, Mercy.
I am that very witch.
When I sleep, my spirit slips
away from my body
and dances naked with The Devil.
- That's how I signed his book.
- No.
He bade me bring him an unbaptized babe,
so I stole Sam
and I gave him to me master.
And I'll make any man
or thing else vanish I like.
- No.
- Aye.
And I'll vanish thee, too,
if thou displeaseth me.
- Be quiet!
- Mercy, she's but telling fantasies.
Perchance I boil and bake thee
since we're lack of food.
- No!
- Stop, Thomasin!
- It's not true!
- It is, thou thing!
How I crave to sink my teeth
into thy pink flesh.
If ever thou tellst thy Mother of this,
I'll witch thee and thy Mother!
And Jonas too!
- Caleb!
- Stop thy tears and swear by silence.
- I swear it.
- You'll not tell Mother nor father.
- I swear.
- Thomasin! Let her alone.
Get away from her, Caleb,
or she'll witch thee!
Why tell Mercy those horrible fantasies?
- Dost thou hate me now too?
- It was a wolf stole Sam.
Leave me be. Go tell Mother
and father of my wickedness.
- Thomasin...
- I hate thy pity. I need it not.
And forgive us the sins we have
this day committed against thee,
free us from the shame and torment
which are due unto us, Father.
We beseech thee, increase our faith
in the promise of the Gospel,
our fear of thy name
and the hatred of all our sins,
that we may be assured that
the Holy Spirit dwells in us.
That we might be thy children
in thy love and mercy,
but as we hunger
for this food of our bodies
so our souls hunger
for the food of eternal life.
Finish soon our days of sin,
and bring us to eternal peace
through the purifying blood of Thy Son,
our Lord and only Savior Jesus Christ.
- Amen.
Thomasin, what's thou done
with the silver cup?
Is't not on the shelf?
Nay.
In the six board, then.
T'ain't there neither.
It's been disappeared for some while.
Didst lose it?
I've not touched it.
Where has it gone then?
I haven't touched it.
I've caught thee trifling with it before.
She says she haven't touched it,
Katherine.
How thou couldst lose my father's
silver wine cup in this hovel,
- I cannot know.
- I haven't touched it.
Peace, child. It's gone.
Did a wolf vanish that too?
She haven't touched it, Katherine.
What is amiss on this farm? Hmm?
It is not natural.
Caleb, will thou read out
a chapter of the Word tonight?
We must find some light in our darkness.
Tomorrow we will have a fast day
but for our sins.
Thomasin, dist not bed them down
before supper?
Baah, baah.
Oh, Holy and blessed Spirit,
be with me and dwell in me heart.
You must sleep tonight, Kate.
This night and evermore, amen.
Thou dost remember I love thee?
I do.
List me, Kate,
I fear thou dost look
too much upon this affliction.
We must turn our thoughts
towards God, not to ourselves.
He hath never taken a child from us.
Never a one, Kate.
Who might earn such grace?
We have been grateful of God's love.
He hath cursed this family.
No.
He hath taken us
into a very low condition to humble us
and to show us more of His grace.
Was not Christ lead into the wilderness
to be ill met by the Devil?
We should ne'er have left the plantation.
Kate.
- We should never have left!
- That damned church.
- There's naught hither!
- Well, what need we? Silver chalices?
How dare you chide me on a cup?
Tis not for vanity
that I am grieved of it.
Katherine, I must tell thee...
- We might have sold it.
- What?
What fool would trade for our corn?
List me, our daughter hath begat
the sign of her womanhood.
Thomasin? Caleb?
Are you abed?
Mercy?
Jonas?
She's old enough.
She must leave to serve another family.
Twas not her fault.
Kate, I must tell thee...
Aye, it was thine
for taking thy family hither.
This is Godly land.
Godly?
Our children are being fostered up
like savages.
Kate!
How oft I begged and begged thee
to take Samuel for baptism?
They'd not baptize
outside the congregation.
Our Sam is in hell!
Go to.
God save us, Caleb is well.
We must keep him still. And Thomasin.
Our corn is trash!
We cannot back to that church.
We will starve!
Peace, peace. You'll wake them, peace.
I'll to the village with the horse
and Thomasin tomorrow.
The Tildens or the Whythings,
they can make use of her.
They're good folk.
Stop, Kate.
We will find food, I know it.
Caleb?
What are you doing?
Go to sleep.
What is this? Tell me, now.
- Running away then?
- No.
- Lie not to me.
- I don't.
Then what?
Tell me!
If thou went back to sleep
and kept silent of this,
I promise thee,
you'll need not leave to serve
the Tildens nor any family else.
I'll be back by mid-day.
- Well, let me along with ya.
- No.
- Let me along.
- I cannot.
If you don't let me along with ya,
I'll wake Mother and father this instant.
Well?
Aye, but we did!
- Nay.
- We did!
No.
We had glass windows in England.
We haven't been hither
so long you can forget that.
As you like, Thomasin?
You've gone mad.
Dost not remember Fowler
laying on the floor in the sun?
- You must!
- Nay.
And where the sun would shine,
would he warm himself.
Remember once he lay upon the table,
and father saw him and he saith,
"We will have him for meat!
Kate! Kate! We will roast this beast."
You must remember that!
I remember that day, but no glass.
Well... it was pretty.
What is't, boy?
Burt, calm thee!
Fowler! Nay, Fowler!
Stand here with Burt.
- Caleb, no.
- I'll straight back.
He's gone mad!
- Thomasin!
- Caleb!
Thomasin!
- Thomasin!
- Caleb!
Thomasin!
Fowler!
O God, my Lord, I now begin,
o help me and I'll leave my sin.
For I repentant now shall be,
From evil I will turn to Thee.
None ever shall destroy my faith,
nor do I mind what Satan saith.
O God, my Lord, I now begin,
O, help me and I'll leave my sin,
For I repentant now shall be,
from evil I will turn to Thee.
None ever shall destroy my faith,
nor do I mind what Satan saith.
O God, my Lord, I now begin,
O help me and I...
Caleb!
- Caleb!
- Father!
Thomasin.
Oh, my girl, my girl.
Where is thy brother?
What's the matter with thee, Thomasin?
What's the matter with thee?
I'll set off at first light.
I'll not return until I've found him.
T'would be better to go to the village
to raise up help, I cannot...
Tis a day's ride and I have no horse.
There's no time to be lost.
Likely you should have left
this morn, then.
You have no gun, William,
nay, not even a dog.
- Be not a fool!
- I am a fool to go.
There is none will help this family.
Let me be!
The moon is bright,
the rain bothers me not.
I'll be back in a two-day,
if any a man will return with me.
- Don't go, Father!
- Enough!
Tell us why you went to the wood.
- I promised.
- I care not!
Let me find favor in your eyes.
Oh, child, tell me and I will!
I, um...
Speak!
I...
I took thy father's cup.
I sold it.
Forgive me, Kate. Forgive me, Thomasin.
What is this?
Katherine, I must make confession.
I yestermorn took Caleb to the wood.
Twas for food,
and the pelts for money, good money.
I knew you were false! I knew it!
I meant it as a surprise,
that is why I kept secret.
I will trap that wolf, Kate.
You stood by whilst our son lied to me!
Twas for thy sake! I love thee, Kate.
- You took him to the woods!
- I will find him!
You've broken God's covenant.
You're a liar.
And you've lost another child.
- I will go now.
- You cannot escape the woods.
I will find him!
And kill thyself too?
Will Jonas be the man of the house?
Will you damn all your family to death?!
- Katherine!
- Let go of me!
Picking apples.
Mother, have the goats
been bedded down yet?
- Nay.
- I'll to it.
Let it wait til the morrow.
They dare not escape with this rain.
Nay, I'll to it.
Please you, Mother.
Come hither, child.
Hurry back.
Caleb...
Father!
Caleb, Caleb...
Shh.
Oh, merciful Father,
both the Lord and giver of life.
Thy sole, Jesus Christ, we beseech thee.
Look down from Heaven upon him
with those eyes of grace and compassion.
Pity thy wounded servant...
Baa, baa. Baa, baa, baa.
What ails Caleb, Black Phillip?
What ails him?
Did Thomasin make 'im sick in the wood?
What say you?
Black Phillip says you are wicked.
Aye, he told me too.
Damn your Black Phillip.
He says you put the Devil
in Caleb, that's why he's sick.
I'd never hurt Caleb, nor Sam, nor thee.
- You beat me.
- T'was a jest.
- You said you'd eat of me.
- Mercy!
Mother and Father will find out.
- What?
- That you are a witch!
Thomasin!
Thomasin?
Dost remember John Kempe's son?
That first winter, he was
tormented of Indian magic.
'Tis not the same.
- This is unnatural providence.
- I know not that.
Look at thy son.
- Will.
- What?
- Think!
- Think what?
- I have no thoughts.
Does this not look like witchcraft?
What witch?
Who does this then? Who?
Thy thoughts are as a child.
What are you doing?
We'll back to the plantation
in the morning.
Find a good family for Thomasin,
take Caleb to the doctor's.
He'll tell if this be
some natural ill or not.
Yet we cannot return as beggars.
I'll scour the field. There must be
some fruit yet untouched by this rot.
I beseech thee, Katherine,
what canst thou do for him presently?
How might we all bare it
to the village with no horse?
Well, the little corn and the goat
should fetch a fair price.
We'll... We'll back with Caleb
and sell them,
return with the horse
for the twins and Thomasin.
- You cannot leave them here!
- Thomasin and thee...
Oh, forget the crop, Will!
What?!
What dost thou want, Katherine?
Tell me and I will give it thee.
I want to be home.
Thou shall be home,
by candle-time tomorrow.
In England.
Oh, Will...
I also have a confession to make.
I never meant to be a shrew to thee.
I have become as Job's wife, I know it.
But since Sam, since...
My heart has turned to stone.
I dreamed once,
t'was when I was of Thomasin's years,
that I was with Christ upon Earth.
Oh, I was so very near Him.
And in many tears for the assurance
of the pardon of me sins.
And I was so ravaged
with His love towards me,
I thought it far exceeding
the affection of the kindest husband.
And since Samuel disappeared...
I have such a sad weakness
of faith, I cannot shake it.
I cannot see Christ's help as near.
I pray and I pray, but I cannot.
I fear I cannot ever feel
that same measure of love again.
Thou shall have of it in Heaven.
I'll be in field.
If you can spare a while, do.
We'll leave at dawn.
I promise thee that.
Jonas, Mercy, come hither!
Speak not a word!
Black Phillip is a merry, merry king
- He rules the land with mirth...
- I cannot abide your songs.
Please you, Mercy.
Black Phillip has a mighty, mighty sting
He'll knock thee to the Earth
Sing bah, bah, King Phillip, the black
- Sing bah, bah, bah, bah, bah
- Peace, thou thing!
Mercy. Thomasin.
Sing bah, bah, King Phillip, the black
- He'll knock thee on thy back!
- Enough!
Come.
Get the broadaxe and cut off her head.
Get the narrow axe and cut off her head.
She's upon me!
She kneels!
My bowels!
My stomach!
She pinches!
Sin! Sin! Sin!!
Thomasin, take the children outside.
What does this to thee? What does this?
His mouth has sealed up.
Oh, God, William!
William! Get him up!
Hold him!
Children, away from this! Thomasin, help!
You'll break his jaws.
Father!
What is...?
William... He is witched!
- 'Tis she!
- No!
- What horrible fancy is this?
- She told me she stole Sam!
Silence!
She gave him to the Devil in the wood!
- They lie!
- What say you?
She turned Flora's milk to blood!
She had bade us keep secret from you!
- It was but a jest to quiet her, I...
- She made bargain with Satan!
- She signed his book!
- Silence!
Don't let her near me!
She'll put a curse on me!
- They conspire against me.
- Thomasin is a witch!
Nay, I'll not hear it.
I'll have proof, or Heaven help thee.
On thy knees!
Look me in the eye, daughter.
- Dost thou love the word of God?
- Yes.
Love you The Bible? Love you prayer?
Yes. Yes!
We are children of sin all,
yet I tell thee, I have raised up
no witch in this house.
Let us pray, then we need fear nothing.
We shall never lie open to the wicked one.
Pray for thy brother.
- You must believe us!
- Evil wretches!
Thomasin!
Pray.
Our Father, which art in Heaven,
hallowed be thy name...
Jonas, pray.
I... I cannot remember my prayer.
- What?
- Nor I. I cannot.
What nonsense is this?
Speak, children.
Our Father, which art in Heaven...
...hallowed be thy name
Stop it! Stop it!
Pray, you beasts.
Get on thy knees and pray!
Thomasin!
I don't hear this. This is not so.
It's her!
A cat.
A crow.
A raven. A three-legged dog. A wolf!
- She desires of my blood.
- Satan upon me!
- She desires of my blood!
She sends 'em upon me.
My Lord, my Jesus! Save me!
- Think on Christ!
- She sends her devils!
I am thine enemy, wallowing
in the blood of my sins!
The Lord is my shepherd, I shall not want
He maketh me to lie in green pastures,
and leadeth me by the still water...
I am thine enemy...
I am thine enemy,
wallowing on the blood
and filth of my sin!
- ...I will fear no evil
- For thou art with me.
Caleb... Caleb...
Cast a light of countenance upon me.
Spread over me the lap of Thy love.
Wash me in the everflowing
fountains of Thy blood.
Holy Thine I am, my sweet Lord Jesus.
My Lord, my love, kiss me
with the kisses of Thy mouth.
How lovely art Thou.
Thy embrace!
My Lord!
My Lord! My love!
My sole salvation!
Take me to Thy lap!
Caleb...
Caleb?
Caleb.
Caleb...
Wake up, please! Wake up!
Wake up, wake up.
Wake up.
He is dead!
Jonas, Mercy, get up.
Get up!
Get away from him! Get thee gone!
Thomasin!
Thomasin. Thomasin...
My girl...
This tree will be lovely come spring.
Do you remember when we came hither?
Such a pretty tree.
Next year I'll just own us a wheat field.
Start it at this tree and end it thither.
We'd have been a proper farm then.
Brought us a big fat milk cow,
finished us the barn.
You must tell me, Thomasin.
Tomorrow I cannot keep secret of this.
The council will be called
and thy life is...
- Thy life...
- Will you not believe me?
I saw The Serpent in my son.
You stopped their prayer, Thom...
- They lie!
- I saw it.
Caleb disappeared with thee.
- I love Caleb.
- And who then found him,
pale as death,
naked as sin and witch'd?
Thomasin, listen to me.
The bargain that was made is of no effect.
- I made no bargain.
- Thy soul belongeth to Christ.
- The Devil hath no interest in thee.
- I am no witch, father.
- What did I but see in my house?
- Will you not hear me?
- Prithee, confess.
Why have you turned against me?
Christ can un-witch us
if you will but speak truth to me.
As I love thee, speak truth.
- You ask me to speak truth?
- I beg thee.
You and Mother planned
to rid the farm of me.
Aye, I heard you speak of it.
Is that truth?
You took of Mother's cup
and let her rail at me.
You confessed not till it was too late.
- Is that truth?
- Peace thee.
- I will not.
- I am thy father.
- You are a hypocrite!
- Hold thy tongue, daughter mine.
You took Caleb to the wood and let me
take the blame of that too.
Is that truth?
You let Mother be as thy master.
You cannot bring the crops to yield!
You cannot hunt!
- Is that truth enough?
- Enough.
Thou canst do nothing save cut wood!
Bitch!
And you will not hear me!
Must I hear the Devil
wag his tongue in thy mouth?
Ask the twins then!
Go on, ask them!
They spend all day long
babbling to that horned beast.
They know well his voice.
Go to.
The Adversary oft comes
in the shape of a he-goat.
And whispers. Aye, whispers!
He is Lucifer. You know it.
- The twins know it too.
- Slander thy brethren no more.
- It is they!
- From my sight!
T'was they and that goat
what bewitched this whole farm.
Lies.
Was't a wolf stole Sam?
I never saw no wolf.
Mercy told me herself by the stream,
"I be the Witch of the Wood."
Get up. Rise!
- What is this?
- Speak.
I am no witch.
Get her from me sight!
I'll not have her in this house!
She is no witch, Katherine.
What is the cause, daughter?
Tell thy Mother!
I cannot know for certain.
Thou toldst me well thou knew.
I cannot look at her.
Aye, but ye shall. Thomasin. Thomasin!
Jonas and Mercy.
They make covenant with the Devil
in the shape of Black Phillip.
Dost hear that, ye black minions?
Dost hear that, you devils?
Wake! Wake from this!
Did ye makes some
unholy bond with that goat?
Speak, if this be pretense.
Dissemblers! Grave pretenders all.
Hear me this:
I will not play a fool
to children's games!
This is no sport, William.
Yet these lies from our babes' mouths
are but trifles to them.
- I do not lie.
- Silence, creature!
Thy son is dead, damned!
- Caleb did but cry Jesus.
- The Devil!
Thou know it not.
- The Devil will speak scripture too!
- Thou know it not.
- Tis not true!
- We are damned!
Wake!
Fetch the billhook, wife,
and I will smite Jonas as Abraham
would have done his seed.
No, stop it! Stop it!
Fetch the billhook
and I will dash his skull!
- No!
- Do you see?
- Stop it...
- Do you see now?
Please, father.
No, it's not safe. Not with them!
Keep me from this goat.
If that old billy be the Devil,
I'd have danced with him myself.
I'll break thee out upon the dawn
and we'll set back to the plantation.
Think on thy sins.
Are you witches?
Does father think I am?
Are you?
No.
Does he really speak to thee?
It is my fault.
I confess it.
Oh, my God.
My own fault.
I am infected with the filth of pride.
I know it.
I am.
Dispose of me how Thou will't...
yet redeem my children.
They cannot tame their natural evils.
I lie before Thee a coward...
and Thine enemy.
And I lick the dust of Thine earth.
I beg thee.
Save my children.
I beg Thee, my Christ,
I have not damned my family.
Me lambs... me angels!
Mother, we have longed to see you so.
As I to thee.
I must wake thy father!
He will be so glad.
No, let him sleep.
We would see you oft, Mother.
- Would that please you?
- Aye.
I have brought a book for you, Mother.
- Will you look at it with me?
- Aye.
Oh, one moment now. Samuel's hungry.
Oh, come, come, little Sam.
Come, come.
Flora? Flora?
Corruption.
Thou art my father.
What hast thou done?!
- Where are they?
- I know not what I saw.
- Where are they?!
- I did nothing!
- She came from the sky! She...
- Devil!
You have their blood upon thy hands!
It is you!
- It is you!
- I am your daughter!
The Devil is in thee and have had thee.
You're smeared of his sin.
You reek of Evil!
- You've made a covenant with death!
- Mother!
You bewitched thy brother, proud slut!
Did you not think I saw
thy sluttish looks to him,
bewitching his eye as any whore?
- What say you to me?
- And thy father next!
No.
You took them from me!
- They are gone.
- No!
- You killed my children!
You killed thy father! You witch!
I love you! I love you!
Black Phillip,
I conjure thee to speak to me.
Speak as thou doth speak
to Jonas and Mercy.
Dost thou understand my English tongue?
Answer me.
What dost thou want?
What canst thou give?
Wouldst thou like the taste of butter?
A pretty dress?
Wouldst thou like to live deliciously?
Yes.
Wouldst thou like to see the world?
What will you from me?
Dost thou see a book before thee?
Remove thy shift.
I cannot write my name.
I will guide thy hand.