Presto, Presto,
Presto, Presto
The nurse.
- Do you have any money?
- No.
Interpreter.
Where are you from?
- What is your name?
- Maria.
What is your name?
Come on, son.
Vito Andolini from Corleone.
Corleone, Vito Corleone.
Okay. Over there.
Next. Your name.
Tell him he has smallpox.
Quarantine, three months.
Vito Corleone?
Here he is.
This is him.
Vito. Come on.
We'll go see her backstage.
Scusa, Scusa
Vito, Come here.
Come On.
Thats Fanucci There
Vito. Come here. Come on.
I bet you don'
know what happened.
A few guys from over on
9th street grabbed Fanucci.
They cut his throat
from ear to ear.
What happened?
Nah.
to make him look bad
you know?
What can you do with
a man like fanucci?
Perché (Speaking Sicilian)
(Speaking Sicilian)
Somebody get the door.
(Woman speaking italian)
I can’t take it
Hey, Madame!
You speak ltalian?
You put in so many
hours of hard work....
...and for what?
You're just like my father.
that poor man used to work over
twelve hours a day, in the subway.
and in the end, he never even
got to take a ride.
Yeah, sure.
Clemenza!
Vito.
(Shouting in italian)
Hey, come in.
(Speaking italian)
Trust me.
Hey Carmine, come here.
Go to get your flute.
Hey, play something for my friends.
(speaking italian)
The song. A song that I like it. What's it called?
Ah, Buongiorno, Signora.
I got these dresses here for five dollars a piece.
you would have to pay at least
fifteen or twenty dollars for them
in any one of the stores.
(speaking Italian)
Vito.
I take care of everything
Salute
Vito, Here's my fifty dollars
Buona Fortuna.
(Speaks Italian)
I’ll make him an offer
he don’t refuse.
Don't worry
Grazie
(Speaking Italian)
If there's something I can do
for you, you come, we talk.
Grazie
(Speaking Italian)
She wants to talk to you
La signora wants to ask you a favor.
(speaking italian)
Santino
Grazie.
I don’t come here
to fight with you.
Hey look
Think about it.
(Speaking Italian)
Vito, the lanlord is here...
Roberto, The one who owns
those ratholes.
He's been asking all around the
neighborhood about you.
Grazie
The rent stays like before
Dieci, Grazie
Vito.
I just found this kid here
on the street,
and he's real good with cars.
he looked at the truck, and he
says, he thinks he can fix it.
Hey what's your name.
Suchowsky.
Hyman Suchowsky.
Yeah, but we're gonna dump that.
I call him Johnny Lips.
Well... we'll give him
a better name.
Who's the greatest man to you
in the whole world?
Hey come on Hyman, Answer
Mr. Corleone when he talks.
Yeah, who is it? Is it Columbus?
Marconi?
Garibaldi?
Arnold Rothstein.
Rothstein, huh?
I like that.
(Speaking Italian) We'll call you Hyman Rothstein.
Vito! Vito!
(Speaking Italian)
What is it?
Vito, what you think?
God Bless America.
We gotta make
a big business.
(Shouting in Italian)
Grazie, Don Vito
Fredo..give this to grandma
Hey Sonny, what are you doing?
you always fighting.
Hello?
Strollo?
-Si?
-Si
Hey, Mike
Me Chiamo Vito Corleone
Michael, say goodbye
I believe in America.
America has made my fortune.
And I raised my daughter
in the American fashion.
I gave her freedom, but I taught her
never to dishonour her family.
She found a boyfriend, not an Italian.
She went to the movies with him.
She stayed out late.
I didn't protest.
Two months ago he took her for a drive
with another boyfriend.
They made her drink whiskey
and then they tried to
take advantage of her.
She resisted, she kept her honour.
So they beat her like an animal.
When I went to the hospital,
her nose was broken,
her jaw was shattered,
held together by wire.
She couldn't even weep
because of the pain.
But I wept. Why did I weep?
She was the light of my life.
Beautiful girl.
Now she will never be beautiful again.
Sorry.
I went to the police,
like a good American.
These two boys were brought to trial.
The judge sentenced them to three years
in prison, but suspended the sentence.
Suspended the sentence!
They went free that very day!
I stood in the courtroom like a fool.
Those two bastards, they smiled at me.
Then I said to my wife, "For justice,
we must go to Don Corleone."
Why did you go to the police?
Why didn't you come to me first?
What do you want of me? Tell me
anything, but do what I beg you to do.
What is that?
I want them dead.
That I cannot do.
I'll give you anything you ask.
I've known you many years, but this
is the first time you've asked for help.
I can't remember the last time
you invited me for a cup of coffee.
Even though my wife is godmother
to your only child.
But let's be frank here.
You never wanted my friendship.
And you were afraid to be in my debt.
I didn't want to get into trouble.
I understand.
You found Paradise in America.
Had a good trade, you made a good living, police
protected you, and there were courts of law.
You didn't need a friend like me.
But now you come to me and say,
"Don Corleone, give me justice."
But you don't ask with respect.
You don't offer friendship. You don't
even think to call me Godfather.
You come on my daughter's wedding
day and ask me to murder for money.
I ask you for justice.
That is not justice.
Your daughter is alive.
Let them suffer, then, as she suffers.
How much shall I pay you?
Bonasera, Bonasera.
What have I ever done to make you
treat me so disrespectfully?
If you'd come in friendship,
the scum that ruined your daughter
would be suffering this very day.
And if an honest man like you should
make enemies, they'd be my enemies.
And then they would fear you.
Be my friend?
Godfather?
Good.
Some day, and that day may never
come, I'll ask a service of you.
But until that day...
...accept this justice as a gift
on my daughter's wedding day.
- Grazie, Godfather.
- Prego.
Give this to Clemenza.
I want people that aren't going to
get carried away.
We're not murderers,
in spite of what this undertaker says.
- (Whistles)
-What?
Did you pay attention?
of course dad, what do you...
- Where's Michael?
- Don't worry, he'll be here.
We're not taking the picture
without Michael.
- What's the matter?
- It's Michael.
Don Barzini.
Hey, Paulie! Let me have some wine.
Paulie! More wine.
Scusi, please.
- You look terrific on the floor.
- Are you a dance judge or something?
Take a walk and do your job.
Sandra, watch the kids.
Don't let them run wild.
You watch yourself, all right?
Hey, Tessio!
(Speaking Italian)
20, 30 grand. In small bills, cash.
In that little silk purse.
If this were somebody else's wedding...
Sfortunato!
Hey, Paulie!
I got two gobbagool...
gabagol and a prosciutto.
Stupid jerk!
What's the matter?
- Have to go back to work.
- Tom.
No Sicilian can refuse any request
on his daughter's wedding day.
Don Corleone, I'm honoured and
grateful that you have invited me.
Get out of here!
It's a private party. Go on!
What is it? It's my sister's wedding.
Goddamn FBI don't respect nothing!
Come here, come here, come here!
...but towards the end, he was paroled
to help with the American war effort,
so for six months he's worked
in my pastry shop.
Nazorine, what can I do for you?
Now that the war is over,
this boy, Enzo, they want to
repatriate him back to Italy.
Godfather, I have a daughter.
You see, she and Enzo...
You want Enzo to stay in this country,
and your daughter to be married.
You understand everything.
Mr Hagen. Thank you.
Wait till you see the wedding cake
I made for your daughter!
The bride, the groom and the angel...
- Who should I give this job to?
- Not to our paisàn.
Give it to a Jew Congressman in
another district. Who else is on the list?
Hey, Michael!
He's not on the list,
but Luca Brasi wants to see you.
Is this necessary?
He didn't expect to be invited to the
wedding, so he wanted to thank you.
Don Corleone, I'm honoured and
grateful that you have invited me
on the wedding day of your daughter.
May their first child be a masculine child.
Michael...
That man over there
is talking to himself.
See that scary guy over there?
- He's a very scary guy.
- What's his name?
His name is Luca Brasi.
He helps my father out sometimes.
Michael, he's coming over here!
You look terrific!
My brother Tom Hagen,
Miss Kay Adams.
Your father's been asking for you.
- Very nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
Why does your brother
have a different name?
My brother Sonny found Tom Hagen
in the street.
He had no home,
so my father took him in.
He's been with us ever since.
He's a good lawyer.
Not a Sicilian. I think he's
going to be consigliere.
- What's that?
- That's a...
...like a counsellor, an advisor.
Very important for the family.
You like your lasagne?
Don Corleone.
I'm honoured and grateful
that you have invited me
to your daughter's wedding.
On the day of your daughter's wedding.
And I hope that their first child
will be a masculine child.
I pledge my ever-ending loyalty.
- For your daughter's bridal purse.
- Thank you, Luca. Most valued friend.
Don Corleone, I'm going to leave you
now, because I know you're busy.
Thank you.
Signora Corleone!
No!
Senator Cauley apologised for not
coming, but said you'd understand.
Also some of the judges.
They've all sent gifts.
What is that outside?
Johnny! Johnny!
I love you!
He came all the way from California.
I told you he'd come!
- He's probably in trouble again.
- He's a good godson.
Johnny, Johnny! Sing a song!
You never said you knew
Johnny Fontane!
- Sure. You want to meet him?
- Great! Sure.
- My father helped him with his career.
- He did?
How?
- I have but one heart
- Let's listen to this song.
- Michael...
- This heart I bring to you
- I have but one heart, to share with you
- I have but one dream, that I can cling to
- you are the one dream, I pray comes true
Please, Michael. Tell me.
When Johnny was starting out, he was
signed to a personal service contract
with a big bandleader.
And as his career got better and better,
he wanted to get out of it.
Johnny is my father's godson.
My father went to see this bandleader.
He offered him 10,000 dollars
to let Johnny go,
but the bandleader said no.
So the next day my father went to see
him, but this time with Luca Brasi.
Within an hour,
he signed a release
for a certified cheque of 1,000 dollars.
- How did he do that?
- Made him an offer he couldn't refuse.
- What was that?
- Luca Brasi held a gun to his head,
and father said that either his brains or
his signature would be on the contract.
That's a true story.
That's my family, Kay. It's not me.
Beautiful!
My godson comes all the way from California
And no one gets him a glass of wine.
Cent'anni! Salute!
I'll take care of it.
Tom...
I want you to find Santino.
Tell him to come to the office.
How are you, Fredo?
My brother Fredo,
this is Kay Adams.
- Hi.
- How are you doing?
- This is my brother Mike.
- Are you having a good time?
Yeah. This is your friend?
I don't know what to do.
My voice is weak. It's weak.
Anyway, if I had this part in the picture,
it puts me right back on top again.
But this... man won't give it to me,
the head of the studio.
- What's his name?
- Woltz.
He won't give it to me,
and he says there's no chance.
Sonny?
- Sonny, are you in there?
- What?
The old man wants you.
One minute.
A month ago he bought the movie rights
to this book, a best-seller.
The main character
is a guy just like me.
I wouldn't even have to act.
Godfather, I don't know what to do.
You can act like a man!
What's the matter with you?
Is this how you turned out a Hollywood
finocchio, that cries like a woman?
"What can I do? What can I do?"
What is that nonsense?
Ridiculous.
- You spend time with your family?
- Sure I do.
Good.
Because a man who doesn't spend time
with his family can never be a real man.
You look terrible. I want you to eat.
Rest, and in a month this Hollywood
big shot will give you what you want.
It's too late, they start shooting
in a week.
I'm going to make him an offer
he can't refuse.
Just go outside and enjoy yourself,
and forget about all this nonsense.
- I want you to leave it all to me.
- All right.
- What time does my daughter leave?
- Soon, after they cut the cake.
Do we give your son-in-law
something important?
Never. Give him a living, but never
discuss the family business with him.
- What else?
- Virgil Sollozzo called.
- We'll have to see him next week.
- When you come back from California.
- When am I going to California?
- Tonight.
I want you to talk to this movie big shot
and settle this business for Johnny.
If there's nothing else, I'd like to go
to my daughter's wedding.
The hospital called
Consigliere Genco, He's not
gonna last out the night.
Santino,
Go tell your brothers
That I want them to
come with me to visit Genco.
And pay their respects.
Tell Fredo to drive The big car
and ask Johnny to come.
- Pop, uh, Michael?
- All my sons.
Carlo, we're going to take the picture.
Wait a minute.
No, Michael. Not me.
Okay, that's it. Just like that. Hold it!
Did your American girlfriend
get back in the city alright?
Tom said he'd
take her in.
What are all these Christmas ribbons for?
For bravery.
What miracles
you do for strangers.
Just a minute, Michael.
I want to talk to you.
What are your plans
when you get out?
Finish School.
That's fine. I approve of that.
Michael, you never
come to me as a son should.
You know that,
don't you?
When you finish school
I want you to come
and talk to
because I have plans for you. You understand?
We'll see.
Genco.
I brought all my boys
to pay their respects.
Even Johnny from Hollywood.
Godfather.
It is your daughter's wedding day.
you cannot refuse me.
Cure me.
you have the power.
Genco, I have
no such power.
But don't be afraid of death.
It's been
arranged then?
The last thing...
Resign yourself.
But you need
your old consigliere.
Who will replace me?
Stay. stay with me,
godfather.
help me to meet death
if he sees you,
he'll be frightened
and leave me in peace.
You can say a word. Pull a few strings, huh?
- Stay with me, Godfather.
- I will.
- Don't betray me.
- No.
Unaccustomed as I am
to public drinking...
I mean speaking, of course.
Janie, seriously,
we took some time off
from the picture
because we all want to
wish you a happy birthday.
now, Janie and everybody,
we have a big surprise for you.
In order to show how much Woltz
International thinks of you
we have brought you
a special birthday present.
Isn't he darling?
Wasn't that nice
of Mr. Woltz to give you
such a lovely present?
- You need a little more heat on that arc.
- Start talking.
I was sent by a friend
of Johnny Fontane.
This friend would give
his friendship to Mr Woltz,
if Mr Woltz would grant us a favour.
Woltz is listening.
Give Johnny the part in that war film
you're starting next week.
And what favour would your friend
grant Mr Woltz?
He could make your future union
problems disappear.
And one of your stars has just moved
from marijuana to heroin.
Are you trying to muscle me?
Listen, you son-of-a-bitch!
Let me lay it on the line. Johnny
Fontane will never get that movie!
No matter how many Dago Guinea
greaseballs come out of the woodwork!
- I'm German-lrish.
- Listen here, my Kraut-Mick friend.
- I'm going to make trouble for you!
- I'm a lawyer. I haven't threatened...
I know New York's big lawyers.
Who are you?
I have a special practice. I handle
one client. I'll wait for your call.
By the way, I admire your pictures
very much.
Check him out.
- It's really beautiful.
- Look at this.
- It used to decorate a king's palace.
- Very nice.
Why didn't you say
you work for Corleone?
I thought you were some cheap hustler
Johnny was running in.
- I only use his name when necessary.
- How's your drink?
- Fine.
- Now I'll show you something beautiful.
You do appreciate beauty, don't you?
There you are.
600,000 dollars on four hoofs.
I bet Russian czars never paid
that for a single horse.
Khartoum.
I'm not going to race him, though.
I'm going to put him out to stud.
Thanks, Tony.
Let's get something to eat.
Corleone is Johnny's godfather.
To the Italian people that's
a very sacred, close relationship.
I respect it. Tell him to ask me anything
else. This favour I can't give him.
He never asks a second favour
when he's been refused the first.
You don't understand. Johnny Fontane
never gets that movie.
That part is perfect for him.
It'll make him a big star.
I'm going to run him out of the business,
and let me tell you why.
Johnny Fontane ruined one of Woltz
International's most valuable protégés.
We trained her for five years.
Singing, acting, dancing lessons.
I spent hundreds of thousands of dollars
on her, to make her a big star.
Let me be even more frank.
To show you that I'm not a hard-hearted
man. That it's not all dollars and cents.
She was beautiful.
She was young and innocent!
She's the greatest piece of ass I've had
and I've had them all over the world.
Then Johnny Fontane comes along with
his olive oil voice and Guinea charm.
And she runs off.
She threw it all away
just to make me look ridiculous!
And a man in my position can't afford
to be made to look ridiculous!
You get the hell out of here!
If that goombah tries any rough stuff,
tell him I'm no bandleader.
Yeah, I heard that story.
Thank you for dinner
and a very pleasant evening.
Maybe your car can take me
to the airport.
Mr Corleone insists on hearing
bad news immediately.
What are you doing out here?
I told you never to go out
of the room.
Come on. I've got a few words
for you, little lady.
(Overlapping shouts)
Hey, Connie,
What's the matter?
They're arguing again.
Connie and Carlo are
constantly arguing.
I'm gonna talk to this brother-in-law.
Sit down.
Sit down. You never interfere
between a man and a woman.
Sit down.
Your business is here
with Tom and me.
Is this woltz so tough?
We'll, he'd risk
a union slowdown.
He'd let that star actor
be exposed as a junkie.
Is he really tough?
Would he risk his honor for this..
You mean is he a Sicilian?
Forget about it.
Now, this little actress,
this child,
- is that true?
- Yeah.
Infamnia
All right, send Luca Brasi to me.
I think we're going to
find a way to reason
with this Mr. Jack Woltz.
- You're not too tired, are you, Tom?
- No, I slept on the plane.
I have the Sollozzo notes here.
Now...
Sollozzo is known as The Turk. He's
supposed to be very good with a knife,
but only in matters of business
with reasonable complaint.
His business is narcotics.
He has fields in Turkey,
where they grow poppy.
In Sicily he has plants to process them
into heroin.
He needs cash, he needs protection
from the police.
He'll give a piece of the action.
I don't know how much.
The Tattaglia family is behind him here.
They have to be in it for something.
- What about his prison record?
- One term in Italy, one here.
He's known as a top narcotics man.
- Santino, what do you think?
- A lot of money in that white powder.
Tom?
Yes. There's more money in narcotics
than anything else.
If we don't get into it, somebody else
will, maybe the five families.
With that money they can buy
more police and political power.
Then they come after us.
Now we have unions and gambling, and
that's great, but narcotics is the future.
If we don't get a piece of that action,
we risk everything in ten years' time.
So? What's your answer
going to be, Pop?
Don Corleone.
I need a man who has powerful friends.
I need a million dollars in cash.
I need those politicians that you carry
in your pocket, like nickels and dimes.
- What is the interest for my family?
- 30 per cent.
In the first year your end should be
three, four million dollars.
And then it would go up.
And what is the interest
for the Tattaglia family?
My compliments.
I'll take care of them, out of my share.
So I receive 30 per cent for finance,
political influence and legal protection?
That's right.
Why do you come to me?
Why do I deserve this generosity?
If you consider a million dollars in cash
just finance,
ti saluto, Don Corleone.
I said that I would see you, because
I heard you were a serious man,
to be treated with respect.
But, I must say no to you.
And I'll give you my reason.
It's true, I have a lot of friends in politics.
They wouldn't be friendly long if I was
involved in drugs instead of gambling,
which they regard as a harmless vice,
but drugs is a dirty business.
It doesn't make any difference to me
what a man does for a living.
But your business is...
a little dangerous.
If you're worried about security,
the Tattaglias will guarantee it.
- The Tattaglias would guarantee our...
- Wait a minute.
I have a sentimental weakness
for my children, and I spoil them.
They talk when they should listen.
But anyway...
Signor Sollozzo, my no is final. I wish to
congratulate you on your new business.
I know you'll do well, and good luck.
Especially since your interests
don't conflict with mine. Thank you.
Santino.
Come here.
What's the matter with you? Your brain
is going soft from playing with that girl.
Never tell anybody outside the family
what you're thinking again.
Go on.
Tom, what's this nonsense?
It's from Johnny.
He's starring in that new film.
- Take it away.
- Take it over there.
And...
...tell Luca Brasi to come in.
I'm a little worried
about this Sollozzo fellow.
Find out what he's got
under his fingernails.
Go to the Tattaglias.
Make them think that you're not
too happy with our family
and find out what you can.
I got something for your mother
and for Sonny
and a tie for Freddy,
and Tom Hagen got the Reynolds pen.
- What do you want for Christmas?
- Just you.
Hello?
Good afternoon,
it's 3:00.
Thank you.
- Michael, it's 3:00.
- What?
It's 3:00.
Have to get up.
Because we have to go
to your father's house.
- Why do we have to?
- Because we have to.
If we go to
my father's house
We can't push
the beds together.
Why not?
Because they're
in separate rooms.
All right, then.
Then we won't go.
We won't
tell your father.
OK.
We'll get married first
and tell him later.
I can't do that.
Then, Michael, Get out of bed.
Let's go tomorrow.
Michael,
they're expecting us.
OK. Get the phone.
What are you
going to do?
Just the get the phone.
woman: Yes?
May I Help you?
May I please have, uh,
Orchard 99539, please?
What are you doing?
You're going to be the
long-distance operator
from New Hampshire.
I can't do this.
Go ahead, you got it.
Tom: Hello.
Hello? This is
long distance calling.
I have a collect phone call
from Mr. Michael Corleone.
um, will you
accept the charges?
- Yes.
- One moment, please.
- Don't laugh.
- I'm not gonna...
- Hello?
- Tom: Hello?
- Hello, Tom.
- Mike, how are you?
Listen, we're up
in New Hampshire still.
We'll drive down
tomorrow morning.
Is there anything
I could do for you?
No, we're fine.
I'm gonna see you Christmas.
Everyone's
going out to the mall?
- Right.
- OK.
Right, Mikey.
Bye-bye.
It's fine...
Andiamo, Fredo.
- Tell Paulie to get the car.
- Okay, Pop.
I'll have to get it myself.
Paulie called in sick this morning.
Paulie's a good kid.
I don't mind getting the car.
Buon Natale, caro. Grazie.
- Luca! I'm Bruno Tattaglia.
- I know.
Sue bequero Scotch? Prewar.
Io no bib'.
You know who I am?
Grazie
Tom! Tom Hagen. Merry Christmas.
- Glad to see you. I want to talk to you.
- I haven't got time.
Make time, Consigliere. Get in the car.
What are you worried about? If I wanted
to kill you, you'd be dead already.
Get in.
Ah, Aspetta, Fredo,
I'm going to buy some fruit.
OK, Pop.
Merry Christmas. I want some fruit.
Pa Pa!
Yeah.
man: Do you recognize my voice?
Yeah I think so. Detective Squad, right?
Don't say my name,
just listen.
Somebody shot your father outside
his place 15 minutes ago.
Uh, is he dead?
We can't get close enough to find out.
There's blood
all over the place.
Look, I'll see what I can do.
Find out what you can.
You got a grand coming. Alright?
woman: Hello?
- Theresa?
- Yes.
- Let me talk to Tom.
- He's not home yet.
Not yet, uh...
Have him call me
the minute he gets in.
Would you like me better
if I were a nun? Like in the story.
No.
- What if I were Ingrid Bergman?
- Now, that's a thought.
Michael.
No, I wouldn't like you better if you were
Ingrid Bergman. What's the matter?
They don't say if he's dead or alive.
- Sonny, it's Michael.
- Where have you been?
- Is he all right?
- We don't know yet.
There are all kinds of stories.
He was hit bad, Mikey.
- Are you there?
- Yeah, I'm here.
- Where have you been? I was worried.
- Didn't Tom tell you I called?
No. Look, come home, kid.
You should be with Mama, you hear?
Oh, my God.
Sonny!
Stay back there.
- Who is it?
- Open up, it's Clemenza.
There's more news about your old man.
Word is out that he's already dead.
- What's the matter with you?
- Take it easy!
- Where was Paulie?
- Sick. He's been sick all winter.
- How often?
- Only three, four times.
- Freddy didn't want a new bodyguard.
- Pick him up now.
I don't care how sick he is. Bring him
to my father's house right now.
- You want anyone sent over here?
- No. Go ahead.
I'm going to have a couple of our people
come over to the house.
- Hello?
- Santino Corleone?
- Yeah.
- We have Tom Hagen.
In three hours he'll be released
with our proposition.
Listen to what he has to say
before you do anything.
What's done is done. Don't lose that
famous temper of yours, Sonny.
I'll wait.
Ma...Where are you?
Ma, I, uh...
I just got a phone call
And pop's been hurt.
I don't know how bad.
I'm going to go change
in case we can see him.
- Tessio.
- Tessio: Hello?
Santino Corleone.
I want 50 good men
out here right away.
Tessio: I heard you, sonny,
But what about Clemenza's Regime?
No, I don't want to use
Clemenza's people right now.
- All right.
Come on, Luca.
Your boss is dead.
I know you're not in the muscle end
of the family, so don't be scared.
I want you to help the Corleones
and me.
We got him outside his office
about an hour after we picked you up.
Drink it.
It's up to you to make peace
between me and Sonny.
Sonny was hot for my deal, wasn't he?
And you knew
it was the right thing to do.
- Sonny will come after you.
- That will be his first reaction, sure.
So you have to talk sense into him.
The Tattaglia family is behind me.
The other New York families will go
along with anything to prevent war.
Let's face it, with all due respect,
the Don - rest in peace - was slipping.
Ten years ago,
could I have gotten to him?
Well, now he's dead, Tom,
and nothing can bring him back.
You've got to talk to Sonny, to the
Caporegimes, Tessio, fat Clemenza.
It's good business, Tom.
I'll try. But even Sonny won't be able
to call off Luca Brasi.
Yeah, well...
Let me worry about Luca.
You just talk to Sonny.
And the other two kids.
- I'll do my best.
- Good.
Now you can go.
I don't like violence, Tom.
I'm a businessman.
Blood is a big expense.
He's still alive.
They hit him with five shots,
and he's still alive!
That's bad luck for me, and bad luck
for you if you don't make that deal.
- Who are you?
- It's the don's kid.
you take the car,
I'll bring him inside.
Your mother's over
in the hospital
with your father.
Looks like he's going to pull through, thank God.
Theresa, you hear
from Tom yet?
Is Sonny inside?
Come on.
- Tessio: Could be
any one of these.
- Yeah...
Hey, Theresa.
Don't worry.
They'll turn Tom loose
the minute they
get the proposition.
Hello, Michael.
Where were you?
- Mikey, you had me worried when
I couldn't get in touch with you.
- How's ma taking it?
She's good.
She's been through it before.
Me too...
- Yeah.
- Hello, Santino?
This is Sam
from the company.
The number you gave me?
It checked out.
Listen, Thank you very much.
You're going to have a very...
...very extra
Merry Christmas, alright?
Sam: OK, THanks a lot.
6Thank you.
You want to wait outside? I got some business
I got to finish with Tessio.
What are you doing?
You hang around
you're going to hear things
- you don't want to hear.
- Maybe I can help you out.
No you can't. The old man
would have my neck
If I let you get
mixed up in this.
Come on!
He's my father too, Sonny.
You wanna hear?
Whose head do we blow off,
Clemenza's or Paulie's?
What do you mean?
What do I mean.
One of them set up the old man.
Yeah.
Not Clemenza.
I don't believe it.
See?
College boy is right.
It was Paulie. That was the
contact in the phone company.
In the three days that
Paulie was home sick
He got these phone calls
from the pay phone across
from the old man's building.
- So it was paulie.
- Thank God it was paulie
Tessio: That skinny punk.
But we need
Clemenza badly.
Is it going to be an all
out war like the last time?
Yeah. Until the old man
tells me different.
Wait, Sonny.
Talk to pop.
Wait? Come on!
Sollozzo's a dead man.
I don't care what it costs.
We'll go after all them families.
The Tattaglias
are going to eat dirt.
That's not how pop
would play it.
Listen Let me tell you something.
When it comes to the action
I'm as good as anybody
And don't forget it.
Tom!
Hey! Boy, if I argue
against the supreme court
I'll never do better than I did against that Turk tonight.
Give me a minute,
will ya?
- So what do you think?
- Sollozzo, Phillip Tattaglia...
It's too personal
That's a lot of bad blood.
The don would consider...
We're gonna kill
all those guys?
Hey, stay out of it
Sollozzo's the Key.
Get rid of him, everything falls into line.
What about Luca?
Sollozzo thinks he can control him.
If Luca sold out, we're in a lot of trouble.
- Has anyone been in touch with Luca?
- We've been trying all night.
- Hey, do me a favour...
- Luca never sleeps over with a broad.
Well, Tom, you're consigliere.
What do we do if the old man dies?
If we lose the old man, we lose the
political contacts and half our strength.
The other New York families might
support Sollozzo to avoid a long war.
This is almost 1946.
Nobody wants bloodshed anymore.
If your father dies...
...you make the deal.
- Easy to say. He's not your father.
- I'm as much a son as you or Mike.
What is it?
- Paulie, I told you to stay put.
- The guy at the gates has a package.
Tessio, go see what it is.
- Shall I stay?
- Yeah. Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
- There's food. Are you hungry?
- No.
- A drink? Brandy will sweat it out.
- Go ahead.
- That might be a good idea.
Take care of that son-of-a-bitch.
Paulie sold out the old man. That Stronz'
- Make that the first thing on your list.
- Understood.
Mickey, tomorrow, get some guys
and go to Luca's apartment.
Maybe we shouldn't get Mike
mixed up in this too directly.
Hanging around the house on
the phone would be a big help.
Try Luca again.
- What's this?
- A Sicilian message.
It means Luca Brasi
sleeps with the fishes.
Beautiful Car.
It ain't a beautiful car.
Stupid Detroit sends it
with wooden bumpers.
They're going to deliver the chromium bumpers
in a couple of months
because of the war.
Hey, the war is over.
I had to wait
for over two years
for the car to come
with stupid wooden bumpers.
.22 Soft nose load.
Accurate up to five-foot.
Today you make your bones
on Paulie.
- You understand everything?
- Understood, Mr. Clemenza.
- I'm going.
- When will you be home?
Probably late.
- Don't forget the cannoli!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Rocco, sit on the other side.
You block the rear-view mirror.
Sonny's running wild. He wants
to go to mattresses already.
We have to find a spot on the
West Side. Try 309 West 43rd Street.
- Know a good spot on the West Side?
- I'll think about it.
Think while you're driving.
I want to hit New York this month.
Watch the kids.
man: He's coming.
It's about time.
It's good for ten men.
All right, go over to the neighborhood.
I got to call in to Sonny.
You wait here,
I'll call Sonny.
Don Clemenza
(Speaking Italian)
He talked my ear off.
We got to go back
to Long Beach.
He got another job for us.
What do you think?
We going to get that last place we saw?
I don't know.
Why do you got to know now?
I don't got
to know nothing.
Drive the car, and watch
where you're going.
Clemenza:
Paulie, Go down 39th street.
Pick up 18 mattresses
for the guys.
Bring me the bill.
Paulie: Yeah, all right...now
Clemenz:
Make sure they're clean
Because those guys will be
stuck up there for a long time.
Paulie:
They're clean. They exterminate them.
Clemenza: Exterminate? That's a bad word to use.
Get this guy.
Watch out we don't
exterminate you.
Paulie:
Think that's funny or what?
Clemenza:
Hey, Paulie..
(Speaks Italian)...
Paulie: Rocco,
What did you do?
Rocco: Not me. Wasn't Me.
Paulie: It's gotta be him
Clemenza: Hey, Pull over, will you?
I gotta take a leak.
Leave the gun
Take the cannoli.
Clemenza: Hey, Mike!
Hey Mikey!
- Yeah.
You're wanted
on the telephone.
- Who is it?
- Some girl.
- Hello. Kay?
- How's your father?
He's going to make it.
I love you.
I love you!
- Michael?
- Yeah, I know.
- Tell me you love me.
- I can't talk.
Can't you say it?
I'll see you tonight.
Why don't you tell that nice girl
you love her?
I love you with all my heart. If I don't
see you again soon, I'm going to die!
Come and learn something. You might
have to cook for 20 guys some day.
You start with a little oil,
then fry some garlic.
Throw in some tomatoes, tomato paste,
fry it and make sure it doesn't stick.
You get it to a boil, you shove in
all your sausage and meatballs.
Add a little bit of wine.
And a little bit of sugar. That's my trick.
Cut the crap. I have more important
things for you. How's Paulie?
You won't see him anymore.
- Where are you going?
- To the city.
- Send bodyguards with him.
- I'm going to the hospital...
He'll be all right. Sollozzo knows
he's a civilian.
- Be careful.
- Yes, sir.
Send somebody with him anyway.
- I have to go.
- Can I go with you?
No, Kay. There will be detectives there,
people from the press.
I'll wait in the cab.
I don't want you to get involved.
When will I see you again?
Go back to New Hampshire, and I'll
call you at your parents' house.
- When will I see you again, Michael?
- I don't know.
What are you doing here?
You're not supposed to be here.
I'm Michael Corleone. This is my father.
What happened to the guards?
Your father had too many visitors.
They interfered with hospital service.
The police made them leave
about ten minutes ago.
Get me Long Beach 45620, please.
Nurse. Wait a minute. Stay here.
Sonny, I'm at the hospital.
I got here late, there's nobody here.
No Tessio's men, no detectives,
nobody. Papa's all alone.
- Don't panic, I'll send someone.
- I won't panic.
I'm sorry, but you will have to leave.
We're going to move him to another
room. Can you disconnect the tubes?
- That's out of the question!
- Do you know my father?
Men are coming here to kill him.
Do you understand?
Help me, please.
- Who are you?
- I am Enzo, the baker.
- Remember me?
- Enzo.
You'd better go,
there's going to be trouble.
If there is trouble, I'll stay here to
help you. For your father.
Listen. Wait for me outside,
in front of the hospital, all right?
I'll be out in a minute.
Just lie here, Pop.
I'll take care of you now.
I'm with you now.
I'm with you.
Get rid of these. Come here.
Put your hand in your pocket, like you
have a gun. You'll be all right.
You did good.
I thought all you Guinea hoods
were locked up!
- Why isn't anyone guarding my father?
- You little punk!
Don't you tell me my business!
I pulled them off.
- Stay away from this hospital!
- Not until my father's room is guarded.
- Phil, take him in!
- The kid's clean, Captain.
- He's a war hero. He's never been...
- I said take him in!
- What's The Turk paying you?
- Take a hold of him. Stand him up.
Stand him up straight.
I'm the Corleone's attorney. These men
are hired to protect Vito Corleone.
They're licensed to carry firearms.
If you interfere, you'll have to appear
before the judge and show cause.
Let him go.
- What's with all the new faces?
- We'll need them now.
After the hospital thing, Sonny got mad.
We hit Bruno Tattaglia this morning.
Jesus Christ.
Looks like a fortress around here.
Tommasuccio! Hey... 100 buttonmen
on the street 24 hours a day.
That Turk shows one hair on his ass,
he's dead.
Mike, let me look at you.
You're beautiful, beautiful.
You're gorgeous.
The Turk wants to talk! Imagine
the nerve of the son-of-a-bitch.
- He wants a meeting today.
- What did he say?
What did he say... He wants us to send
Michael to hear the proposition.
He promises that the deal
is too good to refuse.
- And Bruno Tattaglia?
- That's part of the deal.
- He cancels out what they did to Father.
- We should listen to them.
No more! Not this time, Consigliere.
No more meetings, discussions,
or Sollozzo tricks.
I want Sollozzo, or we go to war...
- The other families...
- They hand me Sollozzo!
Your father wouldn't want to hear this.
This is business, not personal!
- They shot my father...
- Even the shooting was business, not personal, Sonny.
Then business will have to suffer.
Do me a favour.
No more advice on how to
patch things up. Just help me win.
I found out about Captain McCluskey,
who broke Mike's jaw.
He's definitely on Sollozzo's payroll,
and for big money.
McCluskey has agreed to be
The Turk's bodyguard.
So when Sollozzo is being guarded,
he's invulnerable.
Nobody has ever gunned down
a New York police captain.
All the families would come after you.
The Corleone family would be outcasts!
Even the old man's political protection
would run for cover.
Do me a favour.
Take this into consideration.
All right, we'll wait.
We can't wait. We can't wait.
No matter what Sollozzo says,
he's going to kill Pop.
That's the key for him.
We've got to get Sollozzo.
- Mike is right.
- Let me ask you something.
What about this McCluskey?
What do we do with this cop?
They want to have a meeting
with me, right?
It will be me, McCluskey and Sollozzo.
Let's set the meeting.
Get our informers to find out
where it's going to be held.
We insist it's a public place.
A bar, a restaurant.
Some place where there are people,
so I feel safe.
They'll search me when I meet them,
right?
So I can't have a weapon on me.
But if Clemenza can figure out a way to
have a weapon planted there for me...
...then I'll kill them both.
Nice college boy. Didn't want to
get mixed up in the family business.
Now you want to shoot a police captain
because he slapped you?
This isn't like the army! You have to get
close and get their brains on your suit.
You're taking this very personal.
Tom, this is business
and he's taking it personal.
- Where does it say you can't kill a cop?
- Mikey...
I'm talking about a cop who's mixed up
in drugs, a dishonest cop.
A cop who got mixed up in the rackets
and got what was coming.
That's a terrific story. We have
newspaper people on the payroll, right?
- They might like a story like that.
- They might.
It's not personal, Sonny.
It's strictly business.
It's as cold as they come. Impossible to
trace, so you don't worry about prints.
I put a special tape on the trigger
and the butt. Try it.
Is the trigger too tight?
My ears!
I left it noisy, so it scares away any
pain-in-the-ass innocent bystanders.
You've shot them both.
Now what do you do?
- Sit down, finish my dinner.
- Don't fool around.
Let your hand drop to your side
and let the gun slip out.
Everybody will still think you've got it.
They'll stare at your face,
so walk out fast, but don't run.
Don't look anybody in the eye,
but don't look away either.
They'll be scared stiff,
so don't worry about nothing.
You'll be all right. You'll take a vacation,
nobody knows where,
and we'll catch the hell.
- How bad do you think it will be?
- Pretty goddamn bad.
All the other families will probably
line up against us.
These things have to happen every five,
ten years. Gets rid of the bad blood.
Been ten years since the last one.
You have to stop them at the beginning.
Like they should have stopped Hitler in
Munich, not letting him get away with it.
You know, Mike, we were all proud
of you. Being a hero and all.
Your father too.
Nothing. Not a hint. Absolutely nothing.
Even Sollozzo's people don't know
where the meeting will be held.
How much time do we have?
They're going to pick you up outside
Jack Dempsey's in an hour and a half.
- We could put a tail on them.
- Sollozzo would lose our ass.
- What about the negotiator?
- He's playing pinochle with my men.
- He's happy. They're letting him win.
- Too risky. Maybe we should call it off.
The negotiator plays cards
until Mike is back safe.
- He could blast whoever is in the car.
- They'll expect that.
Sollozzo might not even be
in the car, Sonny!
I'll get it.
Louis' restaurant in the Bronx.
- Is it reliable?
- My man in McCluskey's precinct.
A police captain is on call 24 hours
a day. He'll be there between 8 and 10.
- Anybody know this joint?
- Sure, I do. It's perfect for us.
A small family place, good food.
Everyone minds his business. Perfect.
They've got an old-fashioned toilet.
You know, the box and the chain thing.
We might be able to tape the gun
behind it.
All right. Mike, you go to the restaurant,
you eat, talk for a while, you relax.
Make them relax.
Then you go to take a leak. No, better
still, you ask permission to go.
Then you come back blasting.
Two shots in the head apiece.
I want somebody very good
to plant that gun.
I don't want him coming out
with just his dick.
- The gun will be there.
- You drive him and pick him up.
Let's move.
Did he tell you to drop the gun
right away?
Yeah, a million times.
Don't forget. Two shots apiece in
the head as soon as you come out.
How long do you think it will be
before I can come back?
At least a year.
I'll square it with Mom, that you're not
seeing her before you leave and...
I'll get a message to that girlfriend
when the time is right.
Take care.
Take care, Mike.
I'm glad you came. I hope we can
straighten everything out.
It's not the way I wanted things to go.
It should never have happened.
I want to straighten everything out.
I don't want my father bothered again.
I swear on my children
that he won't be, Mike.
But you have to keep an open mind
when we talk.
I hope you're not a hothead like Sonny.
You can't talk business with him.
He's a good kid.
I'm sorry about the other night, Mike.
I've got to frisk you, so turn around.
On your knees, facing me.
I guess I'm getting too old for my job.
Too grouchy.
Can't stand the aggravation.
You know how it is.
He's clean.
Going to Jersey?
Maybe.
Nice work, Lou.
- How's the food in this restaurant?
- Try the veal. It's the best in the city.
I'll have it.
I’m going to speak Italian to Michael
Go ahead
(Italian) I'm sorry. - Michael: Are you serious?
You must understand. That what happened
between me and your father...
...was a matter of business.
I have a great respect for your father.
But your father’s thinking is old-fashioned.
And he doesn't understand that I
am a man of honor.
Don’t tell me these things. I know them.
You know?
And you understand that I helped the Tattaglia family.
I believe that we can come to an agreement.
I want peace.
And we should end all this nonsense.
You want to pull my leg?
What?
How do you say...?
(English) What I want
Whats most important to me
Is that I have a guarantee
No more attempts on my Father's life.
What guarantees can I give you Mike.
Im the hunted one
I missed my chance
You think to much of me kid
I'm not that clever
All I want is a truce
I have to go to the bathroom
is that alright?
You gotta go, you gotta go
I frisked him, he's clean
Don’t take too long
I frisked a thousand young punks
(Italian) Do you feel better? - Yes
Mikey, you understand me, don't you?
You're Italian, just like your father (aren't you?)
Your father is doing badly.
When he is in better health, we'll try and arrange a meeting
meeting (or "form an union") and bring everything into balance..
This bullshit must end.
Okay, you take over.
I love you, Grandpa.
I'm sorry, Pa. He doesn't know you yet.
- Hey, big guy. Give it to Grandpa.
- Okay.
"I hope you get well, Grandpa, and wish
I see you soon. Your grandson Frank."
Go with your mother.
Take them downstairs.
Go on, Carlo, you too.
Go on.
- What's the matter with you, Carlo?
- Shut up and set the table.
Since McCluskey's killing, the police
have cracked down on our operations.
And also the other families.
There's been a lot of bad blood.
They hit us, so we hit them back.
Through our newspaper contacts
we've been able to put out material
about McCluskey's link with Sollozzo
in the drug rackets.
So things are loosening up.
And I sent Fredo to Las Vegas, under
the protection of Don Francesco of L.A.
- I want him to rest.
- I'm going to learn the casino business.
Where's Michael?
It was Michael who killed Sollozzo.
But he's safe. We're starting to work
to bring him back.
Did you find out where that old pimp
Tattaglia is hiding? I want him now.
Sonny, things are starting to loosen up.
If you go after Tattaglia, all hell
will break loose. Pop can negotiate.
- He must get better first. I'll decide...
- War is costly. We can't do business.
- Neither can they. Don't worry about it!
- We can't afford a stalemate.
- No more stalemate. I'll kill the bastard!
- You're getting a great reputation!
Do as I say! If I had a Sicilian wartime
consigliere, I wouldn't be in this shape!
Pop had Genco. Look what I got.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean that.
Ma made a little dinner. It's Sunday.
Niggers are having a good time
with our policy banks in Harlem.
Driving new Cadillacs,
paying 50 per cent on a bet.
That's because they've started
making big money.
Poppa never talked business
at the table.
- Shut up, Connie...
- Don't you ever tell her to shut up.
Don't interfere.
I'd like to talk to you after dinner.
I could do more for the family...
We don't discuss business at the table.
Big Shot
Hey,
Take me to the America!
If you need a good
gunfighter in America, take me!
I'd be the best
Man you can got.
Hey, hey, take me to the America, G.I.!
Clark Gable!
America! Take me to the America, G.I.!
Clark Gable, Rita Hayworth!
I apologize if I offended you.
I'm a stranger in this country.
I meant no disrespect
to you or your daughter.
I'm an American, hiding in Sicily.
My name is Michael Corleone.
There are people who'd pay a lot
of money for that information.
But then your daughter
would lose a father...
...instead of gaining a husband.
I want to meet your daughter.
With your permission, and under
the supervision of your family.
With all respect.
Grazie
Prego
I'll knock you dizzy.
Save it for the library.
We've got to pick up my sister.
What's the matter?
- It was my fault!
- Where is he?
It was my fault. I hit him.
I started a fight with him.
I hit him, so he hit me...
I'm just going to get a doctor
to take a look at you.
Sonny, please don't do anything.
What's the matter with you?
What am I going to do?
Make that baby an orphan
before he's born?
You spic slobs still betting Yankees?
Tell them to stop taking in action.
We lost enough money last week.
Come here, come here!
If you touch my sister again, I'll kill you.
Hey! We weren't expecting you, Kay.
You should call.
Yes, I have. I've tried writing and calling.
- I want to reach Michael.
- Nobody knows where he is.
All we know is that he's all right.
- What was that?
- An accident, but nobody was hurt.
Tom, will you give this letter to Michael.
Please?
If I accepted that, a court could prove
I have knowledge of his whereabouts.
He'll get in touch with you.
I let my cab go, so can I call
another one, please?
Come on. Sorry.
- Hello?
- Is Carlo there?
- Who is this?
- A friend of Carlo.
Tell him that I can't make it tonight
until later.
Bitch!
Carlo!
Your girlfriend
just called.
She said she can't
make it this evening!
What girlfriend?
I don't have
a girlfriend.
Can't I take
a shower in
my own house?
I just talked to her
on the telephone!
What's going on?
Are you starting
in today?
Aw, Carlo...
What's the matter
with you?
you give your whores
my telephone number?
You're getting to
be a little too much.
Where do you think
you're going?
I'm going out.
You're not going..
you're staying home!
Then make me something
to eat at least
And let me finish
washing up!
Now come on, get out
of here.
Go in the kitchen and
make me something to eat.
Your dinner's ready.
- I’m not hungry yet.
- Its on the table
It's getting cold.
I'll eat out.
You just told me to make you dinner!
(Shouting in Italian)
Leave me alone!
I'll vafangool you!
She has a filthy mouth, this Guinea brat.
That's it, break it all, you spoiled
Guinea brat. Break it all!
Why don't you bring your whore
home for dinner?
Maybe I will.
- Clean it up!
- Like hell I will!
You skinny, spoiled brat.
Clean it up! Clean it up!
Clean it up! I said, clean it up!
Clean it up!
Clean it up. Clean that up, you...
Clean it!
Clean it up! Yeah, kill me.
Be a murderer, like your father!
- All you Corleones are murderers!
- I hate you!
Come on, kill me!
Get out of here!
- I hate you!
- Now I'll kill you.
You Guinea brat. Get out of here!
Connie, what's the matter?
I can't hear you.
Connie, talk louder. The baby's crying.
Santino, I can't understand.
I don't know.
Yeah, Connie.
You wait there.
No, you just wait there.
Son-of-a-bitch.
- Son-of-a-bitch!
- What's the matter?
Open the goddamn gate!
Get off your ass.
Sonny!
- Sonny.
- Get out of here!
Go after him, go on!
Son-of-a-bitch. Come on!
Give me a drop.
My wife is crying upstairs.
I hear cars coming to the house.
Consigliere of mine,
tell your Don what everyone
seems to know.
I didn't tell Mama anything.
I was about to come up and wake you
and tell you.
But you needed a drink first.
Yeah.
Well, now you've had your drink.
They shot Sonny on the causeway.
He's dead.
I want no inquiries made.
I want no acts of vengeance.
I want you to arrange a meeting...
...with the heads of the five families.
This war stops now.
Call Bonasera.
I need him now.
This is Tom Hagen. I'm calling for
Vito Corleone, at his request.
Last year they were killing one another.
So now what?
The Godfather
comes to me.
Why?
They have killed
someone so important
that they wish to
make his body disappear.
Amerigo
They could make me
an accomplice
to their murder.
They could send me
to prison.
And if the other families,
find out
They will make me
their enemy.
I curse the day
when you and Comare Corleone became friends.
Well, my friend, are you ready
to do me this service?
Yes. What do you want me to do?
I want you to use all your powers
and all your skills.
I don't want his mother
to see him this way.
Look how they massacred my boy.
Monday, Tuesday, Thursday,
Wednesday, Friday, Sunday, Saturday.
Are you driving yourself, Boss?
Is your wife coming with you?
No, take her to her father's house
until things are safe.
Okay, anything you say.
Fabrizio!
No, Apollonia!
Don Barzini, I want to thank you
for helping me organise this meeting,
and the other heads of the five families
from New York and New Jersey.
Carmine Cuneo from the Bronx,
and from Brooklyn...
...Philip Tattaglia.
And from Staten Island
we have with us Victor Strachi.
And the other associates that came as
far as from California and Kansas City
and all the other territories
of the country. Thank you.
How did things ever get so far?
I don't know.
It was so unfortunate, so unnecessary.
Tattaglia lost a son, and I lost a son.
We're quits. And if Tattaglia agrees,
then I'm willing to let things go on
as before.
We're grateful to Don Corleone
for calling this meeting.
We all know him as a man of his word.
A modest man who listens to reason.
Yes, Don Barzini. He's too modest.
He had all the judges and politicians
in his pocket.
He refused to share them.
When did I ever refuse
an accommodation?
All of you know me.
When did I ever refuse,
except one time? And why?
Because I believe this drug business
will destroy us in the years to come.
It's not like gambling or liquor
or even women,
which is something that most people
want nowadays, and is forbidden to them
by the pezzonovante of the Church.
Even the police that have helped us in
the past with gambling and other things
are going to refuse to help us
when it comes to narcotics.
I believed that then...
and I believe that now.
Times have changed.
It's not like the old days,
when we could do anything we wanted.
A refusal is not the act of a friend.
If Don Corleone had all the judges and
politicians, then he must share them
or let others use them. He must let us
draw the water from the well.
Certainly he can present a bill
for such services.
After all, we're not communists.
I also don't believe in drugs.
For years I paid my people extra, so
they wouldn't do that kind of business.
Somebody says to them
"I have powders."
"If you put up 3-4,000 dollar investment,
we can make 50,000 distributing."
They can't resist. I want to control it
as a business, keep it respectable.
I don't want it near schools,
I don't want it sold to children.
That's an infàmia.
In my city we would keep the traffic
to the coloured.
They're animals,
so let them lose their souls.
I hoped that we could come here
and reason together.
And I'm willing to do whatever is
necessary to find a peaceful solution.
We are agreed. The traffic in drugs
will be permitted, but controlled.
Don Corleone will give us protection
in the east, and there will be peace.
I must have strict assurance
from Corleone.
As time goes by and his position
becomes stronger,
will he attempt any individual vendetta?
We are all reasonable men.
We don't have to give assurances.
You talk about vengeance.
Will vengeance bring your son
back to you?
Or my boy to me?
I forgo the vengeance of my son.
But I have selfish reasons.
My youngest son was forced
to leave this country...
...because of this Sollozzo business.
And I have to make arrangements
to bring him back here safely.
Cleared of all these false charges.
But I'm a superstitious man.
If an unlucky accident should befall him,
if he should be shot by a police officer,
or if he should hang himself
in his jail cell,
or if he's struck by a bolt of lightning,
then I'm going to blame
some of the people in this room.
And that I do not forgive.
But, that aside...
...let me say that I swear...
...on the souls of my grandchildren,
that I will not be the one to break
the peace we've made here today.
Should I insist that all of Tattaglia's
drug middlemen have clean records?
Mention it. Don't insist.
- Barzini will know without being told.
- You mean Tattaglia.
Tattaglia's a pimp. He could never
have outfought Santino.
But I didn't know until this day
that it was Barzini all along.
Lettuce...
Tomatoes, Pepper
Flowers.
Eight...
Fig trees.
- Beautiful.
- Pop...
What about Sonny?
What about Sicily?
I swore that I would
never break the peace.
But won't they take that
as a sign of weakness?
It is a sign
of weakness.
You gave your word that
you wouldn't break the peace.
I didn't give mine.
You don't have
to have any part in it.
I take all responsibility.
Well.. we have a lot of time
to talk about it now.
Come on, Nancy.
Keep together, everyone. Brian.
Okay, all right.
How long have you been back?
I've been back a year.
Longer than that, I think.
It's good to see you, Kay.
I'm working for my father now, Kay.
He's been sick. Very sick.
But you're not like him. You told me you
weren't going to become like your father.
My father is no different
than any other powerful man.
Any man who's responsible
for other people.
Like a senator or president.
- How naive you sound.
- Why?
They don't have men killed.
Who's being naive, Kay?
My father's way of doing things is over.
Even he knows that.
In five years the Corleone family
is going to be completely legitimate.
Trust me. That's all I can tell you
about my business. Kay...
Michael, why did you come here? Why?
What do you want with me after all
this time? I've been calling and writing.
I came because I need you.
I care for you.
- Please stop it, Michael.
- Because... I want you to marry me.
- It's too late.
- Please, Kay...
I'll do anything you ask to make up for
what's happened to us.
Because that's important, Kay.
Because what's important is that...
...we have each other.
That we have a life together.
That we have children. Our children.
Kay, I need you.
And I love you.
Barzini's people chisel my territory
and we do nothing about it!
- Soon I'll have no place to hang my hat!
- Be patient.
I'm not asking for help.
Just take off the handcuffs.
- Be patient.
- We must protect ourselves.
- Let me recruit some new men.
- No.
- Barzini would get an excuse to fight.
- Mike, you're wrong.
Don Corleone...
You once said that one day Tessio
and me could form our own family.
Till today I would never think of it.
I must ask your permission.
Michael is now head of the family.
If he gives his permission,
then you have my blessing.
After we make the move to Nevada
you can leave the Corleone family
and go on your own.
- How long will that be?
- Six months.
Forgive me, but with you gone, me and
Pete will come under Barzini's thumb.
I hate that Barzini. In six months' time
there will be nothing left to build on.
- Do you have faith in my judgement?
- Yes.
- Do I have your loyalty?
- Always, Godfather.
Then be a friend to Michael.
Do as he says.
Things are negotiated that'll solve your
problems and answer your questions.
That's all I can tell you now.
Carlo, you grew up in Nevada.
When we make our move there,
you'll be my right-hand man.
Tom Hagen is no longer consigliere.
He'll be our lawyer in Vegas.
That's no reflection on Tom,
just how I want it.
If I ever need help, who's a better
consigliere than my father? That's it.
- Thank you, Poppa.
- I'm happy for you, Carlo.
Michael, why are you
cutting me out
of the action?
We're gonna be legitimate
all the way, Tom.
You're the legal man.
What's more important
than that?
I'm not talking
about that.
Im talking about Rocco Lampone's building a secret regime.
Now why does Neri report directly
to you, instead of through me?
or the Capo Regimes?
How'd you find that out?
Rocco's men are a little too good for their jobs.
They're geting more
money than the job's worth.
I told you this
wouldn't escape
his eye.
Mike, Why am I out?
You're not a wartime consigliori, Tom.
Things may get rough
with the move we're trying.
Tom.
I advised Michael. I never thought
you were a bad consigliere.
I thought Santino was a bad Don,
rest in peace.
Michael has all my confidence,
just as you do.
But there are reasons why you must
have no part in what is going to happen.
- Maybe I could help.
- You're out, Tom.
I want to be
alone with my father.
I think you found
your Luca Brasi.
I'll need him.
I can't get over
the way your face looks.
it really
looks good.
This doctor
did some job.
Who talked you into it? Kay?
Hey, Hey!
Leave them here.
We'll deal
with that later.
He’s tired, wants to clean up.
Let me open the door alright?
- Hello, Mike! Welcome to Las Vegas!
- All for you, kid! It's all his idea.
- Your brother Freddy.
- Girls?
I'll be right back. Keep them occupied.
- Anything you want, kid, anything.
- Who are the girls?
- That's for you to find out.
- Get rid of them, Fredo.
- Hey, Mike...
- I'm here on business. Get rid of them.
I'm tired. Get rid of the band too.
Hey, take off. Take off. Let's go.
Hey, that's it. Hey, Angelo.
Hey, come on! Scram!
Come on, honey. I don't know
what's the matter with him, Johnny.
Sorry.
I don't know. He's tired.
What happened to Moe Greene?
He had some business. He said to
give him a call when the party started.
Well, give him a call.
- Johnny, how are you?
- Nice to see you, Mike.
- We're proud of you.
- Thanks.
Sit down, I want to talk to you.
The Don is proud too.
Well, I owe it all to him.
He knows how grateful you are. That's
why he'd like to ask a favour of you.
Mike, what can I do?
We're thinking of giving up our interests
in the olive oil business and settle here.
Moe will sell us his share of the casino
and the hotel, so we'll own all of it. Tom!
Are you sure? Moe loves the business.
He never said nothing about selling.
I'll make him an offer he can't refuse.
See, Johnny...
We figure that entertainment
would draw gamblers to the casino.
We hope you'll sign a contract
to appear five times a year.
Perhaps convince some of your friends
in the movies to do the same.
We're counting on you.
Sure, Mike. I'll do anything
for my godfather.
Good.
Hey, Mike! Hello, fellows.
Everybody's here. Freddy, Tom.
- Good to see you.
- How are you, Moe?
Have everything? Specially prepared
food, the best dancers, and good credit.
Draw chips for everybody,
so they can play on the house.
Is my credit good enough
to buy you out?
Buy me out?
The casino, the hotel. The
Corleone family wants to buy you out.
The Corleone family wants to
buy me out? No, I buy you out.
Your casino loses money.
We can do better.
- You think I'm skimming off the top?
- You're unlucky.
You Guineas make me laugh.
I took Freddy in when you had a bad
time, and now you try to push me out!
You did that because we bankrolled
your casino
and the Molinari family guaranteed
his safety. Let's talk business.
Yes. First of all, you're all done. You
don't have that kind of muscle anymore.
The Godfather is sick. You're getting
chased out of New York by the others.
Do you think you can come to my hotel
and take over?
I talked to Barzini. I can make a deal
with him and still keep my hotel!
Is that why you slapped my brother
around in public?
That was nothing, Mike.
Moe didn't mean nothing by that.
He flies off the handle sometimes,
but we're good friends.
I have a business to run.
I've got to kick asses sometimes.
We had an argument,
so I had to straighten him out.
You straightened my brother out?
He was banging cocktail waitresses!
Players couldn't get a drink.
What's wrong with you?
I leave for New York tomorrow.
Think about a price.
Son-of-a-bitch!
I'm Moe Greene! I made my bones
when you were out with cheerleaders.
Wait a minute, Moe. I have an idea.
Tom, you're the consigliere.
Talk to the Don...
Just a minute. Don is semi-retired and
Mike is in charge of the family business.
If you have anything to say,
say it to Michael.
Mike, you don't come to Las Vegas and
talk to a man like Moe Greene like that!
Fredo...
You're my older brother, and I love you.
But don't ever take sides with anyone
against the family again.
I have to see my father and his people,
so have dinner without me.
This weekend we'll go out. We'll go to
the city, see a show and have dinner.
Your sister wants to ask you something.
- Let her ask.
- She's afraid to.
They want you to be godfather
to their boy.
- We'll see.
- Will you?
Let me think about it. Come on.
Barzini will move against you first.
He'll set up a meeting with someone
you absolutely trust.
Guaranteeing your safety.
And at that meeting
you'll be assassinated.
I like to drink wine more than I used to.
- Anyway, I'm drinking more.
- It's good for you, Pop.
I don't know.
Are you happy with your wife
and children?
- Very happy.
- That's good.
I hope you don't mind the way I keep
going over this Barzini business.
- No, not at all.
- It's an old habit.
I spend my life trying not to be careless.
Women and children can be careless,
but not men.
- How's your boy?
- He's good.
He looks more like you every day.
He's smarter than I am. He's three
and can read the funny papers.
Read the funny papers.
I want you to arrange for a telephone
man to check all in- and out-going calls.
- I did it already. I took care of that, Pop.
- That's right. I forgot.
What's the matter?
What's bothering you?
I'll handle it. I told you I can handle it,
so I'll handle it.
I knew that Santino would have to
go through all this.
And Fredo...
Fredo was, well...
But I never wanted this for you.
I worked my whole life. I don't apologize
for taking care of my family.
And I refused to be a fool,
dancing on a string
held by all those big shots.
I don't apologize. That's my life,
but I thought that...
...that when it was your time, you would
be the one to hold the strings.
Senator Corleone. Governor Corleone.
Something.
Another pezzo da novanta.
Well...
Just wasn't enough time, Michael.
Wasn't enough time.
We'll get there, Pop. We'll get there.
Now listen, whoever comes to you
with this Barzini meeting,
he's the traitor. Don't forget that.
Can I hold it, please?
- Can I water these?
- Yes, go ahead.
Over here, over here.
Be careful. You're spilling it.
Antony!
Come here, come here.
That's it. We'll put it right there.
I'll show you something. Come here.
Stand there.
Give me an orange!
That's a new trick.
You run in there. Run in there.
Where are you?
Mike, can I have a minute?
Barzini wants to arrange a meeting.
He says we can straighten out
any of our problems.
- You talked to him?
- Yeah.
I can arrange security. On my territory.
- All right?
- All right.
Do you know how they're going to
come at you?
They're arranging a meeting
in Brooklyn. Tessio's ground.
Where I'll be safe.
I always thought it would be
Clemenza, not Tessio.
It's the smart move.
Tessio was always smarter.
But I'm going to wait.
After the baptism.
I've decided to be godfather
to Connie's baby.
And then I'll meet with Don Barzini
and Tattaglia.
All the heads of the five families.
Michael, do you believe in God, the
Father, Creator of Heaven and Earth?
I do.
Do you believe in Jesus Christ,
His only Son, our Lord?
I do.
Do you believe in the Holy Ghost,
the Holy Catholic Church?
I do.
Michael Francis Rizzi,
do you renounce Satan?
I do renounce him.
And all his works?
I do renounce them.
Oh, God!
- And all his pomps?
- I do renounce them.
Michael Rizzi, will you be baptised?
I will.
Michael Rizzi, go in peace, and may
the Lord be with you. Amen.
Kay!
Kiss your godfather.
Can't go to Vegas. Something's come
up. Everybody has to leave without us.
- Mike, it's our first vacation!
- Connie, please.
Go back to the house, wait for my call.
It's important.
I'll only be a couple of days.
We're on our way to Brooklyn.
- I hope Mike can get us a good deal.
- I'm sure he will.
Sal, Tom, the boss says he'll come in a
separate car, so you two go on ahead.
- That screws up my arrangements.
- That's what he said.
I can't go either, Sal.
Tell Mike it was only business.
I always liked him.
- He understands that.
- Excuse me, Sal.
Tom, can you get me off the hook?
- For old times' sake?
- Can't do it, Sally.
You have to answer for Santino, Carlo.
- Mike, you got it all wrong.
- You fingered Sonny for Barzini.
That little farce you played
with my sister.
- You think that could fool a Corleone?
- I'm innocent. I swear on the kids.
- Please, don't do this.
- Sit down.
Don't do this to me, please.
Barzini is dead.
So is Philip Tattaglia.
Moe Greene.
Strachi. Cuneo.
Today I settle all family business,
so don't tell me you're innocent, Carlo.
Admit what you did.
Get him a drink.
Come on.
Don't be afraid, Carlo. Do you think
I'd make my sister a widow?
I'm godfather to your son, Carlo.
Go ahead, drink, drink.
No, you're out of the family business.
That's your punishment.
You're finished.
I'm putting you on a plane to Vegas.
Tom.
I want you to stay there. Understand?
Only don't tell me you're innocent.
Because it insults my intelligence.
Makes me very angry.
Who approached you?
Tattaglia or Barzini?
It was Barzini.
Good.
There's a car waiting outside
to take you to the airport.
I'll call your wife and tell her
what flight you're on.
- Mike...
- Get out of my sight.
Hello, Carlo.
- I'm trying to tell you...
- Mama, please!
Michael!
- What is it?
- Where is he?
Michael, you lousy bastard!
You killed my husband.
You waited until Papa died,
so nobody could stop you.
You blamed him for Sonny.
Everybody did.
But you never thought about me!
Now what are we going to do?
Connie.
Why do you think he kept Carlo at the
Mall? He knew he was going to kill him.
And you stood godfather to our baby.
You lousy cold-hearted bastard!
Want to know how many men he had
killed with Carlo? Read the papers!
That's your husband,
that's your husband!
No! No, no...
Take her upstairs. Get her a doctor.
She's hysterical.
Hysterical.
Michael, is it true?
- Don't ask me about my business, Kay.
- Is it true?
Don't ask me about my business.
Enough!
All right.
This one time.
This one time I'll let you ask me
about my affairs.
Is it true?
Is it?
No.
I guess we both need a drink. Come on.
Don Corleone.
Do something exciting.
That's good
Here's your big chance.
Come on.
I don't care if you
are my husband.
keep your greasy hands
off of me!
And I will not
shut my mouth!
Honey, wait a minute.
- Let's take a drive, huh?
- I already had a drive!
I want to see my brother-in-law Michael.
I don't want him to see you
in this condition.
Would you park this thing, please?
Come on, honey, please.
Just listen to me for one minute.
uh-huh. Ow!
No! Let go of me! Ow!
No! Ow!
Ow! Do you know what you did to me?
Ow! Oh!
You listen to me.
Michael's got a lot of nice people here.
They're friends of Kay's.
If you ruin this party
I'll never live it down.
Oh yeah? How come
you're so scared of
your kid brother, anyway?
Because he's
the head of the family.
Hey did you bring your car key?
woman: Laurie.
Laurie!
Ma Ma
- Look who's here.
- Father Carmelo.
- This is Father Carmelo.
- I'm Merle Johnson.
Nice to meet you. Hi.
Excuse me.
- Here I am.
- After one week?
I sent the car out to the airport
last week to pick you up.
It was chaos.
Anyway, here I am,
just one week late.
And this is for my mama.
- What is this?
- You remember Merle, don't you?
- Hello, Mama.
- Yeah, hello.
How are you?
Thank you.
Where's Michael?
I gotta talk to him...
and get a few things straight,
and I can't wait on line.
You go see your children first...
and then you worry about waiting
on line to see your brother...
Like everybody else.
Waiter, you got a glass
of red wine?
I'm sorry, only
champagne and cocktails.
A cold beer for my throat,
I'm very dry.
I'll try.
Hey, Frankie,
have some water.
over here.
Fredo, you son of a bitch!
You look great!
Frank Pentangeli!
I thought you was never
coming out west, you big bum.
I gotta check on my boys, huh?
- What's with the food around here?
- What's the matter?
Kid comes up to me
in a white jacket...
gives me a Ritz cracker
and a chopped liver...
he says "canapes."
I said, "Can of peas my ass!
That's a Ritz cracker
and chopped liver."
- Bring out the peppers and sausage.
- Hey, Freddie.
Seeing you reminds me of New York.
The old days, huh?
Hey, Fredo,
you remember Willi Cicci?
We was with old man Clemenza
in Brooklyn.
We were all upset about that.
Heart attack, huh?
No, there was no heart attack.
That's what I'm here to see
your brother Mike about.
- But what's with him?
- What do you mean?
I mean, what do I gotta do?
Do I have to get...
a letter of introduction
to get a sit-down?
You can't get in to see Mike?
He's got me waiting in a lobby!
Michael, this is Gardner Shaw.
Francesca and he have
been seeing each other.
for six months now.
Gardner, this is Francesca's
Uncle Michael.
- How do you do, sir?
- Hello.
I've heard a lot about you,
Mr. Corleone.
They would like to
set an engagement date.
I was thinking that
perhaps two months...
Let them.
Let them talk
for themselves.
Why don't you sit down.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Francesca, how are you?
Fine. Thank you,
Uncle Michael.
Michael: And what
do you want to tell me?
Well, Uncle Michael,
we love each other very much,
And we want to be married.
I came to ask
for your blessing.
Fredo: Hey, Mike,
Guess who's here?
Not now, Freddie.
Tell Mike old Frankie
'Five-Angels' is outside,
all right?
- I'll tell him.
- What's going on?
Family matter.
You see, Gardner,
Francesca is my
oldest brother's daughter.
and my brother Sonny
died many years ago
and I've been sort of a father to her,
rather than an uncle.
I love her very much.
So do I.
Well, I appreciate
you coming here
before you went ahead
with your plans.
it shows you're
a considerate man.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
- Do you go to college?
- Yes, sir, I do.
- What do you study there?
- Fine arts.
How do you plan to support
your new wife on fine arts?
That's a good question.
Well, I'm sorry,
I just get embarrassed
to say it, sir,
But I'm a major stockholder
in the family corporation.
You shouldn't be
embarrassed about your wealth.
This contempt for money is
just another trick of the rich
to keep the poor without it.
Well, what can I say
after that?
Of course you
have my blessing.
Thank you.
I'm so happy for you.
Don't you worry,
You're going to be next.
Congratulations.
Thank you, sir.
You might consider
taking a course
in business administration,
just to be on the safe side.
Make sure her dowry is big.
He comes from a family
who think italian brides
go barefoot.
Kay! Aunt Kay!
Uncle Michael is the most
wonderful man ever!
His name is Fred Vincent.
Runs a small pizza parlor
up in Buffalo.
American wife, two small kids.
We traced him back,
found that he's in this country
illegally from Sicily.
Came over around 1956.
Sponsored by
the Barzini Family.
That's him.
Fabrizio.
What took so long?
My God!
I can't believe...
out of 30 professional musicians...
there isn't one ltalian
in the group here.
Come on.
Let's have a tarantella.
You, up! Come on!
Up, up, up!
I'll see my sister alone.
It concerns me too.
Is it okay if I stay?
How are you, honey?
You've met Merle.
He was with me in Vegas.
- I saw him with you.
- Could I have a drink or something?
Al, would you please
get him a drink?
We're going to Europe. I'd like
to book passage on the Queen.
So what do you come to me for?
Why don't you go to a travel agent?
We're getting married first.
The ink on your divorce isn't dry
yet, and you're getting married?
You see your children on weekends.
Your oldest boy
was picked up in Reno...
for some petty theft
you don't even know about.
You fly around the world with men
who use you like a whore.
- You're not my father!
- Then what do you come to me for?
'Cause I need money.
I wanna be reasonable with you.
Now, why don't you stay here
with us, with the family?
You can live here on the estate
with your kids.
You won't be deprived of anything.
You can have everything you want.
Now, I don't know this Merle.
I don't know what he does.
I don't know what he lives on.
Tell him marriage
is out of the question...
and you don't want
to see him anymore.
He'll understand.
Believe me.
If you don't listen to me...
and marry this man...
you'll disappoint me.
-Johnny Ola.
- AI Neri.
Do you know my lawyer
Tom Hagen? Johnny Ola.
Sure. I remember Tom
from the old days.
Rocco, what's this?
It's an orange from Miami.
Take care of Johnny's men.
They look like they might be hungry.
- Good to see you.
- Tom isn't gonna sit in with us.
He only handles specific areas
of the family business.
- Tom?
- Sure, Mike.
What are you drinking, Johnny?
Anisette.
If you need anything
I'll be outside, all right?
Just tell Rocco we're waiting.
I just left Mr. Roth in Miami.
- How's his health?
- It's not good.
Is there anything I can do,
anything I can send?
He appreciates your concern,
Michael, and your respect.
That casino you're interested in,
the registered owners are...
Jacob Lawrence, Allan Barclay,
both Beverly Hills attorneys.
The real owners are the Lakeville
Road group from Cleveland...
and our friend in Miami.
Meyer Klingman runs the store.
He owns a piece of it too,
and he does all right.
But I've been instructed to tell you
that if you move Klingman out...
our friend in Miami will go along.
That's very kind of him.
You tell him
that's greatly appreciated.
Hyman Roth always makes money
for his partners.
One by one,
our old friends are gone.
Death, natural or not...
prison, deported.
Hyman Roth is the only one left...
because he always made money
for his partners.
Anthony. No!
Anthony, No, No.
I don't want you
going near that house.
(announcer) ...Red Cadillac, Nevada Licence plate number
Anthony!
(announcer) ...240792,
Please move the car in the
parking lot.
- Ladies and gentlemen.
- Frankie, wake up.
A most distinguished guest
would like to say a few words.
Would you please welcome Senator
Pat Geary of the state of Nevada.
And there's Mrs. Geary.
Thank you very much,
ladies and gentlemen.
And this is a very,
very happy day for me...
and my wife, Mrs. Geary.
We see Nevada far too seldom...
but particularly today...
when we can join with old friends,
we can make new friends...
and we help celebrate
a young man's first communion...
and also to thank
that boy's family...
for a magnificent contribution
to the state.
I have here in my hand a check...
made out to the university...
and it is
a magnificent endowment...
in the name of...
Anthony Vito Corleone.
And the check is signed
by that young man's parents...
whom I think
we should recognize now.
Mike, Pat, Kay--
Stand up, please.
Let the folks see you.
Folks, I want you to join with me...
in giving a real
Nevada thank-you...
to Mr. and Mrs. Michael Corleone!
We also have,
as a special added attraction...
the Sierra Boys Choir...
who have chosen...
a certain special song
and a special arrangement...
to honor their host,
Mr. Michael Corleone.
Boys.
- Why this feeling
- Why this glow
-Just why this glow
The plaque.
Okay, fellas, I got that one.
Okay, this is yours.
Senator, just you and Mrs. Corleone.
- Excuse me.
- This is my lawyer Tom Hagen.
- Senator Geary.
- Mr. Hagen.
He's the one who arranged this whole
thing through your man Turnbull.
- Yes, yes.
- Sit down.
I was under the impression
that you and I would talk alone.
I trust these men
with my life, Senator.
If I were to ask them to leave,
it would be an insult.
It's all right with me, but I should
tell you I am a blunt man...
and I intend to speak
very frankly to you...
more frankly than anyone in my
position's talked to you before.
The Corleone family has done
very well here in Nevada.
You own, or you control,
two major hotels in Vegas...
one in Reno.
The licenses
were grandfathered in...
so there was no problem
with the gaming commission.
But now my sources tell me that...
you plan to make a move
against the Tropigala.
They tell me that within a week...
you're gonna move Klingman out.
That's quite an expansion.
However, it will leave you
with one little technical problem.
The license will still be
in Klingman's name.
Turnbull is a good man.
Yeah, well, let's just--
Let's cut out the bullshit.
I don't want to spend any more time
here than I have to.
You can have the license.
The price is $250,000...
plus a monthly payment
of five percent of the gross...
of all four hotels...
Mr. Corleone.
Now, the price for the license
is less than $20,000.
- Am I right?
- That's right.
Now, why would I ever consider
paying more than that?
Because I intend to squeeze you.
I don't like your kind of people.
I don't like to see you come out
to this clean country...
in your oily hair...
dressed up in those silk suits...
and you try to pass yourselves off
as decent Americans.
I'll do business with you,
but the fact is that...
I despise your masquerade...
the dishonest way
you pose yourself--
yourself and your whole
fucking family.
Senator...
we're both part
of the same hypocrisy...
but never think it applies
to my family.
All right, all right.
Some people have to play
little games.
You play yours.
Let's just say that you'll pay me
because it's in your interest to.
But I want your answer
and the money by noon tomorrow.
And one more thing:
Don't you contact me again, ever.
From now on, you deal with Turnbull.
Open that door, son.
Senator, you can have
my answer now if you like.
My offer is this:
nothing.
Not even the fee
for the gaming license...
which I would appreciate
if you would put up personally.
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
Ladies. I didn't know
you were out here.
- We have to go. We're late.
- Really? I'm sorry.
It's been a delightful party.
Thank you for inviting us.
It's been our pleasure.
It was wonderful talking to you.
What's cent'anni?
Cent'anni.
It means a hundred years.
It means we should all live happily
for a hundred years, the family.
It'd be true
if my father were alive.
Merle, you've met
my sister-in-law Deanna.
- Fredo's wife.
- A pleasure, Merle.
- How do you do?
- My pleasure.
What did she mean by that?
Mr. Pentangeli,
you were talking
to Anthony today, right?
(Speaking Italian)
We talked in Sicilian
It was a one-sided
conversation.
I see.
He's a little boy,
you know.
(Speaking Italian)
What's the matter?
I just wanna dance.
Dancing is one thing.
You're falling all over the floor.
I know what's the matter. You're
jealous 'cause he's a real man.
I swear to God, I'm gonna
belt you right in the teeth.
You couldn't belt your mama.
You know something? These dagos are
crazy when it comes to their wives.
Michael says that if
you can't take care of this...
I have to.
- I think you'd better.
- Never marry a Wop!
They treat their wives like shit!
I didn't mean to say Wop!
Stop that!
What are you doing to me?
You big slob! Help!
I can't control her, Mikey.
You're my brother, Fredo.
You don't have to apologize to me.
Clemenza promised
the Rosato brothers...
three territories in the Bronx
after he died.
You took over,
and you didn't give it to them.
- I welched?
- You welched.
Clemenza promised them "ugatz. "
Clemenza promised them nothing.
He hated those son ofa bitches
more than I do.
Frankie, they feel cheated.
You're sitting high up
in the Sierra Mountains...
and you're drinking--
- What's he drinking, Cicci?
- Champagne.
Champagne cocktails.
And you're passing judgment
on how I run my family.
You're a good old man.
I like you.
And you were loyal
to my father for years.
The Rosato brothers,
they're taking hostages.
And Mike,
they spit right in my face...
all because they're backed up
by that Jew in Miami.
I know. That's why
I don't want 'em touched.
- You don't want 'em touched.
- No.
I want you to be fair with them.
You want me to be fair with 'em?
How can you be fair to animals?
Tom, for Christ's sakes, listen.
They recruit spics.
They recruit niggers.
And they do violence in
their grandmothers' neighborhoods.
And I tell ya,
everything with them is whores.
Whores and junk. Dope.
And they leave the gambling to last.
Now, I wanna run my family
without you on my back...
and I want those
Rosato brothers dead.
Now, I have business that's
important with Hyman Roth.
I don't want it disturbed.
Then you'll give your loyalty
to a Jew before your own blood?
Come on. You know my father
did business with Hyman Roth.
He respected him.
Your father did business
with Hyman Roth...
your father respected Hyman Roth...
but your father
never trusted Hyman Roth...
or his Sicilian messenger boy
Johnny Ola.
And I want everybody here to know...
there's not gonna be
no trouble from me.
Don Corleone.
You want him to leave now?
Let him go back to New York.
I've already made my plans.
The old man had too much wine.
It's late.
(Speaking Italian)
Ahhh![
(Speaks Italian)
I give you $1,000.
I don't wanna
embarrass your father.
Put that in
your pocket.
You hide it
under your pillow,
Don't tell nobody.
Look, angel face,
you got a face...
(speaks Italian)
I got children, too.
I love you.
Let me say it.
Now go ahead.
(speaks Italian)
How's the baby?
Sleeping inside me.
- Does it feel like a boy?
- Yes, it does, Michael.
I'm sorry about
all the people today.
Bad timing.
It couldn't be helped, though.
It made me think
of what you once told me.
In five years, the Corleone family
will be completely legitimate.
That was seven years ago.
I know.
I'm trying, darling.
You Klingman?
Who's askin'?
Where can we talk?
Right here.
I represent the interest
in the Corleone family.
I'm makin' the invitation
to you to tie up your affairs.
Be out of the hotel
by Monday morning.
Who do you think
your talking to?
You says your name was Klingman.
You can't come in here
and talk to an owner
like that.
You miss my point.
You're no longer an owner.
Get outta my hotel.
Boys, get him out of my hotel. Get him out...
Somebody help me!
All right.
All right! I'll clear out.
OK, keep it going.
What's the matter? Didn't you hear me?
Keep it going.
What's the matter?
Can't you sleep?
You all right?
Did you like your party?
I got lots of presents.
I know.
Did you like 'em?
I didn't know the people
who gave them to me.
Well, they're my friends.
Did you see my present for you?
You got me a present?
Downstairs on your pillow.
Well, I'll see it when I go to bed.
Anthony, I'm going to be leaving
very early tomorrow.
Will you take me?
- No, I can't, Anthony.
- Why do you have to go?
'Cause I have to do business.
I could help you.
Well, someday you will.
Get some sleep.
Good night.
Did you see this?
Michael, why are the drapes open?
- Kay, you all right?
- Yeah.
- Are you hit?
- No.
It's over. It's over.
Now! Shut it off!
Hold it!
They're still on the property.
Please, stay inside.
- Keep them alive.
- We'll try.
Rocco! Alive!
Stay by the door.
Check by the boathouse!
Yeah, come in.
- Mike, are you all right?
- Yeah.
Yeah?
There's a lot
I can't tell you, Tom.
Now, I know that's
upset you in the past.
You felt it was because of some
lack of trust or confidence...
but it's because
I admire you and I love you...
that I kept things
secret from you.
That's why at this moment you're
the only one I can completely trust.
Fredo?
Well, he's got a good heart...
but he's weak and he's stupid...
and this is life and death.
Tom, you're my brother.
I always wanted to be thought of
as a brother by you.
A real brother.
I know that.
You're gonna take over.
You're gonna be the don.
If what I think has happened
has happened...
I'm gonna leave here tonight.
I give you complete power
over Fredo and his men--
Rocco, Neri, everyone.
I'm trusting you with the lives
of my wife and my children--
the future of this family.
When we catch these guys...
do you think we'll be able to
find out who's back of all this?
We're not gonna catch 'em.
Unless I'm very wrong,
they're dead already.
They were killed by somebody
close to us.
Inside.
Very, very frightened
they botched it.
Yeah, but your people,
Rocco and Neri...
you don't think that they had
something to do with this?
See, all our people
are businessmen.
Their loyalty's based on that.
One thing I learned from Pop...
was to try to think
as people around you think.
Now, on that basis,
anything's possible.
I seen them!
Right out my window!
I wanna get out of here!
They're lying there dead!
Get her inside!
Over here.
There's two of'em.
Looks like they were
hired out of New York.
I don't recognize 'em.
We won't get anything
out of them now.
Fish 'em out.
All right, get rid of the bodies.
- Where's Mike?
- Rocco.
Come on in.
It's all right. Come on.
Hyman's in there.
I was just making some lunch.
Would you like a tuna sandwich?
Uh, no, thankyou.
Pickup of two by Holden.
Second and eight for S.C...
and the ball is at
the Trojan 38-yardline.
Mr. Roth?
Come in, Michael.
Sit down.
Make yourself comfortable.
It's almost over.
You follow the football game?
- Pickup offive.
- Not for a while I haven't.
I enjoy watching football
in the afternoon.
One of the things I love
about this country.
Baseball too.
I've loved baseball...
ever since Arnold Rothstein
fixed the World Series in 1919.
...47. Marked down there,
say the officials.
And at that point
it'll be first and ten--
I heard you had some trouble.
It'll be third and ten, another
of those big plays now...
- Stupid.
- coming up for S.C.
People behaving like that
with guns.
...but it looks like
it could stall here.
The important thing is,
you're all right.
Good health.
The most important thing.
More than success.
More than money.
- Now he's back to pass.
- More than power.
Rolls up field for Hayes.
He's intercepted.
Hurd has it to the lrish 40.
To the far sideline. Gets by the 45.
He's hit and dropped
at the S.C. 42-yardline.
Notre Dame's first bigbreak
of the game.
I came here because there's
gonna be more bloodshed.
I want you to know about it
before it happens...
so that there's no danger
of starting another war.
Nobody wants another war.
Frank Pentangeli came to my home
and he asked my permission...
to get rid of the Rosato brothers.
When I refused,
he tried to have me killed.
He was stupid. I was lucky.
I'll visit him soon.
The important thing is that
nothing interfere...
with our plans for the future.
- Yours and mine.
- Nothing is more important.
Good.
You're a wise
and considerate young man.
And you're a great man,
Mr. Roth.
- There's much I can learn from you.
- What can I do to help, Michael?
To the 32, and is downed there
by Danny Zika.
- Excuse me. Lunch.
- Oh.
- Okay.
- Ohh!
Hyman, you're gonna
break my ear drums.
- Okay, enjoy it.
- Thanks.
You're young.
I'm old and sick.
What we'll do together
in the next few months...
will make history, Michael.
History.
It's never been done before.
Not even your father would dream
that such a thing could be possible.
And Pentangeli is a dead man.
- You don't object?
- Pickup of four.
He's small potatoes.
What's up?
We got company, huh?
Don Corleone, I wish you would've
let me know you were comin'.
I could've prepared
something for you.
I didn't want you to know
I was coming.
You heard what happened
in my home?
- Mike, I almost died myself.
- In my home!
In my bedroom
where my wife sleeps!
Where my children come
and play with their toys.
In my home.
I want you to help me
take my revenge.
Michael, anything.
What can I do?
Settle these troubles
with the Rosato brothers.
Mike, I don't understand.
I don't--
I don't have your brain
for big deals...
but this is a street thing.
That Hyman Roth in Miami.
That--
He's backin' up
those son-of-a-bitches.
I know.
Then why? Why do you ask me
to lay down to him, Mike?
It was Hyman Roth that
tried to have me killed.
I know it was him.
Jesus Christ, Mike.
Jesus Christ, look,
let's get 'em all.
Let's hit 'em all now,
while we got the muscle.
This used to be
my father's old study.
It's changed.
I remember
there used to be a--
A big desk was here.
I remember when I was a kid,
Frankie...
we had to be very quiet
when we played near here.
I was very happy that this
house never went to strangers.
First Clemenza took it over.
Now you.
My father taught me
many things here.
He taught me in this room.
He taught me,
keep your friends close...
but your enemies closer.
Now, if Hyman Roth sees that
I interceded in this thing...
in the Rosato brothers' favor...
he's gonna think his relationship
with me is still good.
That's what I want him to think.
I want him completely relaxed
and confident in our friendship.
Then I'll be able to find out
who the traitor in my family was.
- Yeah?
- Fredo. This is Johnny.
Johnny Ola.
We need some more help.
Johnny?
Jesus Christ,
what the hell time is it?
- Who is that, honey?
- Listen good, Fredo.
What are you callin' me here for?
I don't want to talk to you.
Pentangeli's set up a meeting
with the Rosato brothers.
- He's gonna go for their deal.
- Oh, God.
- Will he come alone?
- I don't know anything.
- You got me in deep enough already.
- Just go along.
Everything will be allright,
Fredo.
Pentangeli says he's
willing to make a deal.
All we wanna know is
if he's on the level.
You guys lied to me. I don't
want you to call me anymore.
Your brother's not gonna
find out we talked.
I don't know
what you're talkin' about.
Who was that?
Uh, wrong number.
Frank, I got nobody here.
- Wait in the car, Cheech.
- Frankie--
It's okay, Cheech.
- What's this, Rosato?
- A lucky "C" note for our new deal.
Richie.
Give us a taste, huh?
Yeah, we're all real happy
about your decision, Frankie.
- You're not gonna regret it.
- I don't like this "C" note.
I take that as an insult.
Michael Corleone says hello.
Get him in!
Close the fuckin' door!
Your friend the cop.
What the--
Hey, Rich, it's dark in here.
- Are you open or closed?
- I just come in to clean up.
What's the matter?
- Is that somethin' on the floor?
- Carmine, no, no. Not here!
- Not here!
- Not here, Carmine! Not a cop!
What?
You open your fuckin' mouth,
I'll blow your head off!
Freddie. Good to see ya.
Where is he?
He's okay. He's in the back.
Come on, girls.
Take a hike, huh?
In this room here.
- I wanna talk to him alone first.
- Come on, huh?
I thought I could
help you, Senator.
Hagen?
- Listen, Hagen, I did not--
- No.
- It's all right.
- I didn't do anything.
It's okay.
You're very lucky.
My brother Fredo
operates this place.
He was called before anyone.
Now, if this had happened
someplace else...
we couldn't
have helped you.
When I woke up
I was on the floor...
and I don't know
how it happened.
You can't remember?
I passed out.
I'll fix it.
Okay.
It was just a game.
Jesus.
Oh.
Jesus! Jesus!
Jesus God.
Oh, God.
I don't know and I don't
understand why I can't remember.
You don't have to remember.
Just do as I say.
They're putting a call in
to your office.
Explain that you'll be there
tomorrow afternoon.
You decided to spend the night...
at Michael Corleone's house
in Tahoe as his guest.
I do remember
that she was laughing.
We'd done it before...
and I know that I could
not have hurt that girl.
This girl has no family.
Nobody knows
that she worked here.
It'll be as though
she never existed.
All that's left
is our friendship.
- Yes?
- I'm sorry, Mrs. Corleone.
- We're not to let you through.
- I'm just going to the market.
Well, if you'll just give us a list,
we'll pick up anything you want.
- Whose orders are these?
- Mr. Hagen's, ma'am. He's coming.
All right, well, I'm just gonna
have to speak to Mr. Hagen.
I wanted to explain this, but
I had business in Carson City.
Now, this is Michael's
request for your safety.
- We can send out for anything.
- I see.
I'm supposed to stay
in my house.
No, within the compound
would be fine.
I was going to take the children
to New England next week.
- That's off now.
- Am I a prisoner? ls that it?
- That's not the way we look at it.
- All right, come on, kids.
We're going back to the house.
Joe.
Cuba! Cuba!
Most respected gentlemen...
allow me to welcome you
to the city of Havana.
I want to thank this distinguished
group of American industrialists...
for continuing to work
with Cuba...
toward the greatest period
of prosperity...
in her entire history.
Mr. William Shaw, representing
the General Fruit Company;
Misters Corngold and Dant...
of United Telephone
and Telegraph Company;
Mr. Petty,
regional vice president...
of the Pan American
Mining Corporation;
Mr. Robert Allen
of South American Sugar;,
Mr. Michael Corleone of Nevada...
representing our associates in
tourism and leisure activities;
and my old friend and associate
from Florida...
Mr. Hyman Roth.
I would like to take this
opportunity...
to thank United
Telephone and Telegraph...
for their lovely Christmas gift:
a solid gold telephone.
Perhaps you gentlemen would
like to take a look at it.
- Mr. President.
- Yes?
Perhaps you would discuss
the status of rebel activity...
and what this can mean
to our businesses.
- Of course.
- Very lovely.
I want to assure you
that although the rebels...
have mounted an impressive
campaign in Las Villas...
my staff indicates
with assurance...
we'll drive them out of the city
of Santa Clara before the new year.
And I want to put you all
at ease.
We will tolerate no guerillas
in the casinos or swimming pools.
He say that they are
making arrest...
and in a few minutes
he'll let us through.
Johnny.
Well, I hope my age
is correct.
I'm always accurate
about my age.
Make sure that everybody
sees the cake before we cut it.
I'm very pleased...
you were all able to come
from such distances...
to be with me today.
When a man comes
to this point in his life...
he wants to turn over the
things he's been blessed with--
turn them over to friends--
as a reward
for the friends he's had...
and to make sure that everything
goes well after he's gone.
- Not for years.
- Hear, hear.
The doctors would disagree,
but what do they know?
These are wonderful things
that we've achieved in Havana...
and there's no limit to
where we can go from here.
This kind of government knows how
to help business, to encourage it.
The hotels here
are bigger and swankier...
than any of the rough joints
we've put in in Vegas.
And we can thank our friends
in the Cuban government...
which has put up half of the cash,
with the Teamsters...
on a dollar-for-dollar basis;
has relaxed restrictions
on imports.
What I'm saying is that we have now
what we have always needed:
real partnership
with a government.
Smaller piece.
You all know Michael Corleone...
and we all remember his father.
At the time of my retirement
or death...
I turn over all my interest
in the Havana operation...
to his control.
But all of you will share.
The Nacionale will go to
the Lakeville Road boys.
The Capri to the Corleone family.
The Sevilla Biltmore also.
But Eddie Levine of Newport will
bring in the Pennino brothers...
Dino and Eddie, for a piece...
and also to handle
the actual casino operations.
And we've saved a piece for
some friends in Nevada...
to make sure that things
go smooth back home.
I want all of you
to enjoy your cake...
so enjoy.
- Happy birthday.
I saw an interesting thing
happen today.
A rebel was being arrested
by the military police...
and rather than be taken alive...
he exploded a grenade he had
hidden in his jacket.
He killed himself, and he took
a captain of the command with him.
- Right,Johnny?
- Those rebels, they're lunatics.
- Yes, I agree.
- Maybe so.
But it occurred to me...
the soldiers are paid to fight,
the rebels aren't.
What does that tell you?
They could win.
This country has had rebels
for the last 50 years.
It's in their blood. I've been
coming here since the '20s.
We were running molasses out
of Havana when you were a baby...
the trucks owned by your father.
Michael.
I'd rather we talked about
this when we we're alone.
The two million
never got to the island.
I wouldn't want it to get around
that you held back the money...
because you had second thoughts
about the rebels.
Ah, sit down, Michael.
Sit down.
If I could only live to see it,
to be there with you.
Ohh.
What I wouldn't give for...
20 more years.
Here we are, protected--
free to make our profiits without
Kefauver...
the goddamn Justice
Department and the FBl--
90 miles away, partnership
with a friendly government.
Ninety miles. It's nothing.
Just one small step,
looking for a man...
that wants to be President
of the United States...
and having the cash
to make it possible.
Michael...
we're bigger than U.S. Steel.
Mikey, how are ya? Okay?
Hiya. Freddie Corleone.
Jesus Christ, what a trip.
The whole time I'm thinkin'...
"What if somebody knows
what I got in here?"
Imagine that. Two million dollars
on the seat next to me.
All right.
- Whoops. Excuse me.
- No, it's okay.
You wanna count it?
Mikey, what the hell's
goin' on anyway?
The family's making
an investment in Havana.
- This is a gift for the president.
- Oh.
Well, that's great.
Havana's great.
It's my kind of town.
- Anybody I know in Havana?
- I don't know.
Hyman Roth? Johnny Ola?
No. I never met them.
Listen, Mikey...
I'm kind of, uh--
kind of nervous from the trip.
Uh, can l-- can I get
a, uh, drink or somethin'?
I thought maybe we'd--
we'd go out together.
I know a place we can spend
some time together. Okay?
Sometimes I think I should've
married a woman like you did...
Like Kay.
Have kids, have a family.
For once in my life
be more like...
Pop.
It's not easy to be a son,
Fredo. It's not easy.
Mama used to tease me. She'd say,
"You don't belong to me.
You were left on the doorstep
by gypsies."
Sometimes I think it's true.
You're no gypsy, Fredo.
Mikey, I--
I was mad at you.
Why didn't we spend time
like this before?
You want a drink, right?
Waiter.
- How do you say banana daiquiri?
- Banana daiquiri.
- That's it?
- That's it.
- Uh, uno banana daiquiri.
- Banana daiquiri. Si, senor.
And, uh, a club soda.
Senator Geary's flying in
from Washington tomorrow night...
with some people,
some government people...
and I want you to show 'em
a good time in Havana.
It's my specialty, right?
- Can I trust you with something?
- Of course, Mike.
In the evening, we're all invited
to the presidential palace...
a reception to bring in
the new year.
After it's over...
they're gonna take me home
in a military car...
alone, for my protection...
and before I reach my hotel
I'll be assassinated.
- Who?
- Roth.
It was Roth who tried
to kill me in my home.
It was Roth all along.
He acts like I'm his son,
his successor...
but he thinks he's gonna live
forever and he wants me out.
How can I help?
You just go along
as though you know nothing.
- I've already made my move.
- What move?
Hyman Roth'll never see
the new year.
He says you have to take it easy
and he'll give you a prescription.
He'll be back tomorrow.
I want my own doctor.
Fly him in from Miami.
I don't trust a doctor
can't speak English.
Honey, go down to the casino.
- If you're sure you're better.
- Feel fine.
- Play the bingo game.
- Nice to see you, Mr. Paul.
-Just make yourself at home.
- Thank you.
My sixth sense tells me...
your brother Fredo brought
a bag full of money.
Where is it?
You're pulling out?
Just wanna--
I just wanna wait.
How do you feel?
Terrible. I'd give four million...
just to be able to take a piss
without it hurting.
Who had Frank Pentangeli killed?
The Rosato brothers.
I know. But who gave
the go-ahead?
I know I didn't.
There was this kid
I grew up with.
He was younger than me.
Sort of looked up to me,
you know.
We did our first work together.
Worked our way
out of the street.
Things were good.
We made the most of it.
During Prohibition...
we ran molasses into Canada.
Made a fortune. Your father too.
As much as anyone...
I loved him and trusted him.
Later on he had an idea...
to build a city...
out of a desert stopover for G.I.s
on their way to the West Coast.
That kid's name was Moe Green...
and the city he invented
was Las Vegas.
This was a great man...
a man of vision and guts...
and there isn't even a plaque
or a signpost or a statue of him...
in that town.
Someone put a bullet
through his eye.
No one knows
who gave the order.
When I heard it I wasn't angry.
I knew Moe;
I knew he was headstrong.
Talking loud,
saying stupid things.
So when he turned up dead...
I let it go...
and I said to myself...
"This is the business
we've chosen."
I didn't ask...
who gave the order...
because it had nothing
to do with business.
That two million
in a bag in your room--
I'm going in...
to take a nap.
When I wake...
if the money's on the table
I'll know I have a partner.
If it isn't,
I'll know I don't.
All right, does everybody
know everybody here, huh?
- This is Senator Geary.
- How are you, Senator?
Good to see you, Mike. I'm glad
we could spend time together.
- Senator Payton from Florida.
- How you doing, Mike?
- And Judge DeMalco from New York.
- How do you do, sir?
- Fine, thank you.
- Senator Ream from Maryland.
- I've been looking forward to this.
- This is Fred Corngold from U.T.T.
- I know Fred. How are you?
- Fred does a mean cha-cha-cha.
- Oh, he does, huh?
- Gentlemen, it's refiill time.
Try some of them local drinks--
uh, cuba libre, pina colada.
I think I'll try one of
those redheaded Yolandas.
- That you got. Congusto.
- Johnny.
You don't know my brother Fredo,
do you, Johnny? Johnny Ola, Fredo.
- We never met. Johnny Ola.
- Pleasure.
Gentlemen, to a night in Havana.
- Happy New Year.
- That's right, huh?
- Checkin' in now. Right now.
- Never fear! Pat Geary's here!
- Hey, Fred.
- Cheers! Hey!
- Hey, Freddie, why are we standin'?
- Come on, man!
Everybody stands,
but it's worth it.
- You're not gonna believe this.
- I don't believe it already.
- That's right. Fifty dollars.
- You got a bet, mister.
That's him. That's Superman.
- Jesus Christ!
- Did I tell ya, or did I tell ya?
- I don't believe it.
- That thing's gotta be a fake.
That ain't no fake. That's real.
That's why they call him Superman.
Hey, Freddie. Freddie.
Where did you find this place?
Johnny Ola told me about
this place. He brought me here.
I didn't believe it,
but seein' is believin', huh?
- I see it and I don't believe it.
- Fifty bucks, Pat.
Old man Roth'd never come here...
but ol'Johnny knows these places
like the back of his hand.
Now watch him. He's gonna
break the cracker with it.
I wanna see him break a brick.
He could knock down a building.
Relax, Senor Roth. We're
taking you to the hospital.
And in my judgment
you'll continue to get those...
because I don't believe
that President Eisenhower...
will ever pull out of Cuba.
Not as long as we have over one billion
dollars invested in this country.
Now, the American public
believes in nonintervention.
Fredo. Where you goin'?
I'm gonna get me a real drink,
'cause I can't--
What kept Mr. Roth?
I understood he was coming.
Ream, what's the protocol? How long
should we stay around here?
Oh, I don't know. I think
a half hour oughta do it.
Just long enough
to bring in the new year.
There's a plane waiting for us
to take us to Miami in an hour.
Don't make a big thing about it.
I know it was you, Fredo.
You broke my heart.
Fredo! Come on.
Come with me. It's the only
way out of here tonight.
Roth is dead. Fredo.
Fredo, come with me!
You're still my brother!
Fredo! Fredo!
U.S. passports only.
- U.S. passports only.
- I'm from the United States Senate.
- Back, please.
- Please! I must leave!
Al, get me a wet towel.
Kay know I'm back?
What about my boy? Did you get
him something for Christmas?
- I took care of it.
- What was it so I'll know?
It was a little car with an electric
motor that he could ride in.
It was nice.
Thank you, Al.
Fellas, could you step outside
for a minute, please?
Where's my brother?
Uh, Roth got out on a private boat.
He's in a hospital in Miami.
He had a stroke.
He recovered okay.
- Your bodyguard's dead.
- I asked about Fredo.
I think he got out. He must be
somewhere in New York.
All right.
I want you to get
in touch with him.
I know he's scared.
Tell him everything's all right.
Tell him I know Roth misled him;
that he didn't know
they were gonna try to kill me.
And they can come in now.
Oh, there was something else.
What?
Come on. What?
Kay had a miscarriage.
She lost the baby.
- Was it a boy?
- After three and a half months--
Can't you give me a straight answer
anymore? Was it a boy?
I really don't know.
From the year 1942
to the present time...
you were an employee
of the Genco Olive Oil Company?
That's right.
But in actuality you were a member
of the Corleone crime organization?
We called it the Corleone family,
Senator. We called it the family.
What was your position?
At first, like everybody else,
I was a soldier.
- What is that?
- A button. You know, come on.
No, I don't know. Tell me.
When the boss says "push a button
on a guy," I push a button.
- See, Senator?
- Mr. Questadt.
- You mean you killed people?
- What?
You killed people
at the behest of your superiors?
Yeah, that's right, counselor.
And the head of your family
is Michael Corleone?
Yeah, counselor, Michael Corleone,
right.
Did you ever get such an order
directly from Michael Corleone?
No, I never talked to him.
Mr. Cicci, could you amplify
your answer a bit, please?
Do what?
Could you expand on your answer?
I'm interested in knowing...
was there always a buffer involved?
Someone in between you
and your possible superiors...
- who gave the actual orders?
- Yeah, right, a buffer.
The family had a lot of buffers.
Mr. Cicci,
you may find this very amusing...
but I promise you the members
of this committee do not.
- Are you the son of Vito Corleone?
- Yes, I am.
- And where was he born?
- Corleone, Sicily.
Did he, at times, use an alias...
that was known in certain circles
as "Godfather"?
"Godfather" is a term
that was used by his friends...
one of affection,
one of respect.
Mr. Chairman, I would like
to verify the witness's statement.
For years now, a growing number
of my constituents...
have been of ltalian descent...
and I've come to know them well.
They have honored me with their
support and with their friendship.
Indeed, I can proudly say
that some of my very best friends...
are ltalian-Americans.
However, Mr. Chairman, at this time,
I have to leave these proceedings...
to preside over a very important
meeting of my own committee.
But before I leave,
I do want to say this--
that these hearings on the Mafia
are in no way whatsoever...
a slur upon
the great Italian people...
because I can state from
my own knowledge and experience...
that Italian-Americans are among
the most loyal...
most law-abiding, patriotic...
hard-working American citizens
in this land.
And it would be a shame,
Mr. Chairman...
if we allowed
a few rotten apples...
to give a bad name
to the whole barrel...
because from the time
of the great Christopher Columbus...
up to the time of Enrico Fermi...
right up until the present day...
Italian-Americans
have been pioneers...
in building and defending
our great nation.
They are the salt of the earth.
They are one of the backbones
of this country.
The chairman is calling
the meeting back to order.
I'm sure we all agree
with our esteemed colleague.
Now, Mr. Corleone, you have been
advised as to your legal rights.
We have testimony from a witness,
a previous witness...
one Willi Cicci.
He has stated that you are head...
of the most powerful Mafia family
in this country.
- Are you?
- No, I'm not.
The witness has testified that
you are personally responsible...
for the murder of a New York City
police captain in 1947.
And with him,
a man named Virgil Solozzo.
- Do you deny this?
- Yes, I do.
Is it true that in the year 1950...
you devised a murder of the heads
of the so-called "five families"...
in New York, to assume
and consolidate...
your nefarious power?
- That's a complete falsehood.
- Is it true...
you have a controlling interest
in three major hotels in Las Vegas?
No, it is not true. I own some stock
in some of the hotels there...
but very little.
I also have stock in IBM and IT&T.
Do you have any interests or control
over gambling and narcotics...
in the state of New York?
No, I do not.
Senator, my client would like to
read a statement for this committee.
Mr. Chairman,
I think this statement...
is totally out of order
at this time.
Sir, my client has answered every
question asked by this committee...
with the utmost sincerity.
He did not take the Fifth Amendment,
as it was his right to do...
so in all fairness I think
the statement should be heard.
No, I'm going to allow Mr. Corleone
to read his statement.
I'll put it in the record.
"In the hopes of clearing
my family name...
and my sincere desire to give
my children their fair share...
of the American way of life
without a blemish...
on their name and background...
I have appeared
before this committee...
and given it all the cooperation
in my power.
I consider it a great dishonor
to me personally...
to have to deny
that I am a criminal.
I wish to have the following
noted for the record:
that I served my country faithfully
and honorably in World War Two...
and was awarded a Navy Cross for
actions in defense of my country...
that I have never been arrested or
indicted for any crime whatsoever...
that no proof linking me to any
criminal conspiracy...
whether it is called "Mafia,"
"Cosa Nostra"...
or whatever other name
you wish to give...
has ever been made public.
I have not taken refuge
behind the Fifth Amendment...
although it is my right to do so.
I challenge this committee...
to produce any witness
or evidence against me.
And if they do not...
I hope they will have the decency
to clear my name...
with the same publicity with which
they now have besmirched it."
I'm sure we're all quite impressed,
Mr. Corleone...
particularly with your love
for our country.
Committee will stand in recess
until 10:00 a.m. Monday morning...
at which time the committee
will produce a witness...
who will corroborate the charges
which were made against you today...
and at which time, Mr. Corleone,
you may very well be subject...
to indictment for perjury.
I remind you that
you're still under subpoena.
Adjourned.
Ten-to-one shot, you said.
Ten-to-one shot
he would take the Fifth...
and I lose.
You sound like my bookie.
I owe that monkey my life.
Well, just get
a good night's sleep.
- Good night's sleep.
- Got a big day tomorrow.
Got you a new suit,
a new shirt, new tie.
I'm gonna shave you myself
in the morning.
You're gonna look respectable for
50 million of your fellow Americans.
My life won't be worth a nickel
after tomorrow.
Come on.
I saw this thing 19 times.
You got a great home here, Frankie.
The rest of your life, nobody gets
near you, you're not going anywhere.
That's great.
Beautiful.
Some deal I made.
You'll live like a king.
You'll be a hero.
You'll live better in here
than most people on the outside.
Some deal.
Jesus.
Alive.
Pentangeli is alive.
- How'd they get their hands on him?
- Roth. He engineered it.
Frankie went to make a deal
with the Rosato brothers...
and they tried to kill him.
He thought you double-crossed him.
Our people with the New York
detective said he was half dead...
scared stiff and calling out loud
that you turned on him.
They already had him on possession,
bookmaking, murder one...
and a lot more.
The FBI has him airtight.
He's on an army base,
24-hour guards.
No way we can get to him.
You've opened yourself
to five counts of perjury.
What about Fredo?
What does he know?
He says he doesn't know anything,
and I believe him.
Roth-- he played this one
beautifully.
I want to talk to Fredo.
I haven't got a lot to say, Mike.
We have time.
I was kept pretty much in the dark.
I didn't know all that much.
What about now? ls there anything
you can help me out with?
Anything you can tell me now?
They got Pentangeli,
that's all I can tell you.
I didn't know
it was gonna be a hit, Mike.
I swear to God,
I didn't know it was gonna be a hit.
Johnny Ola bumped into me
in Beverly Hills...
and he said
that he wanted to talk.
He said that you and Roth...
were in on a big deal together...
and that there was something in it
for me if I could help him out.
He said that you were being tough
on the negotiations.
But if they could get a little help
and close the deal fast...
it'd be good for the family.
You believed that story?
You believed that?
He said there was something in it
for me... on my own.
I've always taken care of you.
Taken care of me?
You're my kid brother.
You take care of me?
Did you ever think about that?
Did you ever once think about that?
Send Fredo off to do this,
send Fredo off to do that.
Let Fredo take care of some
Mickey Mouse nightclub somewhere.
Send Fredo to pick somebody up
at the airport.
I'm your older brother, Mike,
and I was stepped over!
- That's the way Pop wanted it.
- It ain't the way I wanted it!
I can handle things!
I'm smart!
Not like everybody says.
Like dumb. I'm smart...
and I want respect!
Is there anything you can tell me
about this investigation?
Anything more?
The Senate lawyer, Questadt...
he belongs to Roth.
You're nothing to me now.
You're not a brother,
you're not a friend.
I don't wanna know you
or what you do.
I don't wanna see you at the hotels.
I don't want you near my house.
When you see our mother,
I wanna know a day in advance...
so I won't be there.
You understand?
I don't want anything to happen
to him while my mother's alive.
There are more people
than a ball game in here.
There's Willi Cicci.
This committee will come to order.
- State your name, please.
- Frank Pentangeli.
- And where were you born?
- Partanego. Outside of Palermo.
Where do you live now?
I live in an army barracks
with the FBI guys.
We have here, finally, a witness
that will further testify...
to Michael Corleone's rule
over a criminal empire...
that controls all of the gambling
in this country...
and perhaps in other countries.
This witness had no buffer between
himself and Michael Corleone.
He can corroborate our charges on
enough counts for this committee...
to recommend a charge of perjury
against Michael Corleone.
- Senator.
- Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
Mr. Pentangeli.
Were you a member
of the Corleone family?
Did you serve under
caporegime Peter Clemenza...
under Vito Corleone,
also known as the "Godfather"?
I never knew no Godfather.
I have my own family, Senator.
Mr. Pentangeli, you are
contradicting a sworn statement...
you'd previously made to me
and signed.
I ask you again, sir,
here and now under oath...
were you at anytime
a member of a crime organization...
headed by Michael Corleone?
I don't know nothing about that.
I was in the olive oil business
with his father...
but that was a long time ago,
that's all.
We have a sworn affidavit.
We have it--
your sworn affidavit...
that you murdered on
the orders of Michael Corleone.
Do you deny that confession?
And do you realize what will happen
as a result of your denial?
Look, the FBI guys,
they promised me a deal...
so I made up a lot of stuff
about Michael Corleone...
'cause that's what they wanted.
But it was all lies--
everything.
And they kept saying...
Michael Corleone did this...
and that Michael Corleone did that.
So I said, "Yeah, sure!"
Mr. Corleone, would you kindly
identify for the committee...
the gentleman sitting
to your left?
I can answer that.
His name is Vincenzo Pentangeli.
- Is he related to the witness?
- He is, I believe, his brother.
Will he come forward
and be sworn, sir?
Sir, this man
does not understand English.
He came at his own expense to aid
his brother in this time of trouble.
He's not under subpoena.
His reputation is impeccable.
Are you saying he knows nothing
about these matters?
To my knowledge, nothing.
I'm gonna find out
what the hell happened here.
Allright, this committee
is now adjourned.
- The witness is excused.
- Senator!
This committee owes an apology!
This committee owes an apology.
Apology, Senator.
- Michael, excuse me.
- Hold on a minute.
The children are outside.
We're going.
What do you mean you're going?
We're all gonna leave tomorrow.
I'll be in my room.
Michael, I'm not going
back to Nevada.
I brought the children
to say good-bye to you.
I want you to know
I'm very happy for you.
I suppose I always knew
you were too smart...
to let any of them
ever beat you.
- Why don't you sit down?
- I'm not going to stay long.
There are some things
I'd like to talk to you about.
Some things that have been
on my mind.
- Changes I wanna make.
- I think it's too late for changes.
I promised myself
I wasn't going to say anything.
You're too late.
What really happened
with Pentangeli?
His brother came, helped him.
I didn't even know
he had a brother.
Where is he now?
He's on a plane back to Sicily.
All he had to do
was show his face.
It was between the brothers.
I had nothing to do with it.
Nobody is going--
not you, not the kids! You hear me?
You're my wife, they're my children.
I love you. I won't allow it.
You say you love me, then you
talk about allowing me to leave!
Things have been going on for years
between men and women...
- that will not change.
- You've become blind!
- Blind to what?
- Look what happened to us.
- Look what's happened to our son!
- Nothing's happened--
- Anthony is fine!
- Anthony is not fine!
- I don't wanna hear about it!
- You will!
Anthony's not fine!
I don't wanna hear about it!
Over!
At this moment,
I feel no love for you at all.
I never thought
that would ever happen...
but it has.
We're gonna leave tomorrow.
Okay? Why don't you take the kids
back to their room?
You haven't heard me.
What do you want from me?
Do you expect me to let you go?
Do you expect me to let you take
my children from me?
Don't you know me? Don't you know
that that's an impossibility?
That that could never happen?
That I'd use all my power to keep
something like that from happening?
Don't you know that?
Now, in time...
you'll feel differently.
You'll be glad I stopped you now.
I know that.
I know you blame me
for losing the baby.
Yes.
I know what that meant to you.
I'll make it up to you.
I swear, I'll make it up to you.
I'm gonna change.
I'll change.
I've learned that I have
the strength to change.
And you'll forget about
this miscarriage...
and we'll have another child...
and we'll go on--
you and I.
We'll go on.
You are blind.
It wasn't a miscarriage.
It was an abortion.
An abortion.
Just like our marriage
is an abortion.
Something that's unholy and evil.
I didn't want your son!
I wouldn't bring another one
of your sons into this world!
It was an abortion!
It was a son! A son!
And I had it killed...
because this must all end!
I know now that it's over.
I knew it then.
There would be no way...
no way you could ever forgive me...
not with this Sicilian thing...
that's been going on
for 2,000 years--
Bitch!
- You won't take my children.
- I will.
- You won't take my children!
- They're my children too.
Can I speak with you
for a second?
- Where's Mike?
- Waiting for you to leave.
Can I talk with him?
Sorry, no chance.
- Can I see him?
- He's in the boathouse.
Michael, it's Connie.
I'd like to stay close to home now,
if it's all right.
Is Kay coming?
Fredo's in the house with Mama.
He asked for you,
and Tom said you wouldn't see him.
That's right.
Kids, why don't you go outside
for a while?
Please, I wanna talk to you.
I hated you for so many years.
I think that I did things to myself,
to hurt myself...
so that you'd know...
that I could hurt you.
You were just being strong
for all of us the way Papa was.
And I forgive you.
Can't you forgive Fredo?
He's so sweet
and helpless without you.
You need me.
I want to take care of you now.
Sit down.
Our friend and business partner,
Hyman Roth, is in the news.
You hear about it?
I hear that he's in Israel.
And the High Court in Israel
turned down his request...
to live there as a returned Jew.
His passport's been invalidated,
except for return to the US.
He landed in Buenos Aires yesterday.
He offered a gift of a million
dollars if they let him live there.
They turned him down.
- He's gonna try Panama.
- Panama won't take him.
Not for a million,
not for ten million.
His medical condition
is reported as terminal.
He's only gonna live
another six months anyway.
He's been dying of
the same heart attack for 20 years.
- That plane goes to Miami.
- Right. That's where I want it met.
Mike, that's impossible.
They'll turn him over directly...
to the lnternal Revenue, Customs
and half the FBl.
It's not impossible.
Nothing's impossible.
It would be like trying to kill
the president. No way to get to him.
You know, you surprise me.
If anything in this life
is certain--
if history's taught us anything...
it's that you can kill anyone.
Difficult, not impossible.
Good.
Why did you ask me if something
was wrong when I came in?
I thought you were
gonna tell me that...
you were moving
your family to Vegas.
And that you'd been offered the
vice presidency of the hotels there.
- I thought you'd tell me that.
- I turned them down.
Do I have to tell you
about every offer that I turn down?
Let's do business.
All right.
Just consider this.
Just consider it.
Now, Roth and the Rosatos
are on the run.
Are they worth it,
and are they strong enough?
Is it worth it?
I mean, you won.
Do you want to wipe
everybody out?
I don't feel I have to wipe
everybody out--
just my enemies, that's all.
You gonna come along with me on
these things I have to do or what?
'Cause if not, you can take your
wife, family and your mistress...
move them all to Las Vegas.
Why do you hurt me? I've always been
loyal to you. I mean, what is this?
What is it that you want me to do?
How would you like it if I taught
you how to catch really big fish?
- Would you like that?
- Okay.
You know, when I was your age...
I went out fishing
with all my brothers...
and my father...
everybody...
and I was the only one
that caught a fish.
Nobody else could catch one,
except me.
You know how I did it?
Every time I put the line
in the water, I said a Hail Mary.
And every time I said a Hail Mary,
I caught a fish.
You believe that?
It's true.
That's the secret.
Wanna try it
when we go on the lake?
Okay.
What else you got?
Things are gonna be okay, Frankie.
Don't worry.
- Did my brother go back?
- Yeah. Don't worry.
He's ten times tougher than me--
my brother.
He's old-fashioned.
He didn't wanna go out to dinner.
He just wanted to go straight home.
That's my brother.
There's nothing...
that could get him away
from that two-meal town.
He could've been big here,
could've had his own family.
What do I do now?
You were always interested
in politics and history.
I remember you talking about Hitler
back in '33.
I still read a lot.
I get good stuff in there.
You were around the old-timers...
agreeing about how the family's
should be organized...
based on the old home allegiance
and called them regimes--
capos and soldiers.
And it worked.
Yeah, it worked.
Those were the great old days,
you know?
And we was like the Roman Empire.
The Corleone family
was like the Roman Empire.
It was once.
When a plot
against the emperor failed...
the plotters were always given
a chance...
to let the families
keep their fortunes.
Yeah, but only the rich guys.
The little guys,
they got knocked off...
and all their estates
went to the emperors...
unless they went home
and killed themselves.
Then nothing happened to them.
And their families
were taken care of.
That was a good break.
Nice deal.
Yeah.
They went home...
and sat in a hot bath...
opened up their veins...
and bled to death.
And sometimes they had
a little party before they did it.
Don't worry about anything.
Thanks, Tom. Thanks.
See you, Tom.
You have to go.
- So pretty.
- Please hurry. He's coming.
Go rest.
Kiss Mama good-bye.
Will you kiss your mother good-bye?
Say good-bye to Mama.
I love you.
Please.
Come here.
Please, kiss me once.
Easy.
He's here!
We're going fishing!
Michael wants to take him
to Reno now!
Oh, shit.
Okay, kid, you gotta go to Reno
with your pop.
Come on, I'll take you
fishing tomorrow, okay?
Okay.
Attaboy.
Hey, Anthony.
Listen. I'll catch one for you
in secret, huh? All right?
Okay, go ahead.
Okay, let's go.
Mr. Roth, you understand
I'll have to take you into custody?
Yes, I understand.
Can you give us your reaction to
the High Court of Israel's ruling?
I'm a retired investor
on a pension.
I went to Israel because I wished
to live there as Jew...
in the twilight of my life.
Hey, Frankie, come on out!
Let's play some hearts!
Is it true you're worth
over $300 million, Mr. Roth?
I'm a retired investor
living on a pension.
I came home to vote
in the presidential election...
because they wouldn't give me
an absentee ballot.
Jesus Christ.
Hail Mary, full of grace...
the Lord is with thee.
Blessed are thou amongst women.
Blessed is the fruit of thy womb,
Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God,
pray for us sinners.
Hey, everybody,
come on, pay attention. Come here.
This is my friend, Carlo Rizzi.
My brother, Fredo.
- You know Fredo.
- Sure.
Here's my stepbrother, Tom.
That's his girl, Theresa.
This cute little thing over here's
my sister Connie I told you about.
Come on, say hello to Carlo.
He's good-looking, ain't he?
Yes.
Oh, that droopy thing over there,
that's my brother, Mike.
We call him Joe Collar, you know
what I mean? Go on, sit down.
- Go ahead. Talk to each other.
- Sit down.
Hey, Mr. Einstein.
- Here's the cake.
- Hey, get in here.
- Where's your father?
- On a wild goose chase.
- Here.
- Let's see that thing.
- Oh, honey, that's nice.
- That's beautiful.
- Should I put the candles on now?
- Go on. You help her, all right?
Sure.
- What is that, rum?
- Yeah.
Sonny, come on, don't touch
the antipasto till Pop sees it.
What do you think, the nerve of them
Japs, them slanty-eyed bastards?
Dropping bombs on our own backyard.
On Pop's birthday, you know?
They didn't know
it was Pop's birthday.
Well, we should've expected it
after the oil embargo.
What do you mean, expected it?
They got no right dropping bombs.
What are you, a Jap lover?
You on their side?
I understand 30,000 men enlisted
this morning.
- Bunch of saps.
- Why are they saps?
Come on, do we even have to talk
about the war?
You talk to Carlo, all right?
They're saps because
they risk their lives for strangers.
- That's Pop talking.
- You're goddamn right.
They risk their lives
for their country.
Country ain't your blood.
You remember that.
- I don't feel that way.
- "I don't feel that way."
If you don't feel like that,
quit college and join the army.
I did.
I enlisted in the Marines.
- Mike, why didn't you come to us?
- What do you mean?
Pop had to pull a lot of strings
to get you a deferment.
I didn't ask for it.
I didn't ask for a deferment.
I didn't want it.
Come on, knock it off! Come on!
Punk.
- Go on.
- Sit down.
Mommy, Daddy's fighting again!
Go show Carlo the tree.
Nice.
Break your father's heart
on his birthday.
That's swell. Congratulations.
That's right, encourage him.
Go on, get me a drink.
Go on.
I don't understand.
Your father has plans for you.
Many times, he and I have talked
about your future.
You talked to my father
about my future?
- My future?
- He has high hopes for you.
I have my own plans
for my future.
Did you go to college to get stupid?
You're really stupid.
He's here, come on!
Come on.
Stupid.
Surprise!
For he's a jolly good fellow
Which nobody can deny
My dear children.
It is now better than several years
since I moved to New York
and I haven't seen you
as much as I would like to.
I hope you will come to this
ceremony of Papal honors,
given for my charitable work.
The only wealth
in this world is children.
More than all the money
and power on earth,
you are my treasure.
Anthony and Mary,
although I entrusted your education to
your mother for your own best interest,
I look forward to seeing you, and to
a new period of harmony in our lives.
Perhaps you might prevail upon your
mother to come to this celebration,
and that from time to time, we can all
see each other at family functions.
Anyway, I remain your loving father.
Hail Mary, full of grace...
...blessed art Thou amongst women...
...and blessed is the fruit
of Thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, mother of God,
pray for us sinners...
Almighty God, bless the insignia
of Saint Sebastian the martyr,
that it may contribute to the sacredness
of him to whom it is given.
Do you, Michael, promise to be faithful
to the noble purposes of this Order,
to have a special care for the poor,
the needy and those who are ill?
I do so promise.
May the blessing of Almighty God,
Father, Son and Holy Spirit
descend upon you
and remain with you forever.
Vincent, our name is not on the list.
Write it in. Mancini. M-A-N-C-I-N-I.
- Problem?
- My name isn't on the list.
- Then you have to leave immediately.
- You want to dance with me?
Joe, it's Vinnie. These are our guests.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, sir.
Welcome to the party.
- It's good to see you.
- Good to see you. This is my husband.
- Sit down.
- My son, Anthony.
The Order of Saint Sebastian is one of
the highest honors the Church awards.
It was first granted by Pope...
What about Mr. Corleone's connections
with gambling?
The press kits have...
What about his involvement
with the underworld?
Cut the crap.
The Pope, the Holy Father himself,
has today blessed Michael Corleone.
Do you know better than the Pope?
Vincent! She loves you.
Yeah?
I love you too.
Hi, Vincent. I remember you.
- From where?
- The last party we were at together.
- Did you come to the club?
- No, it was a wedding.
I was eight and you were 15.
I had many girlfriends when I was 15.
- Eight-year-olds?
- Especially them.
Where's Mary?
Would somebody please hail Mary?
Excuse me, Your Excellency.
You haven't kissed me hello yet.
Relatives always kiss.
- Now we're related?
- I'm your little cousin.
- Who's your father?
- I'll give you a hint.
He's Italian.
Mary, we've been waiting for you.
Remember to keep your voice low.
And smile. Don't forget to smile.
The honorary chairman of
the Vito Corleone Foundation,
my daughter, Mary Corleone.
Thanks.
I think I inherited my father's love
for speechmaking. Here it goes.
The Vito Corleone Foundation helps
the poor in every country,
gives grants to artists,
funds medical research,
and is particularly dedicated
to the resurrection of Sicily.
Archbishop Gilday,
here is 100 million dollars for the poor
of Sicily, in the name of Vito Corleone.
Don't spend it all in one place.
Mary, I'm so proud of you.
Michael...
You've done a wonderful thing for Sicily.
Let's hope that the money gets
to the people who need it.
Amen.
...the most important part:
Johnny Fontane!
Thank you very much.
I'm happy to be here.
I would like you to join me in honoring
Commendatore Michael Corleone.
I have something special
for our godfather.
I happen to know his favorite song.
Michael, where are you going?
I'm off to the kitchen
to hear some Tony Bennett records.
Your favorite song, "Salsiccia's Own".
I'm having a salsiccia sandwich.
I'll be back.
Hello, Kay.
Congratulations, Michael.
That's quite an honor.
But a little expensive, wouldn't you say?
- Cake?
- No, thank you.
- It's been a long time, hasn't it?
- Yeah.
- Eight years.
You look wonderful.
Your son has something he wants to
talk to you about. I came here for him.
- What's wrong with being a lawyer?
- He wants his life to be in music.
Music is great, I love music.
But he should finish what he started.
Anthony...
- I'm going my own way.
- Your own way?
- Professional singer?
- Yes.
What happens if you fail?
- I won't fail.
- Men always believe that.
A law degree is like taking
out insurance.
- After that you can work for me...
- I will never work for you.
I have bad memories.
Every family has bad memories.
I'll always be your son, but won't have
anything to do with your business.
Anthony... finish the law degree.
No.
Well, that he got from you. That "no".
- You could've helped me convince him.
- Convince him of what?
Of what?
He throws his life away.
He throws greatness away.
This is greatness?
Now that you're so respectable,
you're more dangerous than ever.
I preferred you when you were
just a common Mafia hood.
Okay.
- Can we talk common sense here?
- All right.
Tony knows that you killed Fredo.
- What did you come here for?
- To protect my son.
Not to see you disguised by your
church. That was a shameful ceremony.
I spent my life protecting my son.
I spent my life protecting my family!
Let's be reasonable, okay?
That's your big thing, isn't it, Michael?
Reason,
- backed up by murder.
- Oh, God.
- You hate me. You hate me.
- No.
I don't hate you.
I dread you.
I did what I could, Kay, to protect all
of you from the horrors of this world.
But you became my horror.
The children still love you, though.
Especially Mary.
That's something.
We can build on that. For their sake,
let's try.
Only if you let Tony go free to have
his own life, away from you.
I'll let Tony go.
Thank you.
- Hi.
You could hurt somebody with those.
Let me show you around.
Can you get me an interview
with Corleone?
No. I'm a relative, but I can't do that.
What else can I do for you?
- Handsome, but useless.
- Oh, yeah?
- That's okay, I'll gamble.
- Do you like to gamble?
Let's go to Atlantic City.
I'll show you how to gamble.
- How do I know what numbers to bet?
- Do I look like a guy who's gonna lose?
Well...
Spooky-looking guy there.
- What's a guy like that doing here?
- That's Joey Zasa's bulldog.
- You know him?
- Yeah, I do.
His name is Anthony Squigilaro.
They call him "The Ant".
He dips his bullets in cyanide.
Don Altobello.
- I've come to pay my respects.
- Grazie.
You honor my father's friendship.
Where is my goddaughter?
- Constanza!
- Don Altobello.
It was not so long ago
that I held you in these old hands.
Michael, I've lost all the venom,
all the juice of youth.
I've lost the lust for women,
and now my mind is clear.
My duty to God is clear.
I have a special favor to ask of you.
Can I attach my name
to the Vito Corleone Foundation,
so that you and I can be joined
in name and spirit?
- One million dollars.
- A lot of money...
- Godfather.
- Don Altobello, you have such a heart.
Come, let's go and sample
some of that old vino.
The Vatican knows nothing
about these shareholders.
Good.
I have a tendency to worry. We've
increased our position substantially.
- Naturally, I worry.
- Stop worrying, we have an agreement.
Good. How do you think
I got this gray hair?
Two seconds... Thank you for your
contribution to the swimming-pool.
We need your help on Sam Wallace's
candidacy for judgeship.
- We can always use a goodjudge.
- Thanks.
Andrew!
My godson Andrew Hagen.
My brother Tom's eldest boy.
He's been assistant to Bishop Breelan
for three years.
- Hopes to be assigned to the Vatican.
- Rome needs fine young priests.
His mother Teresa Hagen,
Bishop Gilday.
Honored to meet you.
Mr. Corleone. Hi. Grace Hamilton.
Vincent Mancini promised to tell you
about me. That maybe you'd see me.
- Did Vincent Mancini call about her?
- No.
- You promised to stay out there, twice.
- I know.
Joey Zasa showed up.
He's waiting in the lobby.
He wants to personally
congratulate you. Show his respect.
- Do I have to see him?
- He says you're his patron.
Hey, Vinnie!
- Who's your favorite aunt?
- You are.
Today I'll talk to Michael
about your little problem.
If you'd warned me, I would have
worn a better suit.
The Meucci Association has elected you
Italian-American Man of the Year.
Meucci...
Who's Meucci?
The Italian-American who invented
the telephone, one year before Bell.
And this is the reason
you've come today?
I...
I've got a stone in my shoe.
A two-bit punk who works for me.
The one who thinks he's related to you.
A bastard.
He's here. Vincent Mancini.
He's at the party.
Bring him in.
I think it's good that we talk.
No, grazie.
I have a problem...
...and I want to find out if it is
my problem or your problem.
Your business is your business. I have
no interests or percentages from it.
Good. Then it's my problem.
Michael, you know Vincent Mancini.
Sonny's boy.
- How are you, Mr. Corleone?
- How are you?
- Good. How are you? Good party.
- You like it?
- Yes, I had to sneak in.
- You're dressed for it.
So, what's the trouble
between you and Mr. Joe Zasa?
- Just trouble. I'll take care of it.
- That's foolish of you.
Foolish of me? It's a little foolish
of this guy, don't you think? Right?
- Right?
- Temper like his father...
Vincent...
Mr. Joe Zasa now owns what used to
be the Corleone business in New York.
Out of kindness, he gave you
a job in his family.
You took it against my advice.
I offered you something better in the
legitimate world. You turned me down.
Now you both come to me with this bad
blood. What do you expect me to do?
- Am I a gangster?
- No...
That was Papa's neighborhood.
Zasa runs it like a disgrace!
- That's the past, Connie.
- I earned that territory.
The Commission gave it to me
and you approved.
Yes.
I came for the party, not to ask for help.
I could kill this bastard.
So kill him.
What does all this have to do with me?
Well, he goes behind your back,
saying "Fuck Michael Corleone".
Say it to his face, one time!
Mr. Corleone, all bastards are liars.
Shakespeare wrote poems about it.
What am I going to do with this guy?
Joey, if there's some guy
running around this city,
saying, "Fuck Michael Corleone"...
...what do we do
with a piece of shit like that?
He's a fucking dog.
Yes, it's true.
If anyone would say such a thing,
they would not be a friend,
they would be a dog.
- My interests don't conflict with his.
- You don't know how much they do.
Quiet, Vincent.
He needs your support!
Don't let me work for this guy,
let me work for you.
As what? Tough guy? I don't need
tough guys. I need more lawyers.
Since we have no conflicts or debts,
I accept your tribute. I wish you well.
Vincent, make your peace
with Mr. Joe Zasa. Go on.
Bastardo...
Vinnie, what's the matter with you?
Get him out of here.
Jesus Christ...
- I told Connie this wasn't the right time.
- Close it.
I know you're into Wall Street,
but you're still the final word.
I want to protect you from these guys.
Your lawyers can't.
- But you can?
- Yeah, I can do that.
Why should I be afraid of Zasa?
You stop him from rising
in the Commission.
I say we make him dead.
Give me the order, I'll do it.
- You'll do it?
- Yeah.
Maybe you should come with me
for a few weeks. See what happens.
- Okay.
- See if you learn.
And we'll talk about your future.
I won't let you down.
It's about ready.
So, what happened?
What happened?
If I'm in a room with Zasa,
what happens? I bit his ear off.
Here we go. Watch the card.
Hold it!
- Vincent...
- Yeah.
Take the picture with us.
Nice jacket.
Closer to the center, sir.
Smile!
Godfather, this is the cake for you
and your family from Enzo the baker.
Do you want to do it?
Cent'anni! Cent'anni!
- Vincent?
- What do you want, sweetheart?
Do you love me?
- Come on, go to bed.
- Come on, say it.
I love you.
I love you, too.
You've got a cat?
Go get us some water, I'm thirsty.
Come on.
Well, I guess I know my place.
I can't believe I'm actually doing this.
"Get me water, bake me a cake"...
What happened to "please"?
Good boy, Sackface. Go for a walk.
- Let her go.
- Cut her throat, man.
- What did you say?
- Cut her fucking throat.
- Okay, chief...
- Drop your gun or he'll cut her throat.
I hardly know her, so cut her.
What the fuck do I care?
You've got no choice. She'll be dead.
If you do, I'll kill you both.
Give up that knife, I'll let you go.
Cut her throat! Right now!
I'll do something that'll convince you.
Don't get frightened. Just watch me.
Oh, shit!
Drop the knife. Drop it!
Good boy. Sit down, I want to talk
to you. It was a wise choice. Sit down.
Lose the mask.
Relax, have a smoke. You smoke?
Whose idea was this? Who sent you?
Tell me who sent you.
- No one.
- Did you take a look at this guy?
- Yeah.
- Who sent you?
It was Joey Zasa.
Are you okay?
- You were going to let them kill me!
- No, I wasn't...
You pig! You sick fuck!
You wanted gambling. That's gambling.
Call the police.
- You killed the other guy too?
- He went for my gun.
It was self-defense.
Go ahead, call the police.
- No, no...
- I'm taking pictures.
No pictures.
You had a gun!
They only had a knife. You could have
handed them over to the police.
Zasa sent them.
I just sent him a message.
- Now he has to send you one back.
- Zasa is going to send me one back?
He did the right thing.
He got Zasa's name!
What has Joey Zasa to do
with anything? Joey Zasa is a pazzo.
All right. You are what you are.
It's your nature. Stay close to me.
Don't do anything. Keep your mouth
shut and your eyes open.
- And you do what I tell you.
- I understand.
- I have problems with the Commission.
- I know.
- You don't make them easier.
- It wasn't my idea that this happened.
- Get out of here.
- Michael...
Yes?
- Now they'll fear you.
- Maybe they should fear you.
- B.J., what's up?
- The Archbishop just called back.
We've arranged some amazing things.
The publicity is phenomenal. You're the
new Rockefeller. A philanthropist.
- Sign here, please.
- Times do change, don't they?
My father hated foundations.
He loved doing it by himself.
Man to man. But we're different.
No different than any large corporation.
We control a lot of money with little.
Minimize taxes.
With no government control.
- Godfather.
- Andrew.
- Off to Rome...
- I wanted to thank you for everything.
- Do you want some breakfast?
- Thanks, I can't.
- How's your Italian?
- Devo fare un po' di pratica.
- His father was a great lawyer.
- I know.
Didn't live to see him ordained. I did.
Did you ever see one of those?
Beautiful. I was so proud.
Let me walk you out.
If you hear any rumors in the Vatican,
let me know.
No, Andrew has the true faith.
Don Corleone,
I need your help. And not just
to light a little candle.
My gift was to be able to persuade
people to give to the Holy Church.
Then Rome decides to put me
in charge of the Vatican Bank...
...but I was never a true banker.
Mea culpa. I trusted my friends.
Friendship and money...
Oil and water...
Indeed.
But these "friends" used the good name
of the Church to feed their greed.
If money was lost...
...then I am to blame.
If only prayer could pay off
our 700 million dollar deficit.
769 million...
The Church owns 25 percent
of a large corporation. Immobiliare.
You know the one I mean?
Largest landlord on Earth.
Real estate worth six billion dollars.
That's true.
And the Vatican vote
is necessary for control.
No, you're mistaken.
This isn't a question of one person
deciding. One deciding vote.
This is like any other company.
We have directors and very old rules.
The Pope himself
would have to approve you.
We've sold the casinos.
All businesses having to do
with gambling.
We have no interests or investments
in anything illegitimate.
The Corleones are prepared to deposit
500 million dollars in the Vatican Bank
when Mr. Corleone receives majority
control of Immobiliare.
Immobiliare could be something new.
A European conglomerate.
Few families have control
of such a company.
It seems that, in today's world,
the power to absolve debt is greater
than the power of forgiveness.
600 million dollars.
Don't overestimate
the power of forgiveness.
Don Corleone,
this deal with Immobiliare can make you
one of the richest men in the world.
Your whole past history, and the history
of your family, would be washed away.
600 million.
The motion under discussion
relates to Corleone Group's proposal
to acquire 100,000,000 newly issued
Class A voting shares.
...Corleone capital invested directly
into International Immobiliare,
an old and respected
European company.
Mr. Corleone has an ambitious program
to expand this real estate company
into an international conglomerate...
...by Eastern techniques of efficiency
and focus and unlimited...
Mr. Corleone, excuse me.
Didn't you recently deposit 200 million
in the Vatican Bank,
which is affiliated with Immobiliare?
True. Why not?
Wasn't there any questioning about
the timing on this particular deposit?
Mr. Chairman, if I may?
The Vito Andolini Corleone Foundation,
of which Mary Corleone is chairman,
has made an endowment
of 100 million dollars.
The money comes from his own family
and will be administered by the Vatican.
Does that answer your question?
I have always believed that helping your
fellow man is profitable in every sense,
personally and bottom line.
My fellow shareholders, if Europe
and America can learn to co-operate,
if we can learn to pool our wealth,
share our markets,
we can defeat any competition
anywhere in the world.
Thank you for your time.
I hope that you will look favorably
on my proposal. Thank you.
Let me have this microphone here.
Will we let a criminal run our company?
He's got the map of Sicily on his face!
Order!
He's either a Catholic or a mafioso...
The Hamilton Investors Group
cannot support this proposal.
Your Excellency...
Mr. Chairman...
...the Vatican Bank feels
that International Immobiliare...
...will be safe in Mr. Corleone's hands.
...subject to audit and final ratification,
which must take place in Rome.
Please join me in welcoming
Mr. Michael Corleone.
Dad?
Tony says that I'm a front
for the foundation.
That you're using me to pull the strings.
- To get the money where you want it.
- Please!
- To shine up your public image.
- Mary!
Mary, this is real.
This foundation is real.
I wanted Anthony to be part of it.
I thought you would be together on this.
I won't interfere.
I'll help, but only if you ask.
What is this really for?
Why are you doing this?
Why am I doing this?
I'm doing this for my children.
You're doing it for your children too.
This foundation is supposed to
help all people.
That's the purpose.
This is legitimate.
Mary, I swear, this is legitimate.
Dad, I want this to bring me
closer to you.
I would burn in hell to keep you safe.
Go in the other car.
I'll ride with Michael.
Go, go, go.
As your family's oldest friend, I'm
always chosen to bring you messages.
Tell me, Don Altobello.
Your old partners are grateful for
the money you made them.
They worship you...
...but their hearts are broken, because
they think you abandoned them.
They want to share your deal
on Immobiliare, to be a family again.
It can purify their money.
This I cannot do.
Immobiliare must be legitimate.
I know.
But they're unhappy.
And you?
I ask nothing for myself.
Only peace in my old age.
But I must please the world around me.
Michael, your father was
a reasonable man. Learn from him.
I learned many things from my father.
Call a meeting, my friend,
so there are no debts or grudges.
We will make the peace, you and I.
The Vatican announced today...
that Pope Paul VI has canceled
his Sunday blessing...
due to ill health.
His physician has ordered
total bedrest...
and cessation of all activities.
They've had a press conference.
The Pope's condition
is grave. "Gravissimo. "
The purpose of this meeting
is to ratify...
the motion passed by our
shareholders in New York.
Please...
Our group represents a consortium
of Catholic businessmen
against the Corleone control.
The Vatican has cast its vote. Corleone
Group already controls the Board.
According to the Lateran Treaty,
the Vatican vote must be ratified here.
Here in Rome, by the Pope.
The Pope is gravely ill.
Until he recovers, I am powerless.
- What if he dies?
- Then...
...as you Americans say, all bets are off.
Gentlemen, please.
This is a brief delay. Nothing more.
Your Excellency, gentlemen...
I advise you to join us in our prayers
for the Holy Father's recovery.
We had an agreement!
This meeting was to be
merely a formality.
- Please sit down.
- I'd rather stand. Give me an answer.
The Immobiliare has its roots in the
European tradition. Please understand.
I understand.
Your tactics are despicable.
That's quite an indictment,
coming from a Corleone.
- Gentlemen, gentlemen!
- Remember you are in the Vatican.
- What is it that you want?
- Yes, you will take control.
We'll gladly put you at the helm
of our little fleet,
but our ships must all sail
in the same direction.
Otherwise, who can say how long
your stay with us will last?
It's not personal. It's only business.
You should know, Godfather.
Very well.
You want to do business with me?
I will do business with you.
Vipers, all of them.
- We're back with the Borgias!
- Uncle Michael...
- Andrew!
- I heard you were here.
It's so nice to see you.
Vincent, it's so nice.
What is this about the Borgias?
Those days are over.
- Recognize it?
- Yeah.
Genco Olive Oil. That's where our
grandfather started as a delivery boy.
Three years later he owned it.
- Only in America.
- That's it.
Vincenzo, where have you been hiding?
We need your help so badly.
- What can I do for you?
- Get rid of Joe Zasa. He sells drugs...
Now that I'm an older woman,
I'm afraid to go out at night.
Where should they be now?
- Lou, what's going on?
- We're late.
- Have I ever let you down?
- I trust you.
- Don't worry.
- Thank you.
Enjoy yourselves.
- What was that?
- The neighborhood's in trouble.
- Do you keep an eye out for them?
- Yes.
- And for me?
- From now on.
- I've missed you all this time.
- I missed you too, cousin.
I missed growing up with my cousins.
I didn't even know you, but missed you.
Do you remember stories about
our fathers? The old days?
Yeah, what do you want to know?
- What was Sonny like?
- Well, he was the Prince of the City.
He died before I was born,
but I've heard a lot about him.
- What about my father?
- He's a great man.
He's a hero. He saved the family.
- Vincent?
- What?
Did he kill his own brother?
No.
So, it's all lies?
Just stories, sweetheart. Okay?
Okay.
I believe you.
- I'm glad you're around.
- I'm glad you're here too.
Cugina...
Cous...
I'd like to take Joey Zasa for a ride
in this and drop him.
Joey Zasa is nothing.
He's a small time enforcer.
He bluffs and threatens.
He's nothing.
You can see him coming a mile away.
- We should kill him before he...
- No!
Never hate your enemies.
It affects your judgment.
Nice to see you again, Mr. Corleone.
Hey, girls. Let's go.
We trusted you to manage
our money in the casinos.
It's not even 20 years. You've sold the
casinos and made fortunes for all of us.
Bravo, Don Corleone!
Thank you.
Friends, I have come here
because our business together is done.
We have prospered,
and now it is time for us to dissolve
the business relationship between us.
That's it.
But I do have a little surprise. Al?
Your shares in the casinos.
I thought I cut through all the red tape,
so you could get your money right away.
50 million dollars!
- Not everybody gets the same.
- Nothing for you...
- It depends on your investment.
- Michael, this is really generous!
Wonderful!
- Parisi, how much did you invest?
- I don't remember.
You're blessed.
My family has done much of
the hard work, taken many risks.
All to make money
for the rest of the families.
You all know Joey Zasa.
He is, I admit, an important man.
His picture is on the cover
of the New York Times magazine.
He gets the Esquire Magazine award
for the best dressed gangster.
The newspapers praise him
because he hires Blacks,
which shows he has a good heart.
He is famous.
Who knows? Maybe one day
he'll make all of you popular.
It's true.
I make more of a bella figura.
That is my nature.
But I also want to make a move
into legitimate enterprises.
I'd like a little pin from the Pope.
Sure, I take the Blacks
and the Spanish into my family,
because that's America.
And you guarantee
that they don't deal drugs?
I don't guarantee that. I guarantee
that I'll kill anybody who does.
- Let me talk to him.
- Who can refuse Don Altobello?
- Joey, are you...
- No!
I say to all of you, I have been
treated this day with no respect.
I've earned you all money.
I've made you rich and I asked for little.
Good. You will not give, so I'll take!
As for Don Corleone,
he makes it very clear to me today
that he is my enemy.
You must choose between us.
No, Joey!
Michael, we could reason together.
No.
Michael, please... let's agree.
He doesn't know what he's...
No, no.
Michael, the news is everywhere.
Everyone says that you
control Immobiliare.
Immobiliare is already laundering
money in Peru and Nassau.
We've worked with you for 40 years.
We should wet our beaks a little.
- We want to do business with you.
- That's right, we've been together...
- It's a hit! Let's go!
- Let's get out of here! Move!
My coat! It's my lucky coat!
It's my lucky coat!
Stay behind me!
Mikey, this way!
Zasa, you son-of-a-bitch...
Come on. We're out of here.
- You did good, Vincent.
- Grazie.
The old Dons were pretty much
wiped out.
The survivors made deals with Zasa.
- Altobello?
- He survived.
He's with his daughters in Staten Island.
He says he's going to retire in Sicily.
Joey Zasa would never pull something
like this without the backing.
He's just muscle. He doesn't have
the wit for that helicopter attack.
He doesn't even have the ambition
to wipe out the whole Commission.
I say we hit back and take Zasa out!
Never let anyone know
what you're thinking.
Let's get a message to Joey Zasa.
I respect what he's done.
The new overthrows the old. It's natural.
How can you do business with this guy?
I'm a businessman, first and foremost.
I want no further conflict.
- Tell him that he can live or he can die.
- Vincent, will you shut up!
That's it.
Joey Zasa...
He can't be doing this alone.
Just when I thought I was out,
they pull me back in.
Our true enemy has not yet
shown his face.
Michael!
- Has he had his medicine?
- I don't know what he took.
- I've got my wind back.
- Call a doctor.
- Run, run, run!
- Vincent!
Run at thunder, girl! Thunder can't hurt!
Harmless noise!
Bullshit! You deceitful old fuck!
Altobello, you fuck!
Fredo!
Oh, God! Dad!
Excuse me.
I'll call Kay.
- Good evening, sir.
- Can we wait here? We'll be back soon.
Mr. Harrison, you said it was urgent.
Have you come to confess your sins?
Michael Corleone has had a diabetic
stroke. I wanted you to know about it.
He's in a coma. I'm here to insist
the deal goes through in any event.
The Pope has not much time left.
So, as you, I am in a difficult position.
We have to ratify this deal
as soon as possible.
- We have an understanding.
- Good.
- I'm going to the hospital.
- I'll pray for Mr. Corleone.
- Our thoughts are with Mr. Corleone.
- Thank you, Father Jim.
Everything will be out in the open
if Corleone dies.
Play for time, Keinszig.
A habit born of
a long contemplation of eternity.
- Forget about it, Vinnie.
- Why? It's a simple hit.
I'd love to smack Joey Zasa and then
whack the fag. But it's impossible.
He's always with people, in front of
TV cameras in his own neighborhood.
- It's not impossible. It'll work for us.
- How?
Do you think he's going to let
Uncle Michael survive? Would you?
He may not survive anyway.
- How would you do it?
- I'd do it myself.
Do it!
- What would you need?
- A couple of guys.
Hello, Michael.
It's Kay.
Kay...
I never expected you.
No, I know.
But I'm here.
- I'm glad.
- You know...
I've never seen you looking so helpless.
It's not so bad, really.
I feel... I'm getting wiser now.
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah.
- The sicker you get, the wiser you get?
- When I'm dead, I'll be really smart.
Michael... I want to thank you for Tony.
He's doing really well.
He's gotten some very good notices,
and he'll make his operatic debut
in Sicily, in Palermo this Easter, so...
So, thank you.
That's a real honor. In Sicily.
I will be there. I won't miss that.
I won't miss that.
Mary, Tony...
Go see Dad.
- Sweetheart!
- Everything's going to be all right.
- Tony!
- How are you doing, Pop?
Your mother told me what happened.
- About Palermo? I hope you'll be there.
- Of course. Kiss me.
- Cousin Vinnie?
- He's not here. Call his apartment.
- It's your cousin Mary.
- Let her in.
Hi, cous. I thought I'd drop by.
Is that okay?
I'll get the guys.
No, it's not okay.
You shouldn't have come, Mary.
Only a couple of minutes, okay?
- You look beautiful, cous.
- Thanks.
So this is your club, your hideout?
- Yeah.
- I came here to check it out.
It's so strange, just me
and Aunt Connie in the house.
- I feel better when I'm with you.
- What's wrong, sweetheart?
- I'm scared about my father.
- Don't be.
When they took him out of
the ambulance, I thought he was dead.
Everybody says he's going to be better.
Don't worry.
I remember a shooting when I was little.
And one time Al Neri and other
bodyguards took me and Tony away.
Is it all happening again?
Not like that, sweetie.
Then why are you hiding here?
Is something going to happen to you?
Nothing's going to happen
to me, cugina. We'll take care of you.
- Can I stay here and hide out with you?
- Can you help me cook for the boys?
You know that I don't know
how to cook, but I'll help.
Okay...
What do I do?
- I love you, cous.
- I love you, too, cous.
Let us cook.
Hold me.
You in the press and the police
use words like "Mafia", "Cosa Nostra".
This is a fantasy. We Italian-Americans
laid the bricks that built this city.
We have Meucci,
who invented the telephone.
We have Don Ameche,
who played the guy who invented it.
Buy yourself a raffle ticket,
maybe you'll win a Cadillac.
The salsiccia is wonderful!
Here, have a sandwich.
- Nice to see you, Mr. Zasa.
- Have a nice time.
Don't forget to buy your raffle tickets.
- What are you doing?
- He didn't mean it.
- Tell him you're sorry.
- Okay, let's go.
Joey! How are you?
How are you, Buddy boy?
Hey, Joey Zasa! Joey, up your ass!
- Who is this? Do you know him?
- Ignore him.
Who's going to win the car? The Ant?
This is what gives Italian-Americans
a bad name. A cappone like this.
Joey, up your ass!
Get off the car!
Do you have a raffle ticket?
Joey, take a look at my raffle ticket!
Here's what I think of you...
and your raffle ticket.
Get the fuck off this car.
I'll break your fucking balls.
Get out of here!
Run, Joey! You piece of shit!
Open the door!
How are you, Joe?
Zasa!
Don't ever again give that kind of order.
Not while I'm alive.
Understand?
You were too sick to make a decision.
I got a go-ahead from Neri and Connie.
Connie?
It was the right decision, Uncle Mike.
It was the wrong decision.
I command this family!
Right or wrong...
...it was not what I wanted!
Do you understand?
Yes.
Come on, Michael.
Good. Vincent, help me to my bed.
I want to talk to you alone for a minute.
You know,
I always felt responsible for you.
You know that.
Your father...
...my brother, we were opposites.
We would fight and argue.
But I never doubted his love.
He would do anything for me.
But his temper...
Too much. It clouded his reason.
I don't want you to make that mistake.
Also...
...he, too, had a way with women.
- Vincent...
- So I hear.
What are you doing with my daughter?
What are you doing with her?
It's too dangerous.
Do you hear me?
Okay.
Vincenzo...
When they come,
they'll come at what you love.
Michael, you must lead another life.
You have everything a man
could desire. It's time for you to retire.
I have too much responsibility.
Immobiliare? It's too difficult now.
You should really get out.
What do you know
about those pezzi da novanta in Italy?
I'm too old to know anything
about those new people.
I must accept my age
and grow my olives and tomatoes.
- We're not that old.
- But you're very ill.
Michael... Let me see
what can be done.
Let me work to make your path
a little easier.
- Your friendship does that always.
- That makes me happy.
Joey Zasa...
You were wrong about him.
I trust too much.
That's always been my fault.
Michael... treachery is everywhere.
You still have your fingers
on the strings, even now.
Let's see more of each other.
- Michael, in Sicily?
- In Sicily.
In Sicilia.
How are you?
Don Bendino, my old friend.
I brought you here, so that my old friend
and protector, Don Tommasino,
could advise us.
What do you think about Altobello?
A very talented man.
He has kept the peace between our
Sicilian and American friends.
The saint of reason.
A blood bath in Atlantic City
left New York a mess.
Joey Zasa at least was running
a tight ship,
but with him out of the picture
we must step in.
- Step back in...
- Or the Chinese and Colombians will.
The Corleones left drugs, so New York
is weak, and Palermo is strong.
Your enemies always get strong
on what you leave behind.
Who could give the order
for that massacre...
and still pressure the Vatican deal?
Only Lucchesi can reach
between these two worlds.
"Our ships must all sail
in the same direction"...
Italian politics have had these men
for centuries. They are the true Mafia.
The Archbishop and the Vatican Bank,
that's the big problem.
They're the same problem.
B.J., they're connected.
The Archbishop has powerful friends.
They totally protect him.
Is there someone in the
Church we can turn to?
Someone we can tell
our problem to?
Cardinal Lamberto.
A wise and good man...
very influential.
He will see you.
I will see this Cardinal Lamberto
and see if we can work things out.
You honor your agreements,
but you are dealing with crooks.
They have no honor.
My word is final.
Politics and crime,
they're the same thing.
I've invited you all here to celebrate
my son's debut in an opera house...
We'll play "Philadelphia".
Seven cards. Two down, four up.
Deuces and one-eyedjacks are wild.
...in the opera "Cavallaria Rusticana".
- It's "Cavalleria Rusticana, " Dad.
- "Cavalleria. "
I think I have tickets to the wrong opera.
I've been in New York too long.
You will all receive tickets,
so come on time.
Dad, I've got a present for you.
It comes from the town of Corleone
and it's authentic Sicilian.
And... I learned it for you.
She was wonderful, beautiful.
I loved her. And then she died.
My trusted bodyguard
planted a bomb in my car.
She drove it before I did.
Why is such a beautiful country
so violent?
History.
Mom was telling me about when your
biggest worry was passing your exams.
- Yes, it was then.
- I worry about you now.
Oh, Mary, you're such a
warm-hearted girl. You always were.
- I love my family.
- Even your cousin Vincent?
I really love him.
- He's your first cousin.
- Then I love him first.
Mary, you can't see him.
Just don't see him anymore.
He's right. It's too dangerous.
Mary, you can't see him anymore.
- Not in that fashion.
- No.
- Please, promise me.
- No!
- Obey me on this.
- No, Dad!
Mary is smart, Dad.
She'll understand eventually.
Bella cugina... Tesoro mio.
- You wanted to see me?
- Yeah.
I want you to do something for me.
It's dangerous.
Good. I'm in. What do you need?
I want you to sell your soul
to Don Altobello.
To betray me.
He'd never believe me.
- That depends.
- Sit down.
I have an idea.
See if you can learn
how high Altobello is connected.
Arrange a meeting.
You say how devoted you are to me.
Tell him your problems.
- Ask for his help.
- What problems?
That you want to run away
with my daughter.
But you know that if you do,
I will become your enemy.
- You know that I would never do that.
- I know.
Ask Altobello to speak to me.
To further the marriage.
But you're cousins, after all. Michael
was always a little old-fashioned.
Say you can't belong to my legitimate
world. That you want your own family.
I could straighten out
what Joey Zasa left behind.
If you could use your friendship
to persuade him,
I would be indebted to you forever.
A Corleone knows the value
of such a friend.
Then you would work for me?
S?
Bacio la mano, Don Altobello.
If he hints that he wants you
to betray me, get insulted,
because that's his trap.
You're not telling me
the whole truth, Vincenzo.
Isn't it true, that with Michael gone,
the girl controls everything?
- Leave the girl out of this.
- Of course, you love her.
And she loves you.
I guessed it, didn't I?
You're a wise man, Don Altobello.
I'll be learning a lot from you.
The richest man is the one
with the most powerful friends.
It's my duty to make the introductions.
Don Lucchesi.
Don Altobello tells me that you have
a strong character. A man of respect.
This is the hero who put
Joey Zasa in his grave.
If we'd known of his existence,
we wouldn't have backed Joey.
No one wants another Joe.
Let me be your friend.
- Even the strongest man needs friends.
- I'm flattered.
You're a man of finance and politics.
Things I don't understand.
You understand guns.
Finance is a gun.
Politics is knowing
when to pull the trigger.
How can I help?
Vieni?
Blessed is the peacemaker,
for he can be called the child of God.
- Tu parli Italiano un poco?
- S?
The wheelchair, for Don Tommasino.
I trusted this business arrangement
with the Archbishop. I trusted him.
I was sure his honesty
was beyond a doubt.
But, as you see,
I'm now the victim of a swindle.
He's stalling me. Vast monies have
gone to people in high political places
and the Vatican Bank is the guarantor.
If what you say is true,
there will be a great scandal.
Look at this stone. It has been
in the water for a very long time,
but the water has not penetrated it.
Look...
Perfectly dry. The same thing
has happened to men in Europe.
For centuries they have been
surrounded by Christianity,
but Christ has not penetrated.
Christ doesn't live within them.
- What's happening?
- Could you get me something sweet?
Some orange juice, candy...
I have trouble with diabetes.
My blood sugar goes low.
I understand.
It happens sometimes
when I'm under stress.
I understand.
To come to you
on such a delicate matter...
Accusations against your Archbishop.
It was difficult for me.
The mind suffers
and the body cries out.
That's true.
Would you like to make
your confession?
Your Eminence, I'm...
It's been so long. I wouldn't...
I wouldn't know where to...
It's been 30 years.
I'd use up too much of your time, I think.
I always have time to save souls.
- Well, I'm beyond redemption.
- No, no...
I hear the confessions
of my own priests here.
Sometimes the desire to confess
is overwhelming,
and we must seize the moment.
What is the point of confessing
if I don't repent?
I hear you are a practical man.
What have you got to lose?
Go on.
I...
...betrayed my wife.
Go on, my son.
I betrayed myself.
I killed men.
And I ordered men to be killed.
Go on, my son. Go on.
It's useless.
Go on, my son.
I killed...
I ordered the death of my brother.
He injured me.
I killed my mother's son.
I killed my father's son.
Your sins are terrible,
and it is just that you suffer.
Your life could be redeemed,
but I know that you don't believe that.
You will not change.
Pope Paul VI, Supreme Pontiff
of the Roman Catholic Church,...
died last night at 9:40 p. m.
The Pope was 81 years old,...
and had been in poor health
for the last several months.
Connie...
All my life I've kept trying
to go up in society.
To where everything higher up
was legal, straight...
But the higher I go,
the more crooked it becomes.
Where the hell does it end?
They've been killing each other
for centuries here.
For money, for pride, for family.
To keep from becoming the slaves
of the rich pezzi da novanta.
I made confession, Connie.
I confessed my sins.
Why? That's not like you. You don't
have to confess your sins to a stranger.
It was the man.
He's a good man. A true priest.
He can change things.
Michael...
You know,
sometimes I think of poor Fredo.
Drowned. It was God's will.
It was a terrible accident.
But it's finished.
Michael, I love you.
I'll always help you.
Oh, Connie...
I am honored, Don Altobello, that
you've come from Palermo to visit me.
Hey, the little kid! He's grown.
Do the donkey for me.
It's been some time since we
did business together.
You are my "ace in the hole, "
as we say in America.
I have a stone in my shoe.
You can remove it.
Only one stone?
It's dangerous. A famous man.
You will have to take precautions.
Tell me what to do.
Then I will tell you my price.
Ah, what bread!
Olive oil...
Virgin... only in Sicily.
Alla salute!
To death.
Kay!
- Connie!
- How are you?
Mary, I've missed you.
- Hello, Michael.
- Mom, look at this.
- It's too bad Douglas couldn't come.
- I know. He had a very important trial.
I know he wanted to come.
- The car is...
- Okay.
- Well, your son is an artist.
- Oh, yes. Thanks to you.
- What for?
- For making me let him go.
Well, after all these years,
here I am in Sicily for the first time.
- I want to get a picture of you together.
- Okay.
Hey, Dad. Smile!
I see you still have Al Neri. Why?
I need him. He helps me
get in and out of the car.
- He carries my briefcase.
- You're still a liar, Michael.
Let me show you Sicily, the real Sicily.
So you'll understand the family history.
I think I understand
it well enough.
Anthony, I have something you made
for me a very long time ago.
- Might bring you luck.
- Thanks.
You saved it... I remember.
Thank you, Dad.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you.
- Are they as good as they look?
- Better.
They're the best. As long as they are
around, Uncle Michael is safe.
Goodbye.
- Tell your father I'll be back for dinner.
- Okay.
- Have fun.
- Tell Tony to wait for me.
I will.
Buongiorno, signora. Atyour service.
If I see Dad, I'll tell him you left.
You're the only one left
with my father's strength.
If anything happens to Michael,
I want you to strike back.
I'll have everything ready.
Do you swear?
I swear to you.
Here it is.
The house where my father was born.
This is where they came to take him
when he was a boy. To kill him.
Wait...
Listen to that.
You know Mary's in love.
Yes, I know.
With a handsome young Italian man
with dark eyes...
I won't allow it.
It's wrong.
It's wrong and it's dangerous.
"Oh father, my father!"
"Give me some time to pray
to the Lord. "
The Baroness of Carini had
betrayed her husband...
and fallen in love with her cousin.
"There will be no forgiveness!"
Her father stabbed her through
the heart.
Honor, huh?
I remember the time you came
to my parents' house
and told me about the family business.
How you'd never have anything
to do with it. You sounded like Tony.
I was a lot like Tony.
- I can barely see him... Kay?
- What?
- Do you mind driving?
- What's wrong?
My eyes.
Sometimes they're all right, but...
I have to see Don Tommasino...
Well...
- There are no bodyguards today.
- I really snuck away.
Father, where are you going?
Would you like a ride?
I know you. You're Mosca
of Montelepre.
You were an assassin then
and you're an assassin now.
I know Michael Corleone
is at your house.
I will pass through the gates
with you.
How are you?
This is Calo, one of my bodyguards
in the old days.
- We can wait here.
- You want a drink?
I spent a lot of time in this room...
...thinking of you.
And then you got married.
- I still thought of you.
- What's in that room?
This is dangerous for you. This is Sicily.
- I love this country.
- Why?
Well, all through history, terrible things
have happened to these people.
Terrible injustices.
But they still expect good,
rather than bad, will happen to them.
Sort of like me and you?
- How so?
- I'm still here, right?
We do have a bad history,
but I'm still here.
Yes, you are, but with dread.
Give me the order!
Is that supposed to make me
not dread you?
We're in Sicily. It's opera.
Okay.
What do we do now?
Be reasonable.
Let's try not to hurt each other.
I want you to forgive me.
- For what?
- Everything.
Oh, like God?
No, I need something a little closer.
You couldn't understand,
back in those days.
I loved my father. I swore I would
never be a man like him,
but I loved him and he was in danger.
What could I do?
And then later, you were in danger.
Our children were in danger.
What could I do?
You were all that I... loved and valued
most in the world.
Now I'm losing you. I lost you.
You're gone.
And it was all for nothing. So...
You have to understand,
I had a whole different destiny planned.
All right, I'll stop.
I really don't know what you
want from me, Michael.
- I mean...
- I'm not the man that you think I am.
- I don't know.
- I love you, Kay.
Don't dread me anymore.
You know, every night here in Sicily...
...I dream about my wife
and my children...
...and how I lost them.
I guess that if it's any consolation,
I want you to know that...
...that...
...I always loved you, Michael.
And you know...
...always, I always will.
What is it? What's wrong?
They found Don Tommasino shot.
Is he dead?
My master is dead.
Blood calls for blood.
I must have revenge!
Some day, you may have to do
a difficult service for me.
Command me.
It never ends.
I will avenge him!
Totals...
Lorscheider, 1 vote.
Siri, 11 votes.
Lamberto, 99 votes.
Do you accept your election
as supreme pontiff?
Oh God, shed light on the decision
they have taken on my behalf.
I accept.
By what name do you
wish to be called?
John Paul the First.
I will do things "right away, "
rather than in "a little while"...
Frederick Keinszig, known as "God's
Banker", has been reported missing.
He was last seen leaving the Rome
offices of Vatican owned Immobiliare.
Also missing was a large sum
of money and several documents.
Keinszig, you fool.
His absence casts further suspicion
on the dealings of the Vatican Bank.
For several years,
the bank and its companies
have been the object of allegations
of disreputable business practices.
Lucchesi, will you please
try to understand?
I have phoned him.
I have waited here by the phone.
You would do well to remember,
Mr. Lucchesi,
that this Pope has very different ideas
from the last one.
Goodbye, my old friend.
You could have lived a little longer.
I could be closer to my dream.
You were so loved, Don Tommasino.
Why was I so feared, and you so loved?
What was it?
I was no less honorable.
I wanted to do good.
What betrayed me? My mind? My heart?
Why do I condemn myself so?
I swear,
on the lives of my children...
Give me a chance to redeem myself...
...and I will sin no more.
You look pale. Bad news?
Tell me right away.
It's not just a bad banking deal.
These guys are butchers.
- What guys?
- Lucchesi.
He controls all of them:
Altobello, the Archbishop...
...others higher up, P2 maybe.
Secret unknown. They're running things.
- I'm in their way.
- He's hired an assassin to kill you.
A Sicilian. I don't know his name.
But they say he never fails.
Then no one is safe.
Even the new Pope is in danger.
We still have time. We can prevent this.
I tried, Vincent.
I tried...
...to keep everything from coming
to this. But it's not possible.
Not in this world.
Give me the order.
You won't be able to go back.
- You'll be like me.
- Good.
All my life I wanted out.
I wanted the family out.
I don't want out.
I want the power to preserve the family.
I'm asking for the order.
It's done.
Because I can't do it anymore.
Well, it doesn't matter.
Vincent knows what to do.
Come on outside.
Take a rest and don't think about it.
- All I do is think about it.
- I'm your son.
Command me in all things.
Give up my daughter.
That's the price you pay...
...for the life you choose.
Nephew...
...from this moment on...
...call yourself Vincent Corleone.
Sit.
Don Vincenzo...
Don Corleone...
Don Vincenzo Corleone...
E tu, Vincenzo...
I know how you feel about Michael,
but you can't save him.
He's lost.
Think of yourself.
What's your answer, Vincent?
Enjoy the opera.
It's all taken care of.
Check the bar. I'll check the top floor.
"Here's hoping Tony sings better at the
Teatro Massimo than in the shower.
"Love, Douglas. "
- My darling Constanza!
- Don Altobello.
- This is a great occasion.
- Come, sit down.
Happy birthday.
You're 80, but don't look more than 60.
You're the only one who remembered.
We've just got the word.
The Pope has ratified
the Immobiliare deal. We've won.
Congratulations.
Strange how things work.
The Pope is doing what you
said he'd do. He's cleaning house.
He should be careful.
It's dangerous to be an honest man.
I want to put more muscle backstage
with Tony.
On your birthday you used to
shower me with treats.
Tootsie Rolls!
The nuns who made this cannoli took a
vow of silence. They're the very finest.
- Hey.
- Hey, cous.
Hi. Where's your leather?
Stop it.
You're so thin. You eat it.
?buono.
Grazie!
It's over. There are things I have to do
that you can't be part of.
It's not your father's decision, it's mine.
Don't hate your father.
There are things I'll be part of
that you can't be around.
After tonight,
you won't see me anymore.
You've got to understand, Mary.
You've got to understand.
I'll always love you.
Love somebody else.
- They won't try anything.
- Everything's fine. It's all clear.
I've already sent Al Neri to the Vatican.
Mr. Lucchesi's house?
Yes.
I bring a message from
Michael Corleone.
Let him in.
Buona sera.
Good. You got him.
Tonight the Corleone family
settles its accounts.
Keinszig...
That little Swiss banker fuck.
He's been swindling everyone
from the beginning. Fuck him.
Don Lucchesi, my friend.
Calo will pay him a visit at his home.
Neri, take a train to Rome.
Light a candle for the Archbishop.
Tea, Your Holiness? It will help
you sleep.
This is from Vincent Corleone.
It's serious. Our man inside the Vatican
says there's a plot against the Pope.
He'll have a heart attack?
This Pope has powerful enemies.
We may not be in time to save him.
Let's go back.
Eminenza...
The Holy Father is dead!
Sleep.
Sleep, Godfather.
Our friend's dead.
Speak... tell me.
You have lost the
faith of the people.
He who builds on the people
builds on mud.
And Michael Corleone's message?
It's very important.
I must whisper it in your ear.
He's clean.
Power wears out those
who don't have it.
- I like this outfit.
- I figured you would.
Say hello.
- Can I talk to you now?
- No, it's not a good time.
- You're just like my father.
- Stay with the family. Go on.
- Talk to me.
- The twins are dead.
In about one minute, there will be
carabinieri all over this place.
Get everybody to the cars, quietly.
- Got it.
- Quiet.
The name Corleone
will be associated with a voice.
Dad...
Dad... Why are you doing this to me?
Move back, move back.
- You don't have to do this to me.
- Do what? What do you mean?
Dad...
No! Mary!
God, no!