"In the name of Allah, Most
Gracious, Most Merciful."
'From Mohammad, the Messenger of Allah,
to Heraclius, emperor of the Romans.
Peace with those which followed Islam.
I invite you to hear the call of Islam.
Converted to Islam and you will be
saved, Allah will reward you doubly.
And if you are diverted, you will
carry the sin of all Christians. '
He speaks of a new prophet in Arabia.
Was he like this, when John
the Baptist, came to King
Harod, he came from desert,
crying about salvation?
For Cyrus, patriarch of Alexandria.
'From Mohammad, the Messenger of Allah,
to Khosro, emperor of the Persia.
Converted to Islam and you will be
saved, Allah will reward you doubly.
And if you are diverted, you will
carry the sin of all Mazdeans. '
You, the barbarian of the desert,
you signs prayer with the Persian King?
'Mohammad, Messenger of Allah'...
Who gave him this authority?
Allah sent him for the
mercy of the universes.
After Agreement of the responsible
commission of Al-Azhar University,
And of High Council Islam of Lebanon,
This film was released.
"If this Coran were revealed to a mount,
it would collapse even off feared Allah..."
Allah, the Great, said the truth.
The Prophet,
elected official by Allah to carry
what the mountains can not,
is too great and inaccessible
to be represented by a human.
For that we will not see nor his image
neither his voice nor his shade,
throughout this film.
At the sixth century,
whereas the world is in darkness,
was born Mohammad in Mecca.
Mecca is a place of trade,
and the cradle of the idolaterist
divinities by the Arabs.
During the crowned months, the
tribes defer their conflicts,
and the convoys flow, carrying
the offerings to Kaaba.
It was built by Abraham prophet
for the believing pilgrims.
Now gathers 360 idols, of the
same number as the Arab tribes.
Mecca was controlled by Koraichians.
Of which Banou Abd Eddar, rich
person and large commercial,
who monopolized the maintenance
of the idols to make deals,
and Banu Hashim, grandfather of Mohammad…
who preferred to accomodate the
pilgrims during their stay.
Lord Omayya.
Bilal!
- That is not enough. - How?
I refunded more than my debt.
That made five years that I refund.
You do not know only that doubles?
That doubles.
He is with you?
I need some to plow, it is
all that it remains me.
The ass does not even pay half.
The boy…
My son?
How you find the market?
I can not decide yet, the
caravans continue to arrive.
This year, the idols bring back gold.
If you combined idolatry and trade,
one would collect more, Abu Sofyan.
I see the caravan of Syria.
It is in advance.
Add five men to the northern well.
How many cuts the throat of sheep, 70?
Hundred. For the prestige of Mecca.
And ten lambs for their chiefs.
Who said to the people
that the money was laudatory,
when it is wasted?
And that, preserved,
it became abusive?
Whit which of other that Abu Sofyan, the
courageous one and the generous one,
can one require help?
Here, son of the Harb.
Thanks to him pass your caravans,
where good seems to them,
finding in this ground the respect.
He hold in high regard poetry,
for which he spends without counting,
because the poems are light breezes.
The silk of China, Madam.
Soft with the touch.
A pleasure for the eyes.
Yes, seven lengths.
Twenty dinars.
For the woman of Abu Sofyan?
Your price will be mine.
Fifteen.
It is well. With each idol its share,
the pledge of its immortality.
Abu Lahab, the man upright over there,
who is this?
Carry far me from here,
He stripped me of all.
Why Mohammad follows us it?
What did it arrive to my nephew?
Give him to place.
Perhaps he will change.
At forty years?
He is improper for a ripe man
to insulate himself in a cave,
and to prefer the nudity of
the caves to a soft bed.
Being the husband of a rich woman,
like Khadija,
can offer what there is best.
A man who dares to enrage Ozza?
And Manat, god of our prosperity,
and Al-Lat,
god of our origins and our virtues.
And Houbal,
on which our destiny depends and
who takes care on our caravans.
This man,
court with its loss.
To disavow the divinities as a public,
is dangerous.
- It is a heresy. - An abjuration.
Insubordination.
I am afraid for him.
Sadness seizes me each time
the market is emptied.
Perhaps that predicts,
that I will re-examine it never again.
- Abu Taleb!
- Abu Taleb! - Gently, Zayd.
Mohammad is descended from the Hira cave?
Not, we did not see he yet.
Khadija sent to me, thinking
that he was at home.
He is perhaps at Abu Bakr.
Not, I went to see.
Then it must be in the cave.
Since three days?
There remained a long time this time.
I am afraid for him in the mountain.
Because I am unaware of his goal.
The man sees the world beter,
the top of a mountain.
"Read!
Read, in the name of your Lord who created.
He created human from a clot of blood.
Read! And thy Lord is Most Bountiful,
who taught to write with the pen.
Taught human what he knew not."
He is always draped in his cape.
The revelation weighs on him.
Hardly arrives at raising the hand.
He is taken tremors,
whereas its face beads of sweat.
But he spoke.
Zayd!
What arrived at Mohammad?
He was alone,
he meditated in the cave.
The angel appeared to him
and he says to him: "Read!"
Mohammad answered: "I can not read."
The angel repeated several times to him:
"Read!"
And Mohammad answered:
"What must I read?"
The angel of the revelation says then:
"Read, in the name of
your Lord who created.
He created human from a clot of blood.
Read! And thy Lord is Most Bountiful,
who taught to write with the pen.
Taught human what he knew not."
And Mohammad read.
As if the verses had been
written in his heart.
Then Gabriel from him went away.
Gabriel?
When Mohammad left the cave,
he intended a voice of the sky to say:
"- Mohammad!
You are the Messenger of Allah.
And I am Gabriel."
And Mohammad from went away at his place,
to tell Khadija what had seen.
And she say to him:
"Delighted my friend, and hold good.
Because in the name of
that which has my heart,
I wish that you would be the
prophet of this community."
Who is well-informed, Zayd?
The first to know it were
Khadija, Ali and Abu Bakr.
And you.
I am his adoptive son.
Are kept to announce in Mecca.
Say him that his uncle who raised him.
Will never drop him.
Why Mohammad called you?
I answered for the knowledge.
The cave, the angels, it is a heresy.
- That Abu Sofyan says?
- That relates to Banu Hashim.
A heresy? It is not new.
- That are for Mecca.
- This did not already arrive.
In Noah, Moses and Jesus
and with all the prophets?
Mousab, who is this?
Jaafar.
What you hold?
A sura of Coran.
"In the name of Allah, Most
Gracious, Most Merciful."
"When the sun is covered,
And when the stars darken,
And when the mountains
are made to pass away,
And when the camels are left untended,
And when the wild animals
are made to go forth,
And when the seas are set on fire,
And when souls are coupled,
And when the female infant
buried alive is asked,
For what sin she was killed,
When the Scrolls are laid open,
and when the sky is unveiled,
When the Blazing Fire is
kindled to fierce heat,
And when Paradise is brought near,
Every soul shall then know
what it has prepared."
Allah, the Great, said the truth.
Jaafar.
You were over there when Allah
revealed these words to him?
He trembled under its cape,
and he claquait teeth.
He tried to stop his shivers.
Then he awoke and spoke.
It is the daybreak.
Ammar, you initially.
Ammar...
Where you were?
Your mother worries, she did not sleep.
Forgiveness, it is my fault.
This god helped us all our life.
But it did not help itself.
I have shame of deifier that.
True Allah is that which sees,
without being seen.
Ammar.
We see the gods in Kaaba.
Ammar, I am afraid for you.
You listenings of people who will lose you.
I listen to Mohammad, Mother.
Mohammad?
All Mecca testifies to its honesty.
It are that which gives without counting.
Greet everyone.
But I do not want only it offends the gods.
Gods?
Which is this god who accepts
that one dies of hunger?
That the rich person exploits the poor one?
That the fort oppresses the weak one?
Which authorizes the fathers to kill
their daughters without reason?
Are this a god that which...
That which prohibits to the
women to choose their husband?
And accept that one imposes a
life worse to them than death?
Your mother was not forced.
You remember, Yasser?
We would never have met.
And you Ammar, you would
not have been born.
My father was Abut to bury me...
…alive.
Like buried my sister.
But he could not do it,
because he remembered that whereas
he covered her with sand,
she clung to one its fingers,
and weas put to suck it,
as if it make always,
later says to my mother.
Hers pressure was soft.
I think that it was soft.
It is a weakness of my father
who saved me the life.
It is the habit, Somayya.
It is a sin, and a god who authorizes
it does not deserve a worship.
I must join the Prophet.
Go ahead, my son. Will join Mohammad.
He is a blessed man.
Two men follow him.
Read? Read? Mohammad can
neither read nor to write.
But he can speak.
How?
He can speak?
Me also, I can speak.
That Mohammad says?
He say only what one reveals
to him of the words of Allah.
Which words? And which Allah?
A god who speaks!
Mohammad is delirious.
Retain all that one reveals to him.
Then he dictate it with
those which transcribe it.
The words of Allah are unchanged.
It is Coran.
Mohammad is famished for his dreams.
You do not say that he hides
under his cape the closed eyes?
Yes, but his heart is open.
You, it for his eloquence strikes.
Not.
It is not a solution.
Mohammad does not realize it,
that our life depends on the gods of Kaaba?
Kaaba belongs to us.
Every year, the caravans arrive,
make it tower of Kaaba and buy our goods.
It is not so easy, my boy.
How to replace 300 gods
by only one, invisible?
You say that is everywhere, here, at home,
in Taif, Medina, Yemen, on the moon!
That the pilgrims would visit
while coming in Mecca,
if they can adore only one Allah
whom they find everywhere?
The gods are for Koraichians,
a worship and a trade.
Allah is not goods.
The whip will correct you.
Take guard with you and pay attention.
I have a question!
It appear that this illiterate bed that
the slave is the equal one of his Master.
Bilal, this Black that
I bought, my is equal?
Yes... if it is a human being.
The Prophet says as:
"The men are equal like
the teeth of a comb."
This heresy tries the slaves and their
fact of hoping for the delivery.
Bilal...
Teach to this boy the difference
between a Master and his slave.
Give him the whip.
So that it can not pronounce
one word any more.
Bilal, whips it.
Whip it.
Kill it.
Obeyed.
Obeyed them.
Do it.
Save your heart.
Disorder invaded Mecca
and reached our slaves.
Same if you are a man who has gods,
they must be ours.
Your body and your heart belong
to me since I bought to you.
I will correct you.
The Single One.
Allah is the Single one.
Which is strongest?
The Single One... The Single One…
- Answer. - The Single One.
Your Master or your single Allah?
The Single One...
Allah is the Single one.
You did not complete it?
This slave does not shout of
pain, it assembles the slaves.
Omayya!
Abu Bakr proposes hundred dinars
more to you than the price of Bilal.
Wait.
One do not sell a slave
during his punishment.
Let negotiate it.
Two hundred dinars, Omayya.
Abu Bakr? That wants to say Mohammad.
After the higher bid of the slaves,
we will nourish our animals
ourselves the next year?
Take it, I do not want it more.
You must obey me of my alive.
Why you put your father in anger?
If I drank alcohol,
in the streets of Mecca, I trailed
would satisfy my father, sister?
Do not call me 'sister'. - What you make?
You are all my children.
And you, I will give you what you wish,
what you will want.
Mohammad gave me serenity and peace.
Let leave it.
That it joins converted,
do not it for us,
but have pity of your father.
Hudayfa, wait!
Your nephew insults our
gods and our fathers,
and corrompt our children.
Step so quickly, Abu Hakam,
step so quickly.
I would not have let it sow the disorder.
The most courageous young
people of Mecca follow him.
And that of us the Arabs will say?
That the young people guide the old ones?
Abu Taleb, say to me,
how the sky would choose an ordinary man?
We were very patient with your nephew.
We let us propose a market to him.
If he rejects it, we
will fight against you,
until the defeat of one of the camps.
If he wants money, he
will be richer than us.
And if he wants a statute,
he will be our master.
If he wants sovereignty,
he will be our king.
If he wants the authority, he
will have the keys of Kaaba.
Now that you heard their request,
Mohammad, my nephew,
save to me, and you with.
And weighed down not burden of an old man.
Mohammad is so great!
One offer the world to him and it refuses:
"My Uncle,
if they offered the sun in my right
hand to me, the moon in the left,
I would not give up my mission,
until Allah me asks it, or which I die."
Allah asked Mohammad to
proclaim his mission.
We leave to protest the truth!
The world must know!
It do not have there other gods
that Allah and we adore only him,
devoted to his religion.
Against the non-believers! Allah is great!
It have other gods there only Allah,
and Mohammad is its Messenger!
"In the name of Allah",
we proclaim our message!
"In the name of Allah", we leave the shade.
Allah is great, Allah is great!
It do not have there other gods that
Allah and Mohammad is its Messenger!
Allah is great, Allah is great!
It do not have there other gods that
Allah and Mohammad is its Messenger!
Koraichians, you hear?
You leave bottoms in favour of Mohammad,
to invade Kaaba?
- Not, in the name of Houbal!
Will throw we them in the flames!
A burning fire!
A burning fire, a burning fire!
Allah is great! Allah is great!
It do not have there other gods that
Allah and Mohammad is its Messenger.
Light it.
Protect the Prophet.
"Perish the hands of Abu Lahab!
He will perish!
His wealth and what he
earns will not avail him.
He shall soon burn in fire that flames,
His wife shall carry the wood,
Upon her neck a halter of
strongly twisted rope."
Allah is great!
Ahead!
Leave Mecca!
Liars!
That the world testifies some!
Like all people!
Abu Sofyan, it is the
occasion to complete them.
They are only thirty.
Not, not in Kaba,
not to ennoble them.
You draw aside us from the divine right,
of the house of Abraham and all the Arabs.
Allah is great!
Allah is great, Allah is great!
Open!
"Say: O unbelievers! I do not
worship that which you worship..."
Move away them from Kaaba!
Stop this liar who claims
to know the skies!
Protect the Prophet!
Hamza!
Abu Jahl, you are valorous.
You attack disarmed men.
They support this impudent...
- The most impudent than you?
You who prevent from expressing yourselves?
Mohammad is a liar.
To me, return if you so hardy!
Nobody wants to face me?
I am in the religion of Mohammad.
I say what he says.
Try of me to divert some.
Mohammad, my nephew,
When I cross the desert the night,
I realize that Allah is too tall
to be confined between four walls.
Which would have believed that Hamza,
wine amateur and hunter of lions,
would follow Mohammad?
Plus one persecute them,
more they become strong.
Where he finds his words?
I do not know, Hind.
How an illiterate man, exceeding forty,
can go down again of a mountain
more eloquent than a poet?
If it were only of poetry…
people believe that they
are the words of Allah.
How to fight a man which one
does not know the force?
Mohammad promises milk
and wine rivers to them.
Therefore it is listened to.
It is necessary to dissuade some.
Let us start with weakest.
Not!
Ammar!
Mother!
- Mother! Mother! - Ammar!
Come to find uprightness!
Somayya!
Not! Not!
Release it! Release it!
Yasser!
Not! Not!
My parents!
Come to join them.
Attach it!
Father... Mother...
It do not have there other gods that
Allah and Mohammad is its Prophet.
It do not have there other gods only Allah.
You do not want to say good of our gods?
Say: 'Houbal'!
I attest that there is only one Allah,
and I attest that Mohammad...
Not! Not!
Mother...
Pity!
I attest that Mohammad is
the Messenger of Allah.
Houbal! Houbal!
Houbal...
Say: 'Houbal the grand!'
Say: 'Houbal', and denies
the religion of Mohammad.
- Houbal.
It do not have there other gods that
Allah and Mohammad is its Messenger.
Unhappy!
Where is your single Allah to save you?
Leave, leave, brothers of Islam.
Would be patient, Ammar, the
Prophet announced a good news:
'Patience with Yasser, the
paradise is promised to you. '
Prophet came.
Messenger of Allah,
how can I raise the head,
whereas I betrayed you
and called upon their gods?
Suffering made me lose conscience,
I shouted with the assistance
and they killed my parents under my eyes.
They obliged me to betray
you, o Messenger of Allah.
My Allah, forgives me.
Confidence as a Allah.
You touched the Prophet
and he cried of pity.
You will not be blamed if you
spoke under the constraint.
Allah charges a heart only
according to his capacity.
You are not in safety here.
Prophet asks us to leave Mecca.
If you remain, they will kill
you the ones after the others.
He say: 'Go in Abyssinie,
where there is a king,
which does not know the injustice. '
Leave now.
Immediately.
Of the riders... Caution!
We found their traces and followed them,
but we turned in round.
And they are thus escaped.
To escape? They volitilized!
Mohammad remained, only the weak ones left.
Forts or weak, they will harm to us,
like with our business.
Abyssinie... Amr?
You are not the friend of their king?
I think of being his friend.
Can you use this friendship?
I can bring back the runaways.
Go for Abyssinie.
These people... Let us see
how they will be humiliated.
You do not incline yourselves?
We prosternons ourselves
only in front of Allah.
Mohammad said to us that he
was the Messenger of Allah.
The Messenger of Allah? Where
are his miracles, Jaafar?
Had he a rise? Went he on water?
Cured he the patients, gave
again the sight or the life?
Where are his miracles, Jaafar?
He is right.
The prophets make miracles,
to prove that Allah sent.
The miracle of Mohammad is Coran.
Of the words?
Of the words written by illiterate,
and allotted to Allah.
Excuse you them now?
I know that Allah sent tongues
of fire on the apostles,
so that they can be expressed
in all the languages,
that they were unaware of before.
But I wonder,
if such miracles exist still nowadays.
I heard some enough.
Your argument is weak.
We came to flee the injustice
and the suffering.
Mohammad said to us:
'Go in Abyssinie,
where the king does not
treat anybody wrongfully. '
What they call injustice
is their right punishment.
Why you send to me?
You form part of people of the Book.
Since you believe in a
God, you will protect us.
Your Majesty, their
speech is like a mirage,
that made thirsty, takes for water.
They convinced me. I must
listen to them, my friend.
Your Majesty,
we were people being unaware of,
we venerated wood and stone idols,
eaten the carrion, made adultery
and broken the blood ties.
We neglected our neighbors and the
rich person oppressed the poor.
Until Allah sends a prophet among us,
we know the virtue,
the sincerity, honesty and dignity.
It invited us to adore Allah,
and to give up our wood and stone gods.
You calumniate our divinities!
We do not venerate the wood
or the stone of the idols,
but the spirit which resides at
it and bring us closer Allah.
Everyone does not see the
things in this way, Amr.
That you your religion orders?
It order to us to venerate
only one single Allah,
to request and say the truth,
to be honest and to respect the
our neighbor and blood ties,
to avoid the taboos and blood.
It prohibit adultery and slanderings to us,
to steal the money of the orphan
and to calumniate the pure women.
Pure women?
And women?
The woman is equalizes of the man.
- She have the same rights. - Which rights?
Let us buy we them and the
infants to be been useful,
and let us sell them if
they refuse to obey.
Mistakes you the woman who
carried you in her belly,
and which nursed to you being small?
Until you would be adult, Amr?
Why your gods are dumb?
Their single Allah it overpowered?
Our Allah is that of all.
Allah of Abraham, Moses,
Zacharie, John and Jesus Christ.
They had a revelation, just like Mohammad.
Which taught you these names?
Coran.
- It was revealed to Mohammad. - Mohammad!
He were only a one orphan shepherd.
And Christ were a ground
carpenter of Allah.
To tell you the truth,
the words of Mohammad,
and those of Christ come
from the same light.
Your Majesty,
what they say of Christ will displease you.
- That they of Christ say? - They says...
...that it is a being like us.
Speak... What you of Christ say?
We say of him what Mohammad reported to us.
He is spirit whose words
inspired the Virgin Mary.
And how was born Christ?
Your Coran says something
on the birth of Christ?
Yes. Can I quote it?
Approach and speak.
"In the name of Allah, Most
Gracious, Most Merciful."
"Relate Mary in the Book,
when she withdrew from her
family to a place in the East.
She placed a screen from them,
then we sent to her our spirit,
and he appeared before her
as a man in all respects.
She said:
'I seek refuge from thee to Most
Gracious, if thou dost fear Allah. '
It said:
'I am only a messenger of your Lord,
that I will give you a pure boy. '
She said:
'How shall I have a son, seeing that no man
has touched me, and I am not unchaste?'
It said: 'Even so, your Lord
says: 'It is easy to me,
and that we may make him a sign to men,
and a mercy from us. '
And it is a matter which has been decreed."
Allah, the Great, said the truth.
It refer there only this
between our two religions.
Amr,
same for a gold mountain, I do
not would yield them to you.
Go with your companions, Jaafar,
and live in peace on this
ground, until your return.
It is intolerable!
Mohammad steals us abroad even our allies.
Very well,
will make we a foreigner of here. - Yes.
Which protects here?
Abu Taleb? We will isolate.
As well as Banu Hashim. - Yes.
More sales with them,
nor of purchases.
More roof to shelter them,
more food, neither sold nor given.
More marriages with them.
Send them in the mountains,
until they give up.
And the years passed.
Mohammad and his partisans were
patient vis-a-vis with misfortune.
And the third year arrived.
Khadija, the mother of believing,
suffered until her death.
And Abu Taleb died of sadness.
It was the year of mourning.
Hisham... Zuhayr...
- That there is?
- We want to tear the bill.
- A shame. - Withdraw this bill!
You are not with Mohammad,
that does not concern you.
We will not fight you.
You eat, whereas a part of
our people dies of hunger?
The chiefs of Mecca concluded an agreement,
will not touch you there,
return on your premise.
Let us go there.
It is a plot.
You claimed a miracle,
here in front of you.
A miracle achieved by
the weakest creatures.
These termites overpowered you,
humiliated you and destroyed your pride.
It is all that it remains you.
Your force is your cruelty.
Your omnipotence and all that you built,
are less in front of the size of Allah.
Here your bill, Koraichians.
There remain only these words about it:
"In the name of Allah."
"And we shall turn to whatever
deeds they did, and we
shall make such deeds as
floating dust scattered about."
Allah, the Great, said the truth.
Chiefs of Mecca, you cannot flee,
the time and the evils
will be right of you.
What a splendour!
Hamza the hunter of lions
drives out the insects!
Yes.
Today and tomorrow, Hind.
I must bid my farewell with
the life, my hour is close.
But I did not convene you for that.
I called you,
for something of more serious still.
I called Mohammad.
In order to reconcile you.
But if he invites us to do what we refuse?
Say to him to stop blaspheme our gods.
We have our religion and he has his.
If he accepts it, we will listen to him.
It required one word of you.
We would have accepted ten other words,
but to say single Allah, not.
You fear...
...of...
...to listen...
...what he says?
Are not there another city,
that this incredulous city and deaf person?
The sorrows accumulated.
Yesterday, Khadija left us.
It were like a mother for me.
And today, Abu Taleb.
We have in Mecca neither support
any more nor protection.
Sinan,
The Prophet wants to move away from Mecca.
Immediately... Without delaying.
It want to go in Taif.
Taif?
Where there will not be nor Abu Sofyan,
neither Abu Jahl, nor Abu Lahab.
Taif, second Arab city,
went the Prophet with
his adoptive son, Zayd,
in the hope to find of the
assistance near the chiefs of Taif.
After his despair in Mecca.
People, fear Allah!
Fear Allah!
You are Christian?
Of Naynawa... Give him that.
It bleed of the feet.
It request Allah.
"O Allah! With you, I lime pits of
my weakness and my lack of skill,
vis-a-vis with these men,
o you Most Merciful.
You are the Lord of weak
and you are my Lord.
A which give me you?
A dour foreigner,
or one enemy to whom you yielded to me?
If you are not in anger against
me, I would not be done any,
your safety is more important to me.
I take refuge under the light of your face,
which improved the life and beyond.
Do not make me undergo your anger,
or to fall under your curse.
I go back to you until your satisfaction.
It have there of force and
power only as a Allah."
I advise you to leave.
Taif is not any more one sure place.
It did not know worse day.
And Allah accept, prayers of its prophet.
One year before, of the pilgrims
had recognized Islam in secrecy.
And at the time of the
following pilgrimage,
without the knowledge
of Koraichians,
came from Aws and Khazraz,
the enemies of always,
to promise immunity and the support to him.
They requested the Prophet
to come on their premises,
to save their city of hatreds and the ruin.
But the allegiance did not take place,
that after having specified
the extent of it.
Wait.
With this promise,
you oppose to all the polytheists.
You promise that the foreign
Muslims will be your brothers,
and inaccurate your enemies even
if they are of your family.
You promise to destroy your stone idols,
and to break and burn your wood fetishes.
People,
if you think of supporting
that, make act of allegiance,
and if you have fears, abstain from.
In the name of that which sent to you,
we promise to defend you
as we defend our children,
and our families.
Let us promise we him with the Prophet.
And which violates this oath, will
undergo the consequences of them.
We believe in a Allah and his Messenger.
Us, Aws and Kahzraj.
We are its partisans.
We promise to the Prophet to obey to him,
to make triumph Islam,
ourselves, with our children,
and our goods,
and to open our hearts and our doors,
with exiled, our brothers in Islam.
Then came the day from separation.
Of the shade towards the light,
Them emigrated left by groups,
The single Allah not leaving their hearts.
Among exiled for the divine
cause: Othmane Ibn Affane,
Abd Al Rahman Ibn Awf,
Obayda Ibn Al Jarrah,
Omar Ibn Al Khattab,
and all powerful Koraichians
which embraced Islam.
They were seventy or to
make this voyage more,
which changed the course
of the history of the man,
and the face of the world.
But the Prophet did not leave Mecca.
It waited until the faithful
ones left in all safety.
Allah is great.
And the day when the
Prophet arrives at Medina,
mark the beginning of the Muslim
calendar with the Hegira,
Mohammad became a nation,
received a city, Medina,
He treated with your people
during your sleep, Ibn Souloul.
You lost your kingdom yesterday
whereas you dreamed of glory.
Do not make me reproaches, you
are between its hands now.
Your caravans will go to Syria
only while leaving in secrecy,
or after the authorization
of the new chief of Medina.
And you, whom you make?
I will wait... and watch for.
How long?
Until the Arabs raise
themselves to crush it,
and that you take again your way of life.
And during this time,
which will be your role?
I will convert with Islam.
To leave him my birthplace? That, not!
Medina deserves the sacrifice
- It is hypocrisy.
Yes, Hind, hypocrisy and conversion.
Ibn Souloul embraces Islam?
Put the face on the ground
five times per day?
I do not believe in it.
- Will perhaps not be obliged there.
If the things occur well, Ibn Souloul.
We prepare a plan which
has before escaped us.
Mohammad...
...will be killed.
Come to see.
We worked out a plan to kill Mohammad.
Young person of each tribe,
of which my Akrima son.
They will strike he all of a blow.
And his blood will be
divided between the tribes.
It is my idea.
That will not put a term at he.
It will remain his call and his words.
But the idea of Abu Hakam
regulate the problem.
And for always.
Not!
Ali slept in his place?
This boy would give him his life.
Contre which fight us?
Will not go far! All the
exits are supervised!
It have only the desert in front of him!
Hundred camels to which will bring
back Mohammad living or dead!
They are three: Mohammad, Abu Bakr
and their guide Urayquit,
which knows the desert.
Go!
Why you seek it here?
Medina is by over there.
They are their traces.
- Nomads going towards the west?
- I know my work. – Yes.
One say that you find the trace of a
bird thanks to your sense of smell.
Let us go with them.
Mohammad,
leave and will bring back
we you to alive Mecca.
Be careful, these caves
are full with snakes.
Mohammad, one found you. Leave from here.
They have nobody there,
the cobweb is intact.
And this pigeon built its nest.
They cannot be here.
Why us to be ventured in the west?
Let us go to the north of Medina.
Allah is the Powerful Whole.
It did not have there
between Mohammad and death,
that some wire of a cobweb.
In the cave, Abu Bakr trembled
for the Prophet and Islam,
and the Prophet whispered
to him with conviction:
"Would not be sad, Allah is with us."
They continued their
voyage in full heat wave.
The Prophet, his companion
and their nomadic guide,
crossed the desert, that
nobody had never pressed.
Medina, the faithful ones awaited
the arrival of the Prophet,
Theirs hearts burning of fear and pity.
You see something? - Not, not yet.
I am very anxious for him and Abu Bakr.
That of them this furnace made?
Here is the Prophet!
Allah is great! Allah is great!
The Prophet!
Here is the guide, the
carrier of a good news!
Will hide you, I do not want to
release to you to make a gesture.
Welcome, Messenger of Allah,
with Medina, the luminous one.
Welcome. Welcome.
You will place at home, Messenger of Allah.
My house is most honourable of Medina,
and the worthiest to accomodate
you, if you accept it.
Come rather at home!
Dear inhabitants of Medina…
You, community of the partisans,
The Messenger of Allah
cannot choose among you.
Listen...
The Prophet known as:
'Allah will guide his Camel. ' - Cheer!
Where it will stop, we will
build his mosque and his house.
With the blessing of Allah!
It is an intelligent idea.
The choice of Camel can not offend anybody.
"In the name of Allah"... Let us
build the house of the Prophet here.
And at this place, the first
mosque to request Allah!
Allah is great... Allah is great!
The Messenger of Allah carries bricks?
You did not suffer enough
during your voyage?
Rest, we work.
It want to continue its work.
He say that work is a veneration.
Fifty-three years.
And you, you have which age?
It were built with the will of Allah.
How to call with the prayer?
The voice of believing
calls with the prayer,
as indicates it Omar Ibn Al
Khattab and a group of Muslims.
If the Prophet agrees.
The Prophet accepts. Yes...
The voice of the man.
You, Bilal.
Me? - Do not hesitate, Bilal.
It is the will of the Prophet.
"Allah is great!
Allah is great!
I attest that there is of Allah only God!
I attest that Mohammad is
the Messenger of Allah.
Run to the prayer!
Run to the salvation!
Allah is great!
It have there of Allah only God!"
My brothers...
The Prophet called to the emigrants
and to the partisans of Medina:
"Be brothers in front of Allah.
That each man of Medina,
kiss an emigrant of Mecca.
That it makes a brother and
divides all with him of it,
you all like brothers Embrace."
Must I divide my clothing with my slave?
Read this, Mohammad was established king.
How my son is?
He request like exaggerated.
That does not burn the hands?
It will burn the house
if it is not destroyed.
He order, prohibit and enact the laws.
His honesty towards Islam would be
higher than that towards tribe.
How?
The Koraichians Muslims and of Medina,
and those which followed them and joined,
and which fought near
them, form a community,
would not be easily deceived.
It will not be able to
unify the Arab tribes.
The danger comes from there.
"The neighbor is like oneself,
neither malfaisant nor sinning.
One see a woman only with the
agreement of its family."
It really think it.
For him, the Muslims and
people of the Book are equal.
Read what he says of the Jews of Medina.
"The Jews have their religion
and the Muslims theirs,
themselves and their owners,
except that which oppressed and sinned."
Look at.
The woman has rights, of
which that of the heritage.
And why not of the rights for the camels?
Coran known as: "There is
not an animal on the earth,
nor a being that flies on its
wings, but communities like you..."
Mohammad upsets all, even
the nature of my city.
Curse is it!
He steal us our children and our lives.
He found what he calls the right,
At the expense of our future.
That are enough!
He should be given to its place.
Whole that exiled left in Mecca,
will confiscate we it.
Their houses, their camels,
their horses, their money,
and even their children belong to us.
Exiled!
I bring news of Mecca.
They stole all your possessions.
Do not remain to you any more money.
The trade of Abu Bakr is sold,
as well as the house of the Prophet.
They sold your goods to
inflate their caravans.
It remain to you nothing.
You for your possessions do not fight?
Which speaks to fight?
You Have an alternative?
We will fight only with the
orders of Allah and its Prophet.
Include understand me well,
you do not disturb us are our guests.
If there remained to us only one bread,
we would give it to you.
Turn over to work.
Will fight we them, I swear
that we will fight them.
Those which oppressed us, drove
out our houses and plundered.
The good will not be overcome by the evil.
We are protected by Allah and
by you, we will overcome.
O Messenger of Allah, I know
that you call with peace.
But if we let them make,
we will lose our honor.
Let us fight them.
Whole that we have finds in their caravans.
Their caravans are within reach,
let us recover our goods by the force.
Forgive me.
Forgiveness if I raised
the voice your involved.
But it is an anger for
Allah and his religion.
Engagements them.
No battle, without the order of Allah.
Allah is great!
Bilal. Looks at the sun.
"I attest that there is of Allah only God."
It is not the hour of the prayer.
"I attest that Mohammad is
the Messenger of Allah."
"Allah is great!"
"It have there of Allah only God."
Listen to what Allah
revealed with its Messenger.
"In the name of Allah, Most
Gracious, Most Merciful."
"Permission is given to those upon whom
war is made because they are oppressed,
and verily, Allah is most
powerful for their aid,
Those who have been expelled
from their homes without a
just cause except that they
say: 'Our Lord is Allah'..."
Allah, the Great, said the truth.
Allah is great!
The sword of Ali,
is the first sword of Islam.
Exiled and in favour!
Comply with the rules
of war of the Prophet.
Save the children, the old men,
the women and the patients,
do not cut down trees.
Do not make evil with the man
who works with the field.
Fight your oppressors and
those which have stolen you.
Now, with the wells of Badr!
Koraichians!
You Arm! Defend your goods! Mohammad!
They attack your caravan.
- How much they are?
Three hundred of which some riders.
We will have 200 riders. How many camels?
- Seventy. - We will have 170 of them.
And twenties of my camels will
carry the wine earthenware jars.
It will be a festival!
It is the war which I waited.
A war without losses.
The war!
Go quickly to the caravan.
Say to Abu Sofyan to go to the
wells of Badr with its men.
Koraichians left.
Koraichians went to face
the Muslims with Badr.
They ask you to join them.
It is not reasonable to risk
the richnesses of Mecca.
I go to the west, far
from the well of Badr.
You must move towards Badr.
If I continue my walk the night, I
will avoid Mohammad until the morning.
And your row among your people?
My position depends on the
safety of these camels.
Yes, today... My influence
is in these goods.
Mohammad took the wells of Badr.
It were thrown between our hands.
Which imprudent.
The imprudent ones are
always thrown in the abyss.
Abu Sofyan goes towards the
west and moves away from Badr.
The caravan is thus with the shelter.
I propose more to beat us.
Not to beat us?
Why start a war?
Which could last forty years?
A war between fathers and sons?
Hudayfa, your son is with them
and it deserves the whip!
Mecca is worth more than him.
Your truth son is Walid.
Known as that it is of my fault
and that Otba became loose,
whereas you know that I
am not more the coward.
Me I say, make the war.
It is our only chance.
If we lose it, we will not
have of it an other. The war!
The war!
You finished?
Your places, dispatch you take!
You dispatch!
In place!
Position of combat! With your places!
Mohammad stopped the wells.
We must reach the other well.
Do not leave your places.
Until the order of the Prophet.
If the enemies surround you,
sift to them arrows!
Send to us your champions!
Which are you?
Mohammad!
Send to us our equal among our people.
Return!
Shaiba my brother,
Walid my son,
and myself.
Await you.
Ubayda,
Myself... and Ali.
The Prophet known as:
"Those which have the heart of
Mohammad between their hands.
Whole man which fights them,
die patient and circumspect,
and advance without hesitating,
Allah will make it enter to the paradise."
Let us be us your equal?
It have there of another Allah only God.
Mohammad is its Messenger.
Allah is great!
Archers!
Ahead!
Retain the shooting...
Draw!
Behind!
They gather.
Ahead!
Behind!
You with the attack prepare!
Attack!
Omayya! With us two!
Omayya! - Bilal!
Allah is great!
Victory!
The Prophet refuses to
attach the prisoners.
A their place, they would have killed us.
We will comply with the
rules of the Prophet.
Do not trail them not attached.
Divide your food with them.
That those which can read and write,
teach with ten Muslims, in
exchange of their freedom.
Why me tracking one?
Why?
They hold me for person in charge.
Why was I to die with them in Badr?
I did not save my skin, but
the goods of Koraichians.
Enough! Enough! Let us go away!
And enough of lamentations!
I require that one points
out my father to me?
My brother? My uncle?
Must one point out my father,
my brother and my uncle to me?
Mohammad!
Ali!
Hamza!
With my nails, Hamza.
With my nails, trenching of throats.
I will shred you!
Hamza...
Hamza!
I will drive out you, hunter of lions!
And when you die...
...I will cut up you,
assassin of my father...
I will cut up you!
Assassin of my brother...
Assassin of my uncle...
And when you die...
...I will drink your blood.
Cease these complaints,
Hind, we do not have time.
This time, we will call upon our allies.
We will prepare in Mohammad
an invincible army.
Hamza...
Are this well Medina? Where
are its inhabitants?
No matter who could be
useful himself at will.
Are this them new religion?
Person does not supervise her shop.
Allah takes care on them.
From which you come?
Of Yemen.
Is you passed by Mecca?
- It was on my road.
Are you stopped to there? - Yes.
Time that my camels rest.
The camels rest there
better than elsewhere.
Of the news of the desert?
They are not good.
They gather.
Young whole being able to carry
a sword moves towards Mecca.
Our force resides here.
Do not underestimate them.
They gather their courage.
Mecca one beats the drum
in all the hearths.
Khalid did not come. - Does not worry you.
It will be soon the best rider.
Continue!
He is an Abyssinian slave.
Named Al Wahshi, the savage,
because of his cruelty...
I will liberate you,
I will give you your silver weight,
and will dress you in silk for
one launched like this one.
Here they are finally. We
will know their number.
A large army... 3000
men, hundreds of riders.
Beat we them in Badr.
- It was one year ago.
They are there to be avenged for Badr.
Seek your sabres.
Blood calls blood!
O Banu Abd Eddar!
O defenders of the hearths!
We strike with our sabres!
Us, girls of Tariq,
We walk on the cushions,
Whereas the house chokes,
and the musk are everywhere,
If you accept, we will embrace.
And will spread out the cushions.
If you flee, we will separate.
A final separation!
Here is Hamza. You see it?
It will make your fortune.
Obayda...
Riders, over there...
Their position worries me.
- Khalid Ibn Al Walid directs them.
Khalid.
This boy always interested me.
Hamza.
- The Prophet asks whether you see them.
- Yes, I am unaware of what they weave.
You in do not make.
The Prophet placed our 50
better archers on the mountain,
and he say to them:
"Protect our backs,
if we are killed, do not come to our help
and if we make a catch, do not come."
Zayd,
say to the Prophet that we are ready.
Glory with Houbal!
That you think Abut it, Hamza?
They are more numerous than us,
But we are stronger with the faith.
Let us see we them, and they see us.
What faces me does not frighten me.
When the Prophet orders it to us,
we will throw ourselves on them.
Archers!
Prepare your weapons!
Advance...
The attack!
Archers, retain the shooting...
Draw!
Hamza died as a martyr!
Will avenge we it!
Turn over to your stations!
Remain in place! Turn
over to your stations!
Remain in place, loose
Koraichians move back...
Their flag falls. Victoire!
- Useless to remain here.
With the spoils! - Remain at your stations!
Do not infringe the orders!
You endanger the right wing of the army!
We lost the battle.
The heart of our army is broken.
Step yet...
Attack with force!
Break their unit!
Where is the Prophet?
- He is said that he died.
If the Messenger of Allah perished,
you until death for his cause beat!
The Messenger of Allah did not die!
He fight!
The Prophet is wounded!
Behind!
Move back towards the mountain!
This victory east holds, Khalid.
It are always over there.
But we avenged Badr.
Step before we finished some
with him and his religion.
If we approach him, they will defend.
It is too risky.
Mohammad, you hear me?
The war has tops and bottoms.
The days are followed and do not resemble.
Days ago with and of the days without.
Glory With Houbal!
The Prophet known as:
"Allah is the Almighty.
Our deaths are with the
paradise and yours in hell."
We have dignity, not you!
Allah is our Lord and not yours.
Hamza...
You hear me?
He is me, Hind.
The girl of Otba.
You remember your victims?
My father...
My brother...
My uncle...
Your death is enough for me it?
Your death is not enough for me.
Wahshi!
Open it!
Open it! I want his liver.
They lost the battle, flung the swords,
and now, they handle the pickaxe.
Imbeciles!
They go against logic.
They are happy of what arrived to them.
They think that Allah the met of the test.
They fight for the cause of Allah.
They want Mecca. - And they will have it.
When the hens have teeth.
Do not underestimate
them, Mecca is for them,
more than one fatherland.
It is the ground of the revelation.
They go there this year as pilgrims.
How?
Without weapons.
Without weapons?
Abu Sofyan will complete
them in the desert.
They think that their faith
as a Allah will save them.
But I agree with you.
Perhaps will complete them.
The Prophet known as:
"The actions are according to intentions."
Remain in your places!
They want to cause you!
Do not move!
That peace is with you.
With the oath!
The Prophet known as:
"That which loves Allah
lends oath under the tree."
"In the name of Allah, Most
Gracious, Most Merciful."
"Certainly Allah was well
pleased with the believers
when they swore allegiance
to you under the tree,
and it knew what was in their hearts,
and it sent down tranquillity to them,
and rewarded them with a near victory."
Allah and his Messenger said the truth.
Another negotiator arrived.
Suhayl Ibn Amr.
Perhaps they want a conciliation.
Mohammad.
You saw yourself proposing the conditions
of a truce between you and Mecca.
You gave your agreement?
What it is?
"In the name of Allah, Most
Gracious, Most Merciful."
I do not know it.
Write in the name of Allah.
"Here what Mohammad was appropriate,
the Messenger of Allah."
If I had believed that you
were the Messenger of Allah,
I would not have fought you.
Write rather:
Here what Mohammad was
appropriate, son of Abdallah
with Suhayl, wire of Amr.
Are not this more correct?
It is better.
"Mohammad and its partisans
leave this year Mecca,
and return on their premises."
Mecca, it is on our premises.
"Next year, we will leave Mecca,
you will enter there for three days,
The swords will be in their sleeves."
If you accept, we will grant
a ten years to you truce.
The people will be in safety.
You will not attack us night
and will not betray us.
Us either.
That which will want to follow
Mohammad, will follow him.
And which will want to follow
Koraichians, will do it.
If you refuse,
or if you wound one among
us or of our allies,
The truce will end.
Ten years.
Ten years of peace.
We need this time.
We will use this time.
They are the letters of the Prophet to
the kings, calling them with Islam.
To Heraclius, emperor of the Romans.
To Khosro, emperor of Perse.
To Cyrus, patriarch of Alexandria.
On the way. That Allah blesses you!
One do not have the faith,
that if one wishes for his next
what one wishes for oneself.
That which falls asleep the full belly,
whereas its neighbor is hungry,
are not Muslim.
Islam releases us from the fanaticism
and the heat of ignorance.
Allah the Almighty said:
"O humans!
We created you starting from
a male and of a female.
You knew each other.
The noblest among you for
Allah is most pious."
Allah, the Great, said the truth.
"Thy Lord hath decreed that
you worship none but it,
and that you be kind to parents..."
Yes.
The faith is thus.
Parents...
"... say not to them a word
of contempt, nor repel them,
but speak to them generous words.
And, out of kindness, lower
to them the wing of humility,
and say: 'My Lord! Bestow on them thy mercy
even as they cherished me in childhood'."
Allah the Almighty said:
"Say: O People! Here that the
truth came from your Lord.
That which takes the right way
takes it only for its own good.
That which takes that of the wander
mislays only with its only detriment.
That which seeks the ploughing of the
ultimate life, we let us give it to him,
and that which seeks the ploughing of the
low world, we let us grant it to him,
and it do not have in the
ultimate life any share."
And Allah said: "Allah does not
change the state of people,
that if it changes what
there is in itself."
"Restore the deposit with its beneficiary,
betrayed not that which betrayed you."
The Messenger of Allah, that
safety is on him, known as:
"You all are of the guards and
persons in charge for your subjects.
The Imam is a guard,
and person in charge for his subjects.
And the man are a guard of his family,
and he are the person in
charge for his subjects.
And the woman are guardian
in the house of her husband
and she is responsible for his subjects.
The servant is a guard of
the goods of his master
and it are responsible for its subjects.
You all are of the guards and all
persons in charge for your subjects."
Are you to take me along still there?
I come to ask you to accept me.
I attest that there is of Allah only God,
and Mohammad is its Messenger.
Allah will forgive me it to
have fought you, Mohammad?
You in do not make, Khalid,
Islam cancels what precedes it.
Allah granted prosperity to you.
I find that this plait
hurts you at the coasts,
You accept my cape?
The Prophet recommends asceticism.
The richness is not eternal.
He do not have that the
cape which it has on him.
I am sorry to have come thus avoided.
If the Messenger allows it to me,
I give them to him, in order to
distribute them to the poor.
Khalid,
Your sabre was hardest on the Muslims.
You will be now
the sabres of Allah.
I will be it with the assistance of Allah.
Whole is easy for Allah.
As it can make death, the life,
it can make of a defeat, a victory.
Two years ago,
we regarded the truce of
Hudaybya as a defeat.
But today,
we accumulate the victories
in the heart of the men.
What it is?
Abu Sofyan!
Where is Mohammad, that I speak to him?
The Prophet is in the mosque.
Mohammad, your people did not violate
your engagement with Hudaybya.
And I came to repair the
fault of the nomads.
Mohammad, why you turn me the back?
Wait.
Mohammad, you in does not go...
They are the wandering gangsters
who violated the truce!
Why us make take the responsibility?
It was the night! How
you could have seen us?
Bara! I am in your city.
Hudayfa, we are parents!
Somebody must listen to me!
Abu Bakr, Omar, Ali...
Nobody wants to approach me?
I am the chief of Mecca! I am Mecca!
I am Abu Sofyan! How can one scorn me thus?
Because you hold neither
promises nor engagements.
Abu Sofyan beseeches it pity?
And you failed...
Because you are always same
the, arrogant one and heading.
You refuse to adore single Allah.
I did not know that you had
changed at this point.
Yes, but of the unbelief in the faith.
That to say?
I am overcome...
I was overcome by the shepherd of Mecca…
...or by his religion,
which began with a man,
two boys and a woman.
This religion which was
established in four hearts,
you do not believe that it is a
hand which takes care on it?
Why it did not choose a powerful
man of the two villages?
Return quickly in Mecca,
any man here you in wants.
Say them that their gods died.
Useless to fight Allah.
The tribes continue to arrive.
We will be ten thousand before the night.
We can finally fight them.
We will strengthen the houses
and will block the exits.
It is useless.
They are ten thousand today.
You are only one loose!
- Rather to die... - Return to the house.
Coward! Are you the chief of Mecca?
Are looked at.
You are broken.
My father and my brother
died so that you capitulate?
You are in the two houses.
You are stupid. We cannot fight them.
They take again Mecca.
We will camp this night here.
Mecca...
...I see it even through these mountains.
I have the impression that
the sky was closed again,
and that the stars dispersed on the ground.
It is beautiful.
It is strange... I feel their bread.
Perhaps They did not come for the war.
It is what I hope for.
I do not think that they want
blood on their thresholds.
Drove out we them of Mecca,
but Mecca are in their heart.
I can still negotiate with them.
Lead me to him.
You came to deliver Mecca to us?
You me offers not of bread?
I know.
You want to perhaps kill me.
Say what you came to say to us.
I saw fires of your camping
and the men around.
I saw the power of which
you nourished your men.
If you agree on...
You installations still your conditions?
Abu Sofyan,
when your heart with the
religion of Mohammad opens?
I still have doubts.
If we cut you the head, you
would not have any any more.
Not, Khalid.
Constraint no in religion.
Some need years, others of moments.
Allah guides who it wants.
You, the black slave,
you are a good example.
I am only what Allah gave me.
Yes.
If my gods were good,
they would not have given up me.
I say sincerely,
without perjury and constraint:
I attest that there is of God only Allah...
...and that you are the Messenger of Allah.
Now, let leave to me.
Return on your premise! The army of
the Muslims between three sides.
The army of the Muslims between
in Mecca on the three sides.
Allah is great! Allah is great!
It have there of Allah only God.
Thanks to Allah.
Allah is the Almighty and
its grace is abundant.
Glory with Allah.
Of the daybreak in the twilight.
It have there of Allah only God.
His word was held. He gave
the victory to its men,
with his dearer warriors and he
overcame the clans all alone.
He have there of Allah only God,
we adore only him,
and let us devote all our devotion to him,
against the liking of the inaccurate ones.
Do not use of violence in Mecca.
Be lenient towards its inhabitants,
do not maltreat anybody.
Behind the doors, you are in safety.
In the house of Abu Sofyan,
you are in safety.
In the mosque, you are in safety.
He held his word.
They did not force a door.
It take the hearts by storm, not the walls.
It is that, the victory.
To see it hurt me.
We must make an appearance.
Were us in mislaying?
Yes, we were in mislaying.
Our pride trapped us.
Our gods were worth even less than us.
Here it is,
it approach Kaaba.
"In the name of Allah, Most
Gracious, Most Merciful."
"And when we assigned to Abraham
the place of the House, saying:
'Do not associate with Me aught,
and purify my House for those
who make the circuit and
stand to pray and bow and
prostrate themselves'."
Allah, the Great, said the truth.
"... The truth has come,
and the falsehood has vanished..."
And the victory of Allah came.
And Mecca were subjected while
waiting for its right sanction.
But the said lenient Prophet:
"Leave, you are free."
And Mecca adhered to the Islam which
preaches justice and the good
and prohibit turpitudes, the
atrocities and the injustices.
And the Prophet felt, after
having achieved his mission,
that his meeting with Allah was close.
The day of the great pilgrimage
in the year ten of the Hegira,
The Prophet went to the Arafat mount,
and invited the people to listen to the
sermon of the pilgrimage of farewell.
"O Humans! Listens to me.
I am unaware of if I will
find you here the next year.
O Humans!
Your blood and your goods are crowned
until your meeting with Allah,
just like this place and
this month are crowned.
You will meet Allah and it will
question you on your acts,
and I transmitted the message.
That which keeps a good returns it
to that which entrusted it to him.
And any wear are inhibited.
But you have your capital, do not
oppress and be not oppressed.
Retain what I say, because
I transmitted my message.
I left you what will light you
and will always guide you:
The delivers of Allah and
Sunna of the Prophet.
O Humans!
Listen to my message and retain it.
Learn that a Muslim is the
brother of any other Muslim,
and that the Muslims are brothers.
The goods of a brother inviolable
are except yielded full liking.
Alors do not be unjust towards yourselves.
My Allah, achieved I my mission?"
After having guided the prayer
of midday and the afternoon,
The Prophet recited them the
ultimate revelation of Coran:
"Today, I completed for you your religion,
and accomplished on you my grace,
and I approved you the
Islam like religion."
Abu Bakr cried.
And came the painful day.
The Prophet was 63 years old.
One Monday of June of
year 13 of the Hegira,
last of the prophets
chooses to join his Allah.
And Medina trembled of sorrow.
Person believed only that which
bless Allah and the angels,
can be in a tomb.
But Mohammad had died.
And here what Abu Bakr says,
in the mosque of the Prophet:
'O Humans!
That that which venerates Mohammad
knows that Mohammad died.
But that that which venerates Allah,
knows that Allah will be always alive. '
And its saint body were buried
in his mosque with Medina.
But its heart will remain, as
its message which does not die.
Allah is great.
A its light, the partisans of
the Prophet continue to preach,
to request only Allah,
and to associate anybody to him.
And not to take for Allah other than him.
Allah is great.
The number of the Muslims increases.
And the man who was alone
became a community.
And the community gather all the
people around the word 'Allah'.
"O Humans! We have created surely
you of a male and a female,
and made you tribes and families
that you may know each other.
Verily the most honored of you in the sight
of Allah is the most righteous of you..."
Allah and its Messenger said the truth.