How did it all start?
I mean,
my girls inspired the first Beanies.
I was employee number 12.
Three years later, we were the most
profitable toy company in the world.
Ty would tell you
he did it all, but that's bullshit.
We built that company together.
From nothing.
I mean, that's the whole point of America,
right?
Work hard. Build something good.
Get yourself in the right place
at the right time, and boom.
We didn't set out
to make America lose its mind,
but that's what happened.
Was it crazy
to turn stuffed animals into investments?
It was a crazy time.
The Internet was new.
The Boomers were taking over.
But we turned Beanie Babies
into little plush lotto tickets.
At the peak of the bubble,
more than half the country owned one.
Ty was the one with his name on the tag.
The one who made billions.
But he couldn't have done it
without the three of us.
- He didn't do it without the three of us.
- Ty!
So this story's not about him.
It's about us.
I met Ty back in the '80s
when we were living
in the same apartment building.
Oh, God, not my husband!
- Ma'am, I need you to just back up, okay?
- Oh, my God. Is this Billy?
When his dad died.
Oh, shit.
Billy,
did you take your meds?
Did you take your meds today?
Yeah.
Did you pick up more Tab?
- Hi.
- I'm so sorry for your loss.
I baked this.
- Here, I'll just put it down for you.
- Yeah. Okay.
Yeah, it's a lasagna. Maybe just here?
I'm not psycho.
I dissect them
to see how they're made for work.
Not for fun.
But to be honest, it is pretty fun.
Right.
My dad would say,
"You gotta make your own luck.
You can't wait for your ship to come in,
Son. You gotta build your own ship."
That's what he would say.
- Have you told your mom yet?
- Oh, God, no.
She is a violent paranoid schizophrenic
who abandoned us years ago.
Where was your dad for all this?
On the road, selling toys.
Oh, man.
It's okay. Was better that way.
Otherwise he would be at home,
beating the crap out of me.
Wait. I...
- I thought you two were so close.
- No.
The only time my dad was proud of me
is when our girlfriend told him
how good I was in bed.
- "Our girlfriend."
- Yeah, the same woman.
- You dated the same woman?
- No.
- At the same time?
- No, not...
- No, not always at the same time, no.
- Okay.
We're gonna need another.
I do and do not want to know
much, much more.
My story started ten years later,
when I first
walked into the offices of Ty Inc.
I was a 17-year-old college
freshman just trying to land a temp job.
Not usher in a new era of capitalism.
You'd be expected to brush
and tweeze the display cats.
- Oh, wow. You're serious.
- Yeah.
But the job's mainly the phones.
Four hours a day, plus some Saturdays.
You said you're in school?
- Yeah, I'm in school...
- Roberta, sweetie,
you need to come tell me
which one of these looks like marigold.
You pressed "Intercom All" again. And no.
Bye.
Yeah, I'm in school,
but the schedule's not a problem.
I just need money.
Tuition's tough these days, huh?
I've got a scholarship. It's for rent.
If I keep living at home,
my soul will soon be fully crushed.
We pay minimum wage.
Not sure that's a salvation salary.
You don't know how cheap my soul is.
We do what we gotta do, right?
This just pays my bungee bills.
Oh, Robbie, I need you. Robbie?
Rose, which color is better?
- Don't know, don't care.
- What about you? What do you think?
I'm not really a cat person.
Are you an amazing things person?
Yeah, I wouldn't go yellow at all.
Too mild.
These little punks wanna be tiger-striped.
But wouldn't stripes make them
too convict-y?
Well, cats are outlaws.
Convict-y is kinda their appeal.
Yes.
Rose, she has a good point. What...
Rose, what are you looking at?
We'll get to that later.
Don't go anywhere.
Does that mean I'm hired?
It did.
But obviously none of this
would have happened without Sheila.
Mr. President and Mrs. Clinton,
and Americans everywhere.
A Rock, A River, A Tree Hosts...
It certainly wasn't my dream
designing lights for people like Ty.
I did it to pay the bills,
to support my girls.
Well, I've been waiting since 9:00.
Does he need to reschedule?
Honestly, if I were you, I'd just bail.
I wanted the world to be better for them.
I wanted it to get kinder and happier
and more human.
I wanted it to hurry up.
Lights, right? I'll be right with ya.
The UK is a mess, and it's not my fault.
And the last thing I would do
is to hire incompetent partners...
Excuse me, what are you doing?
Do you often keep people waiting
three hours?
It has been a hectic...
'Cause I told my sick daughters
I'd be back as quick as I could,
and then I waited here
- for longer than a human should...
- I run a company
- that's highly unpredictable...
- Okay. I know you're busy.
And I know you're rich.
But I also know that life is too short
to waste on assholes,
so please move your car,
or I'll move it for you less gently.
I got better places to be.
Wow.
May I come?
I am not joking.
I am so sorry. Let me make it up to you.
Let me take you to dinner.
No. I only eat dinner with my daughters.
Well, I'll take all of you.
It'll be fun. Kids love me.
Look, this isn't personal. I...
Despite what I said
about you being an asshole...
Assholes used to be my type.
I just... I don't date anymore.
Anyone? Ever?
No. Not till my girls grow up.
Goodbye.
Okay.
- Your loss.
- Okay.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
Mommy, when is it gonna warm up?
That is a great question. You know what?
Soon.
And if it doesn't,
we're gonna go to Uncle Jeremy's,
stay the night there.
He's not really our uncle.
No, but he really is a Jeremy. I think.
- We got it!
- Hang on, girls.
- Are you Sheila Harper's daughters?
- Yeah. Who's asking?
This is from Mr. Ty Warner.
He hopes that they're feeling better.
- Okay. Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Thanks!
- Hang on.
- What is it?
- I don't know. Let's find out.
Let's get the door.
All right. Hang on, hang on.
- Okay.
- Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my God.
Ty was good at knowing what people wanted.
Wow, look at all of this.
First,
I wanted to be a wide receiver in the NFL.
Then I wanted to star in air shows.
I stole a crop plane to practice.
Then I wanted to beat up Sam Walton.
The Walmart guy?
Walmart puts family stores
out of business.
- Well, I think you could take him.
- Duh.
Damn it,
I had so many plans back in Arkansas.
Life was gonna be so fun
if I just got out into it.
Like, I left...
I left so that I wouldn't get stuck
taking care of people.
I wanted to live my life for me.
And here I am. This tub.
Look at this.
- It's like I'm my mother.
- Dad was hiding the good stuff.
I like good stuff.
- Scotch. Yeah.
- Me. Oh, yeah, yeah.
So graceful.
We should be synchronized swimmers!
- From now on.
- Robbie, Robbie.
Listen to me.
You can do anything you want.
You're not stuck.
You're tough, and you're strong.
Let's start our own business, you and me.
A synchronized swimming business?
A stuffed Himalayan cat business.
A synchronized stuffed Himalayan
swimming business?
- I'm serious. Well...
- Robbie!
- Robbie, is that you?
- No!
What?
How are you even walking?
I sold all my dad's antiques
so we could start
our own business together.
The swimming thing?
The cats. Yeah, the stuffed cats.
Don't you understand? This is happening.
This is the first day of
the rest of your life, young lady.
Could you just take it down a little bit?
This is the first day of
the rest of your life.
Here we are.
- Okay. For you.
- Wow.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
For you. It's hot. Hot, hot.
And I like mine cold.
You know,
we were supposed to be treating you.
Mr. Warner, this is very kind.
Please, it's Ty. Mr. Warner was my dad.
And his stuffed animals
weren't as cool as mine.
Yours are so cool.
Yours are the bestest best.
Thank you very much.
Do you have a favorite?
The pig.
And the frog.
I tried to bring it to school
for show-and-tell,
but it wouldn't fit in my backpack.
Oh, no.
Well, I'm gonna have to
make a smaller one then.
And maybe a little softer too.
- Okay, let's stick to the thank-yous.
- Softer. Okay.
- Hey, Ty?
- Yes, ma'am.
Do you wanna go roller-skating
with us sometime?
- I would love to.
- Honey, no. Okay.
- Can we, Mommy? Soon?
Okay... Well, I mean, Ty's a busy man,
- so I don't know when he would find time.
- Listen, let's...
- let's keep your mom out of this, okay?
- Okay.
I'll have my people contact your people.
How's that?
Ben, 9 and 11.
- Thank you.
- Your left hands.
- I declare a thumb war.
- Ladies.
- Hi.
- Hey. There you are.
- Hi, Ty.
I have been looking forward to this
all week.
And I brought a surprise.
- Oh, my God. Froggy!
- It's a Beanie Baby.
That's a miniature version
of your favorite.
- I know.
- He's small enough to go everywhere,
and he loves to ride in backpacks.
Wow, then you can take him to school.
What's his name?
I don't know yet.
What does he look like to you?
Can I take a closer look at him?
What do you think he looks like?
- Greenie.
Kids' 11 and 13, Sheila.
- Yeah. That's us.
- Can you give us a minute?
We're working here.
All right.
Why don't we name him Mar?
- Mar?
- Yeah.
I mean, Leaper's a great name.
I'm just not sold on it yet, but it's...
What about Sir Jumps-a-Lot?
That's a good one.
Or maybe, like, Jumpy?
- That's too on the nose, Jumpy.
- Jumpy.
I dance with my arms.
I dance with my head.
I dance with my butt.
I dance with my belly.
I dance with my legs.
I dance with my arms.
I dance with my belly.
- Well, that's it.
- What?
- Legs.
Legs.
- The name?
- What?
- That's great. Legs.
- That's the name.
- Legs the frog. I named it!
- Legs!
- We have a name.
- Good work, ladies. Great.
And I think
- Legs has a friend.
- Oh, my gosh.
We'll go roller-skating eventually.
No, I think we're having a great time.
Yeah, okay. Talk to you later.
Within a few months,
Ty was completely obsessed
with his new Beanie Baby line.
And working there was actually fun...
- Hey.
...'cause if he liked the way you think,
he'd listen to you.
- Hey.
- No matter who you were.
Case in point: his design team.
Hey, Ty. Like my ghost?
- It's fantastic.
- Thank you.
- First batch of puppies is here.
- Yeah.
- Look at them.
- Cute.
So cute! The face.
Let them hug. Let's hug.
I see you named him Dots.
Oh, yeah. After much deliberation.
Well, I dig it.
It's just... Don't you think
he should actually have some dots?
It's a she.
I'm sorry.
I'm very sorry, ma'am.
Well, you know what?
She definitely should have some dots.
Maya's right, as usual.
All right, ladies. For the next batch,
where should we put Dots's dots?
On her butt!
On the butt?
- How many dots on the butt?
- A million.
- A million dots?
- A million dots.
When Ty's Beanie Babies
were ready for their world debut,
he put me in charge of
smaller trade shows.
'Cause I rocked at selling stuff.
I killed it.
- I raked in the orders.
- So soft.
For everything except Beanies.
Their big launch was a total flop.
For two years,
we couldn't sell any at all.
It drove Ty crazy.
What is this, a comic book stand?
No, Ty Inc. is all about
high-quality stuffed animals.
None of them are looking at me.
What?
These animals are supposed to be
making tantalizing eye contact with me.
They're supposed to be alluringly tweezed.
Yeah, you should go blond more often, Ty.
- It really brings out your cheekbones.
- I'm undercover.
- Why aren't you wearing something sparkly?
- This is my version of sparkly.
How are sales?
Good. Well, except for Beanies.
Though there have been
a lot of requests for Woolly.
Maya,
if you can't sell what we actually have,
I'm gonna have to find someone that can.
Someone a little bit more focused.
Hi. I'd like my regular order,
plus a batch of those cheap little lambs.
Do you still have those?
That design has been retired.
That was a special limited edition.
- A what?
- A limited edition.
If you still have some,
they're pretty valuable.
You know, the first issue of Action Comics
sells for over a million dollars.
Are any of these others,
limited editions too?
Yep. All the Beanie Babies are.
Be a good idea to stock up.
Okay. Put me down for five of each.
Frank Carlson.
Uncle Frank's Toys in Glenview, I know.
I got you.
Thank you.
- "Retired." That's genius.
- Limited editions always get people.
I love it. It's fantastic.
Get this comic book off the table, please.
So you're being an assistant
to some man selling worthless toys,
instead of studying full-time
to be a surgeon?
- Yep.
- Fascinating.
After we sacrificed so much
to come to a country
where women can do anything they want.
Exactly.
Anything they want, not their parents.
- And I'm still in school, don't freak.
- Do I look like a freaker?
- I mean, you do kind of freak out...
- Not a word from you, mister.
Okay, come on.
I don't have all day to help my daughter
shatter her parents' hearts
into a thousand tiny pieces.
- My new place is a mile away, Dad.
- 1,000 tiny, irreparable pieces.
So dramatic.
You wanna sell
high-end stuffed Himalayan cats?
Understuffed, actually.
For greater posability.
It's a revolutionary new design
that's going to electrify the market.
I assume you're aware
that the current economic conditions
are crippling stagnation,
soaring inflation and record unemployment.
Which makes this the perfect time
to sell a little joy.
We're professionals.
We're giving the people what they need.
I'll draw up the paperwork.
And just like that, Ty Inc. was born.
- See here?
- Yeah.
- The threading is not...
- Well, you can see it right there.
Now, this is what we call the... stitch.
Ty taught me everything
about stuffed animals,
which hadn't changed much in 50 years.
They'd been made pretty firm,
stuffed to the seams.
His big idea? Make 'em softer. Posable.
This is, like, a old lady and...
I was a fast learner.
And I had a thing or two to teach him.
- It's so boring.
- This one works.
- Look at this. Look at this. That's it.
- Doesn't work.
Open, open. Hurry. hurry.
We were a good team.
It's good.
It's good! I love it!
Robbie! Hey!
Turns out I was born for this shit.
Yeah, I hear you!
Robbie! Hey, Robbie!
J... One sec!
One. One each. Oh, my God. One.
Who knew it only took
inventing a line of stuffed animals
to break your strict dating embargo?
- It took way more than that.
- Did it?
Yeah.
And they're understuffed, by the way.
One of his many innovations.
You seem kinda happy.
I don't know, Ty's different. He's...
He's strange and magical,
and the girls, they love him.
And you?
They love me too.
Wow.
- Is that the one she designed?
- Yeah. I brought you one.
- Here.
- Look at this.
It's got her name in it.
Look at his cute little dots!
Oh, my goodness.
- These are adorable.
- Our friend, Ty, makes them.
I designed Spooky.
Really?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
Little poems inside their tags.
How darling.
Girls.
Our little world
was getting better and happier.
Before we knew it, we were a family.
A funny, weird, happy family.
You a doctor yet?
It's so boring.
If it weren't for computer science,
I'd kill myself.
Good news is, Stripes turned out great.
Wanna hear?
Nope.
My name is Stripes
And I'm fun to snuggle
I was born too soft
For the jungle struggle
So, I packed my bags, waved goodbye
And came to live with my friends at Ty
I still can't believe
Ty let you print raps on their tags.
Poems, Rose. This is poetry.
Uh-huh.
Stripes has a birthday coming up.
Should we blow it out?
You're doing something right.
Regional Beanie sales are way up.
For real?
No "piggity"?
If you start with puns,
I might actually have to punch you.
All right.
My bat.
- Bird up!
- Okay.
No, come on. I'm just kitten around.
All right.
Watch out.
What the fox?
Hey. This is unbearable.
The local surge had started
in a small suburban neighborhood
outside of Chicago,
just after the holidays.
Some kids who'd gotten Beanies brought
them to school and showed them off.
It wasn't long before
some parents got pretty into them too.
Three of them
lived on the same cul-de-sac.
Two were named Linda.
All of them started Beanie hunting
at the local toy store.
Frank even published a checklist,
which brought out the crazy.
'Cause once you have a checklist,
it's no longer about what you have.
It's all about what you don't have.
Initially, the regional boom
was all word of mouth,
'cause Ty didn't buy TV ads.
But word of mouth was about to get
a hell of a megaphone.
In summary,
the Midwest market is going bananas.
Hey.
Bravo. Exciting.
- Exciting, right?
- Yes.
Hey, did you get a chance to check out
that modem I left for you yet?
- The what-em?
- Modem.
That little computer box I put in your
office that connects you to the Internet?
All of these messages
are about Beanie Babies?
This whole section is Beanie Baby boards.
Everyone writing on here
is writing about them.
But how do they all know each other?
Well, they don't.
It's kinda like a big conference call.
We're dialed into this thing
called America Online,
and so is everyone else here.
Can we go back to the chat pad thing?
Chat room.
Okay.
- It's so fast.
- Right?
- Look at that. There's new thingies.
- Yeah. All the time.
We're just watching Beanie lovers
hang out in real time.
Even if they're in different
cities, time zones. Wherever.
How many people
are into this sort of thing overall?
My professor says 18 million homes
now have modem-equipped computers,
- up from 11 million a year ago...
- What?
...and that number's gonna keep growing.
Wow, 18 million people
just talking about Beanie Babies.
Well, and other things.
I mean, the Internet's a whole new way of
connecting to the rest of the world.
It's amazing.
We really should start a Ty web page.
What's that?
We can make a place
that anyone who wants to know
anything about Beanie Babies can go to.
A place we control.
Completely?
And we'd probably be the first business
to make one for our customers,
'cause no one else is using it that way.
Most web pages are just boring academic
stuff and phone directories,
but we could make ours fun.
Different. Sparkly.
Sparkly, I like that.
- Wait. Your version of sparkly or mine?
- Yours.
Are these toy shindigs fancy?
Ty says we have to put on a show
and "pack something flashy," so...
Is he gonna wear a dress also or does
he not do that sort of thing in public?
He is not a cross-dresser.
Yeah, well, he is the kinda guy
who's hiding who he really is.
Ty had a rough life too, you know,
but he's going after things.
He's making things happen,
getting what he deserves.
- It's inspiring.
- Uh-huh.
For once, I feel like I'm being
pulled up, not just dragged down.
It's a fucking miracle.
- I didn't mean... I meant work stuff.
- It's fine. It's fine.
You're allowed to go have fun.
It's nice feeling
like someone believes in me.
That's all I meant.
Well, you'll have to tell me
what that feels like.
I made you a lasagna,
and there's pizza too.
And I'll only be gone for two days. Okay?
- Make it longer.
- You know what, Billy?
- I'm fucking trying to do s...
- No. I'm serious, okay?
Let's stop fucking pretending.
I'm sick of it.
You're not the only one
who's feeling fucking suffocated.
- Checking in?
- Yes. Roberta Jones.
- I'm... The toy convention?
- Welcome.
Here's your keys.
And Mr. Warner left you a note.
He said to tell you he's "fetching
a chariot to collect you at 3:00."
And he left you this.
Give them a look and give them a try.
There you go. What do you think? Not bad?
- Let me grab that from you.
- Not bad.
That's great.
- This is not your dad's stuffed animal.
- Enjoy your day.
Fifty-two poses for the head alone.
Thirty fucking thousand dollars!
In an hour! For stuffed cats!
We are great together,
just like I said we would be.
- Fucking great.
- Ship-building champs, we are!
Motherfucking Vikings!
Hotel, please.
You're one in a million, Robbie Jones.
You are.
Oh, God.
Do you know what the greatest thing
about America is?
- Toys!
- Milkshakes!
Well, that's number... Yes.
Number seven and 14, of course.
But the number one
greatest thing about America?
It's the land of comebacks,
of new chances, of opportunity.
You can make things happen here
like nowhere else, ladies.
- Yeah!
And never forget that you
have the power to create your own future.
Never forget that you can be anything,
- you can do anything.
- I'm gonna be a unicorn!
You already are, darling. You already are.
The past few years have been
just the greatest ever.
I think we make an unbeatable team.
I think we do.
- We make an unbeatable team.
- Yeah.
- Me too.
- Me three.
Me four.
And I think some really amazing things...
You ready?
I think some amazing things
are getting ready to happen.
Can we do it now?
Ladies.
What is happening?
Oh, oh
What?
Oh Oh, Sheila
Let me love you till the morning comes
Oh, my...
Oh Oh, Sheila
You know I want to be the only one
Oh, baby, love me right
Let me love you till we get it right
Why can't you let the others be?
'Cause with you is where I wanna be Yeah
Oh Oh, Sheila
Let me love you till the morning comes
Oh, Sheila
Oh Oh, Sheila
You know I want to be the only one
Oh, Sheila
- Here we go
- Oh, my God.
Sheila Marie Harper,
will you make me the happiest man alive?
Say yes!
Yes. Of course.
Mommy!
She said yes!
Yay!
You know, I thought it was just gonna be
me and the girls till they left home.
Man, did you screw with my plans.
Well, get ready for me to screw
with your plans for the rest of our lives.
You know, this is serious,
what we're doing.
- You're not reconsidering, are you?
- No.
No. No, sweetheart.
I just...
In the past, I have relied on men,
and they turned out to be the wrong men.
I would die before I let you down.
You know, I don't need this.
I don't need to get married.
Well, I do.
- You feel that, right?
- Yeah.
Your face-lift scar
from just before we met.
'Cause I was ready for a fresh start.
Wow.
You know, I never knew
that plastic surgery could be so romantic.
My life had gone bad...
before you.
And now it is more wonderful than ever.
And I cannot wait
until you become Mrs. Warner.
Mrs. H. Ty Warner.
You know that I'm keeping
my own name though, right?
Right.
Well, whoever you are,
whatever your name is,
we should get married
and grow old together.
Deal.
Kumar residence.
I was hoping you'd answer.
I've got exams all morning.
Could you update the site at 11:00?
Yeah, I could go to the library
in between my classes.
Awesome. Thanks.
I swapped Peanut in this morning.
He needs to drop a hint about Digger
tunneling out of the Beanie nursery.
The collectors are gonna go crazy.
Hey, did you check out
that new auction website I told you about?
No. Shit. I meant to. I'll do that today.
- "ePort" or some shit?
- eBay.
eBay. Right.
Crap, I'm so late.
- Because of the Peanut crab?
- Wha... Mom?
Shit. Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
Who are you shit-shit-shitting?
There is no shit-shit-shitting
in this family.
Sorry, she must have
picked up the extension.
No shit, Sherlock.
Get to school, both of you.
Yes, ma'am.
All right, gremlins, time-out!
- Hey, Maya. Come on in.
- Hi.
You know, you made Ty's year
with that new computer setup.
He won't stop talking about his RAM.
Sorry.
He's just through here.
Wow. So cute.
We spotted an enemy!
- Not so cute. Warmongers.
- Yes, yes, yes!
- Hey. Look who's here.
- Hi.
200 new thingies since noon.
I've got something even more exciting
to show you.
- Now you're trapped!
- Hey. Come on.
- Rascals.
- Sorry.
Okay, dazzle me.
Show me what couldn't wait till tomorrow.
You are not gonna believe this.
May I?
I'm sorry.
Okay.
- Come on.
- One sec.
Here.
Why are there photos and prices
of retired Beanie Babies on here?
- They can't sell these.
- No, these aren't retailers.
They're customers,
reselling what they've already
bought from us.
It's an online auction site,
a genius idea.
Anybody can sell anything they want,
but we're the biggest thing on it.
By a lot. Look.
Dotless Dots is listed at $55,
11 times retail.
- Well, we should sue them then.
- Well... No, we... What?
We should kiss them.
Are you seeing what they're doing for us?
Yes. They're making a huge profit
on my products.
Infringing on my trademarked...
- trademarked name.
- No, making everybody greedy
for what we sell.
Not just as toys, but as investments.
As money makers.
I mean, we could not pay
for this kind of marketing.
These photos are just awful.
I mean, amateur camera angles,
abysmal eye con...
Look at the eye contact. There's none.
Zero. This is a disgrace.
The disgrace that's gonna
multiply our sales by a zillion.
Well, maybe we won't sue.
Yeah. This is a big deal, Ty.
We gotta play it right.
Okay, listen though.
I'm way too busy to handle all this crap.
You're gonna have to manage it, okay?
- Yeah. Plan to.
- Okay.
I'm deferring med school
to come on board full-time.
You're still in school?
You know I am.
My parents want me to be a doctor.
Doctors are a dime a dozen.
You are special.
You don't need degrees to succeed.
Tell your folks
that all the greats quit school early.
I quit my freshman year.
Yeah. Like you said, all the greats.
We're a great team, Maya Kumar.
Yes, we are.
We are a dream team, Robbie Jones. Unbeatable.
It's the cats!
Oh, God. Keep the fatties away.
We don't want fatties near the booth.
Are you joking?
No, they sweat on the fur.
Everyone is talking up this booth.
Can I help you?
These are incredible.
They're so lifelike, and they're soft.
What a good idea,
under-stuffing them like this.
Thank you.
Can I get an order started for you?
- For sure.
- Great.
- I'll take two dozen for my store.
- Wonderful.
And a few for my kids.
They will just die for these.
I love that.
Oh, my God. I love this.
It's amazing how quick ten years can go.
By '92, we'd built a six-million-dollar
business together from scratch,
broken up five times,
and felt like we were
just getting started.
You are one of a kind, Robbie Jones.
- One of a kind.
- Back at ya, Ty.
Though I can't believe you're
from Arkansas
and you've never met Clinton.
- Do you think he's gonna win?
- Yeah.
- He's younger than I am.
- And taller.
And he has a kid.
Do you think we should have kids?
You're probably too old though.
We have a lot on our plate already,
don't you think?
I mean, we're birthing an empire.
Listen. I think that we should
expand internationally.
- What? No. No.
- Yes.
- Yes. Yes.
- No.
The market is perfect
for us to move into the UK.
- Plus, it'll stimulate domestic.
- I said no.
The number one mistake
that people make is they get too greedy.
They start expanding too fast.
Plus, I'm loyal to America.
Okay,
what does that have to do with anything?
My products are made
by Americans for Americans, end of story.
Our products are made
for Americans by Asians.
Ty Inc.'s plush animals
are manufactured in China
- and Korea, as you well know.
- Yeah.
Paying us back for all the bills
America's paid for the entire world,
and I think it's about time.
If you want other countries to pay us,
then we need to sell to them,
not buy from them.
And I am proposing
that we figure out how to sell to Europe.
Don't double-cross America, Robbie.
- I'm being serious.
- Okay.
- No, I am.
- I know. I hear.
You just sit there looking pretty,
okay, Paul Revere?
I'll be over here,
running the actual real business,
like always.
I take requests, you know.
I wish we were doing this
at the new place,
but it's still under construction.
It's bigger than this place.
Gorgeous light.
This is perfect.
- So, when's the wedding?
- Very soon.
- We're not sure.
- Soon though. Right?
- But we just... we don't know exactly when...
- Yeah, soon.
- ...but soon.
- Very soon.
Things have just gotten busy.
Well, these little critters
surely have taken off.
It must be so exciting for your family.
Very. Yeah.
Well, we love doing it all together.
- Don't we, girls?
- Yeah.
Take one of me and Ava's ghost!
Yes, ma'am. Look at that.
- Can I get one of the entire family?
- Sure.
- Okey dokey.
- Yeah.
Come on up.
Thank you.
All right. Look at this.
The girls are thrilled by the photo.
Isn't it nice, what they said
about it being a family business?
Yeah.
I mean, it's just a dumb magazine piece.
But great, yeah.
Yeah, but...
You know,
it's gonna be really wonderful to get away
and have some time to finally relax.
You know?
I think when we get back,
I'm gonna get another face-lift.
What? Why?
Just to tighten things up.
We can get a family discount.
You could get some work done
on your nose or something.
- What's wrong with my nose?
- Nothing.
It's just, you have this...
a little bump on it.
Maren has one too.
Maren is not getting a nose job.
Of course not. She's a child.
I mean... But you're old enough.
Are you serious with this?
Sweetie.
Sweetie, you're beautiful. You are.
It was just a thought.
I like having the power
to be able to shape myself,
and I thought you would too.
We have a big year coming up,
and as the saying goes,
"Genius is 1% inspiration,
99% presentation."
That's not how the saying goes.
Okay. I... Yeah, all... Forget I brought...
Forget I brought it up. It's just... Yeah.
Mom, I can't find my floaties!
Yeah, I'm coming.
Are they honeymooning in Florida?
Just holiday vacationing.
He says he'll be tuning in tonight.
T-minus eight hours till showtime.
Move her this way.
Make her dance a little.
Will a 40-minute Shockwave movie
even play online?
'Cause I've only ever seen 30-second ones.
Welcome to the future.
You've reached Maya.
Tell me something good.
How about you tell us when
you decided not to go to medical school?
Your life is your life,
but we could at least be informed
all that money we carefully saved
for your education is ours again,
to do what we want with.
Maybe we'll do something risky
and impulsive.
See? See what you're doing to us?
Okay. Think about it.
Hey! Hey! No, no, no, no!
It's almost midnight,
and my Beanies movie's about to go live.
Hey, do one of the raps!
You mean the ones that boosted sales 40%?
Yeah. Maybe later, maybe...
Okay, here we go.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four,
three, two, one.
- Beanie Babies!
- What?
Beanie Babies! Beanie Babies!
It won't download. I keep trying.
Too many people are
logging on to the site at once.
So, no one can see anything?
Oh, shit. I'm gonna get fired.
We broke the entire Internet thing!
Not exactly.
It was our personal server lines
that got overwhelmed.
By 18 million Beanie Baby lovers. Unbelievable.
Again, that's not the amount
of people on our site, but...
Amazing. It's just fantastic.
Did I get any press calls about it?
- Who are you?
- Hi.
This is Linda Wallace, one of
the original Beanie Baby collectors.
- Oh, God.
- It is such an honor to...
Just one sec.
Remember I told you about the cul-de-sac
that started the local craze?
Well, Linda was ground zero.
Guilty.
Linda does the Beanie Baby Collectors
radio update on WGN now.
You agreed to meet?
And it... I am just beyond excited
to meet you,
Ty Warner, in person. Wow.
You do a radio show about my products?
Plus, I actually publish
the Beanie Baby Price Guide,
which people call the bible
of the collectors' market.
I was hoping you'd sign it.
And who gave you permission to do that?
Just out of curiosity.
I didn't know I needed to get...
Well, the guide drives tons
of customers to our site.
I mean, nothing hooks new collectors
like hearing Linda made $300,000
on Beanies.
300,000?
In just three months.
How exactly?
Well, there I was, just snapping up
as many as I could here in the States,
but then my sister went to Liverpool,
which... She's a real Beatle maniac...
And she saw piles of Iggy the Iguana
and Whisper the Deer,
which I have been looking everywhere for.
So, I tracked down the number
of your UK distributor,
ordered 200 pieces direct,
plus shipping fees.
Whole thing cost me $2,000
and very nearly my marriage,
but 90 days later,
those babies bought us a BMW
and a time-share in Florida.
So now people listen
when I tell them Beanies
are the best investment around.
Plus, they're cute as all get-out.
You know that.
Oh, gosh, you just gotta come on my show.
Ty filed a lawsuit by the end
of the following day.
And he forced eBay
to change its "Beanie Babies" category
to "Beanbag Plush."
But by then, the craze was uncontrollable.
Beanie Babies
are selling hotter than tamales.
The beanbag has
been transformed into a commercial rage.
To protect themselves,
delivery workers have been painting
over Ty's logos on the boxes they deliver.
People were buying
and selling half a million dollars
of Beanie Babies on eBay every month,
which was bonkers.
But what they couldn't see
was that everybody who wanted a piece
of that was buying new,
off the shelf from us.
So when eBay did half a million dollars,
we did 400 times that in retail.
$200 million every month.
It was so much money.
And we were constantly
expanding just to keep up.
Everything just got
a little bit out of control.
Ty included.
Maya. Did you see the latest numbers?
People keep wanting more.
Mr. Warner, a word?
No, thanks. Who's this?
Rep from Toys "R" Us or Walmart.
- Well, get rid of him.
- We tried. They keep coming back.
Hey! We only sell to mom-and-pops.
No big-box stores, is that understood?
And why don't we sell to big-box stores?
Anyone?
Okay, Maya, go ahead.
Their cheap product displays
invite price wars and comparison shopping.
The America...
The... More the America stuff.
Right.
Big-box stores kill small businesses
and trash the dreams of the little guy.
And America is all about the little guy.
And we are all about the little guy.
Marcus, is that shipment
from China on time?
Yes. They wanna know how many
new models we're introducing next month?
Well, everybody wants to know that.
Also, they asked about
an Asian distribution deal like the UK.
No, listen! No UK! No UK!
Hey, did you see those tweaks
that I made to the platypus design?
I did. They were very good.
- Yeah. I knew you'd like them.
- Yeah.
I'm sorry to interrupt, but Parade needs
an answer about the profile.
They'd like to interview Ava too
about the popularity of Spooky.
The audience reach could be huge.
First of all, Spooky is not that popular.
And also, no more dinky press, okay?
Parade has over 20 million subscribers.
I only want to speak to Oprah Winfrey.
Has she reached out?
- Not yet.
- Thank you.
Steven Spielberg's office called again
and now they're offering
- triple what they were offering before.
- Not interested again. I'm not a sellout.
Is that selling out to Mattel
and the Barbie tie-in then?
I am sorry for that. I will pass,
and I'll pass on McDonald's as well.
Why would you do that? I love McDonald's.
- You do?
- Yes. Of course.
Of course I love McD... Everybody loves...
The president loves McDonald's.
- You love McDonald's, right?
- Fiercely.
Don't you think partnering with them
might be too big a strain
- on our distribution system?
- Oh, my God.
Can you imagine the markets
that's gonna open up?
Sure, but we can barely keep up
with the mom-and-pops already.
It would be like a Super Bowl ad
for a bake sale.
- You heard her. We love McDonald's.
- Great. I will follow up.
- Mickey D's!
- Ty, I mean, it's thrilling
the demand for Beanies is so nuts,
but we gotta be able to handle it.
Remember New Year's?
Listen, we can put even tinier
Beanie Babies inside of Happy Meals.
Little tiny guys. It'd be so cute.
And adorable.
Profitable. Go with me to the airport.
I wanna go over designs.
It's hard to know how
to reason with delusion.
And sometimes you just
go along to get along.
By late '92, Clinton was president,
and I was in London
nailing down foreign expansion.
It's only 3:00 my time.
I could stay here all night,
but I don't want to keep you.
Were you able
to look at the proposal I faxed?
- Yes, and it's quite tempting.
- Good. Good.
But I'm afraid there's a bit of a snag.
Surely there's nothing we can't work out.
Legal says we can't make a deal with you
since you're not technically
the owner of Ty Inc.
My partner and I run the company together.
I do the deals,
he signs off once I walk him
through the numbers.
It's... We've been working
like this for years.
I'm sure it's just a miscommunication.
But we've been told differently.
I thought you knew.
He said your priorities had changed
and he was restructuring the company
based on both your wishes.
I got the sense you were trying
to have a child.
No. No, no, no. No.
You need to restore
the previous agreement immediately.
I'm sorry, Robbie, but my hands are tied.
That looks great, Ty.
I'll tell you when I'm ready.
I'm just working on my smile. Okay.
Just let me get my smile,
then I'll go like this,
and then you snap your picture.
Sure. Okay, you let me know when.
- Go.
- No, I... Okay.
No, I think we got it.
- I'm gonna fucking kill you.
- Hey, Robbie, just...
- Take five.
- Yeah.
Okay, hon, what seems to be the...
Welcome back.
Fuck you.
You know exactly what the problem is.
Your little restructuring stunt
is a sick joke.
Robbie.
This has always been Ty Inc., right?
I mean, you've been an incredible helper,
but this has always been my company.
Are you fucking kidding?
Roberta,
you know I don't like that rough language.
You know what I don't like?
Getting fucked out of a company I created,
that we created together.
That's not happening.
Why do you have to be so dramatic?
I am no longer cofounder,
and my salary has been reduced 75%.
Okay.
Can you keep your voice down a little bit?
Don't fucking tell me
to keep my voice down!
That wasn't salary. That was commissions.
And commissions don't make sense at the
level we're working at now. They don't.
Do you even know
what you're talking about?
Yeah, I'm just doing what's necessary.
You know, running the real
actual business over here.
And as far as expanding into the UK,
now's not the time.
But when it is,
I have our perfect partners lined up.
Actually came up with the idea
in the shower, believe it or not.
Jehovah's Witnesses.
The greatest one-on-one salesmen
in the world. How brilliant is that?
Robbie,
I... Honestly, what is the big deal?
I mean, we're still together.
We're not breaking up.
We're still partners in everything.
I mean, what is mine is yours.
You have the golden ticket. You have me.
What a prize.
It's pointless to talk to you
when you're like this.
- I mean...
- When I stand up for myself, you mean.
Yeah, what a bummer for you.
You should call one of your easier women.
Lorraine from the coffee shop.
- Julie from the dry cleaner.
- Okay.
Any one of the dozens
from the trade circuit.
I know about them all, Ty.
- Okay. We mutually agreed to occasion...
- Go fuck yourself.
You're a child. A selfish child.
And I cannot believe
how long I've put up with it.
Hey, listen to me.
If it wasn't for me, you'd still be
wasting away at the Speedi-Shop.
Where's the gratitude?
I've given you an amazing life.
I made you.
Mrs. Warner. We're waiting.
You guys, this is definitely the one.
- No, you don't like it? What?
- We love it.
Never take it off.
Have I told you how excited we are
that this wedding is finally happening?
Thank you.
So have you guys picked a honeymoon?
Yeah, Fiji. All of us, we're all going.
"Familymoon."
A familymoon in Fiji, all right.
Better live this dream.
- Hello? Ty?
- Hi, Mom!
We're in here.
Ty ran away.
What? Where'd he go?
Out the door. I don't know.
Maybe the new house?
Oh, my God.
- Thank you so much for coming.
- Of course.
They're asleep in their room,
and I don't know how long I'll be, but...
Okay, don't worry. Just go.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Yeah, be careful.
Ty?
Sweetheart?
Sweetheart? What happened? Are you okay?
I can't. I just can't. I can't.
Can't what?
I can't do this.
Honey, what's happened? What's going on?
I just... Getting married.
I don't know how to do family.
I don't know how to...
I don't know how to do this. I...
I didn't have a family.
No one ever...
Do you know... No one ever even...
- Hey. Sweetheart.
- Do you know...
- No one ever...
- You're loved now.
The girls and I love you so much.
I can't be a parent.
I'm the child.
I need to be taken care of.
Hey.
It's okay. Sweetheart.
I need you.
Hold me like I'm a little boy.
- Hi.
- Hi, ma'am.
I'm gonna need access
to the garage to unload.
- Returned products, 48 boxes?
- Yeah sure.
Okay.
All right. Thank you.
- Great. I'll open up.
- All right.
Gorgeous light, isn't it?
I know you love window seats,
so I ordered a whole wall of them.
We need to talk.
Listen, the freak-out last night.
It's over.
I feel much better now. I do.
Good. Well, I wish I did.
You don't wanna sit down?
I'm in love with you, Ty.
But I didn't wanna be.
I was gonna stay single
for Maren and Ava, remember?
Spare them a man abandoning them.
But you convinced me you were different, devoted.
And then you pull this?
No.
No, you gotta
find someone else to be your mom.
- I'm booked already.
- Wait.
What are you saying?
I'm saying, I let you in to be a partner,
to really build something good together.
And if you can do that, wonderful.
But I'm not gonna stick around
if you plan to fuck it up.
I'm sorry. You're right.
You're right. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I will never let you down again. I swear.
Please don't leave. Please.
Everything good that's happened to me
is because of you guys. Did you know that?
We are bonded forever.
There's no one I'd rather be with.
Do you understand that?
You're my home.
You're my rock.
You're my life.
Break out those raincoats
and umbrellas, folks.
We got a few days of rain...
- Do you know what you want?
- Nuggets. Always.
Same. Sweet and sour or honey?
Barbecue. What's wrong with you?
Riots broke out at McDonald's
restaurants across the nation today
as the company
launched their Teenie Beanie promotion.
Yeah.
The first batch of Beanies was meant
to last two weeks, but ran out...
Can you believe something we work on
is that popular?
Yes.
What is happening?
At one McDonald's,
a delivery man arriving with a case
of the Teenie Beanies was tackled
by overzealous customers.
Thanks to this little guy,
the Cubs sold out Wrigley Field today
for the first time in decades.
Two divorces unable to reach an agreement
about how to split their
prized Beanie Baby collection
were ordered to make their picks
under judicial supervision.
US Trade Rep Charlene Barshefsky
has turned over
the 40 Beanie Babies she procured
in Beijing during her trip
with President Clinton,
in violation of trade law.
Traffic on I-95 shut down for hours
after a crashed semi
carrying Beanie Babies
sparked a frenzy you have
to see to believe.
Looking good.
Did you see the latest numbers?
Billion dollar profit year. Congrats.
I'm gonna make over $700 million. Just me.
Did you see the truck crash
with the Beanies?
Insane.
Poor Beanies. But...
I mean, managing the craze has
become a whole separate job.
Which is why I wanted
to talk to you, if you've got a sec.
I'm all ears.
I think it's time for you
to consider a company restructure.
And what do you mean by that?
Well, everyone knows you're
a superstar design and marketing genius,
like no one else alive.
I mean, it just...
it seems silly to distract you
from your natural talents
with mundane business chores.
I know Robbie used to handle all those.
I don't wanna hear that name. Thank you.
But this company has transformed into
a mega success since then. Thanks to you.
You just need
to keep channeling your brilliance
where it's most fun and fulfilling.
While you, you know, tap someone you trust
to handle pesky, day-to-day headaches.
Chief operating officer.
A consigliere. A right hand.
Someone to deal with all the boring stuff,
freeing you up to continue doing the real,
important work.
I like it.
Yep. There we go.
You're the best. Keep it up.
I liked the bullshit and the boring stuff.
What's next?
- Solving puzzles, connecting dots...
- Hi.
- ...streamlining the system. Making it grow.
- I actually have this for you.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Thank God for the great equalizer
of the Internet,
saving me from ten years
of higher education,
setting me up to take charge of...
- Everybody, listen up! Meet Blaine.
- Hi, team.
Ty has brought me
on to put the fun in restructure
and take this company to the next level.
So, who's with me?
Who is ready to go big or go home?
Come on. Let me hear ya.
Let me hear you now.
There you go.
What a bastard.
Well, if it's any consolation,
everyone knows you're the one
really running the show.
It isn't.
I created and built this company,
and I have no rights, no salary claims.
How is that even possible?
'Cause the system isn't designed
for people like us.
Fucking hell.
I spent my whole fucking life
taking care of people.
And I thought Ty was the one person
who didn't need that.
What the fuck is that? Come here.
Oh, boy.
That ass-face is spying on me?
- All of us probably.
- That fucked-up motherfucker.
He's heard a lot of stuff
I really wish he hadn't.
There's gotta be a way
we can use this against him.
Uh-huh. See you then.
Hey. Showtime.
So, I just didn't see the brilliance
of the whole UK, Jehovah's Witness idea,
because I was so mad.
Sure, that temper of yours.
But it is pure genius.
I just... Not that I would tell him that.
Of course not. But Jehovah's Witnesses,
who'd have thunk?
It takes a brain like Ty's.
That total virtuoso,
off-the-charts mastermind.
So, you guys good again?
Getting there. He'll probably buy me
some amazing gift,
and then I'll be putty in his hands again.
Haven't you been wanting to learn guitar?
- I don't know.
- No.
- Beta, tell us what's wrong.
- Everything.
Thought I had it all figured out.
But my boss hired some slick
idiot consultant instead.
You've been fired? After all that you
gave up, they fired you?
I still have my job.
I just wanted a better one.
Okay, you're 22.
These things, they take time.
I've been there five years.
I understand the company better
than anyone, and I see where it's going.
Which is where, exactly?
Well, soon we'll finally be able to keep
up with the demand for Beanie Babies.
Which will actually be a problem,
because a lot of their appeal
has been how hard they are to get.
So, you're saying this will be trouble?
Yeah, if we don't get ahead of it,
yeah, definitely.
How much time do we have?
I mean, it's not like there are
precise metrics for measuring, like...
Wait.
You'll be sick of me, I'll be
in Tokyo so much, as much as needed.
The Asian launch is my top focus.
Hey, team.
What a surprise. This is Maya Kumar,
our online girl.
Maya, this is Mr. Harano. Mr. Suzuki.
They're interested in partnering with us
for the Japan market.
We were just laying out a road map
for creating the kind of demand there
that we did here.
Great.
Then you already talked about our unique
relationship with the secondary market
and the crucial role it plays
in any smart strategy going forward?
Yes. We covered how we control
the collector craze
with limited runs and retirements,
and how that fuels demand
for the entire line.
And how it's the unlimited runs
where we and our distribution partners
make the big bucks.
See, the primary market,
that's where the profits are.
And the secondary market, while handy,
well, it's secondary.
- No offense, Maya.
- No, none taken.
Demand is what we all care about.
Demand is king.
It's amazing how we can now measure
and understand that demand
using secondary market tools to help us
steer our business
more skillfully than ever before.
Uh-huh. So, back to the rollout.
I think the smarter...
What are these tools?
Well, the most basic is using
eBay markups to measure demand.
So this is how much we ship, and this is
how much they're marking them up on eBay.
On the high end, we've seen
Peanut the Elephant go for $7,000.
And on the low end,
there's no markup at all.
The more we ship, the lower the markup.
But if we ever cross zero,
market collapses.
- Which will not happen.
- No.
We actively monitor that threshold,
and we ship
up to 33 million Beanies a month,
before there's any cause for concern.
Right, 33 million.
But that's just our simplest projection.
And it's not the full picture,
because demand isn't static.
We now have a gold mine of data
from the eBay market.
Bids on a given model,
percentage where reserve is never met.
Timing of response bids,
plus a half a dozen others.
These metrics give us incredible
new insight on where demand is headed.
So in three months,
it'll be in this range.
So number is not 33 million.
It could be as low as 26 million.
I mean, worst-case scenario.
And thankfully, our worst-case scenario
is still overwhelming global demand.
Provided we understand,
respect and protect it.
So instead of just blindly pushing
our numbers up and hoping for the best,
we here at Ty grow our market
strategically, confidently,
using tools no one's ever used before.
I mean, we're light-years ahead
of everyone on this stuff.
And that's why we're the most
successful toy company in the world.
Well, that was great. They were impressed.
Good. I'm glad. But it wasn't for them.
My life is this company.
You know that, right?
They're totally in. They just asked
for the same terms as the UK.
Hey. No. We don't talk about the UK! Ever.
Okay. Yeah, I'll... No worries.
I'll fix it.
- They're gonna be incredible partners.
- Thank you.
Gotta be honest, Ty.
Blaine doesn't understand our company.
I don't think we need his advice.
Well, he has some things to learn,
but he has an amazing track record.
Maximizing profits
at soulless corporations.
But we're unique.
Our dysfunction is part of our heart.
I mean,
no one knows that better than you. And me.
I'm the person for this job, Ty.
You don't need outsiders.
I helped take Ty Inc.
from millions to billions.
And I've loved it.
Coming up with the poems,
running the website, fostering the market.
I mean, everything. But in all this time,
I've only ever had an "assistant" title
and an hourly wage.
You've had raises.
True. I started at minimum wage.
And now I make $12 an hour.
Well, I know a lot of people
that would like to make $12 an hour.
Considering all I do,
I think there's room for improvement.
We were the first company to have
a website for our customers.
Have you noticed everyone does that now?
That was my idea.
But using my resources, or my initiative.
I mean, I'm paying you to have ideas.
Well, I've netted a fortune
for this company, over and over.
I mean,
I understand our business inside and out,
and I'm telling you now,
there are signs of real trouble.
Have you seen that piece about this being
a bubble about to burst?
I don't accept babbling from outsiders.
Sure, but even some of our most
loyal collectors are getting frustrated.
Complaining about overproduction
and oversupply, pleading with us
to be more thoughtful
about new Beanie intros.
The collectors are idiots.
I hate the collectors.
- They're our bellwether, our engine.
- I'm the bellwether. I'm the engine.
Who's the billionaire here?
You. Of course.
But if there's turbulence ahead,
you need me helping navigate.
Not some clueless hotshot.
Okay,
Blaine might be great at old-school sales,
but our value is online now, and I run
that. I run fucking circles around that.
- Okay, I've heard you.
- No. Are you sure?
'Cause I thought I was being clear
the first time,
so I wanna make really sure
that I'm being clear now.
I'm your right hand, Ty. Me. Maya Kumar.
You know how much you mean to me
and this company.
I'll make it right.
- Good. Thank you.
- Okay.
I looked into suing him.
It would cost every penny I have,
and I still wouldn't win.
Have you considered poisoning him?
Countless times.
I'm sorry, hon.
Doughnut?
I think coffee will mask
the antifreeze better.
And let me just say,
I couldn't be more thrilled
that this proud American company
is gonna take over the world.
Starting with the UK, and then beyond.
So, everybody, buckle up! Let's do it!
Thank you, guys. Thank you.
They say good artists borrow
and great artists steal.
And Ty was the greatest
bullshit artist around.
Robbie, baby. There you are.
I've been looking for you.
Hope you're not too mad.
About?
Foreign expansion plan.
My foreign expansion plan.
No. I'm glad it's finally happening.
- Good.
Good, good, good.
We have a killer UK deal in the works,
and our distribution partners
are raring to go.
Amazing.
It is amazing, yes. I'm excited.
Hey, the cats came in.
They're... Listen,
they're a different color than you wanted.
- You wanna take a look at them?
- I'm a little busy.
Okay.
All right, hot sauce.
Come find me when you can, okay?
I bet that guitar looks good on you.
I... You...
You're a mind reader.
I knew you were gonna say that.
Come find me, okay?
I wanna show you the cats.
Okay.
It took me a while to realize all
the ways hurt people hurt people.
Turns out, all you have to do to have
a first day of the rest of your life
is wake the fuck up.
...job's mainly the phones.
Four hours a day, plus some Saturdays.
- You said you're in school?
- Yeah, I'm in school...
Roberta, sweetie,
you need to come tell me
which one of these looks like marigold.
You pressed "Intercom All" again. And no.
Bye.
Yeah, I'm in school,
but the schedule's not a problem.
All good?
Mexico, here we come.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Robbie!
What's going on?
Robbie.
Oh, God.
Okay.
Shit.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Sorry. I'm so sorry. Sorry. Okay.
Just in time.
You look cute.
- Thanks.
- Stressed, but cute.
I'm already an hour late
to Ty's office holiday party.
I still can't believe he scheduled it
for the same night.
- Yeah, it's a busy time of year.
- Great job, Dragons,
- go ahead and stand up.
- Yes, sir.
Shake. Make circles.
Mom!
- They're all calling her a liar!
- What?
- What happened?
- Hey, sweetheart. Come here.
- What's going on?
- Drew got a new Spooky
and the tag doesn't say my name anymore,
so now no one thinks I made it.
- Sweetheart, of course you made Spooky.
- Yeah.
I'm sure it's just a misunderstanding.
Let's see.
This must be just a...
It's a factory mistake...
- Yes.
- ...or this is a fake Spooky.
- It's not a real one.
- And whatever it is,
- it's all gonna be all right, okay?
- Absolutely.
I'm gonna go see Ty now
and get this whole thing sorted out.
Yeah?
In the meantime, I am so proud of you.
What you...
What's this you're wearing, huh?
- A green belt.
- Yeah!
- And I'm a yellow belt!
- Yes, you are.
Are you gonna celebrate?
- Yeah.
- Yes. We're having a pizza party, yeah?
Yay.
- Yes, we are.
- Yeah, well, Mommy's gotta go.
But, I love you. I love you.
- Love you.
- Everything's gonna be okay. Okay?
- Thank you.
- Call me later.
So before we go to this pizza party,
how about we burn this fake Spooky?
A little light arson, maybe?
What is arson?
You know,
even when you built your own ship,
you still gotta protect it from pirates.
God, I can't wait
to be rid of that douchebag.
Which one?
Here he is,
ladies and gentlemen. Ty Warner!
Hey, everybody! Hi!
Look at all these festive faces.
I hope you're all enjoying the party?
And I hope everybody
is enjoying the present?
- Yeah!
- Those little bears.
Those little bears, I guarantee are worth
$10,000 already on the World Wide Web.
Those little cuties! And as a holiday
bonus this year, everyone's...
Drumroll, please.
Everyone's getting double their salary!
What?
Double your salary!
Feel the energy of the room!
Feel the energy of Ty Inc.!
Merry Christmas, everyone.
Merry Christmas.
Happy Hanukkah, whatever it is.
It has been an extra special year,
and we are an extra special company.
Yes.
- We're amazingly unique, as you all know.
- Yep.
And because of that,
we're doing amazingly well.
- We are winners.
- Yes!
We create demand.
And this year,
we're gonna move more product than ever!
Yes!
- Because at Ty Inc. you go big...
- Wait, what?
...or you go home!
That's right.
How fun is this?
Blaine's coming on board full time.
- There he is.
- See a lot more of me. Right?
So I can go all in
on new design and innovation.
I have loved taking Ty Inc.
from millions to billions.
From the website to retirements,
steering the market, everything.
And there's so much more to come.
We're headed for the best year ever!
Merry Christmas, everybody!
- Enjoy the party!
- Ty! Ty!
To think I actually believed him.
I'm sorry it hurts, honey.
Your problem is, you don't know
you're playing a rigged game.
But if it's any comfort,
at least you had the privilege
of believing in the first place.
Oh, honey.
You gotta come on a jump sometime.
God, he looks terrible.
Look at the bags under his eyes.
I've been looking for you, Maya.
I've been right here.
Don't be mad.
Blaine's just a figurehead.
You know you're always
my secret weapon. You know that.
Look,
I wanted to tell you, I'm...
bumping you up to $20 an hour.
Twenty smackeroos.
- I'm done, Ty. I'm through.
- What do you mean?
I'm not your secret weapon. I'm
not a secret, and I'm not yours. I quit.
Wanna dance?
- Maya. Maya.
- Absolutely.
Okay.
I never imagined
just walking away from Ty.
But once you do, man, does it feel good.
The thing about Ty is,
he draws you in, wins your trust.
When things get bumpy, you just think
he's complicated, a little damaged.
You wanna keep believing in him...
until...
you just can't anymore.
I mean, what's the big problem
with disillusionment, right?
I mean, who wants to live
in "illusionment?" Not me.
Hey, Maya. Have you seen Ty?
Oh, Sheila. Oh, no.
I want so much better for you.
For all of us. It's...
You okay, honey?
Oh, yeah. Yeah. I will be.
Yeah?
- Can I ask you a question?
- Yeah.
Why did Ty change the Spooky tag?
Is he...
Is he so insecure
he had to take credit away from a child?
You know, it's... The funny thing is, like,
all the ones with the Ava tag
are worth way more
since he discontinued them.
Like...
But you know, it's not gonna matter
much longer, 'cause...
What do you mean?
Well, I mean...
Main bar.
It's all gonna go...
Okay, got a scotch and a chocolate milk?
Well, the scotch I can do,
but we don't do a lot of chocolate milk,
so it'll take us...
Yes, sir. Room 1433. We are on it.
Did you order something?
No. No, I did not.
Okay. I'll tell them to get lost.
You must be Sheila.
I'm Robbie.
Hey, did I tell you I bought a hotel?
I'm sorry this is how we're meeting.
It doesn't mean anything, if that helps.
I just like to show him who's boss.
What the fuck are you doing here?
You are making a huge mistake, Robbie.
We... I mean, we belong together.
Who's that?
You followed me to Mexico.
Of course I followed you. I'll follow you
anywhere. We belong together.
No one will ever love you
the way that I do.
Promise?
Who was that?
Sheila.
She's lovely.
No. No!
What happened? What did you say to her?
- Nothing, really.
- Okay, good. If I have her call you,
will you just say this was work?
What did you think it was?
Robbie!
You're fired, you hear me?
You get nothing! You get nothing, Robbie!
You're dead to me!
Robbie!
Wanna swim?
Come on.
Okay, Sheila. Listen.
- Oh, fuck.
- Oh, God. Wha...
My face. Oh, God.
Oh, God.
President Clinton
asked noted educator Dr. Maya Angelou
to compose a poem for this historic day.
If we knew at the beginning
what we did by the end,
would we do it all the same?
...and Americans everywhere.
A Rock, A River, A Tree
Hosts to species long since departed...
Who are you?
Maya. New receptionist.
I saw you on your way out a few weeks ago,
but we didn't get to meet.
Well, welcome, new receptionist Maya.
- Thank you.
- Let me ask you something.
Do you stand up for yourself?
Yeah. Every day.
Is Ty here?
Yeah, and he's running
super late for an appointment,
- so he should be leaving any second.
- Hey, out.
- I'm just here to pick up...
- You're not welcome here.
- ...the rest of my things. No, I...
- Get out. Out!
- Did you get a face-lift? You didn't.
- Don't touch my face.
Do not touch my face. Out, please.
I should tell you, the foreign
expansion plan, it was a terrible idea.
The UK is a disaster.
Oh, no. Don't tell me your door-to-door
preachers aren't working out?
Don't give me that.
You raved about the idea.
You said it was brilliant.
You said it was genius.
I don't recall saying that. Not to you.
You're a fraud.
And I will never, ever,
ever talk to you again. Ever!
Aren't you late?
I'm the one asking you to leave.
I'm asking you to get out.
Could we have security?
Your assistant said
you're late for an appointment.
Ty Inc. How can I help you?
This is Sheila Harper
from Oak Brook Lighting.
I'm at Mr. Warner's new residence
for our meeting.
Yeah, I'm so sorry.
He's obviously running really late.
He's in the middle of something right now.
Well, I've been waiting since 9:00.
Does he need to reschedule?
Honestly, if I were you, I'd just bail.
But we didn't bail. We leaned in.
Are we sure
we don't have any other options?
I'm kinda new here, Ty.
It's such a mess over there.
God, I hate this!
Okay, dial for me, please.
Yep.
Shut the door.
- Hello.
- Roberta.
Well, look what the understuffed
posable cat dragged in.
I think you know why I'm calling.
Listen, I need you to come back and
help me out. I need you to fix the UK.
No.
Okay. Robbie, please,
I really just need you, okay?
Why would you need me, Ty?
Because I can't do it without you.
I'm sorry, what was that?
"I can't do it without you,"
is what I said.
No fucking shit.
But the answer's still no.
What? Why? Why?
Because I'll never, ever, ever, ever,
ever, ever work for you again, Ty. Ever.
But you can work for me.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm starting my own company.
And it happens to be available
to be the exclusive wholesaler
of Ty products in the UK.
Wait, are you being...
Is this... Are you being serious?
Deadly. You want me to fix the UK?
Those are my terms. I run the UK.
Okay, I'm gonna put you
on hold for two seconds.
God Almighty!
God!
Okay, just get it fixed.
I will. Nice doing business with you, Ty.
Shut up.
He got one thing right.
You gotta build your own fucking ship.
So I did.
We all did. And not a minute too soon.
The Beanie market
has crashed spectacularly.
From gold to garbage.
The Beanie Baby bubble has popped.
A veritable Beanie Baby apocalypse.
By the end of '99, all that money,
$20 billion worth of Beanie wealth, evaporated.
That's the whole point of America, right?
Everybody chasing something
too good to be true.
And there's always another hustle.
Always a next new thing.
There's always another player.
What you gotta do is beat the game.
Maya-san...
We'd like to discuss something with you.
This card will be a big hit.
So these are our "Pokemans"?
Pokmons.
- Pokmon.
- What?
- Just Pokmon.
- Pokmon. Okay.
Just keep on poking them on.
It's so, so gorgeous here. And warm.
You should come visit.
And you really think
you're there for good?
Oh, yeah. I mean, Ava's Spookies,
they paid for the whole house and the car
and both girls' school through college.
- Oh, Jesus.
- Uh-huh.
- Seconds before the crash.
You really did get out just in time.
In so many ways.
You sound happy. For real.
I am. You know, I really am. I...
Do you know I realized
what the problem was.
It wasn't relying on the wrong man.
It was, I don't know,
having the wrong man rely on us.