Ladies
You're in love. Nothing wrong with that.
Hey! A little token of my appreciation.
Thanks, dude.
You got that *token*?
Right. That's funny, man.
Hey, thanks for getting my back down there.
I appreciate it.
I hope we do business again real soon.
Real soon.
Sorry to harsh your mellow, dude.
Freeze!
Hands up!
Hey, Shane.
Hey, Billie. Last time
I saw you, you were *naked*.
What'd he say?
Legendado e Sincronizado
Créditos : Truta
Revisado por Truta
Fastlane - 1x10
Dogtown
What test you can take to tell if
you can no longer have children?
We going to flip this whale or what?
He'll flip. Look he's looking
at a third strike.
He's a good snitch,
I've used him before.
Clean bust every time.
I trust him.
Personally, I'd like to know more
about the whole... *naked* thang.
That could help ease my pain.
I wasn't totally... *totally* naked.
I like this story.
Actually, technically, I think I was.
I really, really like this story.
Guys, I did vice. Remember?
Grow up, come on.
I've just gotten a visual.
So, Shane. You've
been a naughty boy.
Yeah. I'm pretty screwed.
So screwed.
Just about every sense of the word.
The lingual sense and
the prison bitch sense.
So, you know the drill, okay.
You can either take the third strike...
and spend the rest of your life rotting
in Pelican Bay or you can deal.
What would I have to deal?
You just busted me with 3000 pounds of weed.
Give us Trey McNeal.
Trey's my best friend.
You've been his whipping boy
ever since you could walk.
Listen, you give us Trey *and* the
Circle gang and *you* can walk.
You make sure Anna and
Latisha make it home.
They're both good girls
that come from nice families.
Well, one of them almost made it so
that *I* could never have a family.
Which one was it?
Thanks.
Okay, Shane. Your choice.
Third strike? Or your last chance?
Let's do this.
Trey McNeal. He moves
3000 pounds a month
with the help of his life long posse,
the Circle gang.
They're loyal to the death.
A group of Orange County surfers
who are either too mean
or too ugly to get sponsored.
So they found something more profitable.
They handle most of Orange County,
South Bay, Venice, Santa Monica,
Malibu, Beverly Hills and the West Side.
They're all about the lifestyle.
If you smell like you're not
about the lifestyle,
you'll be rejected like a bum kidney.
Shane is going to buy us
a ticket on the inside.
After that, it's up to you
to win Trey over.
We interrupted the Mexican pipeline,
where the gang has been getting
their weed for the last eight years.
At least temporarily.
So Trey?
He's going to be hungry for product.
If Trey doesn't have his weed
when his clients come calling?
He's going to be out of business.
We're going to give Shane
Candy Store cash.
He's going to explain that
he got away with the cash,
but the Mexican connection is over.
You guys are going to be introduced
as new potential suppliers from
Humboldt County up north.
You'll be selling him the weed
we confiscated off the boat.
Each pound will be tracked with
a radioactive dye marker.
We'll be following every single pound.
Bust this entire network wide open.
How much do we tell Shane?
Like any snitch - minimum.
No offence, but uh,
I can keep working the Serbian thing
and let Van take this one.
Are you getting close to the Serbians?
Not really.
So?
He hates the beach.
Hate's a strong word, Van,
but not strong enough.
I *despise* the beach.
I do not dig sand or (?) waves.
I look bad in shorts and I'm not into
skinny white girls with dreadlocks.
I could go on.
Please. It's fascinating.
Well, there's the Beach Boys.
Okay, don't even.
Brian Wilson is the greatest pop
composer of the 20th century.
What? Next to Barry Manilow?
You know what? I feel so
confident in what I know that
I don't even need to dignify
that with a response.
Please don't.
Okay, I will.
Do you know how ground breaking
his orchestrations were?
Wild Honey? 1968?
All right, you know what? I can't decide
which one of you is more annoying.
Well, I guess then we can't
give you your present.
Present?
What present?
Oh, you don't want a present
from two annoying guys, eh?
Noooo. Never that.
I like presents. I do.
I want a present.
Then we should.
All right. Turn around.
Close your eyes.
Oh no.
All right. Go ahead. No peeking.
Okay. You know what? I can't see.
My eyes are closed.
You don't have to do that.
All right. Right here.
Open. Peel it.
Is this? Is this the
Steve McQueen car?
1968 fastback. Bullet is back.
Well, we wrecked it.
We figure. We restore it.
Wow. It... It looks pretty good.
Well, it'll look a little
better with you in it.
Hey, make sure you put a
third coat of wax on her.
You know, before 'she'
deals with the elements.
Chance of rain.
Hey Trey.
Dude, your phone call
freaked everyone out.
I'm glad you're okay, Fetch.
Barely got back with the cash.
And what good is cash
going to do us now? Huh?
Well, you know...
Well, you know? What am I supposed
to tell my clients when they show up?
Uh, sorry, could you, uh, come back later?
We're gone fishing?
Come on! What are you thinking?
Tell him what you told me, Shane.
Nah. He'll just get pissed.
Oh. I hurt his feeeelings.
Is the baby gonna cry? Huh?
- Just tell him, Shane.
- I know these two guys.
Yeah?
And they deal volume
out of Humboldt.
And where did you... meet
these guys? On a bus?
Carlos.
*Carlos*?
Yeah.
Carlos, the V-13 gang banger, Carlos?
Carlos, who got capped in his money car,
Carlos? You mean, dead Carlos?
Yes. He said they did some
business with them.
So, maybe we should call
them up and order...
what do you think? Three, four
thousand pounds? Sound good?
I don't know.
No, seriously. Let's call 'em.
Yeah? Okay.
Yeah, right.
Fetch, like I'm gonna get
my hook-up through you.
No, I don't think so.
We've got to start looking
for a new hook-up or
word is going to get out
that we've lost our juice.
Soon as that happens, we're dead.
Ah, what the hell?
They got some nice stanky up
there in Humboldt, huh?
Why don't you bring these jokers by?
We'll see if they're down.
Cool.
This is Van. That's Deaq.
- What's up?
- Trey.
This is Jimmy. That's Zoe.
Your boy Shane says you might
wanna... hang some time.
Maybe.
That's cool. Let me tell
you something though
- I got a system of checking references
that makes TRW look amateur.
You don't check out, you won't
ever hear from us again.
Except maybe by way of
a single hollow point.
Found us a couple of
hard guys, huh, Fetch?
I like it. Go ahead.
Do your due diligence.
We'll do ours.
If it all checks out, why don't you
come hang out at the house later on?
Come on.
Betrayal.
Oh yeah, somebody's gonna
be zoning somebody.
How would you feel if that
somebody was Trey McNeal?
That's one bad surfer boy.
He's been dumping weed into the
neighbourhood for ten years.
Yeah, we're taking him down.
But we need you to put
in a word for us, playa.
That boy's own mother could
vouch for ya and that would mean
absolutely nothin'. Gonna take more
than my word to get him to set up.
Like what?
He needs a boot in his ass.
Like a Jack boot.
You're a genius.
Somebody wanna let me in on this?
VRB.
Venice Ride Boys.
Surf Nazi gang. They been looking
to jump in on Trey's action for years.
Aquarius puts out the word
that Trey is vulnerable,
he'd be more than
willing to buy from us.
Create the need for weed
and we deliver the goods.
Bingo, baby.
Damn. Dude is hella a surfer, though.
Drop in on me once and BOW,
knocked me right outta a curl.
Come on, man. Don't even start that.
I know you ain't surfing, now.
Stop playing.
I don't surf? What?
Fat people don't surf?
Take a look at this right here, man.
You know what this is?
That's Zuma.
This right here.
That's the Pipeline.
And this right here?
Todos Santos.
Exactly.
I'm a big wave man.
Hey, Van, on the real, partner.
We should come out here
one morning, hit a little somethin'.
Anytime, anywhere.
As we should. Now, check this, man.
I unleash those skinheads on the Circle gang.
Y'all better be ready throw down
on them swastika asses, man.
Leave the ass whooping to us.
You make the phone calls.
All right, now.
You really like it?
I love it. You gonna love it too.
Don't hate. Congratulate.
Room for all of us, man.
Seriously, Van. Surf Nazis?
That pretty much closes deal on how
I feel about this whole beach thing.
What about that?
You like that?
I'm feeling that.
Hey, guys. I don't know, man.
What? What's the matter, Shane?
Talk to us.
He's too smart. I feel like he knows
I'm selling him out already.
And you know what? He's going to
kill me. That's what he's gonna do.
Whoa, man. Chill out.
He's smart. We're smarter.
And we got your back.
And all you gotta do,
man, is just be Shane.
I don't even know who
that is any more, Deaq.
I go to Mexico and I
know exactly who I am.
They love me. I go down there.
I stay in my house in Ensenada.
I'm a hero. They think
*I'm* the cool guy.
Ok. You're the cool guy,
wherever you go.
This guy Trey's just got
you all twisted, that's all.
No, man. He recognized
you guys were cool.
He accepted you, just like that.
Man, you got it bad.
I mean, real bad.
But you know what? We gonna
get you out of this, man.
So you're saying, if I work this out,
I got a shot at a new life?
That's part on you, dude.
That part's on me.
So your operation checks out.
I was very impressed.
Thanks, dude.
Maybe one of these days,
we can talk business.
You've really never
been on a surfboard?
Where I grew up, a surfboard
would get you shot.
Out here, a surfboard will
*keep* you from getting shot.
Come on.
Where we going?
I'm gonna give you a surfing lesson.
That's very funny.
Cos it sounded like you said
you're giving me a surfing lesson.
I'll grab you a wetsuit
and we're going surfing.
Yeah, right.
Wait. I let you on *my* beach and
you're going to refuse to get on a board?
Looks like the moment of truth
has arrived, partner. Surf or die.
Oh, so I'm supposed to let a
bunch of wimpy white dudes
convince to do something
I ain't never gonna do?
Ever.
Come on.
All right, dude.
That's it! You got it!
Get back on that horse, dude!
So, Fetch.
Yeah?
You've been in love with Zoe for
like what? Five? Six years, is it?
I don't know.
I don't know. You should learn
something from Deaq, dude.
He's known her for what? A day?
He could nail her tonight if he wanted to.
So what, man? It's not like
she'd go out with me anyways.
Fetch, Fetch, Fetch. Loser
mentality, amigo. I told you.
Now that? Is the right way to
burn through the last of our stash.
- That's the last of it, huh?
- So what?
You tell me, dude.
Up, up. We got visitors.
Now, ladies. Word is out that you're
having some supplier problems.
Guess the, uh, wetback
connection is out of business.
Yeah? Where'd you hear that?
- Dan Rather.
- What if it was?
Well, then. We could help you out.
Take over your territory.
Till you're back on your feet again.
And what then?
We could work something
out. We split it.
You walk into our territory...
Hey! It's only your territory as
long you've got the product, chief.
Hey, why don't you run
off back to the bunker and...
get your lips pretty for the funeral?
Why don't you do that?
What did you say, boy?
I think he said you
were his Nazi bitch.
Nazi?
You wanna sit? Huh?
A'right. Who wants to
play hide the bullet?
Who want it?!
Nice to meet you.
Get it? This is circle territory.
Van. Deaq. That's some heads up play.
And where the hell were you, numbnuts?
Shut it!
Why don't you guys come by
the house tomorrow?
Maybe we can do some business, huh?
And Fetch, got to save your new
boyfriend, didn't you? That was so cool.
Straight up, Shane.
You saved my life, dawg.
Thank you, Deaq.
You know why I want
to make this case?
So you can have Zoe all to yourself?
Nah, man. I'm just tired of watching
Trey punk his homeboy, Shane.
I want Shane out from under
that dog. I mean, it's sad, right?
I mean, he's so deep in it,
he can't even see how bad it is.
End of the day, that's up to Shane, man.
I know what I'm talking about.
I grew up with a lot of kids like that.
Me too. And you know what?
It's a tough place to come
from, I know that feeling.
What are you talking about?
When I was banging, I was
the skinny puppy of my set.
I was a little younger, I was small,
and I guess those cats knew...
I didn't really wanna be there.
There was this OG(?),
Maurice, they used to call him eight ball,
and this cat used to ride my ass
from the moment I came in...
'till the moment I left. I mean he
made every minute living hell for me.
Man.
You know how much grief
I'm going to give you about that right?
Why? Why you gotta do
me like that, dawg?
I mean, I'm trying open up here.
Right, no. No, don't stop.
I like it.
You see, I'm expressing, a'right?
All right. Express yourself.
Open up. I wanna be the
shoulder you lean on.
- Tell me more.
- I have nothing else to say.
All right. Healthy power,
Scrappy Doo.
A'right.
Zoe!! Zoe! Help!
You're Deaq.
You're a funny man there, Trey.
But you know what, I sell Chronic.
I deal in volume to avoid all the
customer relations hassles, man.
So if we don't get with the kiss called
closure by the end of business *to-day*,
we're taking our goods
down the road.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It's just
you, on the water, was, uh...
Maybe I do have a stereotypical black
man's version of water sports,
but you know what?
I will get on anything with wheels except
a skateboard and crush you, playa.
Really?
Believe it. And just to
make it interesting,
when I do crush you?
We start business today.
All right. I like that.
Hey, if you don't have a cast iron
nutsack, you better (?) in quick.
You better get a mint.
Fastest wheels without a motor.
These things are custom built.
Five large a pop.
I was thinking like a nice
motorcycle race or something.
What's the matter? Brothers
don't luge either, big mouth?
You know what? After I kick
his ass, I'll be kicking yours.
Okay. Do your thing,
Captain America.
First one to the intersection
rules the world.
Yeah!
Here's to a long and
profitable association.
I hear that.
Make your payments well,
we'll be best of friends.
Mmm mmm. You know what that
means for Fetch, huh? Don't you? Huh?
No more trips to Mexico to
be the conquering hero.
He goes back to being *full*
*time* *bitch*. Don't you?
Here's to Fetch. Full time bitch.
You don't have to do anything.
Just stay in until the bust happens.
Dude, it's almost over.
Just. Just play tight.
We make the deal, then track
the weed to the distributors.
Keep your head in the game,
we have a lot riding on this.
Shane's head's been in the
game this whole case, Billie.
Then what is it?
What's the problem?
Okay, look. Let's say
this all goes great.
In the perfect world of this thing,
I'm going to frame all my friends and...
send them off to prison
for a long, long time.
So you get new friends, man.
You need new friends. Trust me.
And then I what?! Sling lattes
at Starbucks and wait...
for someone to come in and bust
a cap in my head? Is that it?
New friends. New life.
Get out from anything and everything
that's been keeping you down, man.
I know there's a new you in
there, just waiting to happen.
If you want it. Otherwise, sooner
or later, you'll find a new circle,
another Trey McNeal to slap you
around and then who knows?
Two years from now we can be
standing around in a dark street,
having this same conversation.
No, no, no. You guys are right.
He's been happening to me
since I was nine years old.
Trey's been picking on me. People've
been telling me to 'fetch'.
You're right. I need to start from
scratch. And you know what?
Nobody's going to recognize
the new me. Nobody.
Let's get out of here.
Got the stuff?
It's in the truck.
What is up with you, Fetch?!
Forget to take your Ritalin?
No. You know, I'm just...
What?! Pissing your pants?
Yeah, I'm pissing my pants, Trey.
Okay, guys. Could you finish
this deal before daybreak?
Why don't you tell him
to get off my back?
Or what? You gonna start crying?
Yeah, I'm going to start crying.
What if you start...
All right, look! How about we all
just maintain before 5-0 busts?
You guys can settle your
domestic disputes at home.
Yeah, Shane. It's all good.
Gotcha.
First thing, tomorrow morning.
You guys should come
by the house.
Talk about the next deal.
Nice doing business with y'all.
You too.
All right. You wanna talk about how
Shane almost screwed up the play?
Look. We're gonna back into this all right?
All we need our boy to do is hang
in there, keep his mouth shut,
and let the weed show
us who's distributing.
But since we're on this subject and
we got some quality you and me time,
what's your problem with the guy?
I know his equation, okay?
I grew up on the same
sand, same waves.
You got nothing at home,
so you start this group.
Your circle. That's your family,
it's the only family you got.
We're dealing with somebody
who's turning on their own family.
One screwed up family at that.
That's not the point. He's the guy
that doesn't fit in. *Anywhere*.
He's not strong enough to stand
without the family and he's too weak...
to pull his weight within
the family. Guys like that,
they always have a problem
they're always going to be on the outside.
Fetch?
Hey.
What are you doing?
I asked you.
- What you're doing?
I heard you. I just didn't care.
That's funny, Fetch.
Well, let me clue you in. I'm
taking the cash and the weed...
and I'm going to Mexico to
live happily ever after.
Dude, what are you talking about?
Oh, that's right. Sounds crazy.
That's because I forgot
to tell you the part where
I'm going to smoke your ass first.
Fetch, you are *so* *high*.
That's right. I'm high. I'm high
on how dead you're gonna be.
Huh?!
That hurts, doesn't it, huh?
You know why? That's the way you've
been slapping me since we were kids.
Awww. Is the baby gonna
cry? Baby gonna cry?
Please.
Don't worry. It'll all be over soon.
Trey!!
It was the new guys. Van and
Deaq. They came in here...
and they took the cash.
And all the weed.
I knew those guys were going
to make a move. I knew it!!
If you knew, why didn't you
*do* something about it!?
I didn't even let them in, Shane!
I didn't let 'em in. Trey brought them in!!
Now we have to go get those guys.
All right, here's the deal, man.
They're probably going
back up north to Humboldt.
They're not going to be speeding, they
got a car full of drugs and cash, right?
So don't sit there and
stare at me. Go get 'em!!
All right.
We're taking you to a hospital.
No, I can take myself to the hospital.
I can't stay here alone.
If you don't stay here, the house
is going to be vulnerable, all right?!
You can get me on the cell phone.
Okay, tell me you don't have like the
smallest urge to get back on a surfboard.
What is it with you, Van?
It's like you're trying to
convert me to your religion.
Just tell me. Be honest.
- No. It's not fair.
- See. You're hooked.
No, Van . It's an
expertise thing, okay?
Okay.
- All right? I like to have mastery, right?
- Mastery.
I would do it again like
to... to get better.
Hooked!
Yeah?
Hey, Van. The dope is
moving. All of it.
The dye marker in the
weed is emitting a signal.
Well, maybe Trey sold
it all to one buyer.
Okay, I'm going to follow this
stuff. You meet with Trey,
see if you can find out
who the buyer is.
We'll come back you up!
You guys need to still
show up at the house.
You don't, you're going to
jeopardize your cover.
All right. Dope's moving.
Something's not right.
I love my job.
Ouch. That's gotta hurt.
Call Billie.
Yeah?
Billie. Trey McNeal is dead.
And the Circle gang looks
like they've been jacked.
They got the money
and the drugs.
All right. Find Shane and
pull him out. This is over.
I want you out of that house now.
I'm going to call for backup to meet me.
Yeah.
Let's check the house.
Drop your guns!!
Whoa! Hold. Hold up. Zoe.
Zoe. Zoe.
Look. We're putting the gun
down, all right? Look.
All right?
What the hell are you doing here?
We came here to meet
Trey. What happened?
You killed Trey!
That's what happened.
Okay. Whoa, whoa. What makes
you think we killed Trey?
You killed Trey and
you tried to kill Shane.
Come on now.
Who told you that?
Shane!!
Ah, that little dwiblet.
Shut up!!
Okay. So wait. Think about it.
We're here. Where's Shane?
He went to the hospital
because of his *bullet wound*.
I was going to take him, but
he said he could drive himself.
Okay, Zoe. He didn't
want the girl he's in love...
with to take him to the hospital?
He wanted to drive himself?
Come on, think about it.
Why would we come
back if we killed Trey?
Come on now.
Shane. He killed Trey?
That's right.
We wanna go find him.
Unless you're gonna shoot
us today, Zoe, come on.
I'm not going to shoot anybody.
I just can't believe this.
Believe it quick.
Put the gun down.
So we can get the hell out
of here and find him, okay?
Now look, you might want to
grab a change of clothes and...
surfboard and get the hell out
of here cause there's gonna be...
a lot of heat on this
place soon. All right?
Just keep heading south, that's
where the dope is moving.
The next time I tell you I hate the
beach, would you please listen to me!?
Next time I say 'Don't trust a
snitch,' will you please listen to me?!
Hello?
Shane. What are you doing?
Going back to the house.
I'm right behind you, Shane.
So you are.
Why don't you pull over
and we'll talk about it?
I don't think so, Billie.
Would you rather get shot?!
Yeah, I guess I would.
Okay, you know what? This
is your last chance, Shane.
And I'm going to take it, okay?
Cause I'm tired of people
like you trying to stop me.
People like me? What is
that supposed to mean?
People who make me go
out and fetch for them...
while they got to
live their lives!
Well, you know what?
I'm tired of fetching, Billie.
So short answer?
I'm not pulling over.
Okay. I see that you're having a
little psychotic Victor moment,
but you know what, Shane.
I don't have time.
I'm on the clock. And I've
got twenty highway patrols...
who are going to
show up any minute.
Well, they can come
and get me, bitch.
Okay, that's it.
Pull over, Shane!
Now!!
Hello?
Billie. It was Shane.
Shane killed Trey.
Yeah. I kinda figured that
when he was trying to kill me.
He ran me off the road.
You all right?
Yeah, no, I've been better.
I think I dislocated my shoulder.
And I might have
broken some ribs.
But I'm really bummed
about my Mustang.
Look, I think he's headed to Mexico.
He has a house in Ensenada.
Ugh. You gonna
call border patrol?
No, no. I think we
can handle this one.
Yeah. I was hoping you
were going to say that.
Okay. This is what
you're going to do.
Screw jurisdiction, screw
protocol, screw everything.
I want you to nail
that scale to the wall.
You're turning me on.
That's what I do.
I want you to find him
and bring him back.
I can't believe how easy it is to
drive guns across the border.
You ready?
Cause I want this guy.
Hey guys. Thought
you'd be stopping by.
Welcome to my crib.
You remember Anna and Latisha.
Ah, how could I forget?
Looking pretty casual
there, buddy.
That's because you
can't arrest me.
I'm out of your jurisdiction.
Estamos en México.
I bet you wished we cared.
Oh, so you're planning some
international inappropriate...
kidnapping thing?
Yeah. Something like that.
I want you to know,
I really like you guys.
You were straight shooters.
I wouldn't want anything
bad to happen to you.
Anything bad to
happen to us?
You're high. Right, Shane?
Absolutely.
You know what? You
mess with your people?
That's one thing. But
you crossed a really...
unfortunate line this time. This
time you messed with *my* family.
Who? Billie? She
was in my way.
Did I miss something?
When did you become
such a bad boy, Shane?
Are you kidding me,
Van? You put me here.
You made me.
Don't you remember?
You showed me my full potential.
You know, starting over?
You really don't
want to do that.
I really want to
do it. Do you?!
Yeah, I really,
really want to do it.
Go inside, girls.
Why don't you just get
into the car with us, Shane?
So we're not forced
to kill your ass.
Yeah, there's that.
Don't you realize, that
in Mexico, I am God?
You can't put God in jail.
You can't kill God.
But Trey? I *loooved* whacking
him. And Billie? Whatever.
Dude. You're alone
and unarmed, okay?
So why don't you tone
down the cocky thing.
Okay, I get the
cocky thing now.
You know what I just realized?
This is a Mexican standoff *in Mexico*.
Guess what? Final de
la música, amigo.
You were right, Shane.
It's fun to play God.
All we had to do was give
them a hundred bucks and...
promised them what
was in your house.
I'm starting to like Mexico,
we should get a time share.
Yeah.
Listen, guys. I was
just playing around.
You know?
We're cool, right?
Is this the bad boy
Shane talking or the...
snivelling snitch Shane talking?
I've got fifty grand in there.
You guys split it up,
that's twenty-five grand a piece
and you walk away, no one...
I was really hoping we could
put Shane on the right track.
I could go really far south.
Like South America or Honduras...
I really didn't want
to be wrong on this.
It's okay. You been
wrong plenty of times.
Really?
Okay. Maybe south is bad.
Maybe I'll go up to Canada.
Shane! Can't you see
me and my man...
are having a little family meeting?!
Yeah! But I just
wanna ask you...
I need some help here.
Long ride, hot day. Hope
he doesn't die in here.
Why's that?
Cause I'd like to see
him in the warm...
embrace of a whole new family.
Oh, so you're talking
about a guy who wanted...
more than a fast way
out from being a punk?
He's going to spend the
rest of his life in prison...
as the lowest form
of jailhouse bitch.
See that's poetic.
I couldn't have said
that better myself.
Well, then let's go on
to a new subject, playa.
Okay. Wanna go
surfing tomorrow?
Créditos : Truta