Hungary Film Archive
73rd Berlin International Film Festival
Berlinale Classics
BUDAPEST FILMSTUDIO COMPANY
HUNGARIAN TELEVISION
TWILIGHT
a film by György Fehér
I'm very sorry.
That I have to bother you with this
filthy business
in your last days.
I don't even know who will replace you.
Greetings, Inspector.
By the cross up there.
A girl, about 8 years old.
Most likely been dead for days.
- How was she killed?
- With a razor.
Had you sent the child somewhere?
Did she often take that route?
The girl was found dead in the forest.
She has been murdered.
My child...
I need... need to... go...
Go... to her...
to see my child...
Need to go see my child...
- Who killed her? Who killed her?
- My child... I must see her...
- My child... My child...
- Who killed her? Who killed her!
- I have to go and see her!
- Who killed her?! Who killed her?!
- You can't go there!
- Who killed her?!
- Don't you understand...
- You cannot go there...
- Who killed her?!
- Who killed her...?
- Who killed her!
- I don't know...
- You must find out...
I beg you...
- You need to find out...
- I will...
- I beg you... Find out...
- Twill... will...
- Find out...
- I promise... I promise...
Do something already...
I've already tried.
They won't listen to me.
These people... They want the hawker.
You were the one who found the child?
Yes, I did, Inspector.
You know what those outside want?
Yes, I do, Inspector.
Do you know why?
Because you've been involved
in a similar case before.
I am innocent, Inspector.
I'll say, you go together nicely...
He hasn't been arrested...
He's being interviewed as a witness...
Your job is...
whether he's guilty or not...
order must be maintained here.
If freedom of movement is
not guaranteed here,
everyone will suffer.
It is your job, is it not, to maintain
order,
to ensure the investigation runs
uninterrupted!
Go out there...
and tell them to go about their business!!
So what was the story with Anna?
Look me in the eye.
What was the story with Anna?
The giant...
He met Anna every week.
And...?
Look me in the eye...
Where?
By the cross.
Look me in the eye...
- Are you sure Anna drew the giant?
- Yes.
- And have you seen the giant yourself?
- Not me, unfortunately.
- Where did she meet the giant?
- By the cross.
And what did the giant give to Anna?
Little hedgehogs.
- Look me in the eye...
- Little hedgehogs.
He gave her little hedgehogs.
- Where?
- By the cross.
Are you sure she drew the giant?
Professor...
He doesn't strike me as a sex killer.
Has he been previously convicted
of sexual assault?
He was with a 14-year-old girl.
And his relations?
With other women?
Well... Just like any other hawker...
He's been around...
Higgledy-piggledy...
Too bad she died...
But the car, on the other hand...
she seems to have observed pretty closely.
So much so...
that I could perhaps even say...
that the car in question might
well be an old-fashioned one.
This, of course, is only a vague
assumption, however.
Because, if it were true...
then the murderer...
is still driving about in
an old-fashioned car.
Let us say for the sake of argument,
that I identified the child's murderer
from this drawing.
If we accept this as a possible scenario...
whatever could we make of this, you and I?
You, Sir...
are trying to do the impossible...
But if you...
wanted to chase a murderer now...
who most likely does not exist...
but even if he did...
You will never find him...
because of this kind of murderer
does not kill by accident...
There are too many.
Well,
then your situation would
get very worrisome.
So, you said
that you went into the
forest after your break,
before you returned to the city,
and you stumbled across the body...
without touching said body.
We took your clothes and gave you new ones.
Do you suspect why?
We found bloodstains on your coat.
The little girl's blood.
I stumbled on the body.
And I assume you only kept
this quiet out of fear?
And you want us to believe you again?
No need to get anxious...
We don't want to torture you.
We're only working to bring
the truth to light.
That's why we've turned to you.
You are our most important witness.
You have to help us.
Yes, Inspector.
Tell me, what sorts of things
do you sell?
Towels?
Tea-towels, too.
What else?
Shoelaces...
Inspector.
Toothbrushes.
Soap.
Shaving cream.
Is that all?
Well, now...
I think you've forgotten something.
Go on now, what else do you sell?
We've gone through your stuff
very thoroughly.
Well?
- Kitchen knives.
- What else?
What else besides the kitchen knives?
Razors.
Why did you hesitate to tell us?
The girl... was killed with a razorblade.
Look, I know that you
committed this murder.
But I also know...
that you were just as
shocked by it as I am.
As we all are.
Something came over you
that turned you into an animal.
You attacked her and killed her
without intending to.
Something inside you,
a compulsion you couldn't control...
You ran to the village to turn yourself in
but on the way you got scared.
Isn't that right?
I'm tired.
We're all tired.
Send for coffee,
and later, beer.
For our guest, too.
We are the police...
we're humane.
I am innocent, Inspector.
Yes?
Tell me, what did you have
for lunch that day?
Stuffed beef.
With braised cabbage.
You hawkers seem to do well.
Did you eat anything else?
When did you have the chocolate?
A report from the Coroner's Office.
The autopsy revealed
chocolate in the child's stomach.
He jumped off the upper floor.
Please, allow me to take over this case.
I don't think the murderer
is from around here.
It must be the same person responsible
for those other murders in the north.
Someone with a car.
Most likely a salesman or traveller.
I cannot agree to this.
You're not with us anymore.
Surely you're not going to just
wait for something to happen?
Something that might never happen?
And you would just wait and wait?
You shouldn't have taken it
to heart, you know.
Wouldn't you consider coming back to us?
First you'd need to do internal service.
The usual conditions.
Perhaps they would even take
you back in the city police.
Looking at all this here...
you should consider it, even if
just for purely financial reasons.
What a pretty little creature.
Do they know why they're here?
Dear God...
Can't...
Can't take it anymore...
I can't take it...
I don't want this anymore...
I don't want this anymore,
do you hear me?
I can't take it, I don't want to!
I'm leaving!
Say something, you!
You said you'd stop drinking!
You said you'd stop drinking,
can you hear me?
I can't take it anymore,
you hear me?
This is not what you promised,
you filthy scum!
Not what you promised,
you filth... you vermin...
You filthy garbage, I'll show you...
Leave me...
Let me go you filthy scum!
You filth, you...
You'll wake the kid...
God...
Let me go you filth...
Is this what you wanted me for?
You filth...
Let me go you scum...
Help me, God...
Leave me...
Filth...
Stop...
Enough...
Don't want to...
You filth, you...
Urgh!
Urgh, you disgust me!
The child...
Don't!
This is not what you promised...
Who gave you chocolate?
A girl.
At school?
Right, show me.
And is there any more?
Hm?
How about in your pockets?
Was it the wizard who gave you these?
Hm?
Did he forbid you to talk about
the two of you?
Well then, don't!
He's a good wizard of the forest.
You can visit him anytime you want to.
Now go back to play.
Go away.
I ask you kindly not to hinder
me in doing my duty,
which is to uncover the truth.
Go away.
Please don't do anything you
would regret later.
I beg you, please, go away.
You wouldn't if you were in
my position, either.
We both want the same thing.
You remember the oath we took.
It is our duty to fight all forms of crime
and to prevent anything unlawful.
We have to ensure there is
peace and order in society,
and we're duly expected...
Who are you waiting for?
Tell me...
Why won't you tell me..?
Someone gave you chocolate.
Show them to me.
They look like little hedgehogs, right?
A man in black gave you
the chocolate, didn't he?
Look, you have to tell me
who gave them to you.
You have to tell me exactly
what he looked like.
You have to tell me!
Who gave them to you?
Do you hear me?
I just don't want anything
to happen to you!
You stupid creature!
Will you tell me at once?
Who gave them to you!
You hear me?
Who gave them to you?!
When did it happen?
Just recently.
Is he dead?
He vanished.
Was it a large man in a black coat?
He was speeding...
as if he were being hunted.
Cast
Written by György Fehér,
based on the themes of
'It Happened in Broad Daylight’
by F. Dürrenmatt
Cinematography
Miklós Gurbán
Studio manager
Gábor Hanák
Production chief
György Lendvai
Production manager
Tibor Dimény
Sound designer
László Vidovszky
Audio engineer
János Réti Péter Kardos
Editor
Mária Czeilik
Dramaturge
József Marx
Consultant
Béla Tarr
Set designer
Tamás Vayer
Stylist
Gyula Pauer
Assistant director
Production assistant
Chief lighting technician
Camera operator
Architect
Éva Martin
Set dressing
Lórántné Mathaidesz
Production designer
Ferenc Ormos
Pyrotechnics
Ferenc Hábetler
Costume supervisor
János Breckl
Make-up
Sound mixer
József Kardos
Dolly grip
Pál Acsai
Assistant editor
Contributors
Produced by
Hungarian Filmsudio Company
Laboratory work by
Hungarian Film Laboratory Company
Colourist
Tamásné Deimanik