[high-pitched ringing]
♪♪
- Oh, no!
Ow, ow! Hot!
- That was quite
a crash, son.
Oh, look at
that goose egg.
Where are your parents,
sweetie?
- I don't know.
- How old are you?
10, 11?
- I-I don't know.
- The crash must
have rung your bell.
Well, let's start simple.
You got a name?
- I don't know!
I don't know!
- [Wandering woman] Shh, shh!
Hey, hey, it's okay.
Let me help you.
I can help
get you home safe.
[groaning]
- Wait!
- Fat chance, kid!
Watkin storm's a comin'.
- Hey, that's my car!
[yelping]
[panting]
[thunder crackling]
♪♪
Who is this asshole?
- Give me those glasses.
The sun's bullying me.
- I can't, I'm dyin'.
Say nice things
at my funeral.
Take the time to speak
highly of my good deeds.
- Man, dudes cannot handle
hangovers for shit.
- No hangovers in
New San Francisco,
I'll tell you that.
Oh, I had this sexy
pork tenderloin last time.
[smacking lips]
God, I can't wait.
- I can't wait for a dog.
- Nah, too gamey.
- What?! No!
Not to eat.
- Oh.
- I always wanted a pet.
You know, like a wolfdog
with three legs named Patrick.
- I'm not taking
care of a dog.
- Nobody asked you to!
- Well, we're living
together. I mean...
- What?!
Are we living together?
- What?! No!
What? No!
Why? No!
I mean, like living together
in the same city.
- Oh.
- You call me to walk your dog
when you're not home,
at your home,
and I'm home at my home.
See, two separate homes.
So, that makes two homes.
- Hmm.
- Unless you want
to live together.
- Do you?
- I don't know.
Do you?
- You seem like
a shitty roommate.
I mean, you can't even share
your fuckin' sunglasses.
- Yeah, I can share
my shitty popcorn.
- Wow, your aim
is so good.
Oh, shit!
[gasps]
Is this the infamous photo?
- Hey!
- Dude, what the hell happened?
You were so cute.
- Take it easy with that.
- Oh!
This is the only photo
you have of your past life
and you keep it
in your visor.
I think I can handle
holding it for one...
Shit!
- I fuckin' told you
to be careful.
Stupid!
Hey, I said stay back
with Evelyn
and watch the package.
- I can do two things.
[sighs]
How old were you
in that photo anyway?
- How does anyone keep
track of that shit?
- I mean, birthdays,
moon phases,
cut your dick open
and count the rings.
- Can we just focus on
finding the picture?
We're running out
of day light.
- [Quiet] Oh, found it!
Ah-ah, what do you say?
- Don't drop it again.
- Hmm.
[engine starting]
- Come on, get in the car!
- No, no, no, no!
[gun firing]
[grunting]
Ugh!
[retching]
- [Quiet] Fucking holy men!
- [John Doe]
Goddamn [indistinct].
[grunting]
- I can't believe some fucking
holy men stole our...
- What the fuck
did you do?
- John.
- Fuck.
♪♪
- Okay, we've been
walking for an hour
and you haven't said shit.
I don't know what else
to say, John.
I fucked up.
If you want to focus on
being mad, then... go ahead.
I guess we'll just
walk until we die.
♪♪
- This isn't the first time
I lost Evelyn.
Vultures took her one time,
Necros another time.
- Oh, shit!
- One time I just forgot
where I parked her.
- Okay, well, that's stupid.
- Yeah, it's stupid,
but every time I've lost her,
she's come back to me.
- Then let me help you
find her this time.
Please.
- Fine.
[church bell ringing]
- [Quiet] Wait, wait!
Where you going?
- I'm following the bells.
That's where Evelyn is.
- We can't just waltz into
a holy man murder-palooza.
You saw what those fuckers did
to the convoy's milkman.
- Evelyn is so close.
We need to go get her back.
And I can't
do it by myself.
So, what do
you say, partner?
- Okay.
Let's go get your car.
- Great.
- What?
- We've gotta go get
those masks off
those holy men we killed
so we can blend in.
- Isn't that like
an hour that way?
I'm just gonna wait here.
Did you hear me?
He didn't hear me.
- Please, please.
Ugh!
[stomach rumbling]
Stomach, shut up!
♪♪
[grunting]
[groaning]
Oh...
♪♪
[groaning]
[gasping]
Oh.
Nasty!
Excuse me, sir.
[engine sputters]
Too bad.
TP, beans...
whoa!
Jackpot!
♪♪
[church bell ringing]
- Sounds like this is it.
- I don't love
how moist this mask is.
- At least your guy
didn't have a beard.
I'm gonna be pullin' face pubes
out of my mouth all night.
- Ick!
- Also, we gotta work
on your dude voice.
- Dude voice?
- Yeah.
Holy men.
You gotta fit in.
Go deep,
let me hear it.
- Um...
I love killing
and guns, I do.
- Just try not to talk.
- Right-o, governor!
[church bell ringing]
[hootin' and hollerin']
- [Holy Man 1]
I'm gonna kill you.
- Well, I'm gonna kill you.
Let's do it.
- Cool party, huh?
- Dinner for the sinner!
[chuckling]
- Holy shit!
How are these guys
not dead already?
- Stop staring.
Just blend in.
- My man!
- I want that!
- Too fuckin' bad!
- From one brother to another,
I propose a clash.
[chuckles]
- Let it begin!
[grunting]
- At least they're
having a good time.
- Uh, he's not.
- Holy shit!
Maybe he deserved it.
- I didn't.
- Cool. I hate this place.
- [Goddess Janice]
Kiss my leather!
[yelping]
- [Holy Man] We worship you!
- [Janice] Bend down.
[yelping]
- Okay, Evelyn
has to be here.
So, just blend in
with these freaks
until we find her.
- Damn, very flexible.
Oh, shit!
Uh, uh...
Oh, bullocks.
- Who told you to speak?
- Agh!
- You like pain?
- I love it so much,
me lady!
- Damn.
- Good.
- Ow.
- The Goddess is pleased.
[groaning]
Cupbearer?
- [Cupbearer] Yes, Goddess?
- Bring forth libations.
- Here.
It's chug-a-lug time!
- All chanting:
Chug-a-lug!
Chug-a-lug! Chug-a-lug!
[sighing]
[gagging]
- Nothing like
a Jack and coke.
- So, wait, why is
it crunchy?
- That'd be the coke.
[laughing]
- It's Preacher.
- The preacher's here.
[hootin' and hollerin']
- [Holy Man]
I love you, preacher.
- [Holy Man] Absolve my sins!
- I think the coke
is kicking in.
- I can't feel my throat.
- I'm gonna shit myself.
[groaning]
- [Preacher] Night, night.
[laughing]
Which one of you
blessed fucks
had seven days
in the death pool?
Blessings on you, Krevin!
[chuckles]
Victory runs
in your veins.
Go on, reward him!
- Here you go.
- [Preacher] Okay.
- Enjoy.
- Gods and Goddesses,
it is my honor
to be with you again
here in Colorado
for our annual pilgrimage,
The Rocky Mountain
Fuck Fest!
[laughing, cheering]
Now, while we are indulging
in the seven deadly delights,
let us recall
our past
and celebrate
our futures!
Me? I was a man of God.
Shit, I was even celibate.
[laughing]
Shut the fuck up, Krevin.
- Oh, okay.
- But when the world ended,
God was nowhere
to be found.
And I thought, huh!
This fucker's forsaken us.
Right? But then
I realized, no!
We are the gods!
Always have been,
always will be.
[hootin' and hollerin']
And the roads will be
forever our domain!
[cheering]
[laughter]
- Great crowd work.
- I can hear you
grinding your teeth.
- Dude, that's you!
[laughing]
- Now...
what gifts did you
motherfuckers bring me?
Ooh, is that
a generator I see?
Okay.
Uh, gasoline, got it.
Okay, guns.
Guns, drugs.
Okay, guys, you gotta get
more creative than just drugs.
- Here you go, Preacher.
- Okay, that's just
more drugs, Jeff.
That's just more drugs.
[Evelyn approaching]
Well, now everybody
shut the fuck up!
Hold on! Oh-ho-ho!
Holy shit!
- Hey, what are you doing?
Where are you going?
John!
- A token for you, Preacher.
- What a hot
piece of ass!
Ooh-ooh-ooh.
[inhales deeply]
I should lube up
with oil
and dick your muffler.
- [Holy Men] Dick her muff!
Dick her muff!
- Don't touch her!
- Who spoke?
[chuckling]
Your tone sounded...
envious.
I like that.
You want her, don't you?
- Say no. Say no.
Say no. Say no.
- From one brother
to another,
I propose a clash.
[exasperated groan]
- Oh, yeah.
[chuckling]
[collective chatter]
- Are you ready, son?
[chuckling]
[sniffling]
- So, what's your plan
here, stud?
- Have you seen this guy?
A strong wind
can blow him over.
I'm gonna kick his ass so bad
I'm gonna be their king.
- That's the blow talking!
[screaming]
Oh, God!
[laughing]
Oof, Coke Jesus
has a right hook!
- I heard something crack.
I think it was my brain.
- Listen up, he's fast,
so keep your distance.
You'll never get a good hit in
if you're too close.
Honestly...
- I told you I got this.
Hit me.
- [Quiet] What? John?
Fine, you're on your own.
[laughter]
- [Preacher] Let's eat this guy!
- Surprise!
- Ah, my eyes!
[grunting, groaning]
- [Holy Men] Ooh!
- Stay the fuck down,
Preach!
[laughing]
- Whoo!
You ever drink
your own blood?
It's intoxicating.
- What the f... Oh!
[manic laughter]
Are you possessed?
- I was once.
By a little demon baby.
Fucker made me kill
a whole church of people.
Here we go!
I can still hear
their screams.
I can't wait
to hear yours!
[grunting, groaning]
I can't stop kicking!
- He's doing really well.
- Heh...
[electricity crackling]
- [Preacher] The Holy Ghost
lives through me.
What should I do?
Should I eat this guy?
Should I fuck this guy?
[grunting]
Dirt nap!
[whistles]
- Get on your knees,
you greasy little piglet
and lick
my soiled boots.
- Oh! Yes, goddess.
Please, goddess.
[whimpering]
- Now, where are the keys
to that car, vermin?
I wanna take it
for a ride.
- Wait! Goddesses
only ride shotgun.
That is our way.
- Not my way!
[groaning]
- Yes, please!
[screaming]
- Oh, where are you going?
[grunting]
[manic laughter]
[grunting, groaning]
[grunting]
[cheers, manic laughter]
Yes! Yes!
[laughter]
Take him to the cross!
Oh, come on, guys!
I've got a guy here
perfectly ready
for the cross.
Meanwhile, this dead fucker
is still up there!
[sighs]
Say it with me.
- When the heart stops,
the body drops.
- See? It's not
that hard. Okay?
Now the whole vibe
is ruined.
I-I guess take the new guy
to timeout
and-and take
that fucker down.
- Don't let it
ruin your night!
- Too late, Janice!
[groaning]
[tree limbs snapping]
- Huh?
Come out!
I heard you!
- Hey!
Hey, whoa!
Take it easy, okay?
I-I'm just looking
for some food.
You haven't got any,
do you?
- Go away, butthead!
- Whoa, I'm not
gonna hurt you.
- I said go away!
- Fuck!
Ugh, what the hell
did you do that for?
Got me right in
the veneers.
- I'm sorry, I was aiming
for your balls.
- Well, that would
have hurt, too.
But that's okay.
You can make it up to me.
- Huh?
- 'Cause it's dinnertime.
He's alone!
Soo-ey!
[whooping]
- Dinner time!
Child back on
the menu, boys.
- I love veal!
- We're gonna getcha.
- Please, please,
please, please!
Come on!
[engine starts]
- Hey there!
[engine revs]
- Fuck you!
- [Preacher] Krevin,
you're a fucking dunce!
This fuckin' idiot
can't even get a hose
long enough to fill up
my new baby.
- Dented Evelyn's hood,
you asshole.
- [Quiet] So, you lost, huh?
- You don't know that.
This could be
a winner's cage.
- Pssh.
I got us some wheels.
Piece of shit,
but it'll get us out
of this nightmare carnival.
- I'm not leaving her.
- What?
John, are you kidding?
You almost died!
I can't believe
I have to say this,
but it's just
a car, John.
- You don't get it.
- [Quiet] No, I don't!
But I fought and bled.
I got whipped,
I drank coke for you.
And your car.
And now you say
I don't get it?
Fuck you!
What happened to us
being partners, huh?
- I'm not leaving Evelyn.
- And I'm not dying
for a fucking car.
- [Krevin] Preacher, Preacher!
Someone attacked Fenchy
and took a car!
- What? Seal the camp!
- [Holy Man] Seal the camp!
[indistinct commotion]
- We have to leave.
[church bell ringing]
Now, John!
- Then go.
- [Young John] All right,
where to next?
We can go
anywhere you want.
Your choice.
[engine dies]
Or not.
♪♪
I owe you for saving me
back there.
I'll fix you up,
I promise.
Just you, me,
and the road.
Sounds good?
♪♪
- Oh, thank God.
I'm here, Evelyn, baby.
Let's get the hell
out of here.
[gun cocks]
- I admire your thirst.
But if anybody's
gonna fuck this car,
it's gonna be me.
[grunting, groaning]
♪♪
You're not worthy
of the mask.
- Good, it chafes.
[laughing]
- For I am
the angel of death!
And I release you!
[gasps]
- No.
No, no, no.
Fuck. Fuck!
♪♪
- Hurry up!
Watch the Preacher's head.
Don't lose those!
That's the last of us.
Drive, prick!
- Yes, goddess.
♪♪
- Oh!
Oh, shit!
Oh, oh, my head.
No.
["My Immortal"
by Evanescence playing]
♪♪
♪ If you have to leave ♪
♪ I wish that
you would just leave ♪
♪ 'Cause your presence
still lingers here ♪
♪ And it won't
leave me alone ♪
♪ These wounds
won't seem to heal ♪
♪ This pain
is just too real ♪
♪ There's just too much
that time cannot erase ♪
♪ When you cried I'd wipe away
all of your tears ♪
♪ When you'd scream I'd
fight away all of your fears ♪
♪ And I held your hand
through all of these years ♪
♪ But you still have ♪
♪ All of me ♪
♪♪
♪ You used to
captivate me ♪
♪ By your
resonating light ♪
♪ Now I'm bound by the life
you left behind ♪
♪ Your face it holds ♪
♪ My once plans
and dreams ♪
♪ Your voice
it chased away ♪
♪ All the sanity
in me ♪
♪ These wounds
won't seem to heal ♪
♪ This pain
is just too real ♪
♪ There's just too much
that time cannot erase ♪
♪ When your cried I'd wipe away
all of your tears ♪
♪ When you'd scream ♪
♪ I'd fight away
all of your fears ♪
♪ You still have ♪
♪ All of me ♪
♪ Ah me ♪
♪ Ah me ah ♪
♪♪