♪♪
[announcer]
- All right, everybody!
Who's ready for
"Billy & 2 Scoops?"
[cheers and applause]
[assistant director]
- Stand by for first team.
♪♪
- I don't get it.
The show has always
been called "2 Scoops."
They can't just add Billy
to the title for no reason.
- Marcus, honey,
they have a great reason.
Everyone loves Billy!
- I know I do.
- But I'm the lead.
So what?
Billy gets a few laughs.
Now, he's the next Urkel?
I mean, even Billy's fanclub
is twice the size of mine.
- Well, he's twice as funny.
[laughs]
- Stop it.
Your dad is so bad.
- Well, at least
he's not my real dad.
- You know, you should thank
your lucky stars for that.
Hmm?
You'd still be living
in a taxi cab
if your unhinged father
didn't go to jail.
Go, take your mark.
[assistant director]
- All right.
We're gettin' ready to go.
[bell ringing]
[announcer]
- All right, gang,
we've got
a great show for you today.
We hope you all...
[indistinct chatter]
- Okay, here we go.
Ready, three, two, one.
[applause]
- Mmm.
- Lenny Scoops, you slow down!
You'll hurt your tummy.
- Oh, yeah?
Tell that to my sweet tooth!
[sparse laughter]
- We have to open
the ice cream store.
I wonder what's taking
Billy so long?
[toilet flushing]
[laughter]
- He's so cute!
[laughter, applause]
[Meemaw]
- Marcus!
[dog barks]
Marcus, it's your line.
Oh!
- Oh, my fucking God!
Holy shit!
[screaming]
- Who's a good boy
now, Billy?
[screaming]
- God! Oh, shit!
Line?
- Hello?
Anybody in there?
How the hell am I supposed
to pick up this package?
- Cross the moat.
- Hell no! You go.
- Uh, that water
is gross as fuck.
I'm not swimming
in that toilet river.
- This doesn't
make any sense.
- I'm gonna throw
a rock at it.
- Oh, great idea, genius.
[grunts]
[elevator dings]
Don't you say it.
Um...
- Oh!
- Right here.
- I... I told you so.
[creepy voice]
- This way.
- The fuck?
Where are you goin'?
- You heard the creepy
disembodied voice.
"This way."
Come on, coward.
[creepy voice]
- Getting warmer.
[laughing]
- Now he's giggling.
I can't believe
you're enjoying this.
- Oh, come on.
It's like a haunted house.
The smoke, the creepy lighting.
I'm half expecting
a vampire to just pop out
of the smoke and say...
[creepy voice]
- Hello.
[screaming]
- God... Oh, my God.
You got me, man.
[laughing]
Oh, please tell me
you live down here.
[laughing]
[creepy voice]
- Oh, no.
I don't live down here.
[gasping]
- Twist!
- I don't have time
for this tomfoolery.
Show yourself.
[creepy voice]
- Why would I reveal my face?
You see,
there's power in anonymity.
- Wait a minute.
Are you Calypso?
[Calypso]
- What?
- I read that name everywhere.
"Believe in Calypso."
"Calypso is real."
- Yeah! Are you him?
[creepy laughter]
- I guess that means yes.
- Huh.
[buzzer]
- Secret compartment.
Choice.
- Hey, Calypso, I usually
get a supply bump
when picking up deliveries.
We need gas, man.
[Calypso]
- The package
is what you've earned.
No more, no less,
no free handouts.
- Well, can we at least
get a peek inside?
- Or a deep dish
for the road?
- What are you gonna
do with a dish?
- It's not a dish, dummy.
It's a pizza.
Oh, my God.
Have you never had pizza?
Oh, we have to try it.
It's like, uh...
imagine a wheel
made of bread and cheese.
- Oh, fuck. I want that.
- Yeah, we want that.
[Calypso]
- You have what you need.
Now, get.
Take it back to Raven
like a good milkman.
Your San Francisco treat awaits.
Ding ding.
- This is really well done.
[Calypso]
- Thank you.
Oh, and John, may all
your wishes come true.
[laughs]
- I mean, I gotta hand it
to that Calypso guy.
What a showman.
Do you think that steam
was actually coming
from the pipes,
or do you think
it was dry ice
that he filtered in
for ambiance.
- I'm more concerned
with making it
to New San Francisco
in one piece.
[brakes squeal]
- Just let me take the wheel.
- I got it. See?
We can't go back the way
we came after Topeka,
so now we're gonna have to go
north and hook back around.
[laughs]
There's a Pits.
- Cool.
That sounds awesome.
Should we stop
at the Taints after?
- Funny.
It's an old milkman pitstop.
You stop off, share intel
on delivery routes,
gas up, maybe get some chow.
Shit, maybe even a shower.
- Uh, why the fuck didn't
we stop by one sooner?
- Well, 'cause there are
only two of them left.
They have very strict
ground rules.
Rule one...
don't talk about your job.
No one cares
what you're moving,
but what you're getting paid...
that's a different story,
so we leave it at the door.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Rule two...
no weapons allowed.
- Anything can be a weapon.
I stabbed you with a pen.
What about your hands?
You can strangle, pummel.
You can thumb-fuck the eyes.
- Your hands aren't that strong.
- They seem pretty strong to me.
- I'll pull over.
- Why would you do that?
We're on a schedule.
- Woah! Oh, got it. Oh...
[chuckling]
[tires screech]
[Roberts]
- Roberts for Agent Stone.
Come in Agent Stone.
- Go for Stone.
[Roberts]
- Agent Stone, sir, it's...
- Look, this better be about
the mute and the milkman.
[Roberts]
- Sir, it's the clown.
Sweet Tooth hit
our Colorado outpost,
just like Utah
and the dam.
He killed everyone and took
the prisoners with him.
[sighing]
- Fuck! Ah! Ugh!
No. Oh, no.
[Roberts]
- Also, not urgent,
but there was a small snafu
at the motor pool.
Minor collision,
Jamie and I are fine but...
[Jamie]
- Shut up, he doesn't
want to hear it.
[Roberts]
- You don't know that.
[Jamie]
- Uh, sir, everything's fine.
- Listen.
Nevada, Utah, Colorado.
These are not just
random attacks.
That smiley faced son of a bitch
is going somewhere.
♪♪
- Now, don't go asking
for different drink flavors.
You get what you get,
and you don't get upset.
So, eat up
and take your shits.
Maybe play some
pick-up basketball.
No snack for you.
You're with me.
Come on.
- Sure.
- Harold!
You're in charge.
- Uh, everything okay?
- Ah, sweet of you to ask.
Look at my fan club.
Growing every day.
But not everybody
believed in me.
We didn't just stop here
for poops and hoops.
We're here
for something important.
- What?
- Closure.
[growling]
- Ow! Steering wheel. Ugh.
- Evelyn leave a love mark?
She likes to play rough.
- She's not a real girl, John.
- I know.
- So, this is where
the milkmen hang out.
Wow, it really is the pits.
All right,
let's divide and conquer.
- My thoughts exactly.
I bless you
an honorary milkman.
You gas up, I supply up.
Hey.
- Hey piss flaps,
I was next.
[growling]
- At least get a girl off
before treating her like shit.
- I outta choke you.
- Ooh, promise?
[laughting]
[grunts]
Bye, Grady.
[chuckles]
He's got nothing.
Tiny little penis.
You're up.
- Thanks.
I thought, uh, weapons
weren't allowed.
[gasps]
- Oops!
♪♪
I haven't seen you
around here.
Are you taking over
a territory?
- Oh, no.
I'm here with...
- Johnny?
- Mary?
- Oh, my God.
- Hmm.
- Hi.
[groans]
You left me for dead,
asshole!
- I thought you were dead,
- I guess you two
know each other?
- What...
wait-wait-wait-wait.
You're with this
son of a bitch?
[laughing]
How clenched do you think
his butthole is right now?
- Oh, I'm gonna guess
it's pretty tight.
- Mm-hm, like a teeny
tiny starfish.
Did you miss me?
♪♪
So seven shots in,
Johnny bets me he can
surf his car.
[scoffing]
We go out in the parking lot.
He gets Evelyn to 60.
And as he climbs
through the window, bam!
His ass ragdolls
on the concrete.
[laughing]
Just blood pouring
out of his head.
- [Quiet]
It's so funny,
because he told me
that he got that scar
from a seven-on-one
vulture car chase.
- That's how I got
the other scar.
- Mm-hm.
- Uh-huh.
So, how did you two meet?
- My mother,
may she rest in peace,
ran one of the first pits
in sunny San Juan Capistrano.
When she croaked,
I took over
and Johnny would pass
through to, um...
what'cha call it?
Drain your tank?
Fill her up.
Nuzzle the guzzle.
- [Quiet]
C'mon, man.
- Then a gang of burnouts
torched the place.
A blessing in disguise,
honestly.
I would've done anything to get
the hell out of there.
Johnny knows.
- I heard about the fire.
- And you didn't
come back for me?
- They said nobody survived.
- Well this bitch did.
Luckily, I knew a place
in a church
where no one
could find me.
- The bell tower?
Oh, my God.
I haven't thought about
that place in ages.
All the bird shit!
- The bird shit!
[laughing]
Of course that's
what you remember.
We made love there.
- So now you're a milkman.
- Mm-hm.
No thanks to you.
I always wanted
to be a milkman,
but no one
took me seriously.
Ain't that right,
Johnny?
So what's
your story, hm?
No way
you're driving cars.
I mean, that ass
is way too perky.
- I'm from the OC where
they cut off body parts
and wear them
like jewelry.
- Sounds fun.
Never leave
a woman's glass empty.
Shots on Johnny!
[pounding]
[cheering]
- Yeah, lucky me.
Okay, Quiet.
Look, about Mary...
- Oh my gosh, you weren't
a virgin when I met you?
I could give two soggy dumps
about your ex.
You're dicking around.
We're on a schedule.
- Dicking around?
Before you came up,
I found out
there was a vultures nest
a few clicks from here
that we definitely
would have driven into.
I say we butter up
these milkmen
with a few buttery nips.
Get what intel we can
and get the hell out of here.
- Okay fine.
One more drink.
- Yeah.
Hey, hey, hey!
[cheering]
All right!
Whoa!
- Bloody Mary's a character,
isn't she?
- Bloody Mary, really?
- [Mr. Slam]
Hey, you're laughing,
but she's made
more runs than anyone.
She'll wipe out
a whole vultures nest
just for craps
and cackles.
[cheering]
Nicknames
mean a lot out here.
We all got one.
Pizza Boy,
Petunia,
Pit Viper.
- Well, I can't wait
to hear yours.
- They call me
Mr. Slam.
- Why?
- 'Cause I can crush anything
with my massive penis.
- Sorry.
[laughing]
[door slams]
You have a shower here?
- Out back.
We got everything
to take the road ass
right off of you.
Here.
For your nooks
and crannies.
- Mr. Slam, don't you worry
about my crannies.
- [Pizza Boy] Pizza, baby!
- [Petunia] Pizza, baby.
- Pizza.
- I'm Pizza guy.
- Yeah. People love pizza.
You never lose.
- You never trust a guy
that wears a jacket inside.
- [Pizza Boy] Yeah,
you fuckin' hang up on him.
- You know,
my parents sent me here
because I got in a disagreement
with my co-star.
Well, actually, they sent me
to the kiddy ward.
And then I moved to
the juvie wellness center.
Oh, and then finally
got bumped up to Blackfield
after I murdered
my roommate.
Trust me, that guy
was a psychopath.
- What did he do?
- He thought Chris Kirkpatrick
was the best member of NSYNC.
Are you nuts?
But this... this is where
I grew up.
It was hard at first.
Nobody came to see me.
Not even my parents.
They said they would,
but they lied!
[echoes]
- You felt alone.
I get it.
- Don't make this
about you, Stuart.
It's unbecoming.
- Sorry.
[groaning]
- Then I got to know
the guys in here.
And guess what?
They were just like me.
Yeah.
Blackfield was
the best ten years
of my 25-to-life.
Hold onto your butt crack.
We're going in.
Home, sweet home.
[sniffs]
Huh, still smells
the same.
♪♪
- Your co-star was a dog?
- Fuck Billy,
that son of a bitch!
Uh, sorry, Mommy.
I-I didn't mean to swear.
Stu, meet my mommy.
Mommy, meet my Stu.
Hi, Wesley.
That's right.
I still won't
call you dad.
- You-you locked
your parents in here.
- I wrote.
I tried calling.
They ignored me.
They always ignored me.
So when the world ended
and the cell block opened up,
I tracked them down
and I left them
in here to rot,
just like they left me!
- You, uh, you got
their attention now.
- Yeah, I do.
Mommy, Wesley,
I never wanted to try out
for that sitcom.
I was perfectly happy
doing summer stock
in the Berkshires.
But you needed
a Lexus!
You were my parents.
You were supposed
to be my biggest fans!
And you know what?
I don't need
you assholes,
because I have found
my people.
And those guys
out there?
They love me for me!
[screams]
- It's okay.
- I don't need you!
[growling]
[panting]
And that concludes
our tour!
♪♪
- Ooh, I'd kill
for those areolas.
Bump?
- Uh, nah.
- All right.
[sniffs]
Ah.
I know that brand.
You lost a finger and you got
the law on your ass?
Are you crazy
or just unlucky?
- Bit of both, I guess.
- Me too.
Check it.
- You got those from law?
- A few of them.
Mostly from being
a pedestrian.
After the fire,
I had to start fresh.
I got this one from playing
possum with some butchers.
Between you and me,
grilled dude
tastes not that bad.
- Hey,
you're on my shit.
- Oops.
So what's it like
driving with Johnny?
Is it as wet and wild
as he always said
it would be?
[scoffing]
- He would say wet and wild.
Riding with John
is mostly irritating.
I'm sure
I'll get used to it.
It's only been
a couple days.
- You just met and you're
already goin' on rides?
[chuckling]
- I mean, just this one job.
[sighs]
- [Mary] Well, must be nice.
Johnny always said
it would be too dangerous
for me to ride with him.
Milkman have
an expiration date,
blah, blah, blah.
Guess I had to
figure it out for myself.
- Listen, I wouldn't
read too much into it.
It's not like he lets me
drive his car.
- Of course not.
But I see the way
he looks at you.
He likes you.
Like, like likes you.
But he will never
pick you over that car.
Evelyn is
his ride or die.
Till death do they part.
But what do I know?
[laughing]
Maybe he likes you
behind the wheel.
Or the wheel behind you.
- Naptime's over, fuck-os!
Time to go...
♪♪
No! Harold,
why did you kill everybody?
♪♪
- Oh, shit.
Get down!
[gun firing]
[yelping]
- {Carl] It's gonna be maggot
Thanksgiving down there.
- That's a good one, Carl.
Jamie, you and your brother,
back with me to base.
Mike, get another guy.
Double taps on everybody,
collect their weapons.
- Uh-huh.
- And grab the clown's mask.
I want it for my wall.
Let's go.
♪♪
- [John Doe] Come on, Ev,
drink up.
Damn, running water
always makes me have to go.
[grunting]
Oh fuck, Mare!
Do you mind?
- No.
[urine trickling]
So Johnny,
what brings you out east?
- Pfft! Are you serious?
- [Mary] Yeah.
- I mean, come on!
My job!
You know I can't
give you the deets.
- Your job.
[laughing]
John Doe would never
leave California.
It gets too cold,
and he doesn't
like goosepimples.
- Maybe it's
a really good job.
- Oh!
- Ooohh!
- Maybe that's why
you need a partner.
- No, okay, it's not
like I recruited her.
She kinda just
fell in my lap.
- Mmm.
- I didn't mean like that.
Look, Quiet saved my ass.
If it wasn't for her,
I'd be road sauce right now.
- Oh, I mean, I've been
doin' it alone for a while.
I seem to be doin' fine.
[scoffing]
Oh.
Unless you're gettin' soft.
- Soft...
Oh, okay.
- Yeah, gettin' soft.
- Well, good thing
it's my last run.
It's gettin' cold out here.
I'm gonna head in.
- Your last run?
- Huh?
- Come on,
you can tell me.
You used to tell me
all kinds of crazy shit.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Okay?
And I told you shit, too.
- Well, let's just say
I'm gonna get
what I always wanted.
- No.
[pops lips]
Inside?
- Mmm, oh!
- [Quiet] Hey John!
- Yo!
- Thought you'd wanna know,
Mistress Lane's
about to perform.
- I do not wanna miss that!
[door closing]
After the show, I gotta
get back on the road.
- Uh-huh.
- Because
New San Francisco awaits.
- John... John!
[chuckling]
Are you serious?
- Jello, Mare!
♪♪
[John Doe] Oh, shit!
Oh, I'm good!
- Y'all in the front row,
you're gonna get wet!
- So, how's the car?
- She's good, gassed up,
and ready to go.
You smell like fresh forest,
like camping.
- Oh! You're drunk.
- You're drunk!!
And also...
I'm drunk.
[crowd chanting]
- [all] Slam! Slam! Slam!
- Slam! Slam! Slam! Slam!
- Slam? Slam?
- Y'all ready to see
this watermelon explode?
Hell yeah!
- Slam!
[chanting "slam!" continues]
Slam! Slam! Slam!
- Shh! Shut the fuck up!
- Oh.
[chuckling]
Gee, Johnny,
looks like word got out
about your package.
Guess you're not
the only one
trying to get inside
New San Francisco, huh?
- You couldn't have
waited one minute?!
- You told them about
New San Francisco?
What the hell happened
to rule number one?
- This is why we have
rule number two!
♪♪
- I told you that was
a fuckin' stupid-ass rule!
- All right, fine!
Okay, there's
no need for violence.
I'll give you the package.
But who do
I give it to, huh?
Give it to you?
How about you?
Don't tell me you haven't
discussed amongst yourselves
who's gonna get it.
[laughing]
Getting in is
a pretty big prize.
- Slam!
[grunting, groaning]
[glass shattering]
- Quiet!
[grunting]
♪♪
- John!
[grunting, groaning]
[sinister laughter]
- Careful, you might
nick yourself.
- Not fuckin' likely.
[grunting]
♪♪
- What the hell is
this jacket made of?
♪♪
[grunting]
[panting]
[groaning]
[giggling]
- Is this just me,
or is this kinda hot?
- It's kinda hot.
- Yeah. Do it.
Fuckin' do it.
Gimme another scar.
Add it to the fucking pile!
[weakly chuckling]
I would have followed
that milkman anywhere.
All he had to do was say
"Come with me," but he didn't!
Okay, I suffered
because of him.
So fuck him if he thinks
he can waltz into a better life!
[panting]
- Here's a little
free advice.
Don't let revenge
ruin a second chance.
♪♪
[grunting]
- Behind you!
[groaning]
[laughing]
[thudding]
[panting]
Goddamn, Mary.
♪♪
- Hey, Slam!
Nice dong moves.
♪♪
[groaning]
[gun firing]
♪♪
- Stu! Stu!
[sniffling]
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to, man.
[gasping]
Holy shit! Shit!
I thought
I killed you, man.
- You tried to kill me?!
- Uh, no?
- [man] No! No, no, no!
- [Sweet Tooth] Who did this?!
Answer me!
Those were my people!
My fans!
[bones cracking]
Oops.
- Fuck-Fuckin' Stone!
It was Stone!
Stone did this, man!
[gagging]
Please! Please! Please!
I can help!
I know where Stone is!
[gagging]
- Wait! Stone hurt you.
He can help
hurt him back.
[gasping, coughing]
- You want a pet?
Fine.
But you clean up after him.
'Cause we all know
what I do...
to naughty dogs.
[grunts]
- Here...
You drive.
At least till
I sober up.
[engine starting]
♪♪
- [Stone] They're going
to New San Francisco.
Huh, interesting.
You guys ever shoot
trout in a barrel?
The fun part isn't
actually shooting them.
It's trapping them
in the barrel.
Boy howdy...
do I love a good trap.
♪♪