♪♪
- [Sweet Tooth]
And that, my friend,
is why I wipe
back to front.
Puppy wanna help?
[electricity crackling]
[yelping]
- Yes! Yes!
Yes, puppy wanna help!
Puppy wanna help!
- Yeah, that's a good bitch.
[grunting]
- Did you kill
all these guys?
- Yeah. I mean,
he did most of it.
- Hey, now, you nicked
that nerdy one over there
in the thigh meat.
Probably hit an artery.
Granted, I had
to finish him off,
but I mean,
all that wailing.
I mean, drama queen!
Yeah.
Hey, don't worry.
You'll get there. I know it.
- Yeah.
- Here, catch!
[winces]
There's a good boy.
Hoo-hoo!
Now load up the rest.
- Please, just let me go.
I-I told you everything
that I know about Stone.
- Bad doggy! No speak!
[whimpering]
Ah, I'm out of ammo.
Gotta fill this up.
You keep an eye on him.
- You know that psychopath's
not your friend, right?
- Oh, and you are?
You sold me out to Stone
for a pat on the head.
You couldn't give
two fucks about me.
- I give more than
two fucks about you!
I'm so sorry, Stu,
but I was wrong,
and you are wrong
about that clown.
He's gonna kill
a lot of people,
maybe even us.
- No, he's not Stone.
Sweet Tooth listens to me.
We're "S" brothers.
Both of our names
start with "S."
- Oh, my god.
- Look, it-it's like
a bonding thing.
- Stu, I've known you since
we were chucking crayons
at Carter Delauro's head
in second grade.
This isn't you.
[grunting]
- Shut the fuck up.
Load up those bombs.
- Ah, I dropped a few
kidney stones in there.
I gotta drink
more water.
Something wrong, boys?
- Nope.
We're just talkin'
about shootin' stuff
and killing things.
- And-and tits.
- Titties.
- Well, my plan has two out
of three of those things,
unless the tits
are ours.
- You know,
Stone thinks we're dead.
We could go
anywhere in the world
if we want to
right now.
What if we, I don't know,
start over maybe?
- Nah. I got
a better idea.
Oh, you look phenomenal,
like chips off the old block.
Harold, open wide!
Stubert, would you
do the honors?
♪♪
- You're an idiot,
John Doe.
- Where the hell even am I
on this map?
Is that a vagina?
[gasps]
[tires squealing]
Ah, fuck.
Fuck you, doe!
- [John Doe]
Where is this package?
Shit.
Goddamn it, Quiet.
Aw, fuck me.
Come on,
you piece of shit.
I know you got some juice.
Come on.
[engine sputters]
Come on. God damn it.
[radio static]
[grunting]
- What am I doing?
What the fuck
am I doing?!
[sighs]
Partners, my ass.
What's the next move?
I just show up in San Francisco
and knock on the gate
and be like,
"Hey, what's up?
"Remember that dillweed
you hired to do that thing?
"Well, he died
in a fiery explosion,
"but I'm here."
Fuck!
[tires squealing]
Go ahead, asshole!
Easiest kill of your life!
- Uh, you okay?
- Do I look okay?!
- Damn, that milkman
did you wrong.
It just goes to show,
you never know where
you stand with someone
'til push comes
to shove.
Reminds me
of my ex, Tasha.
The two of us
used to love jackin' people,
scavenging,
having fun.
We were thick
as thieves.
- It sounds like
you were just thieves.
- Yeah. Then she left me
for her true love.
- Mm, John had
someone else, too.
- Oh, let me guess.
Blonde, huge cans,
curves in all
the right places,
and a big old donk,
firm yet pillowy
at the same time?
- That's very specific,
Mark, but no.
It was a 2002 Subaru.
- Kinky.
Not that I'm judging,
seeing as how Tasha
left me for meth.
Loved that beautiful blue
crystal so much it killed her.
Now she's up in heaven doing
angel dust with baby Jesus.
Our nest broke up
not soon after.
- I'm sorry.
Um, you know, since
we're being honest,
that whole vulture nest thing
is really fuckin' dumb.
- Do you think I like wearing
tires in my spare time?
No. It's impractical
as all hell,
but if you wanna be a vulture,
you gotta stick to the theme.
- Mm.
- And me?
I'm a vulture,
through and through.
- Come on, Mark,
I thought we were bonding.
- Yes, we shared a moment,
and it was lovely.
You're a great person,
but that's not gonna stop me
from taking that fancy backpack
you're so keen on.
I know it's worth
something.
So hand it over.
- Fine, you want it?
Go get it.
- Now that's
just childish.
[squelching]
- Tasha,
I'm comin', baby.
[horn blaring]
- Need a lift?
[giggling]
[engine revving]
- How'd you know
I was out here?
- We didn't.
- Here.
These'll help.
- Hey. I'm so happy
I could find you.
I figured
you'd follow the map.
Sorry for everything
I put you through out there.
I made a mistake.
- Where's Evelyn?
- She didn't make it.
- Cool. So it was
worth it then.
- One is squirrel,
one is opossum.
Didn't know which one
you preferred, so...
Figure we could do
a taste test.
Talked to the chef.
He said the opossum
is real tender today.
He likes to take
herbs and spices
and stuff 'em
in the gut pouch.
[smacks lips]
[clatters]
- Goddamn, Quiet, don't do that.
Squirrels
don't grow on trees.
I mean, they do kinda,
but still gotta hunt 'em,
and they're hard
little fuckers to hit.
So I got good news
and bad news.
What do you want first?
- Good news.
- Bad news.
- Okay, glad to see you're
both on the same page.
I'm a glass-half-empty gal,
so let's start with bad.
Stone's men fell back
to the dam
ever since the clown
took out his bases.
- Sweet Tooth?
He still kicking around?
- He's got Stone
all hot and bothered.
He basically just pissed
in a hornet's nest.
So getting to New San Francisco
through the dam,
it ain't gonna work.
But now the good news,
I heard tell
of another way through.
There's a hole
in Stone's blockade.
It's a night's drive
from here.
I mean,
the lawmen on the road,
they're not gonna make
your trip any easier,
but at least
you won't be walking
right into
Stone's kitchen.
And we can get you close,
but after that
I'm taking the convoy north.
We don't want
any part in this fight.
So if you want
to get through,
you're gonna need
one motherfucker of a car.
- It sounds like we have
our work cut out for us.
- So there's a we now.
Get this straight.
The only reason
I haven't thrown you
out of the back
of this fucking rig
is because
I want inside.
I want a new life,
a life where I don't have to
look at your fucking face
every goddamn minute.
- My grandfather
was a rancher.
Cattle.
He had a huge herd,
hundreds of animals.
Cattle, they're delicious,
of course.
Cheeseburgers,
whatnot.
But you know
what else they are?
They're dumb.
If you leave
a gate open,
these stupid assholes
will just wander through,
eat your crops,
destroy property,
shit all over
the place.
Hell, they'll even
shit on each other.
[laughing]
Like I said, dumb.
Like Carl!
But my grandfather
also had dogs,
strong, proud, fierce.
A dog can control
these beasts,
move 'em from pasture
to pasture.
A stray runaway,
they bring that stray back.
They were
in control.
Now we have strays
in our herd.
The mute, the milkman,
they defy us!
This is our land!
These are our roads!
We're the dogs;
we control the herd!
We will never go back
to the way things were.
Never!
Am I right?
[cheering]
[wincing]
Bababooey.
- Don't worry, baby,
you're in good hands.
Thankfully,
this isn't my first time.
I just need to check
your eyeballs, okay?
- Come on,
you stupid motherfucker.
[scoffs]
Oh, Tasha.
I bet you hated
all these fucking songs.
I'm so sorry.
[horn honking]
[groans]
[clatters]
- Can you grab that
for me?
- You have hands.
- Yeah, and both of 'em are
deep in this car's guts.
So can you just pass it
to me, please?
- I would love to.
- Goddamn it!
I said I'm sorry.
What else do you
want from me?
- Um, for you to eat shit
and kiss my ass.
- So should I eat shit before
or after I kiss your ass?
'Cause the order
mattres.
Just want to make sure
I'm doing it right.
Come on, talk to me.
- Why?
It doesn't matter.
- Of course
it matters.
- Fucking bullshit.
If it mattered,
you would've come with me
instead of choosing to stay
with a fucking car.
You told me we were partners
in this, but we're not.
I'm a passenger
riding shotgun.
- Quiet...
- You got something snappy
to say now, John?
You gonna tell me
how wrong I was?
When I watched that fireball
explode in the woods,
I thought you were
fucking dead.
I thought
I'd lost you.
And I'm so fucking tired
of losing people.
And you knew that, John,
and you didn't care.
'Cause you don't care
about anyone but you.
[hissing]
[clatters]
Tire's got a leak.
♪♪
[rumbling]
[sighs]
- That was supposed
to be a surprise.
Figured you'd like
the easy access.
But if you don't,
I can take it out,
and you can use it
for whatever you want.
- No, it's fine.
I like it.
[door shuts]
- Quiet...
I fucked up.
Evelyn has been my home
for 20-something years.
Before her,
I just felt cold.
Alone.
And I promised myself
I'd never feel like that again.
So losing her meant
I would go back to being
that same sad-ass
little boy.
But that's not even
what hurt the most.
Look, in the past
ten days
we've fought,
tried to kill each other,
did interesting things
to each other's bodies
in a ball pit.
I can't imagine day 11
without you.
I'm better with you.
I think maybe
you're better with me, too.
I know what I did
was shitty.
And I'm sorry.
I don't have to be in
the driver's seat all the time.
I want to be
a partner
if that's
still a thing.
- It was
pretty shitty.
the shittiest.
[crashing, tires squealing]
Damn, girl, you gonna
jump up on it already. Ow!
- Come on, man,
something's wrong.
[alarm blaring]
- [Trucker 1] Drive-by!
We're taking fire!
- It's the law.
Get down!
[gunfire]
- [Trucker 2] We have
casualties in rig four!
- [Trucker 3] We need
a medic on rig eight!
- [Trucker 4] I need
backup now! Move it!
- Some piece of shit lawman
killed three of our drivers.
We're about to make it
more than even.
If I were you, I would get
some better artillery
than them dinky pea-shooters
everyone had.
Looks like she's got
the right idea.
- This one.
It speaks to me.
- Yeah, it speaks
to me, too.
It says,
"I'm too heavy."
- The car can handle it,
dickhead.
- It's about balance.
We have weapons, armor,
speed, and handling.
Too much of one,
you lose the other.
Car's too heavy,
low speed,
sluggish handling.
So if we're gonna add
any weight,
I say we add armor.
- If you're fast enough,
it won't matter.
- Did you just give me
a compliment?
- I said if.
[background chatter]
- Oh, hello.
[knocking]
I can't believe Watts just
had this shit laying around.
Do you know how rare
ballistic glass is?
- It's a windshield,
you fucking dork. Relax.
You're acting like
you just got your first BJ.
- This shit
is bulletproof!
And when I got
my first BJ,
I was very nice,
I'll have you know.
I even said thank you.
- I bet you had
to say please, too.
How do you know how to do
all this stuff anyway?
- Mnh, you just try
different pieces
'til you find
the one that fits.
- That doesn't make
any sense.
Somebody had to teach you
how to do this.
- Some things come natural,
like breathing or driving.
- No, it's not natural.
You have to be taught
how to drive.
- Nuh-unh.
- Uh-huh.
- Babies don't know
how to drive.
Think about that.
I think it's done.
- Here's the moment
of truth.
[engine starts, revs]
[chuckling]
What do you
want to name her?
- Pfft, I don't know, I mean,
how did you decide on Evelyn?
- Mnh-mnh, she just felt
like an Evelyn.
And I found a license plate
that said "Evelyn."
- Okay, thief.
I don't know,
this hunk of junk
feels like...
Roadkill.
- Roadkill.
I love it.
[chuckling]
I wish we had
some tunes.
- Oh.
- Oh, no,
not a mix.
No, that's like
Russian roulette.
- Come on.
For Tasha.
["Epic" by Faith No More
playing]
- You got lucky.
Okay, Watts,
we're ready to roll.
♪ You want it all ♪
♪ But you can't
have it ♪
- I think we're ready
to fuck shit up.
- Oh, there's a "we" now.
Look, if we don't make it...
- Fuck that shit.
San Francisco or bust,
baby.
♪ It's it ♪
♪ What is it ♪
- So this is
Stone's blockade.
Girthy.
[metal creaking]
- I don't see any lawmen.
Maybe they all left.
- A car graveyard,
not creepy at all.
- Huh, "resisted."
- What'd you say?
- What? I'm just saying
what they're saying.
- Stone's here.
- What?
[gunshot]
- Why'd we stop?
[flare firing]
[engine starts and revs]
- I'm gonna make truck nuts
out of your ballsack, milkman!
[laughing]
[engines revving]
- Gotta hand it to the guy,
he's got good traps.
- A little help?
- We're on it.
Uh, baby, things aren't
looking so good out here.
You ready?
- The wind's about to change
in our favor, Amber.
A twister's coming.
♪♪
[upbeat jingle playing]
[whistling]
[giggling]
[laughing]
- I'm so sick
of that fucking clown!
- It's time, Stu.
Light 'er up.
[laughing]
[growling, laughing]
Time to play.
♪♪