♪♪
["The Distance"
by CAKE playing]
♪ Reluctantly crouched
at the starting line ♪
♪ Engines pumping
and thumping in time ♪
♪ The green light flashes
the flags go up ♪
♪ Churning and burning
they yearn for the cup ♪
♪ They deftly maneuver
and muscle for rank ♪
♪ Fuel burning fast ♪
- If they're not black and blue,
they're not gettin' through.
♪ Reckless and wild
They pour through the turns ♪
[Sweet Tooth laughing]
- Time to send in
the clown.
- Let's clear a path.
♪ Driving and striving
as fast as he can ♪
[truck horn honking]
♪ And long ago somebody
left with the cup ♪
♪ But he's driving and striving
and hugging the turns ♪
♪ And thinking of someone
for whom he still burns ♪
[gunfire]
♪ He's going the distance ♪
♪ He's going for speed ♪
♪ She's all alone all alone
all alone in her time of need ♪
[gunfire continues]
- Line me up.
♪ And plotting the course
he's fighting and biting ♪
♪ And riding on his horse
He's going the distance ♪
- Fuck, that was cool!
- [Watts] These cops can't
drive for shit! Ha!
[gunfire]
- Uh, they're still alive!
- I noticed! The gun is jammed.
- Take the wheel!
[tires squealing]
Watch your left. Swerve!
- Stop backseat driving
and fix that fucking thing.
- I am!
[gunfire]
[clicking]
Fixed!
[gunfire continues]
Jell-O, Lawman!
[laughs]
- Why do you always
say "Jell-O" like that?
- It means "good-bye."
- What? No, it doesn't.
It's a dessert, you moron.
- No, it's insider slang.
A dude said it after
dinner before he...
Oh, God damn it!
[car approaching]
- Behind!
[gunshots]
[moaning]
- Aw, I always knew you two
would work things out,
and I love what you've
done with the car.
- Hey, thanks, man.
Love what you've done
with your, uh, fire hair.
- Looks really good.
- Aw, I'm just trying
something new.
- Hey, I heard you got
a beef with Stone.
- [laughs] Beef? I got
a whole butcher shop.
Stone is mine.
Ta!
- Bye!
- Screw you, man!
- Holy shit!
It's... I wanna say,
uh, Blue?
- No, it begins with "S."
It's on the tip of my tongue.
- Stu! Stu!
- [both] Stu!
- Haha, that's my guy!
- Oh, my God. Oh, shit!
[gunfire]
[gunfire continues]
[tires squealing]
[engine revs]
[Quiet gasps]
[tires squealing]
- [growls]
Duck, duck, goose!
- Oh!
- [gasps]
- You're welcome!
- Fuck!
- [Watts] Come on, baby,
come on, baby.
Follow me, follow me...
[clinks]
Oh, no, too close.
[engine revving]
[gunfire]
Here's your kiss
from mama, baby!
- No!
- [screaming]
- Oh, shit!
- Now's your chance
to skedaddle.
- We can't leave you
to fight this.
- The fuck you can't.
I'm tired of y'all.
You're bogarting my kills.
[truck horn honking]
- [Amber] Juggernaut to Twister,
we're flying in.
- [Watts] Amber, you keep
laying down that fire.
These chickens are
flying the coop.
- [Quiet] Thanks a lot.
This next round's on us.
- Shit. Would someone kill
this fucking truck?
- [Lawman]
You got it, sir!
- Amber!
- [gasping]
[gunfire]
- [Sweet Tooth] Where do you
think you're going, Stone?
You can't hide from me.
Ice cream?
No, you scream.
[laughing]
[explosions]
- No! No! Amber!
[tires squealing]
- [Sweet Tooth laughing]
- [groaning]
- [breathing heavily]
- Why'd you do that?
They were on our side!
- [laughing]
There are no sides, Stubert!
Everybody burns!
[gun cocking]
- Fuck this shit.
- Gotcha!
- [grunting]
- [laughing]
Okay, Stubie,
now's your chance
to show me your fangs.
Pull the trigger,
and put your doggy down.
- [breathing heavily]
- Do it!
- Come on, do it!
- Come on.
Come on, Stewie.
You can do this.
- [grunting]
- [breathing heavily]
[gunshot]
- Holy shit!
- Mike, let's go!
[grunting]
- You saved my ass!
- I-I think I skinned
my wang.
- Oh, don't talk
about your wang, man.
- I don't want
to look at it, man.
- [groaning]
Stubert!
[gunfire]
- You'll abide
by the law, clown.
- Harold,
take the wheel.
[grunts]
- Get off my car!
- You! Took! Everything!
From! Me!
- What the fuck?
Hey! You're dripping
eye blood on the hoo...
Oh, fuck it.
[gunshots]
- [groaning]
[breathing heavily]
- Oh, shit!
Did I...
Did I kill him?
- I don't know.
You want to turn around
and check for a pulse?
Let's get the hell outta here!
Let's go!
Get outta here!
[engine revving]
- Holy shit, I think
we're gonna make it.
[gunfire]
- [growling]
- God, I'm so tired of running
from Officer Dick Cheese.
Hang on.
- Thanks for the warning.
Whoa!
[tires squealing]
- Oh, okay,
we can play chicken.
[gunfire and rockets whistling]
Come on, fuckers!
[gunfire continues]
- Now!
[birds chirping]
- John?
John! John!
[screams]
- Get outta there!
Well, oh, well.
It's just you and me again.
You know, when I was walking
a beat in Topeka,
I used to see pieces
of trash just like you.
They'd mock me,
call me names, spit on me,
just because I was tryin'
to keep the streets safe.
When the power grid blew,
all of those same fuckheads
came to my door
wanting to be protected,
wanting to be safe,
but you know what
they really wanted?
They just wanted
to be kept in line.
- [laughing]
- What's so fuckin' funny?
- You talk so much.
All this talk
about rules and laws,
it's all bullshit.
You're just a sad,
lonely man,
and you think
you're in control.
- I am in control.
- No.
You're just the one
holdin' the gun.
- Any last words?
- Knock, knock.
- Who's there?
[screaming]
[whimpering]
[gun cocks]
[gurgling]
[ragged breathing]
[groaning]
- I'm gonna give you
a tough choice.
You can die slowly,
or...
[whispers]
You can die fast.
You have a good day now,
motherfucker.
[engine starts]
[gunshot]
[engine revving]
- Oh! Oh! Oh!
[laughing]
- Oh, I fucking thought
I lost you again.
Oh, where's...
[sniffles]
- I'm sorry.
- Those fuckers
are gonna pay.
[engine revving]
- Hey, Bill, I'm back!
You miss me?
- Bill got promoted.
You do not have clearance
to approach.
- Look, I know you're just
trying to do your job,
but I have a life-changing
opportunity
that's going to expire
if I don't deliver this package
in one minute and 17, 16, 15...
You see where
I'm going with this?
- Yeah, that's not my problem.
- Uh, it will be
if Raven hears her delivery
expired right outside her gate.
- Holy shit.
Tell Raven
the Milkman made it.
- Let's go.
- Open the gate!
- You didn't tell me
she was so hot.
- Someone's had
a busy ten days.
- And I'm not
the only one.
Hey, congratulations
on the promotion, Bill!
She treatin' you well?
Good pay? Good benefits?
- Just give her
the package, John.
- Wow. Fuck you, Bill.
- How do we know she's
actually going to pay up?
- This is how Milkman
deliveries work.
Only person who's making it
weird right now is you.
- Congratulations, John.
Welcome to New San Francisco.
[gun cocking]
- Hey, hey, whoa!
Hold on, man.
Bill, calm down.
She's with me.
- John, she's not
allowed to enter.
- Well, you wouldn't have it
if it wasn't for her.
- We had a deal, John,
you and me.
- And she's with me.
That's all you need to know.
[guns cocking]
If she can't go in, fine.
I'm not goin' in either.
- John, don't do this.
You wanted this
your whole life, right?
- Yeah, but...
- Then you need to go.
- What are you doin'?
- I'm not gonna be the reason
you don't go inside,
so you're gonna go in,
and you're gonna be happy.
You got it?
[gun cocking]
Don't, John.
I mean it.
- Quiet...
[gunshot]
Aah!
- He needs medical attention.
Get him inside.
- Go on.
- [grunting]
What? Quiet, no!
Quiet!
- Jell-O, John.
[door slams]
[sniffling]
- Stop, now!
Here. John usually
makes this run,
but since he's retired...
- What the hell am I
supposed to do with this?
- Deliver it.
We need a new Milkman.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
[cheering]
That was for San Diego.
- Fuck San Diego.
[car door slams]
- The Milkman
has stabilized.
Doc said he'll be fine,
but the girl...
Couldn't you have
let her in?
- She complicates things.
[laughing] Imagine
what John went through,
driving halfway
across the country,
all to deliver...
this.
Yeah.
- What do you think?
- It's fine.
I ordered pistachio.
Of course, they fucked up
my order.
- I meant about John.
- Oh.
He passed his test,
and Calypso kept
his end of the bargain.
Mostly.
[gags]
Marshmallow. Blech.
- So it's time that
we start prepping him
for his new position?
Not yet,
let him acclimate,
get a feel for
the good life inside.
Then we'll talk
about what comes next.
♪♪
- That's a nice dick.
All right, jerkoff,
it's just me and you.
Now are we gonna work it
out today, or not.
Come on!
Yagh!
Oh, fuck!
This...
[grunting]
Fuck you, fuckin'...
Come on.
Why do you make me
do this to you?
Don't be such
a fuckin' asshole!
[grunting]
[bicycle bell ringing]
[screaming]
Fuckin' bike.
What?!
♪♪
- Good morning, John.
- Hi
[chuckling]
- Hey, what's up, John?
- Hey, John.
- Good morning, John.
♪♪
[laughing]
- Oh my god.
- I'm telling ya.
Look, the weirdest thing
I've ever eaten was an owl.
- No shit?
- Yeah!
- Why?
- I got the midnight
munchies.
You know what
I'm talkin' about!
[laughing]
- You're such a badass, John.
Oh, god, you must have,
like, killed so many people.
- Uh, yeah, yeah.
A few, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Mmm.
[chuckling]
But, like how many?
- Aw, I mean,
I don't keep count, dude.
[laughing]
- He doesn't keep count!
Okay, like I said,
you're a badass.
Oh! You gotta tell 'em
about the clown!
This is so crazy.
I think he had, like,
bondage stuff, I don't know.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was a lot of leather
and sweat.
- This guy!
[laughing]
[knocking]
- Hi.
- Diane, right?
- Yeah.
Come in.
It's okay.
I won't bite.
- So, uh, I've never
been set up on
a thing like this before.
- Oh.
- But Chester told me
you're a guard with him.
- You don't remember me?
You do not have clearance
to approach.
- Oh, shit!
Bill's replacement!
- Mm-hmm.
- I didn't even recognize you.
- Well, must be the hair.
- I didn't even
see past the gun.
- Let me get you a drink.
Do you like wine?
- Uh, toilet or sink?
- How about red?
[stuttering]
Yeah?
- Okay.
[knocking]
Oh, that's the pizza.
Would you mind
grabbing that?
- Sure.
- Hey, got a cheese pizza
for you.
- Wow.
I've never been on
the other side of a delivery.
I'm supposed to
give you something, right?
Here you go.
- Bullets.
- Would you prefer gasoline?
- There is cash
right there, dude.
- I hope that makes
a warm fire for you.
And hey, thanks.
I really appreciate
what you went through
to get this here.
- It's not a big deal, man.
- So this is pizza.
- You've never had pizza?
- Oh, my gosh,
you've never had pizza?!
- No.
- I'm honored to be here
for your first time.
- Thanks.
- Good?
- Uh-huh.
♪♪
[humming]
[clattering]
♪♪
- I know you're out there.
You don't know
who you're messin' with.
If you're gonna kill me,
do it quick,
you goddamn vulture.
- I'm not a vulture,
you buttmunch.
And I don't
want to kill you.
Your delivery.
I want half.
- I heard of you.
You're the one
who's been robbin' milkmen?
I've scratched my taint
with twigs bigger than you.
[chuckling]
You ain't gettin' shit!
[screaming]
[groaning]
- Next one I throw, you'll be
drivin' with your feet.
So, half!
- Fine! It's in the back.
I hope you choke on it!
- It's not for me,
you jag-off.
The insiders have been
runnin' this shit
for far too long.
It's time somebody
shared the wealth.
♪♪
- So tell me,
how is John adjusting?
- He's doin' greet.
Uh, we all get along.
I-I mean I think
me and the guys
would be friends with him
whether or not we had to,
right, fellas?
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
- And Diane?
- She-she set him up well.
She's pushing
for a second date.
- Good.
Make sure that happens.
I want John
to be happy.
And because I want it,
you should want that, too.
- John is happy.
I mean, he'll...
he'll be ready to drive
for you
any day now.
- Raven.
Just got word that John Doe's
only two blocks away.
[gasping]
[sighing]
[laughing]
- Right? Yeah!
John! You wanna
join us for a beer?
- No thanks, Chester.
I'm leavin'.
- You really wanna leave
after I gave you
everything I promised?
I even heard things
are going swimmingly with Diane.
- How do you know
about Diane?
- It's my job
to know everything.
- [laughing]
- The only thing I don't know
is what else I could
possibly give you.
- Something
you can't give me.
- The girl?
[scoffing]
John, you're seriously gonna
give all of this up
for some chick you knew
for 10 days?
I've had colds
last longer.
- Her name's Quiet.
- No way
that's her real name.
You do know her real name,
don't you?
Also, didn't she shoot you?
- Yeah, that happened.
- John, that doesn't
sound healthy.
Okay, look, if that's
really how you feel,
I will escort you
to the gate myself.
We just have to make
one quick stop first.
Come on.
- [scoffs]
What the fuck is
wrong with you now?
It finally happened.
I'm talking to a car.
I know something
didn't die in you.
Last time that happened,
you smelled like
burnt baby raccoon.
Thank you, by the way.
That was delicious.
- Maybe something shifted
when I slammed into that
Milkman the other week?
Oh, my God, now I'm fucking
asking the car
a God damn question.
That's great.
That's really great.
That's super healthy.
[screams]
Why won't you work,
you rusted piece of shit?
[sighs]
I'm very sorry.
Um, that was very rude.
You did not deserve that.
It's not your fault
that you're rusted.
It's just, we've been
together a month,
and I have no clue
how you work.
Oil goes in your mouth,
and fuel goes up your butt.
Everything in the middle
makes no sense.
[sighs]
I guess I just
keep trying pieces
until I find one that...
- You just try
different pieces
'til you find
the one that fits.
- Fits.
You better not be
fuckin' with me.
[engine turns over]
Aah! Holy shit!
I did it!
I fucking did it!
What the fuck did I do?
- Where are you taking me?
- Here.
- Nice house.
- I'm glad you think so.
It's yours.
- [chuckles]
You think a residential upgrade
is gonna keep me here?
Pass.
- No, John.
This is yours.
This is where you grew up.
- Wait.
I lived here?
- You've got mail.
When I first heard
of John Doe the Milkman,
I did a little digging,
and when I learned
that you had roots here,
I dug some more.
I'm sure you'll have
lots of questions,
and if you stay,
you'll get answers.
- I don't know what name
I was born with
or who I am really.
♪♪
- Drive!
- It's just like
I promised you.
I brought you home.
♪♪
- This isn't my home.
It's his,
whatever his name is.
This isn't me anymore.
I found my home
out there with Quiet.
- Hmm.
Wow, I never took you
for such a romantic,
but if that's
your decision...
[sighs] This isn't normally
how I like to do things,
but, hey, I'm flexible.
I have a job for you.
- I'm not gonna be
your Milkman.
- Milkman?
[laughing]
No, those days
for you are long gone,
but you're still a driver.
Best I've ever seen.
You proved that to me when
you made my little run.
See, you passed
the test, John,
and now I need your skills.
There's gonna be
a tournament,
the first of its kind
where the best drivers
from all across the country,
from all walks of life,
are gonna be invited to compete.
See, the tournament
only has one rule:
Survive.
And you better believe who
you face won't play fair.
This is where
you come in, John.
You are my horse,
and I need you to win,
because Calypso is offering
quite a prize.
The winner gets
their heart's desire,
their greatest wish
come true.
You're gonna
help me win, John,
and you're gonna do it
by getting behind the wheel
and turning every
car and contestant
that crosses your path
into nothing but a flaming pile
of twisted metal.
You will drive, John Doe,
and you will win.
- Okay.
Where to next?
[chains rattle]
[tires squealing]
♪♪
- Hey, girl.
I've been dying
to talk to you.
I heard you know
my brother.
He goes by John.
♪♪
[laughter]
- I told you we'd find it,
and we did.
Shangri-fuckin'-la.
- We got everything we need:
Ladies, liquor,
and long dogs.
This is Strawberry.
She's a doctor
and a lawyer.
I met her in a strip club.
- Okay. Okay.
This is Cleopatra.
She, uh, specializes
in French cuisine.
- Ooh-la-la.
- She, uh,
is also a stripper.
I'm thinkin' about
takin' a swim.
What do you guys think?
- No, she'll sink
right to the bottom.
I've tried before.
- [Sweet Tooth]
Good evening.
- Holy shit!
- [roaring]
- Actually,
I have a better idea.
[laughter]
[growls]
- Oh, no! Mike! Aah!
[Sweet Tooth laughing]
[screaming]