[laughing]
- We don't have time
for this.
You're hurt.
I get it.
Now, there's a way
out of this.
Okay?
[laughing]
[clicking]
This never happened
to me before.
Really.
Man.
Oh, man.
Damn it.
You never get a second chance
to make a first impression.
You know?
[engine starting]
Hey!
Oh, no, no, no, no! No!
This time it's loaded.
Six bullets,
each with your name on it
if you don't get out
of my car right now!
That said,
I'm willing to negotiate.
[engine sputtering]
Oh, I guess Evelyn
doesn't like you very much.
I'll make you a deal.
You scooch over,
I'll get you out of this alive.
But you better
think fast,
'cause that ain't
no birthday clown.
Okay, go!
[horn honks]
Oh, shit.
Okay, L1, R1, up, down, left,
right, right, down, up.
[engine revving]
All right, Evelyn,
we have nine days
to get away
from this clown,
ditch this psychopathic
hitchhiker,
and make it
to New Chicago.
Hey, look!
You forgot your seatbelt.
[brakes squealing]
Agh!
- Here for the show?
- I'm definitely here
for the show!
[gunfire]
Oh, shit!
[laughing]
- You're not
coming to my show?
Well, then the show
is coming to you!
♪♪
♪ Oh baby
I like it raw ♪
♪ Yeah baby
♪ Oh baby
I like it raw ♪
- Suppertime!
- Stu, I love you,
but this is all your fault.
- How was I
supposed to know
the woods would be
crawling with butchers.
- They're talking about
getting us exiled.
You had to get caught
sleeping on duty!
- Hey!
You were sleeping, too!
- I wasn't the one snoring
like a goat in heat!
- It's called sleep apnea.
It's a real
medical condition.
And it would be
a lot more manageable
if you hadn't traded in
my CPAP machine for porno.
- Well, excuse me for trying
to get you something dope
for your birthday!
- You know what's dope?
A full eight hours
of sleep.
Dreaming is dope!
- [Butcher] Francis!
- [Francis] What?
- Why did you season
both meat baths
in teriyaki sauce?
Francis, we talked about
diversifying flavors.
- Fine! Um...
Oh, I'll cover the thick one
in lemon pepper.
- No, no!
[sputtering]
Oh, god,
it's so tangy, dude!
- I call dibs
on the man titties.
[gunshots]
- Holy cow!
- Clear!
[whimpering]
- We don't usually find
the pigs alive
before the luau.
You can cut 'em loose.
Butchers!
They'd rather eat the flesh
of their own kind than starve.
You guys are guards?
- We, uh, we used to be.
Uh, Mike and I were...
- On a scouting mission
from Seattle
looking for trading routes.
Our car broke down
and the next thing you know
we're getting grabbed
by these assholes.
- We're always on the lookout
for upstanding citizens.
I'll give you guys
a choice.
You can try and make
your way back up north
where it can be
pretty dicey,
or if you can
take the grit,
join us in bringing
law and order
back to the Divided States
of America.
What do you say?
- Come on.
- Sweet.
- All right.
Welcome to the law, huh?
[cheers and applause]
- [agent] Yeah!
- [Agent Stone] You guys.
- [agent] Don't go dying on us.
- [John Doe] I can't believe
I already got
a flat tire.
Way to go, John.
Way to go.
Hey, silent
but not very deadly,
you gonna come over here
and help me with this?
Don't shush me!
You come over here
and help me with the tire.
[Sweet Tooth]
♪ Toyland Toyland ♪
♪ Little girl
and boy land ♪
- I'm gonna handle this shit.
Watch my back.
Ahh!
Ah, shit. Ahh!
[Sweet Tooth]
♪ When you dwell within it ♪
♪ You are ever
happy then ♪
You can hide,
but I have ways
to find you.
Marco! Marco!
- I'll be right back,
Evelyn.
I'll get us outta here.
- [Sweet Tooth] Marco!
Damn!
That usually works.
[electrical humming]
[clangs]
Huh?
- Shh.
[glass breaking]
Oh, shit.
[jackpot ringing]
- Marco.
[growls]
- [Sweet Tooth] Well, hi there!
[laughing]
Oh, that tickled.
You know, my dad always
wanted to play catch,
but he could never
catch a ball.
He could catch
a bullet.
[gunshot]
Why are you scurrying away,
little squirrel?
Looking for a nut?
This is gonna be fun!
Machete!
Huh, swung
a little wide there.
Well, aren't we
a tall glass of water!
Me, I'm more of
a Hawaiian punch!
[groans]
I'm guessing
you don't fight much
outside of your car now,
do you?
- Look, clown, I don't need
four wheels to kick your ass.
[laughing]
[growling]
Any chance we could get this
back in the cars?
[laughing]
- How about a little
kill music?
♪ Livin' la vida loca ♪
♪ She had dumps like
a truck truck truck ♪
♪ Thighs like
what what what ♪
♪ Baby move your
butt butt butt ♪
♪ I think
I'll sing it again ♪
♪ She had dumps like
a truck truck truck ♪
♪ Thighs like
what what what ♪
♪ All night long ♪
♪ Let me see that thong ♪
♪ Likin' where
the beat go ♪
♪ Da-da-da-da ♪
♪ Baby let your bootie go ♪
♪ Girl you wanna show ♪
♪ Da-da-da-da ♪
♪ That thong
thong thong thong thong ♪
- Do you love
the silver-haired god?
And don't lie to me.
- Yeah, man.
Look, I listened to
"Unleash the Dragon"
so many times
the disc broke.
I'm not a liar.
- Well, you said you were
coming to my show
and then you
shot at me!
- It was
a misunderstanding.
I been getting shot at
ever since I can remember.
It's force of habit,
I guess.
- Sounds like
you have trust issues.
- Yeah,
you're not wrong.
Nice pipes, dude,
I have to say.
That high note, whoo!
It was perfect.
- Oh, word?
- Yeah, can I go?
I got somewhere to be.
- I thought you said
you were coming to the show!
- Of course, I am.
Just can I leave
after the show?
- Well, in that case,
tonight is opening night!
[laughing]
- How were your showers?
- Aw, I don't know
the last time
I felt hot water
that wasn't my own piss.
Uh, sir.
- Consider it
your recompense
for upholding
law and order.
Warm showers, warm blankets,
warm meals.
- Oh.
- Aw, fuck, mashed potatoes?
- [Mike] And goddamn,
look at all that gravy!
I wonder how we can get
one of those punch cards.
- Now, let's proceed
to your initiation.
Right this way,
gentlemen.
What you see down there
is our supply truck.
It brings us
important provisions.
As you can see,
it's broken down.
That's why
it's not moving.
What I need for you to do
is to protect that truck.
- From what?
- Seagulls.
- [Sweet Tooth] Skittles?
- [John Doe] No, I'm good.
[chomping]
- Pre-show jitters.
Listen, I really appreciate
you coming along willingly.
Normally I have to drag people
into the theater
kicking and screaming.
But word of advice,
you won't like
what happens if you run.
What? Oh, him?
Nah, he was here
before.
Hey, Donald.
Don't worry,
he can't hear us.
I love names.
I'm kind of a name guy.
You know, the right one
can send a shudder
down your spine.
Wanna know
what I go by?
- There's not a person
on the West Coast
that hasn't heard
of Sweet Tooth.
- See what I mean?
I mean, you really
feel that in your bones!
What's your name,
friend?
- John Doe.
- Nah, I'll give it
a seven.
- Hey, I didn't
pick it.
I don't know what name
I was born with
or who I am really.
- Oh, amnesia.
What's your brand?
Post-traumatic,
transient, dissociative?
- All I know
is my first memory
is me waking up
in my car
with blood coming
out of my head.
- Wait, that's
my first memory too!
My head
covered in blood.
Of course,
it was being pushed
out of my mom's
whisker biscuit, but...
- Whoa!
You remember that?
- Oh, yeah.
I remember everything.
You should consider
yourself lucky.
There are some things
I wish I could forget.
Like the time
I shit my pants
in my elementary school
production of "Oklahoma".
I can still see
the audience's faces
laughing,
mocking.
Did you know Sisqo's
real name was Mark?
[grunting]
- [Stu] Oh, a rock.
- Man, what is
wrong with you?
You holding in a fart
or something?
- If the truck is so important,
why don't they just move it?
Something doesn't
smell right, man.
- Smells good to me.
Back in Seattle,
they treated us like morons.
Now look at us;
we holding .30-cals, dude!
Come on, baby,
get your head in the game.
Come on. Come on.
There you go.
- Fuck you!
- Eyes up, boys.
Those seagulls lay a fingernail
on our supplies,
it's open season.
- What the hell?
Hey, why do you
call 'em seagulls?
These look like
normal survivors to me.
- What else would you call
a bunch of fucking trash eaters?
- Dude, are we really
gonna kill these guys?
[suppressed gunshot]
- There's one left, Stu.
He's all yours.
Clean it up!
[suppressed gunshot]
[laughter]
Melon down.
- I saved your ass.
- [Agent Stone] Seagulls,
butchers, exiles.
They see the world
in shades of gray.
What I need
from you two lawmen
is to just show them
that there's only two colors
in the world,
black and blue.
Now, you missed, Stu.
It can happen to anyone.
Rookie mistake.
Hey, don't let it
happen again.
Okay.
You guys want
some burgers?
- Bubby-baby,
bubby-baby.
Tip of the teat,
tip of the teat.
Tip of the teat.
My marvelous mutterer
makes me mingy on Monday.
- You sleep here?
What, the penthouse
was booked up?
- Nah, way too much
space up there.
Nice bidet, though.
Like taking a shotgun
up the ass.
No, I sleep here
because it reminds me
of where I was
before Vegas.
Back then, I lived with
a real solid group of dudes.
But then the world took a shit
and I came to Sin City.
Now that was a party.
- You've been here alone
for over two decades?
- Oh, shit, has it been
that long?
Look at this guy.
Hasn't aged a day.
What a beauty.
Nah, I'm not alone.
I got Harold,
which, have you...
you haven't met
Harold yet.
I'm gonna introduce you.
This is Harold.
Been my best friend
since I was a kid.
You know, my entire life
people have been lying to me.
Even my fucking parents!
But, uh, never Harold.
No, he can't lie to me.
He can't lie to anyone.
- I can see that.
[sighing]
- I don't know what I'd do
without him.
Look at that smile.
So, you got a Harold?
- No.
I got an Evelyn.
- Oh, that's cute.
- Before I met her,
being alone was all I knew.
You know, she makes
everything easier, you know?
Sometimes I wish I could
make her laugh. Right?
I have to say
after all this time
that's the sound
I miss the most.
- [Sweet Tooth] You know
what sound I miss the most?
The sound of hand meat
clapping together.
Nothing like that
glorious applause.
I mean, it's almost better
than, I don't know,
hearing somebody choking
on their own blood.
But look at me
getting carried away.
Good thing that your Evelyn's
got hands, huh?
She must clap for you
all the time.
- Nah, she doesn't.
She's my car.
- You talk to your car?
That's weird, man.
Ah, mwah!
There you are.
So, if Evelyn's not the girl,
who's she?
I caught this little pest
crawling through my vents.
See, I was gonna
starve her.
Watching the life slowly
drain from their eyes.
Kind of
my artistic process.
[laughing]
You know, the last guy
lasted almost four weeks.
Hey, Wilbur!
I think she's gonna give you
a run for you money.
She won't.
Bubby-baby, bubby-baby.
- Hey, you tried to kill me
every chance you get.
Why should I
show you mercy?
Goddamn it!
Hey, man,
why don't you let her out?
- And why would I do that?
- No, no, no, listen.
What good
is an audience of one?
Think about
all the meat slapping
you'll hear
with four hands.
- Ah, that's true.
I don't often
get feedback
from the 18 to 35
female demographic.
Fine!
[sighs]
You fish her out
and take a seat.
Don't worry,
I got a table just for you.
- And what happens
after the show?
- Well, you go on
your merry way.
- Really?
- Well,
if I'm being honest,
nobody has survived
all three acts.
Gird your loins!
- Tonight,
you will be enjoying
white tiger
prepared three ways.
There's a whole pack of those
milky white assholes
breeding up on
the fourth floor.
Anyway, enjoy.
Bony tit!
- Give me back those keys!
Hey, hey!
If it wasn't for me,
you would be
a starving corpse right now.
Listen, neither one of us
made it pretty far on our own.
So, instead of us trying to...
holy shit, this steak is good.
Instead of us trying to stab
each other in the back,
we should put our heads
together and figure out
how in the hell we're going
to make it through the show.
Is any of this
getting through to you?
Blink twice for yes.
Cool, we're fucked.
[clapping]
[clears throat]
- Tonight, I will be presenting
a one-man play entitled
"That's In-Room
Entertainment",
based on the hotel's
in-room entertainment.
♪♪
Hi, I'm Debra
from guest services.
And welcome to Nevada!
Deep in the heart of Vegas
is the Monte Cristo,
a veritable oasis
in the sand.
And don't forget
about our promenade.
It features
all the latest brands
and is just a stone's throw
from the salon.
Girl, might be time to take care
of those split ends!
And for all you
lovebirds out there,
Las Vegas is still the marriage
capital of the world.
Time for kisses!
And you have selected
express checkout.
Please leave your key
at the drop box
at the front desk.
And thank you
for staying with us.
Well, we've come
to the Q&A
where I ask the Q's
or I kick your A.
So, now is
the moment of truth.
What do you think?
- Oh, um, I loved it.
- Liar!
What exactly
did you love about it?
- Uh, your performance!
I was moved!
What? It was
a tour de force!
- I am gonna tour de force
this machete down your throat!
If you're not gonna
tell the truth,
then I'm gonna make you
shut up and bleed.
- It was a fucking
snooze-fest.
- Now you talk?
- What the hell
did you say?
- It sucked.
Your performance was
dull as dick water
and frankly beneath you.
- And you?
You agree with her?
- Yes.
I agree with her.
Come on, man,
it was boring.
I get it,
you've been here forever,
but you did a play
about a hotel!
- But didn't Mark Twain say
you should write what you know?
- Well, Mark Twain's
a dumbass.
You gotta get out
in the world, man.
- Yeah.
Look, trust me,
you don't want to spend
the rest of your life alone.
You end up
talking to a car.
- Yeah, like this guy.
- You know what?
You're right.
I can't wait here
for my audience.
I need to get out there
and hunt my audience down.
- Oh, no, no,
that's not what I meant.
- No, that's exactly
what you meant.
I'm gonna get out there,
and I'm gonna embrace the chaos.
Who knows,
maybe I'll even fall in love!
The show is going
on the road!
♪♪
- That was
beautiful, man!
♪♪
- Well, a night
of firsts.
My first
honest critique,
first people I ever let
leave here alive,
but most importantly,
my first two fans.
You two.
I got you a headshot.
There's an inscription
in that.
- [John Doe] "See you soon."
- I hope not.
- Hey, thanks
for being honest.
[engine revving
and tires squealing]
♪♪
[gunshots]
♪ Come on ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Baby
That thong ♪
♪ I said I like
the way ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Listen
Said I like the way ♪
♪ I don't think
you heard me ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ All right ♪
- [John Doe] You know, I have
to admit I didn't think
we were gonna make it
out of there alive.
I mean, it would have been
a lot easier
if you had piped up
instead of just trying to...
oh, come on!
Have you learned nothing?
What is your problem
anyway?
- I'm trying
to find someone.
- Well, I'm trying
to get somewhere,
and I lost a hell
of a lot of time
watching that
god-awful play.
If you put the gun down,
I'll drop you off
as close as I can
to where you're going. Deal?
- Fine.
But I'm keeping the gun.
- No, come on, that one's new.
All right, all right, take it.
What's your name anyway?
Okay, I'll start.
Hi, I'm John.
You're...?
Bridget?
Yolanda?
Jennifer?
Okay. So, since you
like to be quiet,
that's what I'm gonna
call you: Quiet.
Is that okay, Quiet?
- Yep.
- So, you're really not
gonna tell me your name?
- Nope.
- Fine.
Makes it easier
when I drop your ass off
in the middle
of nowhere, Quiet.
- [Agent Shepard]
Sack up, newbs.
Got a live one.
I'll stop the vehicle
and demand to see
their open road license.
If they don't got it,
they don't pass.
What?
- Hey, sorry,
just one question.
Where do we bring 'em?
Oh, and why are we
stopping them?
And what's
an open road license?
Is it common at the...
- Just get in.
- We learn on the job.
I respect that.
- I've never seen
a checkpoint
that wasn't outside
of a settlement.
And these guys
aren't on the map.
So, more delays.
Let me do
all the talking.
I deal with these guys
all the time.
I speak their lingo.
- Hey, ORL, please.
- Did you just ask me
for oral?
- Uh, no, sir.
ORL.
Open road license.
- That's an awful acronym.
Hey, look,
I'm just a milkman.
I'm just passing through, man.
Come on.
And you guys look great,
by the way.
I love your shirts, man.
What are you, like a club
or a team or something?
- We're officers.
Of the law.
- Ah, angry black friend.
Okay.
Hey, where...
Get back in the car!
- [Stu] Listen to
your friend!
- Eat my ass,
motherfucker!
[clicking and buzzing]
[wincing]
♪♪