♪♪
- You know, it'd be great
if you could warn me
before you drift
like that.
I fucking slammed my goddamn
head into the window.
- I said, "Hang on."
- You say that all the time.
"Hang on.
I'm taking a curb.
Hang on.
It's a speed bump."
I mean, at this point
it's meaningless.
- I should be mad at you anyway.
The reason we got robbed
is because you needed
a piss break again.
- Oh, come on!
You also needed to pee.
You sounded like a broken
fire hydrant back there.
- [John Doe]
Ha! You were listening.
- [Quiet]
It was so loud.
I bet that vulture heard you
from three states away.
What'd he take, anyway?
- Ooh, found it!
[laughs]
- Are you serious?
You almost got us killed
for a bunch of stupid CDs?
- Stupid CDs? I've been building
this collection for a decade.
I have more memories in here
than I do in here.
And, I'll have you know,
good music is worth
its weight in gold nowadays.
Let's see what other CDs
this guy's got.
DMX.
Got that.
Dave Matthews Band.
Pass.
Hm, I've ever seen
this one before.
- Uh, it's pretty good.
I mean, you'll hate it at first,
but it grows on you.
Especially track two.
- Track t...
You know the tracks?
- What? No.
Shut up.
- Should I toss it?
- No! No.
I mean, keep it or not.
I don't care. Whatever.
[chuckling]
You know, we're not
far from Topeka.
I can walk
the rest of the way.
If you leave now,
you can probably make it
to New Chicago
by nightfall.
- A milkman's job
is never done
until his package
is safely delivered
to its final
destination.
And I'm sure your brother
would have wanted that.
Besides, you think
I'd come this far
and not see the fabled
Topeka for myself?
- Fine.
If you're
dead set on it,
how about one
for the road?
["MMMBop"
by Hanson playing]
[laughs]
- It was close.
You gotta
follow through.
Like this.
- That's what
I'm doing.
Like this.
- Here.
To the end of
our road together.
- Mmm,
now you're
just showing off.
[music slowing]
[groans]
[bottle breaks]
- Sorry, John.
I can't have you
coming with me.
Sweet Dreams.
♪ Yeah yeah ♪
♪ Mmmbop ba daba du bop
du yaba du bop ♪
♪♪
- Loquacious.
Boy, you're a loquacious lad,
aren't you?
[knocking]
Come in!
Jamie, Carl,
how's the search going?
- We have yet to find
the Mapmaker,
but we think
we're close.
- I'm talking about
the Milkman
and the four-fingered girl.
Where are they?
- Uh, there's been
no sign of them
since they
vacated the dam.
- When they pop up,
we'll be ready.
- Pop up? Hmm.
So, pop up.
[sighs]
Pop up.
These two lawbreakers
ran rip-shod through
my largest outpost.
They killed
my second in command,
beat his brains in.
And you're waiting for them
to pop up?
Are they pieces of bread,
Roberts?
Are we making
fucking toast here?
- Sir, what Carl meant
was that...
- Shut the fuck up.
They defied the law,
and they defied me.
Now get out there
and look for them harder
than if you were checking
your lover for body lice.
- That's actually
my sister, sir.
We have the same...
- I know what a sister is!
Look, I want their bodies
hung from the rotunda
by this weekend.
Provide the people
of Topeka
with some light
Friday night entertainment.
What do you say?
- [both] Yes, sir.
- Okay.
Fuck off.
♪♪
♪ Here comes Sweet Tooth
here comes Sweet Tooth ♪
♪ Don't you run
don't you run ♪
♪ If you run I'll find you
turn you into red goo ♪
♪ Ding dang dong
ding dang dong ♪
Well, you look like a man
who values top-shelf
entertainment.
Want to see a show?
- I don't care
about your show.
I need to see
your ORL now.
- My ORL.
"Orl" what?
- I'll bring you in.
[growls]
- I think...
I'll bring myself in.
[gagging]
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
[whimpering]
I've really enjoyed
this conversation,
but let's pull a pin in it,
shall we?
[whimpering]
[sighs]
Now, don't go touching
that grenade.
Very sensitive.
Hope you got
some friends inside
who appreciate
the arts.
[laughing]
[screaming]
♪♪
- [Lawman #1] Did you hear how
they found Shepard?
- He killed himself, right?
Shit's messed up, man.
- [Lawman #1] No.
I heard a new recruit
found him half naked,
hand on his pecker,
head busted to shit
with a sexy schoolgirl
comic book next to him.
- That's the most fantastic
thing I've ever heard.
- [Lawman #1]
Right?
- [Lawman #2] So Shepard
was a sex pervert?
I mean, I kind of see it.
I do.
- Oh, fuck me.
Ham again.
- I'll eat that shit.
What kind of side
you got?
Got any chips
or puffy Cheetos?
- [Lawman #1] Hey, don't you
worry about my sides.
- [Lawman #2] I will.
I'll trade you.
- [Lawman #1] I'm not
eating those peanuts.
They're nasty.
[Patrol Lawman] Patrol vehicle
approaching outer gate.
[Gate Lawwoman]
Car 22 is approved.
[stabbing, groaning]
[tires screaching]
♪♪
- [Quiet]
"Pick up after your pet"?
Jesus.
- [Loud] Damn, dude,
this place is fucked up.
Who would do that
to a dog?
Separating a dog
from his best friend.
It's kind of like me and you.
I mean...
I mean, you were
my best friend.
Not that I'm calling you
a dog or nothing.
You know, you can be
a mean bitch
when you want to be
with, you know,
throats and shit.
That why we're here,
little bunny?
You gonna rip
some throats?
Nah, I think
you're gonna end up
just like me.
[bell dings]
- [Clerk]
Now serving C42.
- Number's almost up,
traitor.
Don't worry.
Something tells me
you'll fall fast.
[laughing]
- First of all, weight
doesn't equate to health.
Second, objects fall
at the same speed
regardless of mass.
Everyone knows that,
except you dipshits.
[grunts]
- You're actually talking
about terminal velocity,
which doesn't apply.
And if you take into account
air friction...
[door slamming]
- Muh-muh-muh...
- Kelvin? What is it?
- [Sweet Tooth] Machete.
[yelps]
Hi, everybody!
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Don't leave me.
[gunfire]
- [Sweet Tooth]
Woman's body!
[whimpering]
I hate cops.
[screaming]
- Oh, what the fuck?
- And, scene.
So, did you like it
or what?
[cheering]
Oh, wow, applause.
Thank you.
You are too kind.
That really feels good.
- I've never seen anyone
cut off a human head
and catch it
as good as that.
- [Haggard Loner]
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Oh.
Oh.
What brought you here,
young man?
"Oh, I just want to
get out of the scene."
Yeah, Topeka's
going to the dogs.
[barking]
- You nasty
motherfucker.
- [chuckling]
[sniffing]
Down goes the zippee.
Yippee!
Ooh.
Can I keep you?
Oh, shit!
It's alive! Oh!
- Where's the girl?
- I didn't see no girl.
I just saw you laying out
here all dead like,
practically
begging for it.
Maybe I'll just
put you back to sleep.
Oh.
- You looking
for this?
- Oh, shit!
Ah!
You missed!
[laughing]
- Shit!
- Nah nah, nah nah,
nah nah!
[screaming]
- Guess that worked.
Quiet?!
[zips]
- [Quiet] Dear Jon...
- What kind of psychopath
spells John without an "H"?
- [Quiet] Sorry
for poisoning you.
Oh, I hope I didn't
accidentally kill you,
but I did it
to save your life.
The truth is, Topeka isn't
what I said it was.
It's Stone's
headquarters.
Killing Shepard
wasn't enough.
Oh, by the way,
I killed Shepard at the dam.
He was jerking off.
It was a whole thing.
- Didn't need that detail.
- [Quiet] At least
you didn't have to see it.
Now that we're here,
I gotta make sure Stone pays
for what he did.
- I would have helped you
if you just told me.
- [Quiet] I would have told you,
but this isn't your fight.
Don't follow me.
Finish your delivery
and live your new life.
Be the first milkman
without an expiration date.
Good luck.
- That's actually
pretty sweet.
- [Quiet]
And go fuck yourself.
- Of course.
I guess that's it then.
Jell-O, Quiet,
whatever the hell
your name was.
- [Loud] Dude, what do you think
they're gonna do to you
when they catch your ass?
They're gonna kill you.
They always said
you were the smart one,
but, man, I don't know.
If this was my idea,
you'd call me
a goose-brained dunder fuck.
- Oh, my God,
will you shut the hell up?!
- Ha! Like that works.
I thought you knew your brother
better than that.
- You're not my brother.
You're just my imagination.
- You got a fucked up
imagination.
You gave me the bullet hole
and everything.
Is this how you really
remember me?
Ah, dope, right?
But imagine me, like,
two feet taller and ripped.
But not, like, too swole,
just enough to show definition.
- Fuck off!
- You fucking miss this.
- I do.
- Same.
I mean, being dead
is a total buzzkill.
At least you have
the Milkman.
- Oh, John was a giant pain
in my crack.
- Dude, I'm literally
inside your brain,
and I know that's not
what you really think.
I mean, I know you've seen him
with his shirt off.
Nice back, huh?
What?
God forbid you feel
anything other
than explosive rage
for a second.
- You died
five days ago.
The rage is hard
to ignore.
No fucking way.
- It's a dumb statue.
Forget it.
- Forget it? They think
he's a fucking hero.
- Who gives a fuck
what they think?
- [Jamie] Officer.
[banging]
Your vehicle's assigned
to patrol duty.
Why are you idling?
- [Loud] You've got to
say something.
Silence will get you
killed here, little bunny.
- Oh, I was just admiring
our boss, ma'am.
- Yeah.
I don't, uh, recognize
your face, officer.
Are you new?
- Transferred recently.
- Hmm.
- She's on to you.
You've got to leave now.
[tires squealing]
[gunshots]
[clicks]
- Fuck!
♪♪
- Holy fuck.
- You're not getting
out of here alive,
you fucking traitor!
[whimpering]
- [Sweet Tooth]
Need a hand?
Oh, I found this one
lying around,
so you'll have to
get your own.
- Thank you.
- Ah, don't mention it.
I really enjoy my work.
Hey, hold this.
- Okay.
- And I'm gonna be
back for that.
Hmm-boop!
So, uh,
what's your name?
- Stu.
- Stu. I like
the mouthfeel of that.
Stu.
I'm Sweet Tooth.
Put her there!
- Nice to meet you,
Mister, uh, Tooth.
- Firm grip
you got there, Stu.
Bet you have a lot of fun
with that.
You know, Stu, I got a feeling
you and I are kindred spirits.
- You think we're a lot
alike?
- You bet I do.
- In, uh, in what way?
- I mean, you're a big guy,
I'm a big guy.
Your name starts with "S",
my name starts with "S".
The S Brothers,
who would have thunk it?
Uh, something catch
your peepers, Stuber?
- [Stu] Yeah.
I found Mike...
and Ikes.
You want some?
- Ooh, yucky.
I'm a Skittles guy.
♪♪
[engine revving]
- Let's haul ass,
Evelyn.
Make up some time.
- Five flatheads
on one lure?
Just a basic spooner.
- Best day of my life.
They were really bitin'
that day.
- [Stone] Best day of my life
is gonna be
when I complete my collection
of state quarters.
The world went to shit
before I could find Idaho.
But you know what?
I'll get there.
The Union
will be complete.
- Finished.
- I think the spot's
still there, Cliff.
[chuckling]
- Oh, there it is.
- [Jamie] Agent Stone,
come in, Agent Stone.
We have a 146A.
- Be right back.
- [Jamie] A woman with
a missing finger, sir.
- What about
the milkman?
- [Jamie] She's alone.
We have two patrol cars
on her tail.
- Don't worry,
we'll bring you her teeth.
- Oh, Carl.
No, do not engage.
It's time I made
an example of her myself.
[sirens wailing]
- You're caught!
You gotta fucking bail.
- No, I can't leave
until Stone is dead.
- The only one dead
is you
if you don't leave
this fucking place.
When I died, I gave you
a second chance.
And you're
throwing it away.
- You're right.
Fuck this shit!
[laughing]
- That's right!
That's the fuck
what I'm talking about!
Come on!
- [Stone] Guard 22.
[brakes squealing]
Come in, please.
What happened to your
loquacious boyfriend?
Did he
bite the dust?
I have people in position
to kill you right now,
but I think I'm gonna
give you a choice.
Although, you remember
how that went last time?
You can run,
in which case
we'll hunt you down
like a dog.
Or, you and I
can get together
and have
a little chat.
Turn around
and we can finally
settle this one on one.
- [Loud] Sis,
you don't have
to do this.
- Shut up.
[tires squealing]
- [Stone] Haha, good.
My men will
show you the way.
- Aww, you remembered.
Thanks, Stuby.
So, where are you off to
now that you're a free man?
- Honestly,
uh, not sure.
After Seattle,
my friend and I
were looking for
a place of our own.
A Shangri-La, you know?
- Absolutely.
- But, uh, then
when I got here,
he, uh, threw me
under the bus.
- Oh, I've done that before.
Crunch!
Never to a friend.
I'm not a monster.
- Listen, uh,
what you did today,
saving me like that,
it's, uh, it's the first time
in a while
anyone's had my back.
So, uh, thanks.
- Well, hell, I mean,
you're a reject, I'm a reject,
we got to look out
for each other.
I mean, you are about to head
out into a dangerous world
where there are
two types of people,
those who kill
and those who get killed.
I know you're no wolf,
but there is gonna
come a time
when you're gonna
need to bite.
And even puppies
have fangs, Stu.
- That sort of thing is just
hard for me, I guess.
I'm sure
I'll figure it out.
- Oh, well, I mean,
maybe you could,
I don't know,
but, tag along with me,
and I could help you
find your fangs.
- Yeah.
You know what?
What the hell?
- You mean it?
- Yeah.
- Fuck yes!
Get in there.
Aww, the S Brothers,
gonna paint the town red.
Whoa, you sit bitch,
Harold's got shotgun.
- Sorry.
So, where are we
off to next?
- Well,
I'm not really sure.
I mean, it felt
so freeing,
ripping into
those law assholes.
And the applause.
Nobody ever cheered for me
like that in Vegas.
- You know, if you want
to chase that feeling,
there are outposts
like this
all up and down
these routes
and all through
the Midwest.
Each one of them is filled
with captives just like me,
waiting to get
set free.
You save 'em
and boom,
you have fans
for life.
- Hmm.
Fans for life.
Oh, I like that.
[laughing]
[cheering]
I don't, um, I don't really
have room for all you guys,
so maybe
you should carpool.
- [Stone] Fall back;
she's mine.
♪♪
Welcome to
Thrills and Spills Park.
I came here every weekend
growing up.
Got my first pickle tickle
on the Ferris wheel.
But you know what
my favorite was?
The Midway,
because I love games.
Don't you?
- Gotcha.
[tires squealing]
[gunshots]
- Peekaboo.
Say goodbye.
[engine revving]
- Fuck!
Where do you think
you're going?
- Shit!
- Miss me, mute?
[gunshots]
[engine revving]
- Fuck.
- See you soon, dude.
[clapping]
- What the fuck?
[gunshots]
["MMMBop" by Hanson playing]
- You look pissed.
- Damn right, I'm pissed.
I only had one of those.
- I told you
not to come.
- And when have I
ever listened to you?
Come on,
we gotta go.
Quiet? Quiet!
Quiet, come on!
No.
Come on, Quiet.
Quiet.
Come on. Come on.
Come on. Quiet!
♪♪