[man] Sector 5 harvesting will
conclude in ten minutes.
- You heard him.
Ten minutes.
[man] Deposit all crops
before curfew.
[boss] Hurry up!
No slacking!
Get back to work!
- Daniel, you dead idiot.
I told you to stay out of
the deep end.
Dude, where you been?
- I got us a contract.
- Fuck off!
- We're both about
to fuck off.
Four years, and then we get
two acres of pristine
beachfront O.C. property
as our reward.
- "The female has been
assigned to domestic work.
"The male, food service."
We got to do four years
of this shit?
- We've been stuck in these
fields since we were kids.
Did you not hear what I said
about beachfront property?
Once we're done, it's blue skies
and yellow sands
for the rest of our lives.
- What about Adrian?
- Come on, Adrian?
It doesn't mean anything.
We're just having
a little fun.
- I know.
We share a wall.
[Tobin] Do you two assholes
ever shut up?
Don't have me report you.
- Mind your fucking
business, Tobin!
- Don't make me shove this
up your urethra, Tobin.
- No one even likes you!
Why are you even talking?
- Come on, man.
We're packing our bags,
and we're getting out.
- Do I get a say in this
at all or what, huh?
- What are you gonna say,
fuckhead?
That you're not interested
in a better life?
That you don't
want to be happy?
You seriously wanna spend
the rest of your days
becoming shriveled up and
useless like Tobin?
- I heard that.
- We wanted you to hear it!
- She wanted you to hear it.
Okay, let's do it.
But you're finishing
off our work
for the rest of the day.
- Done. Pick em up, fuckhead.
[distant laughter]
- Fuck. My head.
[John Doe] Quiet?
[groaning]
- Why are we here?
- We're okay.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
He left a note.
"The astral nauts
of store LIS004
"have left this ruined world
"to ascend to our new home
on the two-ringed planet.
"I, Zachary, await an escape
pod for my mortal flesh.
"Please do not move me."
See? They ascended.
We're good.
Fine. I'll take out
the leftovers.
Come on, Zach.
Oh, these bones feel
like spaghetti.
You're lucky I got you
out of Topeka.
Stone almost
smoked your ass, right?
Ow! What's that for?
- I had him!
That was my kill.
- Who, Stone?
Are you delusional?
When I saw you,
your car was sideways
and you were
covered with blood.
Matter of fact,
you're still bleeding.
- At least
he's dead, right?
- Stone? Yeah.
Maybe.
Now that I think of it, no.
- What the fuck, John?
- I was busy trying
to get your ass out of
that amusement park alive.
The fact that we're
both standing here,
I think I made
the right call.
- That wasn't
your call to make.
- Says the asshole
who poisoned me.
- And I told you
not to come back for me.
- Well, I ignored that.
- Why?
- Because it was a stupid
fucking thing to say.
- Well, you're
fucking stupid.
- Well, so are you.
♪ Yeah ♪
- Do you think something's
about to happen?
Because it definitely is.
- It's been a while since I...
- Why do you talk so much?
♪ One here comes the two
to the three to the four ♪
♪ Like she a groupie
and I ain't even on tour ♪
♪ Everybody in the club
gettin' tipsy ♪
♪ Everybody in
the club gettin' tipsy ♪
♪ Everybody in the club
gettin' tipsy ♪
♪ Everybody in
the club gettin' tipsy ♪
♪ Here comes the five
to the four to the three ♪
♪ Hands in the air
if you cats drunk as me ♪
Ugh! Ahh! Oh, nasty!
♪ Dude I don't care
I'm a P-I-M-P ♪
♪ Everybody in the club
gettin' tipsy ♪
♪ Everybody in
the club gettin' tipsy ♪
[seagulls calling]
♪♪
- [gasps] Giselle?
You majestic bitch.
It has been forever.
Mwah. Mwah.
Oh, my God,
I love your earrings.
I treated myself to
a new necklace too.
Idiot didn't finish
her chores.
Oh, my God,
I'm starving.
I want a number one,
no bun, fries.
Atkins, right?
♪♪
Hello!
I totally can see you
holding the tray.
♪♪
[slurping]
- May I have your
attention, please?
Excuse me, everyone.
I was just informed there's
an active shooter nearby.
[collective groan]
Yes, another one.
Now, we're totally safe,
but as a precaution,
we will be locking down.
Now until we get
the all clear, please enjoy
endless Shooting Star fries
on the house.
- Oh, my God,
I totally will.
Yes.
- [Kerwin] How we doin', folks?
- [customer] Good, thanks.
- Can I get you
some more fries?
- [customer] That would
be awesome.
♪♪
[snoring]
- Well, that
complicates things.
♪♪
[sighing]
[bell ringing]
- Hey, you're awake.
Where are you going?
- I-I gotta go.
- Are you seriously going
back to him?
- You don't understand.
Bye.
- Goddamn balls.
Next time you see Stone,
he'll give you a bullet enema,
if you're lucky.
- Not if I give him
one first.
- Yeah, like you'll get within
ten miles of Officer Psychopath
after the shit
you pulled.
[electricity crackling]
- What was that?
- Shit.
We need to get
inside right now.
That's a Watkyn's storm.
[screaming]
[electricity crackling]
- Well, bad ass,
what's the plan?
Only a complete idiot
would go out in this.
- Isn't that
your car out there?
- Shit!
Oh, fuck!
Evelyn!
- Man, he runs weird.
[shouting]
- Ow! Jesus!
- Oh, Zachary.
That's why you shouldn't
join cults.
[groaning]
[grunting]
- Oh, fuck me.
Fell on my burn.
[grunting]
That's what I get
for saving your life.
- Oh, thank you.
[chuckling]
♪♪
[indistinct chatter]
This is why I tell you
to drink less water.
Just go.
[scoffs]
- I missed you too,
little bunny.
You holding up okay?
No one even
comes back here.
Come on.
It's been three years.
Let me hear that
annoying-ass voice of yours.
Please?
It's me.
See? They can't take
everything away.
See? You're still
the same annoying pest
who's great at
slicing tree fruit
and even better at making Tobin
feel like a piece of shit.
Hey. Hey.
Hey, when my manager
isn't looking,
I fart on his lunch.
Yeah.
Yeah, but I'm not talking,
like, a one-cheek squeak.
I'm talking like a full,
bullhorn fucking blast.
[laughing]
There you are. There you are.
[Kerwin] Jesus, these morons.
I gotta do everything
myself.
The hell are you two
doing back here?
You're not allowed here.
Oh, your keeper's
not gonna be happy.
- Don't touch her!
- Know your place!
How dare you speak...
[screaming]
Oh, we are not done.
- All of this is lies.
Lies!
- It's okay, everyone.
Reaper should be here
any moment.
I hope.
- You promised me!
I gave you four years.
Where's my beach?
My freedom?
That contract is bullshit!
All of this is bullshit!
[gunshot]
[gasping]
[laughter]
[applause]
- Well, that was stressful.
[laughs]
Anywho, lockdown's lifted.
You're all free to go.
And, please,
grab a Black Hole burger
for the road.
[chuckles]
Just you wait.
[wincing]
- Just give me
the napkin.
- No, I don't
want your help.
- You need it.
- Do I?
I'll show you.
[humming]
[groaning]
- You've done this before,
haven't you?
[grunts, chuckles]
[thunder crashes]
What is a Watkyn's storm,
anyway?
- A nuclear plant in
Watkyn's Harbor exploded
when the power went out,
poisoned the atmosphere.
The further east you go,
the worse it gets,
so we just got to
wait it out a while.
- How long is a while?
Oh, my God.
[thunder crashes]
- Oh, lucky shot.
- Really?
You wanna make it
interesting?
- Okay.
I sink it, I get to ask
you whatever I want.
You sink it,
same deal.
- Fine.
You go first.
You fucker.
[chuckles]
You played me.
- Me? No!
That was just luck.
But since you lost,
what's the coolest place
you've ever been?
- Are you seriously not
gonna ask me my first name?
- Oh, shit. Wait, no.
- Nope!
Disneyland.
- What's that?
- You never heard of
Disneyland?
I went there
when I was a kid.
Before the fall.
Lots of kids did.
It had a castle, rides,
princesses, Mickey Mouse.
- Why did this mouse
have a name?
Why was he so special?
- Excuse me.
Mickey was very cool.
He had a snappy little tux,
and he gave very
good hugs, too.
- You hugged a giant mouse?
That's disgusting.
I would never take a child
to this land of monsters.
- It was the happiest place
on earth, motherfucker.
Let me guess, the coolest
place you've ever been
is up your own ass.
- Ah, ah, ah, play the game.
The Container Store.
- The Container Store?
- Yes.
Picture a store full of
plastic containers, dispensers,
big, small,
all different colors.
When I get my own spot
in New San Francisco,
everything is gonna have
its own place to go.
- Do you own anything
of value?
- Ah... You already asked
your question.
Now it's my turn.
[laughs]
- What do you mean you've never
stepped in the ocean?
- Never have and never will.
- What? Why?
- Ghosts.
The ghosts in the ocean?
- There aren't any fucking
ghosts in the ocean!
- Have you ever been
to the ocean?
It's dark, man.
Look, the shadows
are the perfect
breeding ground for spirits.
And, have you ever heard of
ghost ships?
Who the fuck do you think
are piloting those ships?
Dolphins?
- You fucking dunce.
- You don't have to laugh, man.
- Yes, I do.
That is the dumbest shit
I've ever heard.
Next, you're gonna tell me
you believe in
life on other planets.
Oh, fuck off!
- Not aliens like this.
But come on,
you mean to tell me
that you think we're the only
ones in the whole universe?
Just us? It's a sad way of
thinking, if you ask me.
- You'd rather
believe in aliens?
- I rather believe
we're not in it alone.
- Oh, well, we're not alone,
because, you know,
ocean ghosts.
- Have you ever been to
the bottom of the ocean,
or space?
- Not lately.
- So you don't know
what's out there, do you?
- I'll give you that.
- Thank you.
- I never saw a Watkyn's storm
before today, obviously.
- But I've never seen
a llama and a goat
in the same room
at the same time.
And if we're being honest...
[both] I think they're
the same animal.
- I've never broken my arm.
- I've never
ridden a bicycle.
- I've never seen snow.
- I've never seen
a baby pigeon.
- I've never fucked
in a ball pit... twice.
[thunder crashes]
- Neither have I.
♪ Burgers and fries
and chips and pies ♪
♪ It was simple and good
back then ♪
[moaning, grunting]
- Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
The other way.
Left, left.
[screaming]
Oh my God! Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
[laughing]
You know what it was?
It was that motherfucker's
teeth, you know?
Like they would have been okay
on somebody else's face,
a bigger face.
Anyway, Adrian was
the last person
that I had sex with,
and it just wasn't very good.
- What, the teeth
got in the way?
- Think about it.
- Oh!
- Yes, they did.
[laughing]
[thunder crashes]
Hey, you were right.
I should have thanked you.
- Thank me for what?
Saving your ass
or crushing that ass?
- Gross!
[laughing]
- Look, I was thinking, um...
- Oh, I'm sorry,
is John Doe the motor mouth
actually tongue tied?
Oh, my goodness.
Come on, man,
spit it out!
You're giving me blue balls.
- You should
come with me.
- What?
- Do this delivery with me.
Look, the only reason
we've made it this far
is because
we've had each other.
- I can't.
- No, we could be partners.
- Partners?
What would I get out of
being your partner?
- What would you get?
You'd get this.
This delivery gets me
into New San Francisco.
It could get you in, too.
You can have a better life
on the inside.
Security, safety.
- No.
I've been on the inside.
I know what it's like.
- No, no, no. New San Francisco
is different than the O.C.
- You don't know that.
- I do.
I've seen it
with my own eyes.
- You really think
you know everything, don't you?
- Well, in this case, I do.
[sighing]
- I can't come with you.
- Okay. Okay,
okay, okay,
look, even if
you go back to Stone,
and even if you succeed
in killing him,
which you won't, by the way...
- Fuck you, I won't.
- There'll always
be another Stone,
and another and another.
Trust me, it's not worth it.
- You don't understand.
- Look, I spent decades dealing
with guys just like Stone.
You think he's the only
crazy asshole out here?
I don't want
that life anymore.
That's why I'm doing this,
to find a better one.
- There's nothing better!
I tried to find
something better,
and I got my brother killed.
- Look, you're
carrying too much,
the jacket, your guilt.
You can't carry around
t-the burden of your brother
for the rest
of your life!
- Well, that's easy
for you to say.
You never had a brother.
You never had anyone.
- Well, at least
I'm not a stubborn asshole
with a death wish because
she's feeling sorry for herself.
- I don't feel
sorry for myself.
- Well, you could've fooled me.
- You know what?
I don't fuckin' need this.
As soon as that storm's over,
I'm gone.
- Fine, you're slowing me
down anyway!
What are you looking at?
- No, no, no.
- So I'm sick of looking
at your shitty face!
[grunting]
But first,
for my collection.
[screaming]
[chuckling]
[whimpering]
Good.
He's all yours.
What the?
[gagging]
- I'm-I'm not leaving
without you...
fuckhead.
- Thanks, little bunny.
- I wanted a better
life for us,
and this isn't it.
Let's go find one.
♪♪
[thunder crackling]
- Stop moving!
- I can't get comfortable.
[rustling]
Stop moving!
- I can't sleep
because of you!
Go to sleep!
- I'm hungry.
[thunder rumbling]
♪♪
[gasping]
Cocksucker.
Fucking piece of shit!
Goddammit!
Fuck you,
you stupid motherfucker.
Piece of dog shit!
God!
Oh!
Fucking piece of shit.
God, come on.
Fuck!
Goddammit, why won't
this shit work?
- The gas must be out.
[sighing]
I can help.
- I don't need your help.
Fuck.
- You don't have to
carry that alone.
- Watch me.
- Come on, you're
gonna hurt yourself. Let...
- I said, I got it!
- Quiet, you have to let go.
- I can't just
let go, John.
- Yes, you can.
[sobbing]
- I can't.
♪♪
- How is it?
- It's good.
- Yeah?
- Yours?
- I'm eatin'
the same thing as you.
[chuckling]
- You were right.
We are not alone.
- Told you.
♪ From this moment ♪
♪ how can I feel ♪
♪ this small ♪
[birds chirping]
Damn.
Hello, Zachary.
Fucking dork.
- Hey, Sleeping Beauty,
I thought we were
on a timeline.
- Oh, it's "we" now?
- Don't make it weird.
- Anything you say, partner.
So, New Chicago?
- New Chicago.
♪♪