[John Doe]
Twenty years ago,
the world fell to shit.
A big ole apocalyptic dump.
Some bug took out
all the world's computers.
Power grids down,
the Internet gone!
And not having
easily accessible porn
freaked people the fuck out!
So, cities put up walls
to protect themselves
and threw the criminals
out into the chaos
so they could fight over
what was left,
which was not much,
mostly cars and guns.
Now insiders stay inside
and outsiders stay outside.
But there are people
who drive between,
badasses, legends,
humble motherfuckers like me
delivering precious cargo
from one walled city to another.
It's not an easy road
because all these assholes
want what I got.
And that's where the cars
and the guns come in.
♪♪
- How about some tunes?
Evelyn,
may I have this dance?
♪♪
♪ So you wanna be
a rock superstar ♪
♪ and live large ♪
♪ A big house
Five cars ♪
♪ You're in charge
Coming up in the world ♪
♪ Don't trust nobody ♪
♪ Gotta look over
your shoulder constantly ♪
- Holy shit!
[gunfire]
- Okay, I got Barry,
so who's left?
Gary, Larry.
Got it.
♪ You ever have big dreams
of makin' big cream ♪
♪ Big shot heavy hitter
in the Bentley ♪
♪ Be a snob and never
act friendly ♪
♪ You wanna have big fame
Let me explain ♪
♪ What happens to these stars
and their big brains ♪
Don't you do it!
Don't you even
think about it!
No!
♪ Then you get dissed
by the media and fans ♪
♪ Things never stay
the same way they began ♪
♪ I heard that some never
give full to the fullest ♪
♪ That's while fools end up
dining on the bullet ♪
♪ Think everything's fine
in the big time ♪
♪ See me in my Lex' with
the chrome raised high ♪
[screaming, gunfire]
[groaning]
Where the hell is this exit?
It's like a goddamn
maze in here.
[gunfire]
So, if I'm here,
then the exit is...
Oh, they have a Footlocker!
Oh!
Son of a bitch!
♪ Gained fame
started gettin' ignored ♪
♪ I warned him
Assured him ♪
♪ this ain't easy
take it from Weezy ♪
♪ Sleezy people
wanna be so cheesy ♪
♪ the fuckin' lethal ♪
♪ Assassins
Assassins ♪
♪ So you wanna be
a rock superstar ♪
♪ and live large ♪
♪ A big house
Five cars ♪
♪ You're in charge
Coming up in the world ♪
♪ Don't trust nobody ♪
♪ Gotta look over
your shoulder constantly ♪
♪ At night I think of you ♪
♪ I want to be
your lady baby ♪
♪ If your game is on
You need to call ♪
Hey there!
- ID!
[grumbling]
It's the milkman.
It must be our delivery.
- Yeah, they know me.
I'm here all the time.
Hey, Doug!
- Hey, John.
He's new.
- A virgin?
Oh, I got
a big package for you.
All the way from Paso Robles.
Some vultures
wanted it real bad,
but not bad enough.
You know what I mean?
Hey, that better be
unleaded 93 in there;
91 gives Evelyn the squirts.
[Abner]
- Payment's been
placed in the trunk.
And we have new deliveries
for you to, um, deliver.
- You're such a lamb.
Where to?
- Fresh batteries
for the Gainsboro Colony
and the usual shipment
of medicine
to New San Francisco.
- New San Fran?
It's been a month already?
- Um-hmm.
- Time makes a fool
of us all.
What's your name, slugger?
- Abner.
- Abner? Really?
I mean, it's a nice name,
but you don't meet too many...
well, anyway.
Come here, Abner.
How about you let me, uh,
slip inside...
- Outside...
you stay outside!
- Hey, take it easy.
Relax!
Atta boy.
All right,
this has been a gas.
I'll see your shiny faces
in a month.
Until then, Abner, eat up!
[snorts]
- What'd the milkman
bring us this time?
Tonight, we feast!
[John Doe]
See, a milkman's job
is never done.
It's a big world out there,
but at the end of the day
all that matters is me, Evelyn,
and the road.
♪♪
♪ How many
special people change ♪
♪ How many lives
are living strange ♪
- No way!
It's the Bosch Icon Premiere
windshield wipers!
Ha-ha!
Mwah!
♪ Slowly walking
down the hall ♪
♪ Faster than a cannonball ♪
♪ Where were you
while we were getting high ♪
♪ Someday you will
find me ♪
♪ Caught beneath
the landslide ♪
[yelling]
- Oh!
Get off!
- Give me the package,
Milkman!
- Goddamn vultures!
[screaming]
See that?
Tension spring
is keeping the blades flexible
for premium
wiping performance.
Oh...
♪♪
♪ Wake up the dawn
and ask her why ♪
[bullet ricochets]
♪ A dreamer dreams
she never dies ♪
♪ Wipe that tear
now from your eyes ♪
- Let's go!
Come on!
Let's go! Come on!
♪ Faster than
a cannonball ♪
♪ Where were you
while we were getting high ♪
♪ Someday you
will find me ♪
♪ Caught beneath
the landslide ♪
♪ And a champagne supernova
in the sky ♪
- It must be nice.
♪ Someday you
will find me ♪
Oh...
♪ Caught beneath
the landslide ♪
♪ And a champagne supernova ♪
♪ A champagne supernova ♪
[John]
At least I was a cute kid.
♪♪
[indistinct chatter]
Damn, look at
all these pedestrians, Ev.
All right,
time to turn on the charm.
Lookin' real efficient
today, Bill.
- Welcome back, John.
- Got a fresh box
of insulin for you.
Life must be good
if the diabetes are that bad.
Oh!
For me?
Oh, you shouldn't have.
You're coming home
with me, baby.
What am I taking
to San Diego for you?
- Stop!
The COO of New San Francisco
wants to talk to you.
Inside.
- Like inside inside?
- Let him through!
[guard]
- Open the gate!
- Holy fuck!
♪♪
[guard]
- Clear the perimeter!
♪♪
- You can park over there.
- Whew!
Y'all got some
big-ass trucks, huh?
All right.
Wait. Oh.
Oh, shit!
Oh! Wait!
Oh-oh boy!
Make sure
I leave you enough room
to get out, you know?
All right, here we go.
Okay.
There we go.
Whoo!
Okay.
- Strip.
- Oh, shit!
[whimpering]
♪♪
All right.
[sighing]
Guess I'm not getting
that knife back am I?
Lemony fresh, what's next?
[Raven]
Hi, John.
I'm Raven, COO of
New San Francisco.
Let me get you a drink.
So, tell me,
what's it like on the outside?
I'm sure you've
got some stories.
- Stories?
Of course, I do.
Okay, how about this one?
Once upon a time
there was a milkman.
Charming, devilishly handsome,
you know the type.
Well, he was an outsider.
Then one day
a miracle happened.
[gasping]
He was invited inside.
For no reason other than to
have a beer with a mysterious,
mildly intimidating
little white lady.
Ta-da!
- Fair enough.
We get a lot of milkmen
coming around here.
- Mm!
- But none have come
more than twice.
You, on the other hand,
have come dozens of times.
You're consistent, reliable,
you got a solid ass.
- Boom!
- I want to hire you.
- To do what exactly?
- What you do best.
Pick up a package,
bring it back.
- It can't be that simple.
- Well, there are
a few complications.
One, you can't know
what you're transporting.
- Oh!
Okay, I have a question.
- It's not organs.
- Dammit!
It's never organs.
So, what's
the second complication?
- The package is in
New Chicago.
[coughs, chuckles]
- Sorry, um,
thanks for the beer.
- John, sit!
- No, look, I'm sorry.
New Chicago is too far
and it's too risky.
- Sit!
Please.
Now, I've gotta tell you,
I've got a lot of power.
I can make peoples' desires,
their dreams,
their every wish come true.
So, John,
what do you wish for?
- Wow!
Okay, I wasn't ready for that.
Um, well, hmm, um,
unlimited gas.
Mm-hmm.
A new tee shirt,
this one's kinda smelly.
Toilet paper.
You have no idea what I would do
for some two-ply.
- I think I can do better.
- Three-ply?
- How about a tour?
- Mmm!
♪♪
[Raven]
- See anything you like?
- That's what I get?
A souvenir?
I mean, I'll take
that girl's hat.
- No, John,
this is your prize.
If you go to New Chicago
and bring this package
back for me,
I will make you a citizen
of New San Francisco.
- I get to live here?
- John, I remember
when the colonies
closed themselves off,
when they threw the murderers
and thieves and bad guys
out into the world
to fend for themselves
without law and order.
But you, you don't
belong out there.
You're not one of them.
John, if you do this run,
you won't be returning
with a package.
You'll be coming home.
♪♪
- Shit!
They're gaining on us!
Faster!
[gunfire]
♪
I'm on it, lil' bunny!
You can't find
shit back here!
If we're gonna steal shit,
we gotta stay organized.
Booyah!
[yelling]
♪♪
Holy shit!
Suck it now, motherfucker!
[laughing]
[officer]
- Gotcha!
- We're home free!
[explosion]
[chuckles]
- Let's go collect 'em, boys.
- Make yourself at home.
I'll be back in a minute.
♪♪
- What?
This is amazing.
[chuckles]
Perfect place
for an ambush.
[thumping]
Called it!
Shit!
Oh...
- You're home early.
- Yeah.
- Good day?
- Yeah, very good.
Come meet John.
John, this is
my husband, Noah.
- Huh.
Hi, I was just admiring
your, uh, this thing.
- It's an honor.
I've never met
a milkman before.
- And you've never
met a baby before,
have you, John?
- No.
- Her name is Dove.
- Hi, Dove.
Oh!
[chuckling]
- I think she likes you.
John's staying for dinner.
- I am?
♪♪
Mmm!
Yeah!
[laughter]
♪ The wheels on the bus
go round and round ♪
♪ Round and round
Round and round ♪
♪ The wheels on the bus
go round and round ♪
♪ All through the town ♪
♪ The mommies on the bus
say I love you ♪
♪ I love you
I love you ♪
♪ The mommies on the bus
say I love you ♪
♪ All through the town ♪
- Oh, I almost forgot
dessert.
- Oh, yeah.
- Jell-O!
- John, aren't you tired
of almost dying every day?
And looking in
the rearview mirror
and only seeing yourself?
Aren't you tired of
always being alone?
So, what do you say, John?
Will you drive?
♪♪
You have 10 days
to pick up the package
and deliver it here.
One second over
and the deal expires.
Can you handle that?
- I can handle that.
You fixed my window!
[gasps]
Smooth!
- See you in 10 days, John.
- Until then, Jell-O, Raven!
Oh, okay...
Oh, boy.
Yep, got it!
Here we go!
All right. Jell-O!
- Bye, John!
Bye!
Get it back to its mother.
Ugh!
The payment's in
your apartment.
[groaning]
♪♪
- Peekaboo.
- Hi.
Bet you kids are wondering
why we pulled you over today.
- I'm not sure
what you think we did,
but-but we didn't
hurt nobody.
I swear we're innocent.
- Oh.
[laughter]
That's some fresh
material right there.
You know, when I was a boy,
my father told me
about a police chief
named Breton.
Have you ever heard of him?
- No, sir, but I...
- Then stop talking.
It was rhetorical.
Well, this Police Chief Breton,
he cleaned up Manhattan,
which is a burrow
of Old New York,
in case you don't know
your geography.
But Chief Breton
had a theory
that little sins
could attract big sins.
And so, he would stamp out
those little sins
like a match before it
ever caught fire.
And you know what?
By jukie it worked.
Crime went down
because he showed
no tolerance, no mercy,
not even for
petty vandalism,
defecating in the park.
Gosh, not even looting.
He saved New York,
and I'm saving this country.
Now then, you two
have a choice.
You and your lover...
- Sister, we-we have
the same mom and dad.
- I know what a sister is.
As I was saying,
you and your sister
have a choice.
You can resist,
in which case,
I'll have to napalm
the both of you.
Or one of you can
make the tough choice.
Take your own life.
Consider it your punishment
for crimes committed
against the law.
♪♪
- Eat my ass, motherfucker!
[gun firing]
- [Agent Stone]
Huh, look at
all those brains.
Who knew?
Officer?
Let's see...
There you go.
Oh, that's
why you're quiet.
You're from Orange County.
I've heard the barbaric things
those insiders
will do to their own
to keep them in line.
But you, you won't need
words to let others know
you crossed paths
with Agent Stone.
Let's go, boys.
[screaming]
♪♪
Just in case,
you decide to take the path
of your brother.
You have a nice day
now, ma'am.
♪♪
- Oh, shit!
[alarm beeping]
Tommy!
[beeping intensifies]
- What's the rush?
Not like you're
going anywhere.
[chuckling]
- A little help, Tommy?
- Saving your ass
once again.
You're lucky.
This baby blew the pants
off a vulture last week.
Took me days to get the blood
and toenails out of the tile.
So, you got
a delivery for me
or are you just here
to chap my ass?
- Neither.
I need a map.
- A map?
- Yeah.
- Well, hell,
why didn't you say so?
Come on over.
Where you headed?
Got a lot of people going to
the great white north.
Hear there's a steel rush.
Huh, I got a route here
through the redwoods
that would make
your nipples spin
like a lady
in the burley-q show.
[chuckling]
- I'm not going north.
- Huh.
- I'm going east.
- East?
How far east are we talking?
- New Chicago.
- Give me your belt, John.
- Why?
- You're clearly suicidal,
so give me your goddamn belt!
- Hey, stop that, man!
It's a once in
a lifetime opportunity.
- You have no idea
what's out east, do you?
- Of-of course, I don't.
I've never driven
past Barstow.
That's why I'm here
seeing your pretty face.
[scoffs]
- Okay...
Okay, New Chicago.
New Chicago is
2,132 miles from here.
You know what that means?
- I shouldn't walk.
[groaning]
[chuckles]
- It means 2,132 miles
of no cover.
No protection,
no safe harbor.
The only shelter means
dealing with
a bunch of brainwashed,
burger worshipping screwballs.
- I'm not that desperate.
- You might be.
The roads out east
aren't like the roads here.
You won't be dealing with
your run of the mill vultures.
These boys are predators.
Even the people trying
to bring the law back
are just as dangerous.
There's chaos
out there, John.
You'll be dealing
with it alone.
So, I've gotta ask...
Is the risk
worth the reward?
Oh...
You're gonna have to
go through Vegas, John.
We both know
who rules Vegas.
["Wheels on the Bus" playing]
♪♪
[engine roaring]
[laughter]
[engine approaching]
♪♪
- Why is the map so small?
Wait, is that a dick?
Whoa!
[tires screeching]
Gah!
You know, it's really rude
not to introduce yourself
before pulling a gun
on someone.
[gun firing]
Oh, this is ruder!
[muttering]
How about you lower
that sorry excuse for a gun
and I'll lower
my exceptionally cool blade.
We don't want things
to escalate, do we?
[gun cocking]
Okay.
See? Now things
have escalated.
It's you.
["Wheels on the Bus" playing]
[laughing]
We don't have time
for this.
So, how about you
tell your partner
to come out from
where he's hiding...
Okay, whoa!
Touched a nerve.
You're hurt.
I get it.
There's a way
out of this, okay?
[laughter]
[laughter continues]
["Wheels on the Bus" playing]
♪♪