I must admit,
I've been seeing another shrink
while consulting you, I confess.
I would like to know,
when my life started to crack.
Mr.Adelaoui, stop harassing me.
I need to work on the file, do you understand? Thank you.
Hi girls.
Hello.
Are you well?
I quit.
What?
It's a pigsty here.
That arrogance is cute.
You are gone all the time.
In theory, you work because I'm away. Right?
We just met twice this week, and I'm your babysitter.
Don't lower yourself,
you're much more than that for me.
It's a dredge plan, isn't it?
I can go to court for harassment.
OK.
I'm a lawyer.
All I do is look after your
daughters in your absence.
Eliott,
We cannot limit ourselves to
confined roles for existence.
I gave you so much freedom.
It's normal, you emancipate yourself.
What?
Well, yes,
you want to show you have character,
that you are someone free, self-employed.
I see that in you, don't be deceived.
I see you.
Your daughters are unhappy.
Get out.
I quit.
Here,
I propose something. You go to take a break,
and to come back in one hour.
No.
I'll increase your pay by 5%.
20%? Do you want to ruin me?
OK! You take the food out of
the mouths of my sweethearts.
No problem.
OK. Get out of here.
OK, get out. That's fine.
You're saving me, Sophie. I owe you.
Girls, this is Sophie.
She will be baby-sitting you. Behave yourselves.
I'm glad it's you, they adore you.
I prefer authority over obsequiousness.
Hey! Axel, congratulations!
My photo, my...Photo!
It's not done yet.
Let's not re-shoot that for the 500th time.
Yes. Yes.
Let's just get on with it. More enthusiasm.
I understand, more enthusiasm.
Yes.
Hey! Wow!
Axel!
Well, this is it!
What's going on, what?
A wedding and everything is...
Axel! You are...
one of the four pillars of my existence.
Even though I don't understand what it means.
But it's just that...
We didn't always much know in friendship...pardon!
Make it simple.
Yeah, more concise, more...
Yes.
Punchy, maybe.
Hey! Axel! Uh...
What a wonderful day, uh...
My photo, what?
Life isn't a local phenomenon.
It is a miracle of life.
The enabling conditions
that made life possible on Earth.
Yes.
If you take the Big Bang and
not a trick, a separate point,
if we take the planar satellite which
observes the astronomical radiation,
Yes.
...we are surrounded by the Big Bang.
We are surrounded, suddenly,
we get the feeling of being in a phew.
Extrapolating this idea that the universe is an egg,
we consider Him creating life.
We have a surprise alongside Vincent,
a little thing has been prepared for you.
Vincent!
(SUSANNA BY ADRIANO CELENTANO)
* Seven days in Portofino *
* More than a month in Saint Tropez *
* Then you told me... *
* "Honey" *
Maybe we are on the shelf of a mad scientist
who reflects on the concept of life.
Mm.
We are at an advanced stage of
civilization which unites people.
Everybody!
* Susanna, Susanna *
Come on, sing everyone!
* Susanna, Susanna my love*
* Me, a tourist from Ticino *
* I, the queen of Pigalle *
* I said to you "come away with me" *
* And a triangle of Rhinestones *
* I told you, "I'll come back" *
* I told you "yes" *
* "But no! Mister, don't worry. Go!" *
* Susanna, Susanna...*
And even on the question of species barrier,
between ape and man for example,
it's very artificial, because the base is the same.
So this would not have been evolved
at the base, to make entities so diverse.
* Susanna, Susanna, Susanna, Susanna my love*
* ...and you shall return to Juorno *
To you, Suzanna.
I spend my days with morons
who think of starting "The day today",
and will be acquitted.
You okay?
This girl is completely crazy,
We're going to separate. I saw her in bad shape.
Shit, but...
but you're going bad all the time.
No, no.
That was different.
Is that all you have to say?
Mr.Mallet?
Yeah!
Hey?
No, he's a guy I know.
What are you doing there?
Good evening.
Good evening, I am a distant cousin of the witness.
Okay, let me introduce a friend,
he is a former client.
What were you accused of?
Stoups.
Narcotics.
And by the way, I wanted to thank you
for getting me out of the business.
You never had the head of a dealer, anyway.
That's nice of you.
It's true.
Oh bah! He was listening, he's a bit...
it's not going very well.
In any case, you look very content.
It's a lot of work, you know.
Besides, I wanted to take advantage of it.
Actually, I'm looking for a job...
Yes.
I have nothing more to see in the middle, and all that.
Mm.
So if you hear about
an internship somewhere or something,
it would help me.
Okay.
Personally, I'm looking for a trainee, but...
No.
I'm already having trouble, you see...to pay,
so I haven't committed to anyone.
If I hear...
I can work for free, for you.
Uh...yeah, well...
It seems strange to me, but...
But you never did it right!
No. No...
I have the motivation, however, it's already...
Yes that's good.
I am worried about my future.
Me as well.
Oh good.
What do you mean?
I meant...mine.
Oh OK.
Yes. Yes.
It will be fine.
(THE LOOK BY METRONOMY)
* You're up and you'll get down *
* You never running from this town *
* Kinda think you said *
* You'll never get anything better than this *
* 'Cause you're going round in circles *
* And everyone knows you're trouble *
* Cause you read it in a big book *
* Now you giving me the look look *
* But just remember how we shook shook *
* And all the things we took took *
* This town's the oldest friend of mine *
* This town, this town... *
She says you took a knife and you planted it.
No, she did it all by herself!
She's a sick woman.
I would never raise my hand on her.
Did people see you go out?
I don't know.
Oh, sure.
At the same time, when you want to
sleep with a woman,
you put yourself in a tight spot.
You're not in the midst of this world.
You got Jamal.
He is bad.
No! He is a brilliant lawyer.
No, Victoria.
I swear, I'm ready for anything,
but a 'no' from you.
Well, I see that, but...
I'm not joking, seriously.
How can I prove she did it alone?
She's a tart...
She's a tart, she wants my skin,
she wants to destroy me.
Maybe you don't remember,
you took out a knife
to threaten her.
No, I didn't do that.
I didn't want to kill her, I'm innocent, okay?
She is obsessed with knives. She dreams of it.
She has plenty of knives,
she threatens me with it.
What's the point of accusing you?
She wants me to pay up.
Well, dammit, you know me!
I'm not capable of that.
I can't be your lawyer.
It's been five minutes and
you bring up our friendship.
Ethically, it's not right.
I was at the your wedding, I can be called to testify. No.
Get Jamal, he's the best.
He does not believe me.
Yes, that's good!
If we accept all clients speak the truth,
we would be unemployed.
But you believe me.
Doesn't matter! I can't defend you
because you are a friend.
I would never measure up to this case.
You've won big trials.
I lost them!
A lot of them.
The ones I won were not
when the customer was at stake.
This is different.
Usually I don't care whether
they are guilty or innocent.
Don't you want to defend an innocent man?
No, I prefer to defend a guilty person.
If you are innocent, what I would wish think is that
"you are my friend",
I would be afraid, I would not have the right to make mistakes.
I don't care about that! That's all in theory.
I'm in deep shit and I need help.
It's your job, I'll pay you.
It's impossible.
You must be open to the world.
I already feel very open,
very explosive out in the world.
I'm talking about a world of sex.
It's not for lack of trying, but...
I don't feel very concerned by sex, right now.
I don't want to hear your story.
And stop the drugs.
I don't take drugs.
I don't want anything happening to you.
I prefer not to talk about my health.
I prefer to talk about love, money.
I say everything and not necessarily
what you come to hear.
I see someone spies on you.
But I can't seem to see
who, nor how.
Someone is watching you.
Hello. What are you doing here?
I was on the way to school.
No just kidding, I brought you your purse.
Thank you.
Girls!
I wanted to talk about something else...
Uh...
Come with me. Hold that for me, please. Thank you.
Hold on. Come, come.
Since my separation, I've lived with a friend.
And in fact, I've stopped dealing,
so that I may pay more for the apartment
and I resume my studies.
But my dream is to be a lawyer.
Okay.
But in between drugs, bakery and avocado, it's a bit...
Yes...no, no...
I would like to take up law studies,
and help you on the side...
Excuse me. Hello?
In the next call,
I'll let go of your cousin,
he'll have trouble finding a lawyer,
24 hours before the hearing. OK?
What do you want?
Be your apprentice,
and eventually your personal assistant.
I'm looking for a babysitter.
Yes, that would includes this as well.
I could be your "Au pair".
And you have room for this?
No, it's true.
Among other things, it's not just that.
And I don't judge your way of life,
you can leave dragging your panties.
I could re-arrange with pleasure.
Well, no, not in that sense!
I misspoke.
Mm. Yes.
I could be...
your man from the shadows.
I could solve your problems and then, if you like,
become your assistant.
We could try out for a week.
Yes.
Okay?
If it doesn't work out, we could stop there. OK?
Yeah.
Good. Okay.
Okay. Great.
One week.
Yeah, I can...
Where do I sleep?
Well, here. In fact, this is your bed.
There are only two rooms.
Oh OK! This is fine.
On a side note, no drugs here.
Oh yes, I'm in the clean phase of my life.
No worries there.
OK perfect.
Well, I'm going to wash myself.
I'm going to get ready.
Are you going out tonight?
No, I have an appointment with a guy from work.
Okay. Well, I didn't think so.
Could I cook?
Great! Grab that card from my purse for groceries.
Yeah OK!
Cool!
What's the code?
3668,
Girls, this is Sam who will take care of you.
It's beautiful!
It's very beautiful!
Don't you want to lie down?
Is it okay?
Yeah, yeah.
Finally, Doc. I'm asking a lot of
questions about my life.
You're smiling. Is this a joke?
No.
No, I meant...
I'm talking about what you would like to discuss.
Bah! We could discuss that two seconds later, right?
Yes.
You see, I...
I have a friend who asked me for help.
And if I did help, puts me in a complicated situation.
But I have to reassure him.
I introduce people who I consider professionally,
and I hope it does.
But...
In the hindsight, I feel guilty
not being able to help him.
I'm wondering,
I don't know how to go about it.
You see?
Yeah.
It bothers me to let him down.
I understand.
It's complicated, he's a friend.
Finally we got together. He counts on me.
I can't read your mind, there.
Oh yeah.
Oh no.
OK, I'll be quiet. Let's start again.
OK.
But as his lawyer if I defend badly...
If he loses, I will not recover.
It will torture me. I'll have to ask myself
if I could have done better.
Well, come on, that's enough.
This isn't serious.
No.
Come on, it's okay.
This could evolve positively.
In any case, don't worry, I won't judge.
I was more in it, there.
Was it okay?
If you want to talk, I'm here.
You know, Sam,
I have imperfections which hides enormous qualities.
I don't doubt it.
Our proximity is a handicap,
this case must be made strong.
If I accept, I need to understand why
Eve decided to stab herself, to accuse you.
I need to know everything.
How was it, sexually?
She wants me to pay for her ex.
Did she sleep with a lot of guys?
Yes.
We were two molecules that attracted but
one was full of gangrenous atoms.
Not too many metaphors with the judge.
I'm paying all this for her ex-psychopaths,
and she doesn't give in to sex.
I didn't force her to live with me, I didn't tie her up.
I'm successful with women
and not wanting to stab one.
Stick to the question, Mr.Kossarski.
Yes. I never struck, offered resistance,
and vice versa.
No! She says you snatched her panties violently.
No! I may have done it,
but in an act of sexual riches and fantasy.
In a playful way, not violence.
But no. Even if I wanted, that's impossible.
She did not wear it.
Let's come back to the seriousness of facts.
We don't solve a couple's disputes.
Of course.
Good.
During the act, did you see
anyone or a witness watch you?
No.
No human witness, but Jacques, her dog.
He was there and it bothered me.
Miss Scorr's dog?
Yes.
And you saw him during the act?
No, he was looking at me. And it disrupted me.
Are we putting him in jail?
Yes, we put him in jail.
Hello!
Hello.
What are you doing here?
I can see my daughters, right?
Are you okay?
I'm part of a writers blog.
You have a central place in my story.
You inspired me a lot.
Girls, stop playing, we're going to eat.
David, say goodbye to the girls.
OK, OK.
Don't underestimate my authority.
Don't underestimate my indifference.
I'm worried, I was a no-go with the judge.
I thought she was going to throw out the complaint.
I'm anxious...
Vincent! Calm down, I'll get you out of there.
I have not done anything, believe me. Talk to her.
The Convaincs,
it's unjust, irrational.
I can't talk to her.
Please.
No!
This trial...
I don't have the right to do that.
Do you understand?
I'm on my knees.
Really, calm down. Get some rest.
Rest?
Ciao.
The judge advised me not to take this case.
Why do you have that phone?
It's unbreakable.
It's designed for the military.
Oh damn, that guy!
Good evening.
I'm IntelloBG75,
Oh no, I don't think so.
Yes, yes.
Oh? I didn't recognize you. Ah yes.
Good evening.
Over there.
Oh no, that's not what I thought I would do.
Sorry. No it's me.
I don't want to. I prefer to get to know one other.
Why did you bring me to your room, then?
This is the only room where we can talk quietly.
Can I sit on the bed?
Yes.
Yes of course.
We mustn't feel compelled, if we don't feel
any attraction for each other.
For you and for me.
We're still...
I find you very desirable.
Did you want to drink something?
Do you have whiskey?
Yes.
I love whiskey with sugar.
Me too! I like it the same way.
Is that true?
No, that was to find something common.
I don't know what's going on, it's difficult.
I don't see the emergency exit.
Yeah.
Well, it's not far off.
What?
The exit.
We all look for it,
somewhere, right?
I wanted to drown myself in sex.
Yes.
That happen to you?
Perhaps, you need a vacation?
Shall I accompany you?
Good and bad news.
The maid?
Look.
I created an account and
asked the guests to be friends.
And they accepted?
Look at my picture.
They don't know who I am. You get the idea!
That's good. It's awesome.
And the bad news?
You know your ex's blog?
No why?
He wrote about you.
Oh yes, no, I know. But I'm not interested.
Look at it anyway.
Your name is Vicky Spock, you defend psychopaths.
You are unstable.
He's talking about cases you've pleaded.
He has a reading tomorrow with the
"Crazy Blogger Club".
They meet up every Wednesday morning in a bar.
They talk about literature in general.
If not, their books, scenarios...
She didn't care what would
happen to this low level dealer.
The important thing was, to feel the €3,000,
the guy was paying in €10 bills,
to this shameless lawyer.
Vicky S. splurged drug money.
In addition, she slept with senior judicial officials.
She had a relationship with a famous judge
and contacted the press, nourishing hope
to entrust important business.
She represents the incompatibility
between a feminist stature to a humanist.
And her fascination for money and power.
I watched as a hummingbird caught in the storm.
I was only a pawn, invisible,
but I could see everything in secret.
Thank you very much, David.
It's great, there's everything...
the intimate life that mixes with professional life,
the bumpy side of legal affairs.
Makes great material to feed the blog.
Don't hesitate to be interactive,
this must be on the trans-media.
Today,
so, offer your ideas, what not.
Go ahead, nurture the workshop with these ideas.
Yes. Flood the blogs and social networks.
Facebook, Twitter.
How could you write these rumors about me?
This is dangerous for me, for our children.
Is it because I didn't give you any money?
I regained the trust that I had lost.
I have a recognized talent, it's my job.
I'm sorry you didn't notice.
I am inspired by my experience.
I always wanted to do that.
You were in my life. This is auto-fiction.
You barely masked the names!
You mess about with my reputation without
even thinking about the consequence.
You reveal things that I confided in you.
Do you realize the gravity of the situation?
You put out confidential details.
It's just a bloody blog!
Just a bloody blog?
Stop holding back information.
You embalm a reality, I lived with.
Now this reality belongs to me and I want to share it.
Hi Suzanna, I can't talk to you.
Just 30 seconds.
I can't talk to you, you are a witness.
You are aware that you defend a monster?
This asshole broke-up my marriage.
I'm sorry.
I have pictures when it was happened.
I spent 10 months for this day.
My parents took out a loan for €20,000,
I understand that.
The investment of it, of course. And the work that went in.
But I have nothing to do with that.
The guy is a psychopath.
Listen, we'll talk about it, in a year's time. Sorry.
In a year?
This chapter is over,
Vincent risks great pain, he deserves a defense.
The guy is a misogynist. I would, would you?
No, this has nothing to do with it.
What has misogynist got to do,
with women as victims by nature.
I'm sorry! I've to go.
Hello.
How's it going, girls?
Did you have a good day?
Yeah.
Did you know the judge arranged for
an expert on Eve's dog?
Oh yeah?
Ouch.
Careful.
David showed me his script.
What?
He's a neurotic blogger riding my back.
I'm going to sue him.
Is it true your slept 497 times with a judge?
No, of course not.
When I hear we had sexual intercourse, it's all fiction.
Girls, enough of the iPad, now.
Oh yes, no more.
Girls, stop the iPad.
No, it's not good for you.
Come on, listen to me a little. Come on.
Stop the iPad, give it to me.
Come on! Well, listen to me, here!
Come on, give me that.
No.
Let go, it's mine.
The dog expert says, the smell is stressing him.
This dog is jealous.
Eve keeps him for protection,
He never corroborated my version.
Sexual?
No, not even a touch.
Maybe you scared him by striking her.
No and of what value would that be, scientifically?
Doesn't prove anything, she doesn't love me.
Who would seriously take the testimony of a pet?
Hello.
Hello, this is it.
I acknowledge the theft,
there was a lot of money. But not aggression,
It's not true, I did nothing. Security had a vengeance.
He wanted to humiliate me in front of all customers.
He hit me with a belt.
He inflicted a cut, but the blow is gone.
David comes from a bourgeois family, supposedly.
He does not give a damn about money.
He has time for purists.
For purists?
Yes, it's a luxury anyway.
To be able to play the moralists, it's naive.
I made-up bull, I had no choice.
So why does he reveal it all?
He suffers from a lack of of personality. He's a slacker.
He is obsessed with the idea that
information must flow.
He loves the idea of ​​transparency.
He sees himself in righteousness. And I, in evil.
Did you sleep with magistrates?
Yes, much earlier though,
I was a little obsessed with sex.
I liked this almost regressive state
and self-sterilizing.
Would it bother you?
No.
Excuse me, I'm a little stressed,
I myself have troubles...
As for the blow I am...
Do you mind if you talk about it?
No, no...
I'm in a situation...that's troublesome.
I confided in someone,
and now he wants to use it against me.
I wonder...
do I attack it, out maneuver or crush him?
Don't cave in, defend yourself.
So do I attack him? Is that it?
Obviously, that's your job.
Yes, yes, I know how to do that. Yes.
Is everything alright?
All good. It's you who is the accused.
Excuse me,
I just wanted an external point of view.
I love sex.
I feel how you feel, thousand times over.
How do you know how I feel?
I know that's all.
I feel everything exponentially.
Have you been sensitive for a long time?
Always.
I learned to live with it.
I love myself more than most people love each other.
I work on it every day.
I love myself to give more pleasure to the other.
I have a body, I respect it.
I don't pretend, I don't cheat.
I embrace the one who spends a few hours with me.
Sex isn't a priority, at the moment.
I wonder why wallow in with such pleasure,
without asking questions.
Sex, sex, sex. I'm into a short cut.
It's like coming back to...
the state of an infant.
Do you understand?
Stop asking me this, otherwise
you will continue on that couch.
Suddenly...
I was panic-stricken.
Everything I've experienced in the week has re-emerged.
And his body seemed heavy on me.
So heavy that I had to get rid of him.
As if I had committed a crime and...
I had to get rid of him, at once.
I pretended to do something,
I went out, he stayed in the room.
And then I panicked.
Sam.
What's the matter?
What's going on?
What's happening?
Calm down, everything is fine, breathes calmly. Breathe.
OK?
I'm going to ask you a few questions.
Where are you? Where are you?
You hear me?
Have you ever had these attacks?
Did he rape you?
A dangerous position?
It's good, I know that, think of something pleasant.
Think of little dwarfs, small rabbits to the sea.
Lexo...
Everything is fine.
Shut up.
You want Lexomil?
Yes. Where are they?
On the book shelf.
In the book shelf? OK.
I got them.
All right, open your mouth.
Here. Here, swallow it.
Here, lie down to circulate blood.
Breathe calmly.
Here, breath.
Breathe.
OK. Do you feel better?
Yes.
Thank you.
Were you a nurse?
No, I helped guys who felt sick after crack.
I need a vanishing point.
Look at the sky.
Okay?
I need space.
You got some space.
Everything is fine.
I need to see in front of me.
Hope I'm not disturbing you?
Oh no, it's okay, she's better now.
Sorry.
Well, I'm leaving.
I'm not sure to go three-way.
That's not what you think.
I look after the children.
Children?
Well, it was nice seeing you.
I'm leaving.
No stay.
Hey guy!
Is he stupid, or what?
It's not serious or anything.
Deep breaths.
I'm going to bed.
Could you come with me, please?
What?
Just two seconds.
Yeah.
In my room.
Yeah, okay.
Come.
Let's go slow.
(WITHOUT HER BY HARRY NILSSON)
* I spend the night in a chair thinking she'll be there *
* But she never comes *
* And then I wake up and wipe the sleep from my eyes *
* And I rise to face another day without her *
* Do-do-do, do-do-do-do, do-do-do *
* It's just no good anymore *
* When you walk through the door of an empty room *
* And then you go inside and set a table for one *
* It's no fun when you spend a day without her *
* Do-do-do, do-do-do-do, do-do-do *
* We burst the pretty balloon *
* Took us to the moon *
* Such a beautiful thing *
* But it's ended now *
* And it sounds like a lie *
* If I say I'd rather die than live without her *
* Do-do-do, do-do-do-do, do-do-do *
* Without her, do-do-do-do, do-do-do *
Miss Spick, I regret to inform you that you are being
summoned by the 'The Order of Lawyers' for contacting
one of the witnesses in the Scorr-Kossarski case.
Article 183 of Decree No 91-1197 dated 27 November 1991,
Organization Of Advocate Profession states that:
Any contravention of laws and regulations,
any violation of the professional rules, any ...
In 12 years of practice,
Victoria Spick has never committed a mistake.
I call into question
the accusation of this woman who sued her.
I would say "pursued to her home",
and even harassed her.
My colleague did not go voluntarily to meet her.
She even explained that she could
possibly influence the case.
Should she be remanded for addressing that woman,
to say that she can't even talk to her?
I don't believe that,
Your Honor.
Blocking her from this case would have consequences
for my colleague.
May I state, she has two dependent
children she raises by herself.
The father of the children...
a fantastic artist, has not paid her in 7 months.
My dear colleagues,
do not impose a suspension
that would aggravate her situation
more than it is already.
Please.
We have decided to suspend you for 6 months.
Till then, you are not to practice.
You knew it yourself, colleague.
It is forbidden to discuss the case with a witness.
You accepted to defend someone you knew,
you should have been more vigilant.
I'm aware this will be hard on you.
But I never familiarized my clients or witnesses.
One must be very careful!
I don't eat with my client,
when on trial in the province.
But I don't dine with a client, or drink.
No one has my number, they go through cabinets,
by the Secretary, there is a filter.
If you leave them no power, it's good.
If they understand,
you can stop defending them at any time,
the guy will respect you.
We must remain in control of the situation.
You okay?
You look completely groggy. Is that a side effect?
No, the desired effect.
Why don't you stop taking that medication?
I need to go down.
I'm here to help.
Sam, you are really great,
thank you very much for everything you done.
But I will have more
to talk to you, with what is happening to me.
No, no, but I...
I'd rather you go.
Take away from this and you should rebound.
I can still help you on the case.
No, you can't.
Jamal took over the case.
I have no control on anything there.
But it's good.
You're very nice.
I'm not nice.
Victoria, this is Vincent.
I don't know if you spoke to Jamal,
in any case, this should be between Eve and me.
He will surely withdraw the complaint.
Thank you for what you did.Thank you very much.
Victoria, this is Jamal.
I convinced Eve not to withdraw her complaint,
I explained to her, what she risked doing that.
We'll play it soft so that it ends in dismissal.
Apart from that, they got back together.
Kisses, later.
You did a crappy job, Victoria.
You could have gotten into business law,
social law, public law, Real estate law...
Yes, yes, I know my options...
You could have been much more fulfilled.
To blossom, that's a trick for a relative treat.
You never made a professional mistake and
then you go talking to a witness.
That's the most you did.
I didn't know it would end bad.
Sorry, can we talk about this later?
You see, you're passive aggressive.
Your actions speak for themselves.
You're a fake person.
If you had assumed your aggressive side,
you would have lived better.
And you would not have been the victim of the impact,
rather you would have dominated it.
I feel I'm not a victim of the impact.
I feel flexible. I bounced on impact.
Sorry, but I prefer to be an ally than your friend.
I love you very much, Victoria, hence my frankness.
What do you see?
It's the same.
Not much.
What do you mean?
It's always the same thing, we go around
with the drug history, with you.
What do you mean, drug history with me?
Why do you still see that?
There's always drugs.
I don't do drugs. There must be some interference.
No, no.
You may see me with an ex-dealer at my house.
This isn't at all what you believe, I fired him.
I see...
a professional breakdown.
What!?
I don't pay you to tell me what I already know.
Tell me about the future, not the past.
Normally, I am impressed by your visions,
but this...
I'm not a shrink! I say what I see.
I see drugs, I see some malice.
So, is there anything good in those cards?
Nothing at all, not even a thin one?
Always the same thing?
Your needles have a great effect on me.
These aren't needles.
You are thinking nonsense.
Do you talk fantasies with your colleagues?
No.
How's the sex going?
I mainly enjoy in my work.
Pleasure, has nothing to do with enjoyment.
Do we agree?
I did not grasp the nuance...
Finally, I did not understand.
The pleasure you take to your work
has nothing to do with enjoyment.
Do you agree?
Mm
Good.
Probably, yes.
Great.
We've started to close the vacuum.
Where are you? With your friend, Vincent?
We got together, I don't understand.
Whether he did it or not, for that matter,
was completely masochist.
Looks like I've bet on all the bad horses.
Or that the eggs are all in the same basket,
And I am afar from the basket.
I love you.
Six months later...
Hello?
Hi Victoria, this is David.
I have a great announcement to make,
I got the "Tumblr Award for Talent 2016"
for Vicky Spock, I have an important proposal.
I'm restless. Falling apart.
If you'd like to get back together, feel free.
I feel strongly at the moment.
Otherwise I hope you are fine with the girls. Kisses, ciao.
You've reached the answering machine of Samuel and Mal.
Sam, it's Victoria.
I'm not very good...
I need to see you.
Excuse me?
It's good to see you.
Me too.
Did you change something?
Well no.
Change what?
I don't know.
You look good, you look good.
Oh good! Thanks, that's nice.
So, what do you do?
I got into law books and took courses.
This a joke?
Not at all.
You told me to bounce back. I did.
And you?
Me, uh...
Every hour weighs a ton.
I've the impression you hit rock bottom.
Yeah.
And know that in the abyss, there is nothing.
You missed the girls.
I also missed them.
You could come back here, some time,
past, I head out of the water.
OK, let me help you in your job.
When does you suspension end?
It's been over 10 days.
I need work. I can't live like this.
I need to reconnect with community.
You are beautiful.
Victoria, this is Vincent.
Wanted to remind you,
One of my ex, Leslie Chevalier,
accuses me of harassment.
I don't know how she knew about the case.
She pit Eve against me,
as a result, she is railed.
I know you're mad at me, but call me.
This is Jamal,
speaks to Vincent, he fights the doorman,
comes in a bathrobe to my office, he is unmanageable.
I need to know the whole case,
why did you send these messages?
Leslie treats me like a psychopath without reason.
She was ultra-violent, so I clarified things.
Clarified things?
It's a thin gap between clarification and harassment.
Why did you not tell me?
Might have helped you a little yourself!
Oh, don't take me on a ride with your moral codes.
This is exactly why I need to be defended, not judged.
I left 6 months of hell.
I am the victim,
it was me who got tossed in a cell for 15 days,
while who filed a complaint against me,
loved me 10 days earlier.
Calm down.
You're the only one who can help you.
You will hurt yourself if you're worried.
Vincent must assert himself
as...
a victim.
Thanks Sam, that was very enlightening.
I don't think of your relationship with women,
I need to understand things.
And you harass me so I may defend you?
Don't talk to me about that,
I'm dangling on a camisole.
Why did you get back with Eve?
It's complicated.
The bullshit, for sure.
Sex, mainly.
I thought it might work, but she wants to be God,
from what I understand.
Jamal is right, you're both crazy.
I don't follow you anymore.
Don't judge me, I beg you.
Vincent,
Victoria touched the limits of her profession.
She must learn to separate work and emotions.
Promise me,
that you will resume your practice.
You know what that means?
That's 15 days!
Looks like you're doing a puzzle.
Let me do it.
Don't underestimate my commitment.
I didn't underestimate it, I was just wondering.
Listen, Sam. I...
I think in my head? That...
When I think about what we did the other night,
it was very good. Absolutely.
But, I think it's not good for us to...
'mix' everything together, in our lives,
business and everything.
It's too much to...
Mm.
Come see. Your recidivist, here,
Nicolas Santos, has damaged everything in your office.
Everyone is shocked.
Look, he tossed your files in the air,
he threw the table, smashed it up!
Smashed the chairs.
There's more to it than buying them.
Look, everything is damaged.
That's the only patch
I was able to save!
That guy was in some state!
What did he want?
I don't know! He was furious you weren't here,
I was here! Fuck, I'm going to smash her, that fat whore,
She let my life on the Internet.
There! That's the other con with his blog.
Well, I called the cops, they will mobilize
someone in close proximity, just in case.
Do you think that would be useful?
He's not that dangerous.
Be polite, and not asshole.
It could be annoying. Be the cool guy.
Since you have neither have a wife or child,
we'll put everything on your case.
You're unemployed...
but an unemployed researcher.
OK.
They must feel that you have a healthy life,
with responsibilities,
professional.
I am unstable.
Know that you always start with disgust.
What do you mean?
Some avoid the dumplings,
you go into it. You face the disorderly.
And in your case, it would be Leslie Chevalier.
OK. How do I dress?
Not too chic. They would see a strategy.
Is it okay?
Yes, I am fine. No, I'm afraid.
Say that your strength is your mind.
Is this a joke?
No.
For two reasons:
They wouldn't believe a nice guy would want to kill,
and statistically good looking ones
win more than the ugly.
And they are also more indulgent
with an intelligent guy.
They would identify with the same.
Don't hesitate to come out of words...
visible, ostensible.
Obviously, incontestable.
Yes, assured.
Are you going to follow me everywhere?
Yes, everywhere.
Finally, it's time for work.
But I know how to keep a certain distance
while ensuring your protection.
OK.
You tricked me, I will destroy you psyche.
You will die by yourself on the inside.
You're a human waste in this cosmos.
Your cowardice left me an indelible trace,
I will be angry with you for life.
Or, remind me, my love,
you don't see how I suffer, it's inhumane.
Or...
You big pile of shit, you will swallow your arrogance.
Sociopath shit, reality will blow you up.
I dreamed I was taking your head
to smash it against a wall.
Again, I dream of skinning you alive, in bits,
very slowly, with a Swiss knife.
The joy in thinking of you,
your deeds, I weep for you.
Finally peace, I love you
and still shit on your grave.
I don't have time to continue to
read this collection of poetry.
Miss Chevalier, explain to us
the context of these emails.
Yes, I lived 6 months with Vincent, in 2008,
He was someone perfect, until I decided to breakup.
He became violent, he did not accept my decision.
I fled for months, I was afraid of him.
Miss Spick?
You speak of violence.
Did he physically assault you?
He tried.
But I managed to escape.
He sexually assaulted you?
No.
Why wait so long to report it?
I recognized myself in her.
That it should not happen again.
Did you experience violence from other partners?
Don't you have several complaints filed
against five of them for similar acts?
Yes.
And yet you did not you come forward
on three of them with your testimonials?
That has nothing to do with this! Vincent was violent.
I may read my testimony.
You may? Very good.
I have no further questions.
I greatly respect Miss Spick,
but I like the idea of ​​transparency.
I am on the side of justice,
that's why that I did not ask for a lawyer.
This would have created a barrier
between myself and my defense.
Thank you, Mr.Gonzalez.
Mr.Mazetti.
Miss Scorr,
Did he snatch your panties violently?
Yes, very violently.
He rushed at me.
I was frightened, under those conditions.
What happened to your panties?
Maybe he kept it.
I never saw her panties. She did not wear them.
Quiet!
Quiet please!
I couldn't have done anything,
had Victoria respected the confidentiality clause.
With regards to the blog, that is an auto-fiction.
I mixed elements of my personal life
with imagination, fantasy.
The problem is that, Mr.Gonzales,
your heroine bears the same name as my client.
She is a lawyer, like my client.
You talk about clients who exist
in her life, who she defended.
And worse, you talk of an liaison with a magistrate.
This constitutes to my client a similarity
and you tell us, you mix truth and fantasy etc?
But the reader, is unable to
totally comprehend all this.
So! What will the reader believe in?
He will believe in the worst,
the most seedy...
that my client had sexual relations with judges.
So you mess up her reputation, her work,
her credibility and you splash the whole profession
with your infamous remarks, and that,
Your honor, is intolerable.
Your Honor, I see the deceit in
the remarks made by the Counsel,
I trust the intellect of the readers.
And speaking of literature,
I quote Flaubert, who said, "I am Madame Bovary".
Well I would say, "I'm Vicky Spock".
Unfortunately, you are Mr.Gonzalez
and you have no imagination.
That was for you.
I was designated
a whore while sexually, it isn't sexual.
Then Why did this client destroy your office?
He thinks I slept with the judge
who sentenced him, it was anything but.
He felt thoroughly betrayed.
You could have slept with the judge to help your client?
No, I was wrong, but not at that point.
But you were fairly well to sleep with a judge, out of envy.
Yes, yes.
I laid with desire, not by calculation.
In a sense, I think that
you would be flattered.
Flattered?
Yes, he writes about your life.
Which means somewhere, there's interest and admiration.
He don't write about something
which does not interest readers.
It's almost a statement.
You kidding?
Nevertheless,
be fascinated to someone for having written that.
Be it looting, stealing...
Usually, people send others shabby text.
He transformed your failure in a sublime trick.
Yes, yes. It's beautiful just
as you believe in humanity.
Eve, pet the dog.
Miss Scorr, for BFM TV.
What...? No comments.
Please, Miss Scorr.
When the animal finds itself confronting a person
who hurt his owner,
it has a backward reaction, out of fear. It is a body language.
A set of fairly readable signals, the look,
finally the position of the eyes, ears, body,
The tail, is very important.
The study wag clearly shows a stressed dog,
the frightened will wag the tail towards the left,
while a confident and happy dog
will wag to the right.
What did you observe from the tests on the dog?
Yes! I'm starting the video.
Here,
in the first test, when one presents the dog, Jacques,
a lambda shirt, it wags the tail to the right.
While in the second test,
when presented with a shirt of the accused,
it acts differently.
It seems worried and wags the tail to the left.
This is a statistical study,
It is an approximation.
Mr.Mazetti?
Defense has no comment.
Miss Spick?
How long have you been practicing
your profession as an expert on justice?
11 years.
Very good.
During these 11 years,
have you come across cases of possessive dogs?
Can you confirm that the animals
may have be dissatisfied
if their masters had not a tender relationship?
Yes, I do.
It can therefore react negatively
to the presence of the accused,
not because it had
aggression towards the victim, but due to
tenderness or sexual issues?
It's not that simple.
Answer "yes" or "no".
So...yes.
Very good. I have no further questions.
Good, bring in the dog, please.
Given the exceptional nature of his testimony,
I ask you not to laugh or make sudden gestures.
Mr.Verban, will interpret what the dog expresses.
Miss Scorr,
if you could get closer to the dog.
And stand straight before him, for a moment.
Good. Mr.Kossarski, approach and touch
Miss Scorr's arm for example.
Counsel, anything to add?
May I come forward?
Yes.
Thank you.
Please.
Mr.Verban?
The animal seems very disturbed.
He was born at a Buddhist sect which made him,
misanthropic by the age of 13,
The mystery remained as to the possibility
that this community advocating serenity
could have nurtured a tortured mind, hysterical,
an Apostle of liberalism than his own.
It left traces in her relation to men.
She had an especially sexual cerebral,
a simple vision of a beautiful pleading.
An avocado sown could make her happy at once.
I felt useless,
She had become a potential monster,
a being totally devoid of emotions.
Her existence than to his desire for mastery.
Before this phallic woman,
I was invisible, but I recorded everything.
Mr.Gonzalez.
What are you looking for us believe?
That this is a novel of pure imagination?
If I may assert the opposite,
I shall be accused of slander.
I, therefore reply this is fiction.
OK, it's fiction.
The portrait you make of your heroine
is of a prospective character.
Yes, but that's the freedom of the novelist.
Who would believe that you didn't
knowingly include objective elements
for everyone to realize the fiction in hindsight,
the defamatory portrayal of Miss Spick?
I have a virile sexuality?
No. It's not like we had practiced a lot.
Am I a cold monster and calculator?
Everyone is a little bit.
No not You. You, you...
not malicious. You're a good person.
Not at all.
You're wrong, I'm not a good person.
I own nothing, maybe that's what makes me
sympathetic or harmless.
I don't appreciate you for these reasons,
that's not what I feel.
It isn't because I feel superior to you.
I don't know.
Even if that were the case,
it is always that.
I appreciate you for your...
human qualities.
You represent an area of non-danger for me.
You have become a priority.
I don't know how I should take it.
Good.
Nantes: Witness has 4 legs
Never seen before in the court of Nantes.
A dog witness to an attempted murder...by Estelle Comillac
Canine trial to the limit of it's power.
Bring in Daisy and her handler, please.
Come here.
This trial is turning out to be ridiculous.
Mr.Mazetti, I would ask you to remain silent.
Monsieur.
Hello.
Are you related or an allied party?
I am a friend of the bride.
Do you have a statement to make?
No.
Miss Spick?
Yes.
Mr Kleinberg,
do you rent your monkey for tricks, is that correct?
Yes, that's right.
What were you doing at the wedding?
We had to put up a small number,
so we came up to do that.
And after the show?
We stayed up, until 3:00 in the morning.
And what did you do with Daisy?
She was with me, she was in the mood,
so we danced and she took pictures.
She took pictures?
Yes.
Can you show us the pictures?
We'll take a picture? OK?
Here. With the finger.
Like I showed you.
Just like that.
Please!
Here, like that. Go ahead.
Photo.
What did you do with the pictures taken?
I have...Ah no, no.
Silence!
Stay here.
I transferred them on to my computer.
Good. Thank you.
Continue, Counsel.
Yes.
Look at these images taken during the marriage.
These are people who danced on the track with desserts
served an hour before the event.
On your left, recognizable in her dress,
Eve Scorr dancing back and forth.
Zooming in,
we see details appearing, thanks to the flash.
We see transparently that Miss Scorr
isn't wearing any panties.
Now, Miss Scorr says that
her panties were snatched from her.
Therein lies 3 possibilities:
Either my client snatched
her panties an hour before the event.
Miss Scorr
handed over panties between 1:00 AM and 2:00 AM
for an impossible reason to imagine
which does not figure on her testimony.
Or perhaps, or perhaps, simply lied.
(DAT DERE BY TONY BENNETT)
* Daddy! Hey daddy!
Miss Spick.
Could we get a picture, please.
* What's that there? *
A photo with the monkey.
* Hey daddy, that's him *
* Hey look at that over there! *
* Daddy O hey, daddy O ho *
* Look over there! *
* Hey why they go in there? *
* And what they doing there? *
* And daddy can I have that big elephant over there? *
* And who's that in my chair? *
* And what's she doing there?
* Daddy, O hey, can I go over there? *
* Hey daddy, what's a square? *
* And where do we get air? *
Hello.
* And daddy can I have that big elephant over there? *
Damn, the computer! I damaged it.
You did?
Are you fine?
No, I'm not, actually...
Wait, I'll open door and come back listen to you.
What are you doing here?
I have ideas to improve my character.
What are you talking about?
I feel completely useless.
You have nothing to do with that, that's my job.
Vincent, don't change your attitude facing the jury.
You have a bodyguard now?
What is it?
Sorry, I met him in the street.
OK, that's okay.
What's the matter?
Oh, Vincent!
I'm having a panic attack.
No! Everything will be alright.
Statistically, it is proven,
that if you survive a crash,
you will not get through another crash.
Mom!
Two seconds!
It's going to be fine, just get some rest. OK?
Sam, I'm going with him to talk.
Come on.
It will be fine.
Victoria, my life is completely...
I'll take rest tomorrow.
What?
I have become more invisible.
I exist more.
I dream...
Are you taking notes?
No, I'm writing a text message.
No this is not possible.
Étienne, can you get him out of here?
Thank you.
Out now, Monsieur.
There you see your true face.
I don't count on you.
No! Don't underestimate yourself.
I don't underestimate myself,
I am leaving because I have esteem.
I have known you all your life,
and you, you know nothing about me.
You don't know why I wanted to live here.
Yes Yes. Of course yes.
Well no.
I did all this to save me from my life.
Good...in English.
Listen.
English? When I...
arrived here, I realized that...
I liked you more than I was thinking
And it surprised me.
I like you very much.
Even when you "tremble" on the floor "in drool",
when you slept with all these guys in night, I like you.
But I was thinking "that"...
that the situation would change.
I was thinking "that"...
you will give me a...
a better place in your life, in your work...
And in fact, nothing at all.
You've enjoyed it without realizing it.
You're the one who underestimates yourself.
I stole money from you.
What?
I stole a bit, at first,
I found it moving that you trusted me, confided in me.
You would've never known had I had not told you,
and you would've never known I exist, had I not left.
No, Sam! Don't go. Not on the day before my pleading.
Sam?
I will not change my mind.
Please stay.
No.
Is everything all right, ma'am?
Do you need help?
Yes, you may enter. I don't feel very well.
Can you stay tonight? I don't feel assured.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
I'll install the sofa bed.
Girls, we are going to sleep.
Can I use your shower?
Yes, it's over there.
Okay.
Where is she?
In the bedroom.
What did you do?
Let's take her to the bathroom.
How much did you take?
I don't know, a few of them.
It was to sleep, but...
Good, mademoiselle, you are young,
You have a whole life in front of you.
Don't let go like that.
Drink lots of water and rest.
Your body will recover slowly.
Thank you, how much do you owe?
€47, please.
Contractually, I'm done with work, but I could stay.
No, it's good, thank you very much.
Thanks for everything, Étienne.
You helped us. Thank you very much. Goodbye.
Quick, we're in a hurry.
I can't go.
Get up.
I...
Will call...
You will have to go plead on all fours.
Take some sugar.
I will not plead sitting.
I'm very good,
You are a force of nature.
No, your aren't a force of nature.
Did you see my eyes?
They are beautiful. We'll put on some makeup.
I can't do this.
Get up and get dressed.
Please don't argue with me.
Stop, come on.
You are going.
Slowly. I am going to vomit.
We'll vomit together.
You wouldn't have a thing, amphetamines,
a trick for...?
Are you crazy?
It's for work.
Good.
I'll be replaced...
This is for your once a lifetime plead.
Here, inhale.
Again.
Are we good?
You frighten me, Victoria.
No...
Deep down, I believe in you.
Why is he there?
Why?
Why are you here?
I saved her life for the girl
who will try to save yours.
Basically, I saved your life. So fuck you.
How's Victoria doing?
Yes.
Leave me alone for half hour.
OK?
Miss.Spick, your turn to speak.
Could a dog be heard as a witness?
The question was raised, today,
in a case of attempted murder.
I ask you to be vigilant to these experiments.
I would like to add
that the intelligence of a dog
is 51% genetic.
And that according to the top dog breeds,
the dalmatian ranks at the bottom of the list,
behind the poodle,
the Doberman,
the German Shepherd and about thirty other breeds.
In other words,
If we
were to trust the word of a dog,
the dalmatian isn't the brightest to
communicate something to us.
How can we...
how can we
accuse someone of attempted murder?
How can we...
And getting back to him...
He's my client.
He's supposed to be the aggressor.
While continuing to pursue her,
which seems irrational given the circumstances,
and leave home again?
You can accuse
my client of softness,
cowardice,
weakness.
It isn't a model of virtue.
Oh no!
But it does not make him a criminal.
Miss Spick, was that a victory?
Much has been said about animals,
what was the role of the judge in this case?
The truth prevailed, which is essential.
Mr.Kossarski?
It is possible that the truth
may have been sad,
but...
Thank you, we're in a hurry.
Mr.Kossarski, please. Monsieur?
Miss Spick?
You were brilliant! It's incredible!
What did you do?
I feel revived.
Thank Sam, really.
You gave a lot.
Did you not you see him after the verdict?
Who? Sam?
Sam.
No.
This is like, as it was before,
I did not realize I was happy and there I realize...
Fuck, I feel so relieved.
Me too.
I can't believe it's over.
You look tired, you need to rest.
Do you know what would give me peace?
Let's see that one more time.
Yeah, I would...
I should not have involved you in my stories.
It's certain, you'll get back together.
That, really, I think I could not.
In her absence, the judge rejected the charges against me
and ordered me to pay her €90 in damages.
The trial brought me advertising in...
No. Given the publicity that
the trial had brought me,
I was also ordered to change
the names of the characters.
I won, in exchange, the undisputed right
to continue the blog and the film
gathered an unexpected publicity.
I was proud that justice gave me back
my freedom of authorship.
You've reached the answering machine of Samuel and Mal.
Sam?
I kept calling you.
I did not know where you were. We won the trial.
Thank you, because I'm thankful to you.
And also, the fact that, ah...
you count on me,
very much.
I understand
why you stole money from me,
you wanted to show me your interest.
I want to prove to you my gratitude.
It's a bit too late.
It works well, chemically, between us?
Chemically?
There's good chemistry in the works, don't you think?
I dunno, I don't understand what you are saying.
I want to live with you.
Without paying me? I'm lost.
Oh yes, no. Of course, I'll pay you.
I'm joking, I'm not a whore.
I think that would be a good thing.
Finally, any relationship
deserves an exchange.
No relationship is balanced.
The very notion of balance
ruins any possible form of connection.
The fact is, I'm afraid of you.
You have the sense of drama abnormally developed.
Sam, I have...
I just understood that...
these last months...
I did not have time to realize that...
that I was in love with you.
I understood this when you were gone,
I realized that...
I was happy with you. I wasn't aware,
but I was happy.
I said nothing, I had my head in the trial.
Now I know.
I could
give you courses in law,
to introduce you to all the lawyers of Paris...
Why did you wait so long?
I don't know.
I rarely have 2 seconds of inner peace.
* I spend the night in a chair thinking she'll be there *
* But she never comes and then I wake up and wipe the sleep from my eyes *
* And I rise to face another day without her *
* Do-do-do, do-do-do-do, do-do-do *
* It's just no good anymore *
* When you walk through the door of an empty room *
* And then you go inside and set a table for one *
* It's no fun when you spend a day without her *
* Do-do-do, do-do-do-do, do-do-do *
* We burst the pretty balloon *
* Took us to the moon *
* Such a beautiful thing *
* But it's ended now *
* And it sounds like a lie *
* If I say I'd rather die than live without her *
* Do-do-do, do-do-do-do, do-do-do *
* Love is a beautiful thing *
* When it knows how to swing *
* And it grooves like a clock *
* But the hands on the clock tell the lovers to part *
* And it's breaking my heart to have to spend a day without her *
* Do-do-do, do-do-do-do, do-do-do *
* I spend the night in a chair thinking she'll be there *
* But she never comes *
* And then I wake up and wipe the sleep from my eyes *
* And I rise to face another day without her *
* Do-do-do, do-do-do-do, do-do-do *
* Can't go on without her *
* Do-do-do, do-do-do-do *
* There's no song without her *
* It's all wrong without her *
* Can't go on without her *