Previously on Suits...
That's not
Woodall coming after us.
It's Sean Cahill.
If your hands weren't full
with Eric,
they will be full with me.
What happened to "You think
I'm staying if you leave?"
Yeah, that was before I knew
you were gonna screw
over Sidwell.
Forstman doesn't throw
money around
without getting something
in return.
I have no other choice!
You two are on opposite sides
of a takeover battle,
and your girlfriend
is your associate.
Are you trying to say
that we're colluding?
You went right there,
didn't you?
So we're just gonna go back
and forth trading favors?
Are you my lawyer or not?
Seriously, Rachel, I couldn't
have done it without you.
Logan, I should go.
Damn right.
You get one, Huntley.
Eisenheim, you
silly son of a bitch.
You think I'd leave you
out of the fun?
Riceman, after you killed
the singer depo.
Out of my way, Johnson.
Coffee's for closers.
You don't get a mug.
Am I to assume I'm getting
my own personal Litt-up mug?
Absolutely not.
Those are mere mugs.
This, My Lady, is a chalice.
Okay.
It looks like
all the other ones.
No, Donna.
What makes this a chalice
is not the mug.
It's what's inside.
Wait a second. Is that...
Mm-hmm, an exact replica
of the one.
Dame Judi Dench wore as Ophelia.
Louis, this must
have cost a fortune.
Donna, please.
You helped me overcome
my stage fright.
You can't put a price on that.
I don't know what to say.
That's all you have to say.
I got one for Harvey too.
You know, Louis,
I don't think that...
I know he is still upset with me
for leading Mike to Forstman,
but I just thought maybe
if he could...
Give it to me.
I will take care of it.
Thank you, Donna.
Hey, Mike,
Sidwell wants to see you.
Shit.
What?
He took Forstman's money
last night.
Do you think he knows
you're gonna cut him
out of the deal?
There's only one way
to find out.
You wanted to see me?
Damn right I did.
Something you want to tell me?
Jonathan,
I don't know what to say.
Well, you better
think of something
'cause I just got off the phone
with some asshole
from the SEC who accused you
of colluding
with Harvey Specter.
That's bullshit.
Then why the hell were the two
of you sharing a porterhouse
when you were supposed
to be buying stock
from me two nights ago?
- It's not what you think.
- What I think is
you better start telling me
what's going on around here.
There's nothing going on.
Look, I know that guy.
He's full of shit.
Well, I don't know him
from a hole in the ground,
but I know that
you're keeping stuff from me.
Jonathan, I...
First you don't transfer
Forstman's money.
Then you blow
a straight-up stock purchase
that any first-year trader
could do in his sleep.
It wasn't straight-up.
I had to set up an auction,
which happened to get postponed.
Yeah, 'cause you were
sipping wine
with Harvey Specter behind
my back.
It got postponed
because my girlfriend
was in the hospital.
What?
Rachel passed out at school.
Harvey and I went
to the hospital,
so we pushed the sale.
- Then you should have told me.
- You're right.
I should have. I'm sorry.
But that's what happened.
That's it?
That's it.
Fine.
But if there is anything else
that you're not telling me,
now is the time.
There isn't.
Well?
Allison is at dinner
with some friends,
but she'll be home soon.
I have to go.
Come on, we're working.
We're not working.
I am sneaking around,
pretending to work
so that I can spend time
with you.
Sneaking around?
That's what I'd call it,
wouldn't you?
I don't know.
I just don't really want
to think of it like that.
I have to go.
Well, she's with her friends.
Aren't you allowed to be
with your friends?
Is that what we are,
we're friends?
I was actually hoping
that we're more than that.
Mm, we shouldn't be
having this conversation.
You wouldn't be here
if you didn't want to be
having this conversation.
Rachel.
We have had chemistry
from the second we met.
You know it.
And I know it.
Rachel. Hey.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
I am here because I wanted
to talk to you
before you came in
to see Harvey this morning.
Do you want some coffee?
No, I won't be here
long enough for that.
Are you sure?
Look, Logan.
I know why you're here.
If you knew why I was here,
then I wouldn't need to be here.
I think you're here to tell me
that what's happening
isn't really happening,
but it is.
I have a boyfriend that I love,
so I need you to
stop pursuing me.
No more flowers, no more looks,
no more attempted kisses,
no more anything, okay?
Look, you said that if
I knew why you were here,
you wouldn't need to be here.
I think you do need to be here,
and we both know why.
You're wrong.
I don't think I am.
You once told me
we had chemistry
the second that we met.
Logan, please.
Tell me to stop, and I'll stop.
I can't.
Rachel. Rachel.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ Suits 4x06 ♪ Litt the Hell Up
Original Air Date on July 23, 2014
♪ the greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Harvey, I need to...
What the hell is this?
It's from Louis.
He wanted you to have it.
What do you mean he wanted me
to have it?
You haven't talked to him
since Mike landed Forstman.
It's a gesture.
Now, can I please
get back to what...
Oh, why didn't you say
it was a gesture?
Mike has access to Forstman
and his $4 billion.
Logan's on his way over
to discuss
our next move, which we can't
make for two more weeks
because Louis thought Sheila
was marrying Lorenzo Lamas,
but I just got a mug
with something stupid
printed on it,
so now everything's okay.
Great.
Are you done being a dick?
Because everything's not okay.
- What did Louis do now?
- Nothing.
And Logan Sanders isn't
on his way here
because he just got
brought down to the SEC.
What the hell do you think
you're doing
talking to my client
without me present?
Oh, he hasn't said a word yet.
We're waiting for you
to get the party started.
And what gives you the right
to bring him here
in the first place?
The United States government
gives me the right,
so if you don't mind,
I have a few questions
I would like to ask him.
You got questions for him,
you ask me.
Okay, here's one.
What makes you think
you can get away
with collusion on my watch?
I already told you
we're not colluding,
and you harassing my client
won't change that.
Will me telling him
about your date
the other night
with Mike Ross change that?
What?
See, I think he and Mike Ross
are colluding
to allow you to purchase
Gillis Industry stock
at a cut rate price.
That's bullshit.
Then why would you set up
a private auction
while neither one
of you ended up bidding?
And Logan here mysteriously
bought the stock
without any competition.
That's it. We're done.
You didn't bring us in here
to ask him questions.
You brought us in here to ask me
questions in front of him.
Am I smart enough to do that?
You're dumb enough to try,
and we're leaving.
I have not dismissed you yet.
Then arrest us on the way out.
Gentlemen.
Hey, what's going on?
You look upset.
No, it's nothing.
I just found out
I have to go to Columbia,
so could you just tell Harvey
that I won't be able
to make the Logan meeting?
Rachel, there is no meeting.
Logan got hauled down
to the SEC.
What?
I just saw him this morning.
That doesn't make...
Well, it must have been...
Wait a second.
They picked him up at his condo.
Why were you at Logan's condo?
Donna, please don't
do your thing on me.
Rachel, what is going on?
The other night
I was working with Logan,
and things got intense,
and he tried to kiss me.
Okay, so what did you do?
Nothing. I didn't do anything.
Then why were you at
his condo this morning?
I went to tell him
that I didn't want him
to get the wrong idea.
Rachel, if you went
to his place,
you were giving him
the wrong idea.
Something happened, didn't it?
I kissed him.
How long?
Too long.
God, I feel horrible.
I'm a horrible person.
No, you're not.
You are a great person
who had a not-so-great moment.
Donna, please, you can't
say a word to anyone.
Of course not.
But Rachel, you can't say
a word to anyone either.
Go ahead,
say what you're gonna say.
You know what I'm gonna say.
Is what he said true?
Logan, I am not
colluding with Mike Ross.
Well, if I thought that,
I wouldn't even
be standing here.
I'm talking about you
buying that stock.
- Look, I can't talk about that.
- Why not?
Because telling you about it
would make it parking,
but that doesn't matter anymore
because now that
that guy hauled you in,
we can't do a thing
with those shares anyway.
Well, what can we do?
You and Mike Ross can get
in a room together,
and put this thing to bed
once and for all.
No, that's a bad idea.
Logan, if we don't finish
this now,
you're gonna have the SEC
crawling up your ass
day and night.
Look, you can try
to scare me all you want,
but I did nothing wrong,
and the last guy I'm getting
in a room with
is Mike goddamn Ross.
Don't you ever knock?
Logan Sanders got taken
downtown this morning.
Sean Cahill.
Son of a bitch is throwing shit
at the wall to see what sticks.
- And what stuck?
- Wexler.
Logan found out
we bought that stock.
Did you tell him
why we kept it from him?
- He didn't seem to care.
- All right.
Well, it doesn't matter
because you're going to end
this takeover battle now.
What do you think I've been
doing for the past month?
Harvey, I don't think you
understand what I'm saying.
This guy's already looking
at us for collusion.
The longer this thing drags on,
the more likely he is
to come after us
for buying that stock.
In other words, end this thing?
Not in other words.
In those exact words.
So I guess Jonathan didn't
know you sold him out.
How'd you know that?
Because if he knew,
he'd have come by your office
and ripped you to pieces.
Instead, you're out here
enjoying a bagel
without the courtesy
of coming by
to tell me that he didn't know.
My bad.
So now what are we gonna do?
Well, we're gonna kick some ass.
Wait.
What are you talking about?
The SEC called Sidwell,
and I guarantee you
they also called Logan Sanders,
which means Harvey can't
use those shares,
and I'm in the driver's seat.
- Well, that explains it.
- Explains what?
Harvey just called.
He wants to have a meeting.
- Jeff.
- Hey.
Did you hear what
Sean Cahill did this morning?
I did. Yeah.
Then you know he's poking
around the Wexler purchase.
Ah, let him.
You don't seem very concerned.
I'm not concerned
because I did a damn good job
protecting this firm
from any liability.
Yeah, well, the question is
did you protect us
from all liability?
Is there something that
you want to ask me, Jessica?
I want you to go
back over your work
with a fine-tooth comb,
and make sure it's airtight.
Jessica, you're the one
who asked me to buy that stock,
and I made it questionable,
like you asked,
but if Sean Cahill comes at
us for attempting to park it,
that is on you, not my work.
Jeff, just go back over
everything like I said.
There's nothing to go back over.
We're as protected as we can be.
Okay, maybe you didn't hear me.
Every partner at this firm
goes over their work
if I say so.
And you know what, Jessica?
I'm not every goddamn partner.
So either you trust me
or you don't.
Hey, look what the cat
dragged in.
Such a serious expression.
It's because we need to have
a serious conversation.
Well, let's get to it.
I want you to come up
with a number
that we can pay you
to end this thing.
And why would I do that?
Because Sean Cahill
hauled Logan into the SEC.
Well, all that means is
that you can't vote
the shares that
you stole from me,
and that is a "you" problem.
Mike, it takes two people
to make a case for collusion.
So if he's coming at us,
he's coming at you,
which means it's a "we" problem.
Yeah, you can try
and spin it any way you want,
but I'm happy right where I am.
I guess you agreed
to this meeting
just to waste my time, huh?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Who said I don't want to deal?
Don't play me.
Here's the new deal.
You don't buy me out.
I buy you out.
- What?
- We tried it Logan's way.
Now we're gonna try it mine...
Mike.
'Cause the only way I'd get
in a room with that guy
is if you guarantee that
I leave with Gillis Industries.
He's not gonna agree to that.
That's another "you" problem.
Rachel, I need to
know what's going on
with Logan Sanders. What?
You spent an extra 20 hours
with him last week.
It wasn't billed
to the takeover,
and I need to know
what it's about.
We were looking at future deals.
- "We"?
- Yes, we.
He asked me if I could help him
put together some ideas...
- Why?
- What are you getting at?
I don't know if you've been
paying attention around here,
but we need to wrap
this thing up,
so I need to know if whatever
you and Logan were up to
can force him to end this thing
with Mike once and for all.
It can.
How?
Logan is under pressure
from his board,
and if he doesn't
close this deal soon,
he might lose control
of his company.
Jessica, I must say
your impromptu lunch
in the middle of the day
is exactly
what the doctor ordered.
Thank you, Louis.
Now, I must admit
that I brought you here
because I have something
that I didn't want
to discuss at the office.
If you're firing Harvey,
I can't be in on it.
I just bought him
an amazing mug,
and we're in
a really good place right now.
And I'm happy for you,
but this isn't about Harvey.
It's about the firm.
We recently purchased
a large block of stock
without realizing
that we represent
a client
with the same interests.
You're worried
about the appearance
of parking the stock? Exactly.
And I just want
to make sure that we are
as protected as possible.
Sure, I can do it.
- You seem upset.
- No, I'm not upset.
I mean, why would
I be upset, Jessica?
You take me to
an amazing restaurant,
then you give me some
bullshit story
about a stock purchase
with a fabricated company,
and when it's clear as day
this is Gillis Industries.
- Louis.
- The very same stock purchase
that you went to Malone
to structure,
and now you want me
to double check his work
because you don't trust him.
Oh, question is can I trust you?
- What?
- This lunch isn't about him.
It's about you.
You knew I'd figure this out.
Just like I know
you'll figure out
whether or not we have exposure.
Now, the question is
can you do it
without telling Jeff Malone?
I can, and I will.
If you're gonna discuss
what happened,
you can just forget it
because I...
I am not here to talk
about that, and you know it.
What?
You told Harvey about
my problems with the board.
I told your attorney
about a situation
you discussed
with your other attorney.
And now he's using it
to strong-arm me
into caving to Mike.
No, now he's using it
to give you
the opportunity
to impress your board.
Did you bring Harvey that
information to get rid of me?
Logan, I didn't bring
Harvey that information,
he asked me for it.
And I don't need to get rid
of you
because what happened
this morning is
never gonna happen again.
Okay, Rachel,
you got what you wanted.
I'm gonna get in
a room with Mike
and come to an agreement.
What do you mean you're
gonna get in a room with him?
Well, how else did
you see this happening?
Did you think I was gonna
let Harvey take care of it?
Look, please, you can't
tell him what happened.
Rachel, I would never do that.
Thank you.
Just to be clear,
it's not for him.
It's for me...
'Cause you say
what happened this morning
will never happen again,
and I'm still hoping
that it will.
But I don't want it to happen
because you two are fighting.
I want it to happen
because you want it to.
- Hey.
Do you want me to heat
some of this up or you?
Mike, I need to talk to you.
Are you upset about something?
No.
I heard you might be
making a deal.
And you're worried because
you're on the losing side?
No, I'm actually happy
that this thing will be over.
But?
I think that you should have
Jonathan Sidwell put this
to bed for you.
Rachel...
You and Harvey
have so much bad blood.
Yeah, and this is our
chance to patch it up.
- And what about Logan?
- What about him?
I'm not gonna let him get to me.
That's what you said
the last time
you two got in a room together.
This is different.
- Mike.
- Rachel, stop it.
Look, we're at the finish line.
I'm not gonna pass the baton
to somebody else,
and I'm not gonna blow it
because this time
I've got all the leverage.
Well, if you have
all the leverage, then...
Maybe you should
ask for one more thing.
You're a halfhour late.
I got stuck in traffic.
I was starting to think
you didn't want this company.
Harvey, I wouldn't be
getting in a room
with that guy if I didn't.
Good. So we're not gonna
have trouble in there?
Not from me.
Then let's get
this thing over with
and get back to normal.
Keep that in mind.
Logan, sorry I'm late.
Let's get to it.
All right, just so we're clear,
we're agreeing to have
you buy us out.
Good.
I think you'll find
this more than generous.
It is.
You gonna try and spread
this over 1,000 payments?
All up front.
Then all that's left is for you
to pull out your checkbook.
Well, actually,
there is one more thing.
You said it, Harvey.
Let's get things back to normal.
What are you talking about?
Once this deal is done,
you go back to being my lawyer,
and he's out.
What?
You sign that,
I'm Harvey's client,
and you're looking
for new representation.
That's... this is bullshit.
It's not bullshit.
Apple and Dell don't
have the same attorneys,
and neither will you and I.
Mike, you two aren't those two,
and I can represent you both.
Yeah, but it doesn't matter
because it's not
about who you represent.
It's about
who Rachel represents.
All right, enough.
We agreed to a number.
We can work this out
another time.
No, we're gonna
work it out right now.
- No, we're not.
- Then you don't have a deal.
God damn it, Mike.
This isn't the time to do this.
This is exactly
the time to do it
because this is the last time
I'm ever gonna be
in a room with him.
Well, finally,
something we can agree on.
Then let's agree
to something else.
We let Harvey choose
which one of us
he wants to represent
after today.
- Mike, do not put me in that...
- Done.
And now that we've agreed
to let Harvey decide,
I'm gonna let you in
on a little secret.
The way he got me into this
room in the first place
was he knows that I've got
ten deals lined up after this.
Logan.
Decide.
I'm going with Mike.
- What?
- Mike's my guy.
You knew that going in.
I don't give a shit,
and I don't think
Jessica Pearson
is going to let you
pick him over me.
Jessica has nothing to do
with this.
You just agreed to those terms.
Those were bullshit terms.
So you're going back
on your word?
What does it look like?
Looks like there's
no deal on Gillis.
Mike, you didn't have
to blow up the deal like that.
Your client blew up the deal.
- Because you blindsided him.
- Fine.
Then once he's had time
to think about it,
you go back and convince him.
Convince him?
You should have come to me first
instead of looking to rub it
in his face.
I wasn't rubbing anything
in anyone's face.
Oh, bullshit. You have leverage,
and you want to make
sure he knew it.
And when he had leverage,
he made sure I knew it,
and I didn't agree to a deal,
and then break my word
ten seconds later.
And I'm giving you my word.
Close this deal,
and as soon as it's wrapped up,
he's out.
And what about Jessica?
Is she gonna agree to it?
Let me deal with Jessica.
Oh, just like you did on wexler.
That was a different thing,
and you know it. Do I?
Get him to agree up front,
or we don't have a deal.
Louis, I don't usually
get summoned to people.
They get summoned to me.
But you wanted discretion,
and your office is within
an earshot of Jeff Malone.
And you don't want him to hear
what you're about to tell me.
So first off, I went through
this backwards and forwards,
and Jeff did a better job
than 99% of all attorneys.
Fortunately for you,
I'm the one.
You found a mistake.
I found a blessing in disguise.
What are you talking about?
Jessica, we're not vulnerable
to allegations of parking
because we never bought
those shares.
We can't sell them back.
I'm not talking
about selling them back.
This mistake makes
the entire sale invalid.
And we don't have exposure
because the sale never happened?
Just give me the word,
and I'll David Blaine
this whole thing away.
Louis, this is great work,
but I don't want you to
do anything
until you talk to Harvey.
Are you sure?
Because I can just...
Louis, I bought these shares
without telling him.
I'm not getting rid of them
Are we clear? As a bell.
Well, someone saved the day.
Do tell.
Jeff Malone just dropped
a giant deuce
on Jessica's desk.
Please tell me
you're being metaphorical.
Nope. Made a huge mess
of the wexler purchase.
- And you cleaned it up?
- Even better.
Because of his blunder,
I'm gonna make it
as though his shit-y deal
never even happened.
- What did Jessica say?
- Oh, she loved it.
- And what about Malone?
- That's the best part.
That asshole doesn't
even know about it.
What do you need me to do
to make this unwind happen?
Nothing.
Jessica just wanted me to run it
by Harvey first,
but I haven't been
able to reach him.
Able to reach him?
Louis, what do you think is
gonna happen
if Malone gets wind of this
before you talk to Harvey?
Ah, shit, he's gonna
try to fix it himself.
And once again, he'll be taking
what's rightfully yours.
And I'll be left holding
a big bag
of Jeff Malone's giant deuce.
Where are you going?
To do what needs to be done.
Rachel,
what the hell did you do?
What are you talking about?
Mike demanded that Harvey
dump Logan as a client,
and it blew up the whole deal,
and based on
what I know and Harvey doesn't,
it wasn't Mike
behind that demand.
It was you.
- I'm so sorry.
- Sorry?
What good does sorry do?
Donna, I thought it was
the best thing
for everyone involved.
You thought it was the best
way to get
Logan out of the picture
and not deal with what happened.
No, I tried to deal
with what happened
without telling anyone,
which is what you told me to do.
I did not tell you
to let your personal life
affect Harvey's business.
I was just trying
to get Mike and Harvey
back on the same team.
I want you to understand
that the way
to do that isn't to pull strings
behind their backs.
I do.
Okay, well, there's got
to be some way to fix it.
That's not the point.
It's being fixed.
What are you talking about?
Harvey's going over Mike's head.
He went to see Charles Forstman
20 minutes ago.
Whoever said size doesn't
matter never saw this table.
Is that an insult
or a compliment?
Knowing you, Charles,
you'll take it as both.
How'd you get in here, Harvey?
You crawled in
through the vents?
I told your secretary I
was George Clooney's brother.
She said it was obvious who
got the looks in the family.
Great. Do me a favor.
Tell her she's fired
on the way out.
Can do.
But first, I wanted
to show you these.
You want to give me
the Aston Martin?
"Give" is a strong word.
You want me to buy you out.
You're going to buy me out.
So why come to me instead
of Mike Ross?
Because I put him and Logan
Sanders in a room together,
and those two assholes let
their personal shit
get in the way of business.
So what makes you think
these two assholes
are gonna do any better?
Because as much
as you hate my guts,
you want this deal
and that car as much as I do.
Harvey, taking
your car is tempting,
but I don't think buying you
out makes sense anymore.
Why not?
Because you're standing
there asking me to do it.
Now, walk your sorry ass
out of my office.
Okay, Charles.
But I'm afraid you're forcing me
to use my leverage on you.
You don't have shit on me, pal.
Who do you think bought
that Wexler block
three days ago?
I don't give a shit who
bought it three days ago.
'Cause it just went back
on the market 30 minutes ago,
and you're looking at
the man who owns it now.
Jonathan, what
are you doing here?
Forstman bought
the Wexler shares.
What?
They went back on the market,
and he snatched them right up.
Holy shit.
We win.
- We do.
- Mm-hmm.
You did.
It's not over yet.
I want you to draw up
a tender offer right away.
- Jonathan.
- What?
I've been thinking
about Forstman.
And?
You know we wouldn't have
been able
to do this without him, right?
No shit.
Just think about what else
we could do with him.
You want to team up with him?
Well, you don't need
to convince me,
but how the hell are
you gonna convince him?
By giving him
a discount on this deal.
How much of a discount?
Thinking somewhere in
the neighborhood of... 100%.
God damn it, Louis!
What the hell did you do?
What are you talking about?
I just came from a meeting
with Charles Forstman,
and when I reached for
my bargaining chips,
he told me I didn't own them
anymore
because you unwound
the Wexler sale.
Well, I was trying to save
the firm from exposure.
And who the hell told
you to do that?
Jessica did.
She told you to God damn wait,
and you know it.
Check your phone.
I tried calling you.
I left three messages.
I don't care if you left me
a million messages.
You were told to
wait for my approval,
and you didn't listen
because you never God damn do.
You know what, Harvey?
I always listen.
I always play the good soldier,
and what do I get for it?
Nothing.
I may not be a name partner,
but I am a senior partner.
You get it?
I couldn't reach you,
and I made
a goddamn judgment call.
You want to know why you're
not a name partner, Louis?
Because every judgment
call you make turns to shit.
Well, then what do you want,
Harvey?
I'll do anything
to make up for it.
You want to do something, Louis?
Instead of using Donna
to give me
some stupid goddamn mug,
stay the hell
out of my business.
You mind grabbing me
a couple packs of sugar there?
I don't work here.
I'm with Pearson-Specter.
I don't give
a shit who you're with.
If you're not here to give me
something...
I'm here to give you Harvey
Specter on a silver platter.
I already have Harvey Specter
on a silver platter.
Not like you will
if you let me buy you out.
Listen, asshole,
Harvey came by last night,
tried to make a deal.
I told him to shove it
up his ass,
and don't think
I don't know good cop,
bad cop when I see it.
The good cop, bad cop
doesn't work
when one of them hates
the other one.
And what the hell is this?
Your niece's diary?
It's a time capsule of my rage.
"April 22nd, 2009.
"Harvey told me to file
a motion to dismiss
the odor emitting
from my armpits."
This is a joke.
Once again, he
took my biggest fear,
put it on display for
the entire world to see.
Oh, yeah, I can go on.
- He hates you that bad, huh?
- No.
He doesn't give
a shit about me at all.
I hate him that bad.
You know, you don't have
the authority to buy me out.
I went to Harvey's client
behind his back,
and I got him. Oh, I see.
I agree to this,
you steal his client.
And he'll have lost to me,
which is far more humiliating
than losing to you.
You'd go to all this trouble
to stick it to Harvey?
Read May 9th, 2012.
I'd go to the ends
of the goddamn earth.
What was so important
you couldn't me over the phone?
I want to offer you something.
My lucky day.
Everyone's bearing gifts.
You want me to
buy controlling interest
in the Sidwell Investment Group.
I want you to buy it
at a $80 million discount.
The exact amount
I was gonna cut him out of.
Was? Wait.
Did you change your mind?
You're not gonna cut him
out of Gillis?
Guess you haven't heard.
I'm done with Gillis.
I sold my interest
to Logan Sanders.
What the hell you talking about?
That wasn't our deal.
What can I tell you?
When you're the biggest bully
in the yard,
people give you
their lunch money
without you even asking for it.
Oh, my God. You son of a bitch.
You promised me
that I would control
what happened to that company.
I promised you if we won.
We didn't.
- You did.
- Yes, I did.
Then our other deal
is off the table,
and you're gonna give
Jonathan Sidwell
his goddamn cut.
How about I give
you something even better.
- What the hell is this?
- A job offer.
You got to be kidding me.
What, did you think
I was gonna hang you out to dry?
I could use a smart son of bitch
like you working for me.
You're the last person in
the world I'd want to work for.
I am the only person in
the world you want to work for.
- Why is that?
- Because you're a nobody.
You're a former lawyer who's
been an investment banker
all of ten minutes, and is about
to blow the biggest deal
that ever came his way,
unless you come over to me.
Go to hell.
Harvey, we need
to have a little talk.
I said everything
I needed to say last night.
Now get the hell out.
I made a deal with Forstman.
What?
You stuck your nose
in my goddamn business
after I told you to never do
that again?
No, I saved
your goddamn business
after you told me
to never do it again.
- You got him to sign this?
- Damn right.
- And who authorized it?
- Nobody.
I lied and told Forstman
I had Logan's approval.
Can we get Logan's approval?
You're goddamn right we can.
Louis, this has got to be
the most genius thing
you have ever done
in your entire, wonderful,
miserable life.
So you're not mad at me?
Mad at you? I could kiss you.
And I can let you.
Then go grab
a couple of your mugs.
I'll crack open the scotch,
and let's see
where this thing goes.
Can do.
Hey, Louis,
how the hell did you get him
to go for it?
We found common ground.
One more thing.
Charles Forstman got
the Litt the hell up.
Mike, Mike,
Sidwell wants to see you.
Don't tell me.
He knows.
Sh...
You little piece of shit.
Jonathan, let me explain.
There's nothing to explain.
You sold me out the second
you connected with Forstman.
No, I thought I could get
out of it, all right?
But then you took
Forstman's money, and I...
Oh, you're gonna put that on me?
I took his money because
I thought we were partners.
I didn't know you were gonna
stab me in the goddamn back.
Stab you in the back?
If I didn't make
this deal happen,
you said you were gonna fire me.
I don't give a shit what I said.
I took a chance on you.
You spat in my face.
Jonathan.
You stood right there selling me
on Forstman to stop me from
finding out you betrayed me.
No, I did that to stop me
from having to betray you.
Jonathan, he still owes us
money, all right?
We can still go after...
There isn't enough money
in the world for me
to ever trust you again.
Listen to me.
I'm... No, you listen to me!
There is no goddamn "we."
You're fired.
Jonathan, we can still talk
to Forstman, all right?
You think I didn't try that?
Who the hell do you think
told me
that you sold me out
in the first place?
Here.
Put this on your mantle.
Remember me every time
you God damn look at it.
There is the man of the hour.
Why didn't you tell me
what you were gonna do?
Because if it didn't work,
I didn't want you
to take any of the blame.
Well, why didn't
you tell me afterwards?
It's all anyone can talk about.
Yeah, I don't care.
Louis.
Forstman's insisting
that I run the money
through Switzerland
and the Caymans
before it comes out on the
other side.
What?
He's trying to avoid taxes.
You're obligated to report it.
I didn't, and I'm not going to.
Louis, that's illegal.
You didn't see the
look on Harvey's face
when he found out that I
was the one who saved the day,
and I am...
Not gonna be the one
to see the look
on his face
when he finds out that I didn't.
Louis.
Leave me alone.
Hey, did you hear the good news?
There is no good news.
Logan won, which means
he's not going anywhere.
You want to tell Mike
what happened, don't you?
I am going to tell Mike
what happened.
No, you're not.
Harvey said he would drop Logan
when this is over, and he will.
And there is no way that
he's dropping Logan
if Mike can't even be a client.
What are you talking about?
I just got a text from Amy.
Donna, Mike got fired.
Now you really can't tell him.
You said I shouldn't
go behind his back,
but not telling him is
going behind his back.
Even if you were gonna tell him,
this is the absolute worst time.
If not now, then when?
I mean, just wait
till he recovers,
and then smack him down again?
How about not
smacking him down at all?
That would be great,
but I already did
when I betrayed him, and I...
Rachel, if you do this,
I am telling you it will
bore a hole in his brain,
and you will be risking
your whole life with Mike.
- I am risking it if I don't.
- Rachel.
Donna, Mike kept a secret
from me that almost ripped us
apart before we
even got started,
and he found the courage
to trust me with it.
So I need to find the courage
to trust him with this.