Previously on Suits...
I want you to decide if you
love me more than you hate
what I did, and if you do,
then I want you to come home.
The only they'll definitely
find if they get a look at
those files,
is that you embezzled money.
Listen to me, God damn it.
We need to undo this deal.
- We have nothing to hide.
- No, no, this is a ploy.
He's trying to get me on
record stating that we have
everything,
and if I find nothing,
he's gonna file malicious
prosecution charges.
Actually, Sean, I'm filing
those charges right now.
Harvey went to court
this morning,
and agreed to hand over
every single document
on the Gillis takeover,
including Forstman.
Shit!
Then it's only a matter of time
before I'm marched
out of here in handcuffs.
If he did make
a dirty deal with Forstman,
it wouldn't have been
in those documents.
It would've been in...
The documents
we just told the court
we're happy to turn over.
What are you going to do?
I'm gonna find out
what the hell Louis did.
I made a huge mistake.
What's going on?
Louis, I want you to tell Harvey
exactly what you just told me,
or I will.
He doesn't have to.
He made a dirty deal
with Forstman.
Harvey, I can explain.
Explain what, that you
put the firm in jeopardy
all because you had
to be the hero?
I didn't do it to be the hero.
I didn't even know
I was gonna do it at all. What?
The deal was closed, and
you were so happy we won.
Then I went back that night,
Forstman said if I didn't
funnel the money overseas,
the deal was off,
so I did it.
There's more.
How do you know there's more?
Because with Forstman
there's always more.
He made me take a million
dollars out of the deal
so I couldn't turn on him later.
- Jesus Christ.
- I had no choice!
Bullshit, you had no choice!
You could've said no at any
goddamn point along the way,
but you didn't, because all
you cared about was yourself.
Okay, if I care
about myself so much,
how come I'm in here telling
you that I'm gonna confess?
You want to confess?
Be my guest!
Harvey, that's enough.
Louis... the problem with
that is that we're innocent.
Cahill's plan is to throw mud
against the wall
and see what sticks.
You tell him about what you did,
and all of a sudden,
everything sticks.
Okay.
But I have to do something
to help.
You will, when the time comes.
Right now, I need
to talk to Harvey.
I can't believe
you're taking this
as well as you are.
I'm not taking this well at all.
Then what the hell are
you being so nice to him for?
Did you hear?
He was going to confess.
I had to calm him down.
So you're not
gonna stand by him?
Stand by him?
The second this thing is over,
I'm gonna fire his goddamn ass.
How was your shower?
It was great.
Rachel, you don't
have to clean up for me.
I live here.
I know, I just... I want
everything to be perfect.
It is.
Is this my parents' photo album?
Oh, yeah, it was in
the back of the closet.
Yeah, I know where it was.
Why is it out here?
Because I was looking for
pictures of you.
What do you want to do
for dinner tonight?
I was thinking
maybe we could hit
that little Mexican spot.
No. You just got back here.
I don't want to go anywhere.
I don't either, but we
don't have anything to eat.
- Don't we?
- Well, I know for a fact
we don't have any bean
and cheese burritos.
Mm, then why are there
six of them in the fridge
right now?
You hate them.
I do, but you love them,
and I wanted you
to have them here
when you came home.
And what if I
didn't come home tonight?
Then I would have bought
fresh ones again tomorrow.
Thanks, Rachel.
It's good to have you home.
It's good to be home.
What happened?
I thought you had a date.
I canceled it,
and I asked you a question.
I don't want to talk about it,
because I know what
you're going to say.
Harvey, I don't even
know what exactly Louis did.
He broke the law
to close Forstman.
He broke it or Forstman
made him break it?
- What's the goddamn difference?
- Harvey...
You don't have to say it, Donna,
I've heard it a thousand times.
Louis only did this
to get my approval.
And you know what,
I don't give a shit
that I agreed to be
his best man.
He put you, me, and every one
of us in jeopardy
to get what he wanted.
Well, I was gonna say that,
but instead I'll say this:
You put us all in jeopardy too.
When the hell did I do that?
The day you hired Mike,
and by the way,
I'm guessing he wouldn't
even be back here
if Louis hadn't done
what he did.
Then tell that to Jessica,
'cause when it's over,
she's gonna fire him.
They keep this
place open late for you?
Ownership has its privileges.
What do you want, Harvey?
I want you to undo
the dirty deal you made
with Louis Litt.
Dirty deal.
Doesn't sound like me at all.
How does prison sound?
Because the S.E.C.
is gonna get a record
of the shit you pulled
tomorrow morning.
There is no record,
'cause I didn't do anything.
Louis Litt came to me,
and he's the one
who embezzled money.
And your grudge
isn't with Louis.
It's with me, so let him go.
Live to fight me another day.
If I let him off, I let you off,
and I don't think
I want to do that.
Then you're forcing me to
turn you in for what you did
12 years ago.
No way.
You're not gonna do that,
because you did it too, pal.
You're right, I did.
But if you did it to Louis
and you did it to me, you
did it to a hundred others.
And if you don't
do what I'm asking,
I'll just have to find
the one in a hundred
that's in a position
to turn on you.
I'll take my chances, Harvey.
Now, get out of my face.
Let me finish my cigar in peace.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ Suits 4x09 ♪ Gone Original
Air Date on August 13, 2014
♪ the greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man.
- You know?
- Of course I do.
- I never meant to...
- Louis...
I understand why you did
what you did.
- You do?
- Yes. You went down a path
with the best intentions,
and then it just got
worse and worse
until it was too late.
- Feel like shit.
- And you should.
What?
But you just said...
I understand? I do.
But I don't think you
understand that every
other time you screwed up,
it was a mistake,
and this time, it was a choice!
That's what Harvey said.
Of course
that's what Harvey said.
And just because I get
what happened,
it doesn't mean that you
deserve to be let off the hook,
so if you've come
in here to ask me
to go to him for
the millionth time, I'm...
No, I'm not here for that.
Then... then what
are you here for?
I'm here to ask you
if I'm gonna get fired.
What?
I saw how he looked
at me, Donna.
I know he trusts you,
but I need to know if Harvey's
planning on firing me.
No, Louis.
To my knowledge,
Harvey isn't planning
to fire you.
Thank you, Donna.
I knew I could count on you.
Can't remember the last time
I saw you in here.
I can't remember the last time
this firm faced prosecution.
Ava Hessington.
And after that, we said
it would never come
to this again.
How the hell did it?
We stepped into the ring
with Charles Forstman.
I'm guessing he didn't
budge last night.
He didn't.
He sheltered himself, and
he'd rather laugh in my face
than be 100% protected
against the S.E.C.
You have a plan "B"?
He doesn't, but I do.
What the hell is it?
What would you do
if you were Cahill?
Go through every
one of these boxes,
and start deposing us.
Okay, so what if
while he's doing that,
we start deposing him?
Did you come here to
personally deliver my files?
I came here to
personally deliver this.
Well, if it's an invitation
to your birthday party,
I think I'm busy that day.
That's too bad.
I promised the children a clown.
You've got to be kidding me.
You got Judge Hopkins
to let you start depositions
on your malicious
prosecution bullshit?
He didn't think it was bullshit,
which is why
he's letting me start
with your boyfriend
Eric Woodall.
You trying to take
my eye off the ball, Harvey?
This is the ball, Sean.
It's a wrecking ball,
and it's headed your way.
Louis, where the hell
have you been?
Those documents are
on their way over.
Katrina, relax.
Relax?
The last time I saw you,
you were worried
about going to prison.
What did you decide to do?
I went to Harvey and Jessica,
and I told them everything.
What?
Jessica said that
I made a mistake,
and they're working
on a way out.
Louis, have you seen
any mafia movie ever made?
I'm not really
a fan of the genre.
I find it to be a little
offensive to Italians...
Shut up, and listen.
She's telling you to your
face she'll let you live,
but behind your back, she's
making plans to whack you.
Holy shit, I'm living
on borrowed time.
Unless you fix this,
because if you don't,
even if Jessica manages
to keep you out of prison,
she'll be coming to fire you.
Jessica, I was just thinking
about our dinner plans tonight,
and I think that...
What's wrong?
We're going after Eric Woodall.
Harvey moved up the time line.
And since this is
Harvey's case now...
Why are you talking to me?
'Cause I need you to find
out every dirty thing
Eric Woodall has ever done,
condoned, or been part of.
Jessica, I really
don't feel comfortable
participating in blackmail
without knowing why.
It's not blackmail,
it's evidence,
and I'll tell you why.
Because malicious prosecution
is easier to prove
when there's a track record.
Yeah, there's only
one problem with that.
You see, just yesterday, we
agreed to hand over our files
because we had nothing to hide,
and now, you want me
to go after the S.E.C.,
which means we do. Jeff-
Jessica, hide it
from them all you want, okay?
But we talked about this,
and you said
that I shouldn't be treated
like any other partner,
so don't come in here
hiding it from me.
You want a straight answer.
I'll give you a straight answer.
Harvey did not collude
with Mike Ross,
but Sean Cahill doesn't
give a shit about that.
So I need you to do
whatever you have to
and get me something
on these guys.
Hey, how did Cahill
handle our surprise?
Actually, I got
to hand it to him.
He handled it pretty damn well.
What? You guys had
your whole Wonder Twins riff,
and now you're
giving him respect?
What's next: A time share
in the Florida Keys?
Easy, tiger.
Just saying, I got
two words for you:
Bro-Mance.
Before you order us
a gift off our registry,
let me tell you
what he's been up too.
He had Judge Hopkins sign
off on his depositions,
meaning he's coming at us
the same time we go after him.
- We can handle it.
- Can Rachel?
What?
Take a look.
She's first on the list.
And you want me
to tell her it's coming.
I want you to do more than that.
I want you to prep her.
Harvey, that's not a good idea.
Yes, it is... you're
the best person for the job.
I am the worst
person for the job.
And you're only saying it
because it makes you
feel uncomfortable.
How do you think Cahill's
gonna make Rachel feel
when he gets her under oath?
Usually, people don't
start by washing their hands.
Usually, people aren't
here to talk about Louis.
- Donna.
- Jessica, he made a mistake.
"Mistake" implies that he
did something by accident.
Louis made a choice.
And you're making
the choice to fire him
when this is over.
And how the hell is that
any of your business?
I just thought if Louis
could help get you out of it...
Help get me out of it?
He's the one
that got me into it.
And if this were Harvey,
you'd let him try
to make up for it.
And if this were Harvey,
I'd have the confidence
that he would.
Jessica, Louis did all of this
because he is dying
for your approval.
You never have
confidence in him,
and you never treat him
the way you treat Harvey.
So this is my fault?
I'm saying
Harvey's made mistakes,
and you've forgiven him.
I've made mistakes,
and you've forgiven me.
You're right, Donna,
you did make a mistake once,
and I did forgive you,
but first I fired you.
And if you don't back off me
right now,
I will do it again.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have a deposition to get to.
Please state your full name
for the record.
Eric ignatius Woodall.
- Ignatius?
- Like the Saint.
I doubt that.
And how long have you
worked for the S.E.C.?
Two months.
And where were you before that?
I worked at
the U.S. attorneys' office.
Until I got you fired
for malicious prosecution.
You didn't get me fired.
You slandered me
to a person in power,
which caused me to leave
a job I loved.
To avoid getting fired.
You have no proof of that,
and he has no knowledge of that.
Does he have any knowledge
of his feelings towards me?
I don't have any feelings
for you, Mr. Specter,
and for your information,
I landed on my feet.
Yes, we know, at the S.E.C.,
but we don't want
to talk about that.
We want to talk
about Jim Pembry.
You don't seem
too comfortable anymore, Eric.
Who's Jim Pembry?
I worked with Jim
at the U.S. attorneys' office.
On the Arthur Cohen prosecution?
I believe he did
some work for me.
You believe? You sent him
over 1,200 emails on that case
over four years.
If you say so.
Actually, your
computer records say so,
and I could read them all,
but I'd rather start
with my favorite.
"I don't care what we
get Arthur Cohen on.
"Tax evasion, insider trading,
jaywalking if we have to,
but we're putting that
piece of shit behind bars."
Where the hell did you get that?
It's not important
where we got it,
but that we got it.
Emails get heated.
It was the middle of a case.
The problem is, Eric,
this was dated two years before
you even brought your big case.
- Do you have a question?
- I sure do.
You decide someone's guilty,
then you find the crime
to fit them.
Isn't that true? No.
You want me to get
you for perjury too?
You tried to get
Arthur on one thing.
Instead, you got him
on another, didn't you?
- Don't answer him.
- Yes.
And that's exactly what you
want to do with me, isn't it?
That's enough. Stop typing.
We're done here.
- To answer your question...
- Don't...
You're damn right it is.
That's okay.
It may not be on record,
but I got what I wanted.
You're not my usual guy.
I'm not a usual anything.
No, you're not.
Thanks to Jim Pembry.
I'm not here to celebrate
with Jim Pembry.
Jessica, we may have
landed the first punch,
but we're next up.
And Cahill's gonna
be brutal on us.
- No, he isn't.
- What do you mean?
We're going to court tomorrow,
and with any luck, we're
gonna get this whole thing
tossed before he even
has a chance to depose us.
Well, then, maybe
we should go to dinner.
I have a better idea.
Let's order in.
Miss Zane, do you
live with Michael Ross,
the lawyer on the other
side of this takeover?
Yes.
And, uh, and at any point
during the takeover,
did you discuss business
with him?
No.
You expect me to believe that?
I don't care whether
you believe it or not,
because it's the truth.
The truth.
Did you discuss Logan Sanders
with Mr. Ross?
- Yes.
- I'm confused.
You just said that
you didn't discuss business
with Mr. Ross,
yet now you're saying
that you discussed the man on
the other side of the takeover.
How can one of those be
true and not the other?
- That wasn't about business.
- Then what was it about?
It was about the fact
that I used to be involved
with Logan Sanders.
And did you assure Mr. Ross
that you wouldn't
become involved
with Logan Sanders again?
What does that have to do with...
- Answer my question.
- Yes, I did.
And yet, over the course
of the takeover,
you did become involved
with him again, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
You had no physical contact
of a sexual nature at all...
- Mike, please, I don't...
- Just answer my question.
We kissed once, and that was it.
- Did you sleep with him?
- He is not going to ask me...
You just lied.
You said you weren't involved,
and then you said
you kissed him.
So I'm gonna ask you again:
Did you sleep with Logan Sanders
after you assured the man
that you supposedly love
that you wouldn't
become involved again?
I'm not gonna answer that,
because it doesn't have anything
to do with collusion.
It goes to credibility.
It goes to
what you're capable of,
whether a jury should trust you.
- A jury or you?
- What difference
does that make?
The difference is
you're the one that's doing it,
because you don't trust me.
- Because Harvey needs me to.
- It is vicious, and it's cruel.
- I am doing my job.
- Mike, I thought
you were over this.
Well, I'm goddamn not!
I didn't sleep with Logan.
I kissed him,
and I hate myself for it.
Mike, I'm so sorry.
And I can apologize to you
every day
for the rest of my life,
but I-I...
I don't know what else to do,
other than to tell you that...
You mean more to me
than anything in the world,
and I need you to believe me.
I need you to believe me
so that we can move on
and live our lives.
Think that's enough
questions for tonight.
Louis, what the
hell are you doing here?
I read
the Eric Woodall deposition,
and I thought I could help.
Help what?
You're here
to shut down Sean Cahill,
and he's not gonna give up
without a fight.
Louis, I don't
have time for this.
So take your arguments
and get the hell out of here.
Please, Jessica, I want to help.
I don't need your help.
We're about to put
this thing to bed.
- And I feel responsible.
- You are responsible.
You are the entire
reason we are in jeopardy,
and you want to sit your
stupid face in front of Cahill?
You may as well wear a sign
that says "depose me next."
And if he does that, you will
tumble like a House of Cards,
because you are ruled
by your emotions,
and that is the reason
why we are in this situation
in the first place.
Can I at least sit
in the gallery?
I don't care where you sit,
but Cahill's gonna be here
in 30 seconds,
so it better be
far away from me.
What the hell is he doing here?
The important thing is
is that he's not sitting
here anymore.
Mr. Cahill, this email
makes a strong case
that Eric Woodall
has a propensity
for malicious prosecution.
Yes, it does, Your Honor,
but I'm the one pursuing
this case,
not Eric Woodall,
and I don't have a propensity
for anything.
I'm a simple man
trying to do my job.
You expect us to believe
that the guy you came up with
at the Department of Justice
comes over to the S.E.C.,
and you immediately
start coming after us,
and it's a coincidence?
Doesn't take much to connect
the dots here, Your Honor.
Well, as long as
we're connecting dots,
I can connect a few too.
Let's start with Jeff Malone.
A man who used to work
at the S.E.C.
Now conveniently works
at Pearson Specter.
It's not against
the law to change jobs.
Yes, but why did he change jobs?
Because he was instructed
to come after us
on behalf of the S.E.C.
So he says.
I think it's because
he wanted to work
with his girlfriend
Jessica Pearson.
Excuse me?
Ms. Pearson hired Mr. Malone,
because if you're planning
to break some rules,
you need someone
to navigate them for you.
Who better to do that
than your boyfriend
who works at the S.E.C.?
That's ridiculous.
Do you have any proof
of this allegation?
Right here.
I can call you up to the stand,
or we can do this right now.
Were you seeing Jeff Malone
during the time
that he worked for the S.E.C.?
Please let the record reflect
Ms. Pearson said yes.
Well, a romantic relationship
isn't proof
of a conspiracy,
but it's not irrelevant.
I'll allow you to move
forward with depositions.
I don't care what we have to do.
I'm not losing
to that son of a bitch.
Despite what we just proved,
you're not losing to him,
you're losing to me.
And as far as depositions go,
now it's our turn.
Louis.
Is there something
I can help you with?
I was just thinking
things were so much simpler
when I was in here.
Yeah, Louis...
I know about you and Jessica.
What?
It came out in court.
See, I thought you were
using me to get ahead,
when you really just wanted
to spend more time with Jessica.
What are you doin'
in here, Louis?
I'm here to apologize.
You wanted to be my friend,
and I rejected you
because you were
trying to protect her.
You must've felt so alone.
And believe me,
I know what it's like
to feel alone.
- You're not alone.
- Oh, I am.
Jessica said that I'm
responsible for everything
that's happening,
and she was right.
No one made me make that
dirty deal with Forstman,
and now she won't forgive me.
I'm alone.
And you want me to
talk to her for you.
You're the only
one I can go to, Jeff.
And you're
the closest person she has.
Sure, Louis.
I'll talk to Jessica for you.
Hey.
You're off the hook with Cahill.
He's gonna start with me
and Harvey in the morning.
Am I?
- Are you what?
- Off the hook.
Rachel...
I didn't mean
for what happened to happen.
- But it did.
- I know.
- Mike...
- I still haven't gotten
a full night's sleep
since you told me.
I know that you're
not completely over it.
But things are gonna
come up, and I...
Want me to not be
vicious and cruel.
Do you think that's possible?
I hope so.
I hope so too.
If it means anything,
I haven't gotten
a good night's sleep
since any of this
happened either.
Maybe we can both
give it a shot tonight.
Let's start with one
for you, Mr. Ross.
Were you on good terms
with him when you left?
- Yes.
- Oh.
Well, then, why weren't
you representing him
on the Gillis Industries
takeover?
Because he wasn't
technically our client
at the time.
Well, if you're
on such good terms,
why wasn't he a client?
Because sometimes
brothers fight.
And sometimes
they pretend to fight.
What are you getting at?
I'm getting at the fact
that you supposedly
were fighting when
this thing started,
yet you claim that you
weren't fighting when it ended.
Who says we weren't
fighting when it ended?
You did,
when you hired him back.
Yeah, and the cowboys
signed Deion Sanders,
even though they were rivals.
You want to know why?
'Cause he was awesome,
and they were tired of him
intercepting their passes.
He didn't intercept passes
for you.
He fumbled the ball.
Bullshit. He hit
it out of the park.
What park are you playing at?
He sides with Walter Gillis,
buys a ton of shares,
then ditches poor Walter,
and then walks away
from the whole thing.
Why would you even want
a guy like this on your team?
What am I missing?
You're missing the fact
that he kicked ass
his first time out, and anybody
would be lucky to have him.
Then why didn't
anybody take him?
What?
I checked with every
major law firm in the city,
and not one of them
received a resume from you.
Why is that?
Because it's clear as day.
You're hiding something,
and I'll tell you what it is.
It's because you always
knew that he was coming back
because you and he were in
this together the whole time.
The problem with your
theory is neither one of us
got a nickel from
this alleged collusion,
and you've got no proof we did.
Yeah, and you're
never gonna find any,
because it doesn't exist.
So you're both insisting
that neither one of you
got any money?
Damn right.
That tells me
that someone else did.
Thank you, gentlemen.
I believe you showed me where
I should focus my manpower.
Somewhere in those files
there's a payment
from somewhere to someone,
and I'm gonna find it,
because you can't hide
money from the S.E.C.
Son of a bitch.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Tell you what?
About Louis making
a dirty deal with Forstman.
- He told you.
- He thought I already knew.
He found out we were together,
and unlike you, he assumed
that people in relationships
share shit like that.
Goddamn ticking time bomb.
Do you hear yourself?
I'm coming to you with
a problem between you and me,
and you're focused on Louis.
I'm focused on Louis
because right now his actions
threaten this entire firm.
Which brings me right
back to where we started.
Why didn't you tell me
about Louis
when I asked you what
the dirt on Woodall was for?
I didn't tell you
because I didn't want you
in the position of having
to lie for me in a deposition.
Is that "focused
on you and me "enough?
Jessica...
When are you gonna understand
that I can handle
crossing lines,
but I won't
handle you lying to me?
Now, how much trouble are we in?
That's what I'm gonna find out.
- Louis, did you see this?
- No, what is it?
It's Cahill's deposition
with Harvey and Mike.
Skip to the end.
Jesus Christ, he's honing in
like a bloodhound.
It's only a matter of time.
There's got to be a way
we can get this filed...
There isn't.
- Louis.
- I'm done.
I'm done.
And if I don't do something now,
so are Harvey and Mike.
- Where are you going?
- To finish what I started.
- You know what I think?
- What?
I think we both could've
used a better lawyer
in that deposition.
- You think this is funny?
- No, I don't.
Then help me figure a way out,
because if we don't, they're
gonna find out about Louis,
and everything Cahill's
been saying about us
is gonna start looking true.
We have to stop Cahill from
going through those files.
- We tried that.
- We have to try again.
We have to prove that Cahill
is only on this investigation
because Woodall hates you.
The problem is we don't
have a link between them.
And they have a link
between Jessica and Malone.
So we'd have to convince
Judge Hopkins
their relationship has nothing
to do with this whole thing,
which...
We'll never be able to do.
How do they even know
about Jessica and Malone?
I don't know.
Someone at the S.E.C. must've
seen them together while
Malone was still working there.
You think
they were holding hands?
Come on, Harvey, this is
Jessica we're talking about.
Talking about me, what?
Holy shit, you're right.
She was married,
and I didn't even know it.
Cahill had us followed
without authorization.
And there's no way
he had authorization
to follow a government official.
You need to pay
that man a visit.
I need to pay that man a visit.
Yep.
Oh, sorry, maybe you
didn't hear the news.
Jeff Malone doesn't
work here anymore.
And I'm guessing you know
exactly where he is,
since you've been
following him for months.
I haven't been
following him at all.
I've been following you.
Well, it doesn't really
matter who you followed,
since there's no way
you got authorization.
You think Judge Hopkins
is going to look into
those dreamy brown eyes of yours
and drop the case
because of that?
No, I think
you're gonna drop it.
- Hmm.
- 'Cause if you don't,
it's no longer
malicious prosecution.
It's abuse of power.
You did it to Mike Ross,
you did it to me,
and we're gonna find out
who else you did it to.
Take a shot.
It'll take you two years
to make a case,
and even if it sticks,
I'll get a slap on the wrist,
but Harvey Specter
will already be in prison.
You dirty son of a bitch.
Dirty?
I may bend the rules,
but I'm doing it
because you are guilty.
That's exactly
what Eric Woodall said
before we got his ass fired.
Well, I'll tell you
what I told Harvey.
I'm not Eric Woodall,
and sending
some guy named Louis Litt
to confess to some
fabricated bullshit
isn't gonna make me stop.
It's gonna make me
come at you harder.
Maybe no news is good news.
All right, maybe
no news means bad news.
When it comes to Jessica,
no news is no news.
Harvey, you have a minute?
What do you want, Louis?
I'd prefer to tell you alone.
Mike knows everything,
so spit it out.
Okay, um, but I think
you both should know
that whatever happens to me,
I had the dignity to come to you
and tell you like a man.
- What did you do?
- He did exactly
what I told him not to do.
He went to the S.E.C.,
and he confessed.
Wait, Jessica, please.
Please what? Don't kill you?
Because one thing is for sure.
When all this is over, I'm gonna
fire the shit out of you.
Fire me?
You should be thanking me.
I read the transcript.
Cahill knows
about the hidden payment.
I went there to save all of you!
And I told you
the second you did that,
these two go from being
probably innocent
to definitely guilty.
- Goddamn idiot.
- Wait a second. We...
Louis, if you confessed,
then why are you here?
- They sent me home.
- What?
What exactly did you
say to Cahill?
I didn't talk to Cahill.
I mean, I was in his office,
but then Eric Woodall comes in,
takes me down the hall.
I confessed to him.
You told the head of the S.E.C.
you committed a federal crime,
and he sent you on your way?
- Yes.
- And he didn't try to get you
to implicate Harvey?
No, in fact,
he didn't seem to care at all.
And you specifically told him
about your deal with Forstman?
Yeah. He said
they're not interested
in little fish like me.
You might be
a little fish to him,
but Forstman is a goddamn whale.
It doesn't matter.
Woodall hates me:
I'm the one he wants.
But why not use Forstman
to reel you in
and get two
for the price of one?
Unless for some reason.
Woodall doesn't want to drag
Forstman into this.
Because they're in bed together.
That's a big leap.
Harvey, you said
you told Forstman
the S.E.C. was on his ass,
and he acted
like he was wearing
a teflon suit.
He acted the same way with me.
And when assholes
act invincible,
it's because
they think they are.
It's the only
thing that makes sense.
You two find the link
between those two,
and find it tonight.
This could be something.
Look.
In April of last year,
Charles Forstman made huge
contributions
to these three senators.
So what? He's got money to burn.
Yeah, but four weeks later,
these same senators
helped appoint Eric Woodall
to head the New York office
of the S.E.C.
That doesn't prove a direct link
between Forstman and Woodall.
- It's still a link, Harvey.
- And it's how this shit works.
It's totally legal, and it's
not gonna do a thing for us.
Well, what do you want?
A picture of him handing Woodall
a bag of money?
Because we're never
gonna get that.
Maybe we don't need it.
You better be here
with something good.
I am.
Charles Forstman made me take
a million dollars
to keep from turning on him.
What if he made Woodall
take a taste too?
You think we don't know that?
That's the "bag of money"
problem.
It wouldn't be a bag of money,
because if it's untraceable,
he wouldn't have leverage
over Woodall.
That's great,
but we can't get access
to Woodall's bank accounts.
We can't.
But Cahill can.
Okay, what good
does that do us, huh?
They're together.
What if they're not?
I told you,
I went to see Cahill.
He wasn't there.
Five minutes later,
Eric Woodall shows up.
I say two words:
"Charles Forstman."
He hustles me outta there
like I'm his mistress
with his wife
coming up the driveway.
Why would he not wait
for Cahill?
You want us to get Cahill
to turn on Woodall.
- Wouldn't you?
- Maybe Louis is right.
Maybe there are lines that
Woodall's willing to cross
that Cahill won't.
That's a big "maybe."
You have a better idea?
No, I don't.
Look, guys, we all know
that Jessica's gonna
fire me after this.
I just want to help,
make things right.
Get your coat.
You really looking through
those all by yourself?
Are the Witches of Eastwick
here to tell me
how to run my department?
We're here to make
things easier for you.
Oh.
Buried in one of these boxes
is a copy of this.
It proves collusion.
Not between me and Mike.
Between him
and Charles Forstman.
And you're just
gonna give this to me?
Yup.
And you're gonna
give it to Woodall,
and we're gonna
see what he says.
And what he's gonna say is
that he doesn't give a shit
about Charles Forstman,
just like he told me
when I confessed to him.
What exactly are you implying?
We're not implying anything.
We're telling you that
after Woodall lost his job,
Forstman got him installed
at the S.E.C.,
and all he had to do
in return was protect Forstman.
Where's the proof?
In Eric Woodall's bank accounts.
Oh, so you want me to go
through his bank accounts
based on your word.
You followed us
based on his bullshit.
Based on the word of my friend.
Why don't you ask your
friend if he has a problem
giving you access
to his accounts?
If he doesn't, then we're wrong,
and we've just handed you
the smoking gun.
And if you're right,
you want me to let him
off the hook for what he did.
Woodall already
said he's a little fish.
We're asking you to
throw him back in the water.
What the hell's
going on in here?
Hey, Eric.
It's good to see you again.
Sean, isn't this great
that we're all together?
Did you see me come in?
Afraid of what I'd say?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Eric, these gentlemen
came in here
with these wild accusations
that you and Charles Forstman
are in bed together.
A bed filled
with Forstman's money.
Yes, Charles Forstman
gave me millions of dollars.
That's why I drive a Subaru.
Yeah, I didn't spend
the money he gave me either.
That doesn't mean he
didn't make me take it.
I don't give a shit.
I'm not you.
Eric, obviously these
allegations are crazy.
Of course they are.
So just...
Prove it to 'em
you've got nothing to hide.
This is ridiculous.
I... am not gonna dignify...
I'm your boss.
Gentlemen, give me a minute.
Yep.
And by a minute,
he means 10 to 15 years.
In about a half an hour,
you're gonna need
a really good lawyer.
And when that happens,
don't call me.
Which lawyer do you
think Woodall called?
Well, if he was smart,
he would call Daniel Hardman.
The best person to defend
a criminal is a criminal.
And Hardman's a much better
lawyer than you anyways.
Oh, very funny.
Thank you.
Thank you, Louis.
Please.
I'll try.
Donna told me she
already said this to you,
but I want you to
hear it from me.
I wouldn't be back here
if it wasn't for Louis.
I'll take care of it.
Woodall's taken care of,
and so is everything else.
- Not everything.
- Jessica...
Harvey, I've already
made up my mind.
You weren't there.
He helped get us out of this.
After he put us goddamn in it.
And I put us in it just as much,
the day I hired Mike Ross.
Are you looking to save Louis,
or to get yourself fired too?
I'm saying he did some bad shit,
but so have I, and so have you.
You and I don't mess shit up.
We fix it.
Which is what he did today.
You want to talk
about what he did?
I told him not to confess,
and he went straight down
to the S.E.C.,
and he sang like a canary,
after he did the same
thing with Jeff Malone.
- That doesn't...
- Doesn't what?
That's just the tip
of the iceberg.
Let's talk about
his greatest hits.
Last year, he blew up
our merger negotiations
because of a cat.
This year, he led Mike Ross
straight to Charles Forstman.
He unwound the Wexler shares
after I specifically told him
not to, and to top it all off,
he took a million-dollar
payout to commit tax fraud
that could've landed
you ten years in jail.
And he didn't tell us about
that until it was too late,
and he only did that
because he had to.
I'm still not doin' it.
I tell him to do something,
and he never goddamn does it.
Now, I told myself
I'm gonna do something.
And I'm gonna goddamn do it.
Then let me do it.
Why you and not me?
Because you want
to deliver the message
"his services
are no longer needed,"
and I want to tell him
"good-bye."
You're really going to do this?
Harvey,
this place is all he has.
I know.
I'm coming with you.
Dear Harvey and Jessica,
there comes a time
when a man must
look at himself in the mirror,
to judge himself
instead of waiting
to be judged by others.
And for me, that time is now.
You both know
I came to Pearson Specter
right out of law school,
but what you may not know is
this is the only place
I've ever worked.
It's the only place
I've ever wanted to work.
It is my life...
It is my home...
And the people that work here
are my family.
You're like my parents.
And the partners,
they're like my brothers,
and associates under my care
are like my children.
And I'm ashamed
to admit it, but...
I put all of you in jeopardy
for my own personal gain.
I told myself
it was for the greater good,
but the truth is
I just wanted to feel
on the same level
as both of you, I...
I can deny that no longer.
I can excuse
my actions no longer.
Although we've had our
differences over the years,
there are no two people
I respect more.
Your names are on the wall
for a reason,
and mine is not for a reason.
And I refuse to put
either one of you
through the pain
of having to fire me.
So effective immediately,
I, Louis Litt,
am resigning
from Pearson Specter.
Please take care of my home.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man