Previously on Suits...
Walter, I can't guarantee you
we'll win,
but I can guarantee you
that I will never sell you out.
Well, you told me that
Mike Ross wasn't a threat,
and then he handcuffed us
with a T.R.O.
I want proof that
he's giving up his bid,
and if I don't get it
by the morning,
I'm gonna call
my private investigators,
and I'm gonna finish
what I started.
What did Harvey tell you?
Looks like he told me the truth.
We're done.
I want you to stop
the personal attacks on Mike.
You told me this
wasn't gonna be a problem.
You don't have to stop this
because you're some changed man.
You have to stop this
because you owe me.
Mr. Ross.
Eric Woodall.
I'm the U.S. attorney for...
The southern district
of New York.
I know who you are.
Since when does the S.E.C.
go around
intimidating law firms
by going after their clients?
They don't, but they will
when Eric Woodall starts there
next week.
It started.
Seven clients, seven subpoenas,
all coming tomorrow.
Uh, excuse me,
you don't have an appointment.
I don't need an appointment.
Sit down, shut up, and listen.
Harvey might forgive you because
you returned those recordings,
but I don't.
- Donna.
- Not done.
What Harvey did with Gillis,
it was harsh,
but using what I told you
in a private conversation...
That crosses a line
that even Harvey never would.
- Donna.
- Still not done.
When you left our firm,
you left me too,
but I honestly thought
that we'd always be friends.
Now I'm not so sure.
Amy, did you send Donna
the package?
Guilt gift. Didn't open it.
It was a balenciaga
classic town bag.
Ivory?
Anthracite
with an outside pocket.
His idea or yours?
Don't answer that.
It was yours.
I'm sorry, Donna.
You and Harvey want to
knock each other out,
you go right ahead.
But don't ever betray me again.
Nice shoes.
She's even better
than I imagined.
Looking for this?
Harvey Specter.
What brings you to Montclair
at 7:00 in the morning?
Oh, you know
what brings me here.
I woke up to find these
on my welcome mat.
Well, as much as I'd love
to have been responsible
for subpoenaing seven
of your firm's top clients,
I didn't even know about this
till just now.
You didn't even have the balls
to come at me directly.
Get off my property.
What's the matter, Eric?
You're afraid
I'll get you fired again?
I get it.
You want to hear me say
I'm using my new position
to destroy your business,
'cause you're the piece
of garbage that got me fired.
Isn't that what you
want to hear me say?
Oh, I know
you'll never say that,
but I do want you to admit
that you sent
an agent Brian Harris
after my firm.
Sorry.
I don't even have jurisdiction
over that department.
That department's run by a man
name Sean Cahill.
So all on his own,
Sean Cahill just happened
to target my firm?
Well, he is a killer attorney
with a nose for sleazy lawyers,
and I should know.
We came up together
at the Justice Department.
You know, that little
governmental agency
that protects their own?
Well, Eric, your big brother
couldn't protect you
from getting fired before,
and I don't see how this is
gonna be any different,
and by the way,
that's yesterday's paper.
You wanted to see me?
Sure did.
Have a seat.
I was going over
our trade sheets.
Couldn't help but notice
you bought another 100,000
shares of Gillis Industries.
It's gonna be fine.
Do I look like an asshole
to you?
Where the hell
did you get the money?
You know where I got the money.
I bought those shares on margin.
And leveraged my company.
The bylaws said I can do it.
I don't care
what the bylaws say,
you did this without asking.
Look, I know you're pissed.
Oh, I'm not pissed.
I've been waiting for you
to have the balls
to do something like this
since you got here.
You raised my risk,
but you also raised my reward,
and on top of it,
you did it like
an investment banker,
without permission.
Well, thank you, Jon.
Go get 'em.
One more thing. Yeah?
You have a week
to de-leverage my company.
If you don't,
you're out of a job.
You want to explain to me why
you went to Eric Woodall's house
this morning?
I understand
you're bent out of shape
because I stepped on
your territory...
You think I give a shit
about my territory?
What the hell are you doing
in here?
Listen, I really don't care
if you work this thing or I do,
but whoever it is has to
not be an idiot.
And how, exactly, am I an idiot?
- You poked the bear.
- Eric Woodall isn't the bear.
No. I am.
And whatever you were
about to say, don't say it.
Harvey, this is his case.
It's why we brought him in,
and I don't want you involved.
Me?
I'm the one who found out
it's not Woodall
coming after us, it's...
Sean Cahill.
You think I didn't know that?
These are my clients,
and when they call in a panic,
I need to be the voice
on the other end of the line.
Then be the voice
on the other end of the line,
but you're not
handling the S.E.C.
I'm the reason
they're coming after us.
Which is why you wanted to
hire Jeff in the first place.
That was before
all this became real.
Now that it's happening,
he doesn't want to
sit on the sidelines.
Damn right I don't.
Well, then find yourself
a comfortable spot on the bench,
because like it or not,
Jeff's in charge.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Suits 4x04 ♪ Leveraged
Original Air Date on July 9, 2014
♪ all right ♪
♪ All that time imagine this ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man.
So it go just like
you said it would?
Exactly, except for the part
where if I don't find
a new investor in a week,
I'm out of a job.
I'm surprised
he gave you a week.
- Amy, it's not funny.
- I know it isn't.
I was just trying to make
the best of the situation.
Well, if you want to make
the best of the situation,
get me a meeting
with Tony Gianopolous,
because if I can't get
in there...
I'm in trouble.
We're in trouble.
You really mean that?
You think I'm staying here
if you leave?
Thank you, Amy.
I'm just kidding.
Epstein's been trying
to poach me
since the day I got here.
Mmm. Tch.
Yeah, you think those flowers
bought themselves?
Mm-mm.
You... wow.
Can I talk to you a second?
If you want an update
on the takeover,
you should talk to Harvey.
That's not why I'm here.
Look, Logan, I-I know that you...
I have five companies here
that I'm looking at
for my next deal,
and I need someone
to evaluate them
from a legal standpoint.
- Your next deal.
- Yeah, my next deal.
Harvey told me
not to hurt my future
by going below the belt
with Mike,
so instead of not
hurting my future,
I thought I'd start
planning for it.
So then maybe Harvey is who
you should be planning it with.
Well, Harvey's got stuff to do,
and he's not the one who
convinced me to back off Mike.
Are you saying that I owe you?
No, I'm not saying that,
but that is what you said to me.
So we're just gonna go
back and forth, trading favors?
Rachel, this isn't a favor.
I have a board meeting
on Friday.
I need to be prepared.
So are you my lawyer or not?
I will get right on it.
Thank you.
Louis, I need your help.
We're gonna need to...
Don't speak.
You may speak.
What were you doing?
Just thanking
the lord God almighty.
We taking down Jessica?
We firing Malone?
I am tingling.
What, Harvey? Just tell me what.
Mike Ross just bought another
2% of Gillis Industries.
He must be leveraged up
to his scrawny little neck.
Exactly, and he's gonna be
scrambling for funding.
You want me
to get your T.R.O. removed.
How do you know that?
Because you pissed off
judge Ramos
and now she can't stand you.
How do you know that?
Oh, because I keep
a list of your enemies.
You want to see it?
Just get it done.
Oh, I'm gonna get it done.
It's like taking candy
from a baby.
Louis, we're splitting
Mike's focus.
That doesn't mean
he won't be prepared.
Oh, he can prepare all he wants,
but the student is about to meet
the master,
because Ralph Macchio
doesn't stand a chance
against Mr. Miyagi.
You know The Karate Kid?
That's not cool, Harvey.
Oh, let me see
if I can guess why you're here.
You came to tell me
the way I handled Harvey
this morning was sexy.
Oh, you mean when I told him
to leave you alone?
And the way that I allowed you
to do that was very sexy.
Uh-huh.
And this is...
The Griffen Cosmetics subpoena.
I looked them all over.
This is the weakest one.
- The weakest one?
- Exactly.
Once this one goes down,
the others fall like dominos.
First of all, if I were gonna
take that strategy,
I would go for the hardest one.
Second of all,
why don't you walk yourself
back to your office
and let me do my job?
Excuse me?
You told Harvey you
brought me in to handle this.
Your job isn't to worry about
what I told Harvey.
Your job is to worry about
what I'm telling you.
And what I'm telling you
is that I'm not walking
into an S.E.C. negotiation
with a babysitter.
Negotiation?
This is going to be a war.
I know that, and I'm gonna
win it with one shot.
Then I suggest you
warm up to this.
You're not walking into
the S.E.C. with a babysitter.
You're walking in there
with a bazooka.
Hey, Mike,
you need to see something.
No, I don't have time.
I'm working on
the Gianopolous proposal.
Yeah, that proposal isn't
gonna matter if they win this.
Goddamn it.
Harvey's trying to roll back
the T.R.O.?
No, it's not Harvey.
Check the docket.
It's some woman named Lois Litt.
Yeah.
I know how to handle her.
Um, here.
This is 90% done. Check it over.
Make sure there's not
one comma out of place.
Mike, come on,
you know I can do more than...
I don't have time, Amy.
Just do it.
Okay.
How long did you work
in this shit hole?
Sorry I'm late.
Been up to my neck in work.
Just filed seven huge subpoenas.
- Yeah, we know what you filed.
- Oh.
I see you brought the missus.
Jessica, whatever you're
about to say, don't say it.
How about I say it with this?
Ooh, a subpoena?
Smells fresh. It is.
And you'll be answering it
in court tomorrow.
Oh, well then I better see
what flavor bullshit
you're serving up.
Ah, ah, now, this is a good one.
"Malicious prosecution
of Pearson Specter clients,"
and how exactly
are we doing that?
I'll tell you how.
You come at our clients.
Our clients leave us.
You drop their cases.
Well, I certainly
wouldn't tell them
that's how to avoid
S.E.C. scrutiny,
but it's not my fault
if dropping Pearson Specter
starts catching on.
Enough bullshit.
You're targeting my clients
on behalf of Eric Woodall,
and you know it.
That is a lovely theory,
but if you had any proof,
you wouldn't be standing here
right now.
I have proof, Sean.
I have proof you filed
seven cases in one day
against our clients,
which we both know
has never happened
in the history of the S.E.C.
It has now.
We've filed nine cases
against clients of Weil Gotshal,
eight against Skaaden,
and six against Cravath.
Welcome to the new S.E.C.
We target law firms.
And as long as we're not
only targeting yours,
the only way to shut this down
is to shut us down.
You and I both know
what's really
going on here, Sean,
and I'm gonna prove it.
Well, good luck,
but how do you think
judge Hopkins is gonna respond
to your allegations
when I tell him
they're coming from a man
who is about to be fired?
Oh, you... you didn't tell her.
Ooh, that's awkward.
I'll see you in court.
- Jessica!
- I don't want to hear it.
- Well, you need to hear it.
- What?
That you lied to me?
You know, I didn't
actually lie to you.
Oh, no, no, no.
You tell me that you didn't lie
because we never directly
asked you the question,
and I will knock your head off.
All right, fine.
I lied.
I lied
because it doesn't matter.
I want to fight for you,
and I'm the best man to do it.
Well, the new part
of the equation
is that you just made me
look like a fool.
- Jess.
- Don't pull that Jess shit
with me... I want to know what
it says in your file.
- I don't know what it says.
- How the hell do you not know?
'Cause whatever it is
is bullshit.
Because the reason
they were gonna fire me
is that I refused
to go after you.
Then why didn't you tell me that
when you came at us
demanding a job?
Because good lawyers negotiate
from a position of strength,
not weakness.
Well, the position
you just put us in
is pretty goddamn weak.
Oh well if it isn't
the boy wonder.
- Louis, hey.
- Don't Louis me.
You left without even
the courtesy
of a "how's your father?"
What does that mean?
It means that I'm not here
to exchange pleasantries.
I'm here to get
that T.R.O. lifted.
Well, I'm sorry
you feel that way.
I'm also sorry
to hear about Sheila.
Bullshit you're sorry
to hear about she...
What are you talking about?
Come on, you have to have heard.
Heard what?
She's engaged.
It's all over Harvard's
Facebook page.
Oh, my God,
how could she do this?
She said she could never be
attracted to a handsome man.
And that picture doesn't
even do him justice,
but this one, however...
- A thong?
- Yeah.
That... What the-
Yeah, it's a whole, like,
beach thing, I guess.
Long weekend.
You're a son of a bitch, Mike.
You're not even sorry at all.
You're using this
to get into my head.
Louis, come on,
I can't believe you.
You think I would use
Sheila's engagement
just to get you off your game?
Never gonna work.
That I would
stick it in your face
that she's all up
in this guy's business
in a way that you've
never seen before?
Water off a duck's back.
That right now
she's probably scrapbooking
the first day
of their relationship,
which apparently happened
just weeks
after you broke her heart?
You're the devil.
Next up on the docket,
Sidwell Investment group
versus Sanders International.
Looks like that's us.
I'll see you in there.
Louis, I can't believe it.
I give you one
goddamn job to do,
and you...
What are you doing up there?
Harvey, please, I can explain.
Oh, explain why you stood in
front of the judge like a moron?
What possible explanation...
Sheila got engaged.
What?
When?
This morning.
Louis, I'm sorry.
I was so sure
that she would just come around
about having children, you know?
That's why I've been
turning down
all those J-date requests.
We'll get Mike another way.
Oh, you're goddamn right
we're gonna get him.
I'm gonna get
that son of a bitch
if it's the last thing I do.
What are you talking about?
He used the Sheila news
to get into my head, Harvey.
Used the news
or gave you the news?
Oh, please,
what difference does it make?
What difference does it make?
It makes all the difference.
Like on the one hand,
I feel for you,
and on the other, you're
the world's biggest idiot.
Look at my computer.
I've been staring at it
for three hours.
It's real.
I don't believe it.
Yeah, that adonis on that yacht,
Sheila's fiance.
That adonis
is a photoshopped picture
of Lorenzo Lamas from 1998!
Who the hell is Lorenzo Lamas?
Well, I can tell you
who he isn't.
He isn't Sheila's fiance!
Oh, thank God.
Are you even listening?
It was bad enough
that Nigel rattled you
with your unread cat letters.
Now you're letting Mike do this?
- Harvey, please.
- Shut the hell up!
Look, I tried to warn you,
and you stood there with your
stupid leg up in the air,
telling me that the student
was no match for the master
and all it took
was one doctored picture
for you to shit the bed!
- I didn't mean to...
- Shut the hell up!
God.
Well, fancy meeting you here.
Rachel, get out of here.
I was just coming to
make some copy...
Louis, what's wrong?
I don't want to talk about it;
Nothing is wrong.
Well, obviously
something's wrong.
You know what,
if you're so curious,
why don't you just go ask
the man of your dreams?
I'm sure the two of you will
have a big laugh about it later.
Okay, I don't know
what you're talking about,
but seeing you like this,
there's no way
that I would laugh at you.
What is it?
Mike convinced me
that Sheila was engaged
to throw me off my game.
I'm so sorry, Louis.
Yeah, well, he sure wasn't.
Stuck a knife in me, twisted it
with the thought of her
and another man.
It felt like
a drill in my skull all day,
and then to top it all off,
it cost me the respect
of my best friend.
Maybe...
Oh, don't you even try
to defend him.
No, I wasn't going to.
I was going to say,
maybe this is what you needed
to decide to reconnect
with Sheila.
And what about Harvey?
How do I repair that?
I'm really sorry
for what happened, Louis.
I am.
- Hey.
Did you eat?
Are you asking because
you're concerned about me
or because you want to know
if I left you any food?
Whoa.
Tough day? I'm sorry.
I've just been working
16-hour days,
and I'm really... stressed.
Yeah, I know the feeling.
Really?
'Cause I heard that you had
a pretty big win today.
You talked to Harvey.
I talked to Louis.
Mike, I know you want to win,
but do you have any idea
what your lie did to him?
It wasn't a lie.
It was a strategy.
It was both, and it ended up
with him near tears.
Come on, Rachel.
It just seems like all
that matters to you is winning
and that you don't care about
what it does to your friends.
You know what?
I'm sorry that I hurt Louis,
but he was going to
that courtroom
so they could put their
tender offer to a vote.
I know.
You also know because we've
had this discussion before
that if he got his way,
they would rip that company
to shreds.
So instead of coming down on me
for what I did to Louis,
why don't you start worrying
about all the lives
that Logan Sanders is
gonna destroy if that happens?
You know, it's funny.
You told me you didn't care
who was in charge.
You just wanted whoever it was
to not be an idiot.
Are you saying
that I was an idiot?
I'm saying we both were.
I shouldn't have gone
to Woodall,
and you shouldn't have
lied to us.
You don't seem pissed.
I've had enough happen
already today.
Besides, lying to me was wrong,
but lying to the woman
you're in a relationship with
is a whole other level.
When do you think
she's gonna get past it?
From personal experience,
that could take a while.
That's not my problem.
That's yours.
Then what are you doing here,
Harvey?
I'm here to tell you
what you're gonna do about it.
No.
No way.
I'm not taking the stand.
Then what are you doing here?
Because Woodall telling you
to go after our clients
is how you got this job
in the first place
and happens to make our case.
He didn't outright tell me
to do it,
and you know it.
You had to find out somehow.
I found out from Brian Harris.
He told me he had
this funny feeling
that the day after
Woodall arrived,
that I was gonna
start issuing subpoenas
to Pearson Specter clients.
When I asked him why,
he said, "you know why."
Then you're gonna
get up on the stand
and tell them that.
I can't. I have no proof.
It was vague, and it's
a third party conversation.
Which makes it hearsay,
and I don't give a shit.
Well, I do, 'cause it opens
me up to slander at best
and perjury charges at worst.
Well, Jeff, you used that story
to get your ass in here.
Now use it to get the job done.
Amy!
I thought I asked you
to leave the Gianopolous
proposal on my desk.
And I did, 20 minutes ago.
What? Okay.
Did you proof it? No.
I thought you'd have
a better chance
if the document
was riddled with typos.
- This is important.
- I know it is,
which is why I read it
backwards and forwards.
Okay, did you add the part
about the leveraged recap
like I asked?
I did, but your figures
on the non-voting stock
didn't add up,
so I proposed a staggered board
to make up for the imbalance.
Staggered board?
Yeah, don't act so surprised.
I'm sorry,
I just thought that you...
You just thought
that I didn't know anything
about what goes on here?
Listen up, T. Boone Pickens,
I actually know a lot
about this business.
Okay, I said I'm sorry...
And I know more than enough
to know
that that looks like
every other proposal
that's comes across my desk.
Well, that gives me
a shit load of confidence
going into this meeting.
I'm not trying to
destroy your confidence.
That's the one thing you have
going for you.
Then what are you trying to do?
Mike, you're not here
because you crunched
Sidwell some numbers.
You're here because
you solved a problem for him.
All right.
Get rid of this, and bring...
And bring you everything
I can find on Tony Gianopolous.
On it.
Amy.
Why aren't you...
Why am I an assistant
and not an investment banker?
I'm getting my PhD
in psychology.
Money bores me.
I don't know why you needed
to talk to me in chambers,
Mr. Malone.
I was clear on my ruling.
Well, with all due respect,
Your Honor,
your ruling didn't cover
the fact that the S.E.C.
has a vendetta
against Pearson Specter.
That's a serious accusation.
And if it were the truth,
he would have said it
out there, not in here.
I'm doing it in private, Sean,
because I don't want to slander
an entire department
based on the actions of two men.
Translation?
He doesn't want to be
charged with perjury
because he's lying,
and this is a joke.
It wasn't a joke
when I was asked
to do the exact same thing
that he's doing right now.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Before I left the S.E.C.,
I was told to target
Pearson Specter clients.
- And who exactly told you?
- Brian Harris.
Then go after him,
'cause all you've got on me
is hearsay,
and might I point this is
the accusation of a man
who is about to be fired,
which I'd say should be taken
with a cubic meter of salt.
Well, that cubic meter of salt
might actually
get a little bit smaller
if Sean here were to, say,
open up his files
and show us his paper trail.
Our work product is covered
under federal regulation,
and he knows that.
I also know you're hiding
behind your office
and using his court to do it.
All right, all right,
that's enough.
Mr. Malone,
I don't appreciate you
using my chambers to testify,
and he may not have proof,
but if one client
leaves his firm
and their charges
miraculously disappear,
you're looking at more
than sanctions.
You're looking at jail time.
Thank you.
Rachel?
It's only been a day.
You already have a suggestion
for my new deal?
- I do.
- Good.
Then which of those five
companies should I go after?
None of them.
So you brought me nothing?
No, I brought you
five better options.
- What's wrong with the op...
- Just take a look.
These companies
have no disposable assets.
No, they don't.
They have underperforming assets
that can be turned around
and built into something.
Did you even look into
the companies I gave you?
- Yes, I did, but I...
- But what?
Sounds like someone's
been drinking
her boyfriend's kool-aid.
Maybe if more people did,
there just might be...
God damn it, Rachel,
I'm not in business
to save the world.
I asked for
a professional opinion.
And I gave you
You just don't like it.
No, I don't.
And now we're gonna have to work
all day tomorrow
to do what I asked you to do
in the first place.
You mean spend all day together.
- If that's what it takes.
- Mm-hmm.
Did you call this board meeting
just so we could
spend more time together?
Did you bring me deals
you knew I'd reject
just to avoid it?
Look, like I said,
I have a meeting on Friday,
and I need to be
prepared for it,
so maybe you should
go back to your office,
get cracking,
and just give me a call
when you have something.
Okay.
You're kidding me.
So this is all mine?
Yup.
In 20 days, the public access
will be gone,
and you will have yourself
1/4 mile of private beach.
What about
the Southampton city council?
What about them?
They're a bunch of
public-access loving assholes.
Like I said, what about them?
How'd you do this, Mike?
Well, the question isn't
how I did it,
it's why I did it.
Oh. You want something from me.
Just your consideration.
Well, you've earned it.
Go ahead.
Not interested.
You didn't even look at it.
Oh, I don't have to.
You just said that I earned
your consideration.
Mm-hmm, and you just got it.
Gillis industries
is ripe for a turnaround,
and I already own 7%.
Congratulations.
Now go beg someone else
for money,
because you're not getting mine.
I don't understand.
You don't have to.
Now get the hell
out of my office.
- Mr. Gianopolous.
- I said get the hell out.
Hey, Mike. How's it going?
Fancy meeting you here.
It was you.
What was me?
I'm just here to thank you
for the advice you once gave me.
You know,
back when we were friends.
- Louis.
- No, no, no.
No, no, no.
You once told me that
my actions had consequences.
Remember?
Your actions yesterday
have consequences too.
What did you say to Gianopolous?
Not much.
Just that you were
the person responsible
for his number two leaving him.
I was responsible?
He agreed to it.
But what he didn't know
was is that
it was his own lawyer
who came up with the idea.
Now he does.
- And what does that...
- Have to do with it?
He may have agreed to it,
but it was a betrayal by you.
And here's a little something
you obviously do not know
about investment banking.
The only thing more satisfying
to these guys than money
is sticking it to someone
who stuck it to them.
Louis.
I'm sorry for hurting you
with Sheila.
Don't you ever mention
her name to me again.
Okay, but it was a move,
like you just did.
So can we move on?
Move on?
You used the woman I love
to extend your goddamn T.R.O.
You knew how I felt about her,
and you did it anyway.
I will never, ever forget it
until the day I die.
Good luck beating Harvey
without money.
I have good news.
James Dolan died
and left me the Knicks?
Louis stopped Mike
from getting Gianopolous.
He blocked his funding.
Good.
You went to Louis
with a problem,
he fixed it,
and all you're gonna say
is "good"?
Donna, I'm glad
he fixed the problem,
but it was a problem he created.
He created it because
when it comes to people
he cares about,
Louis has a blind spot.
Yeah, for people and cats
and who knows what else?
I'll tell you what else.
He cares about you.
What do you want from me, Donna?
I want you to tell him
he did a good job.
I'll tell him
when we come out on top.
Okay, Harvey.
You do what you're gonna do,
but just remember,
when Louis asked Sheila
to marry him,
you were the one he picked
to be his best man,
and you said yes.
I'm sorry,
but we're not hiring today.
I think you'd be
looking for a job
given the beat-down
you took in chambers.
I'm not sure what
Jeff disgruntled employee here
told you,
but I'm still standing.
Well, what I told her
is that you lost.
Then why are you here?
We're here to make you an offer.
You drop all seven cases,
we drop the malicious
prosecution claim.
No deal.
Judge Hopkins is going to be
waiting for you to take action.
Too much time goes by,
he's gonna think
you're full of shit.
But if you fold right now,
he's only gonna sanction you
for the exact claim
that we're willing to drop.
Which is why
we'll tell the judge
that in exchange for those
cases being dropped,
we'll give the S.E.C.
unprecedented access
to our clients' books.
Which, of course,
you won't be doing.
No, we won't.
So what exactly
am I getting out of this?
You get to save face.
I do like my face.
However, I also like my ass,
which will be on the line
if I take this deal.
Then you have 24 hours to
decide which one you like more.
Mr. Forstman, Mike Ross.
No.
Sir, I think that
if you hear me out...
How the hell
did you find me here?
The article in Forbes said
you can't go more
than three hours
without Rosa's cafe cubanos.
That article in Forbes
was six years ago.
It also said you never change.
Did you also read where I have
every Bud Fox wannabe dumped
in a local landfill?
If you do that,
you'll miss the opportunity
to get back at Harvey Specter.
And what does
a little shit like you
know about Harvey Specter?
I know that he bought that
'63 Aston Martin
out from under you,
and you've hated him ever since.
You know he keeps it
in a garage?
Doesn't even drive it.
What do you want?
Gillis Industries.
Gillis Industries...
Is a black hole
of distressed debt.
I want nothing to do with it.
No, it isn't.
It's a '63 Aston Martin.
Who do you work for?
Who says I work for anyone?
Because a young kid like you
with enough clout
to go after Gillis...
I'd know you.
I work for Jonathan Sidwell.
Okay. You've got my 230 mil.
I only need 80.
You don't know what you need.
What happens to the company
is my call.
Done.
Oh, one more thing,
when you get those papers.
I have a feeling there'll be
a provision buried in there
that says that
once the deal closes,
you cut Sidwell out.
I'm sorry, what?
I don't know him,
and I want need him
sucking a chunk out of a deal
that can't happen without me.
Well?
He went for it.
That is great.
No, it's not all great.
He'll only give me the money
if I agree to cut out Sidwell.
What?
What does cut him out even mean?
It means make sure Sidwell
doesn't get a penny
from this deal.
Mike, the second he finds
that out, you're gone.
He's not gonna find out
until the deal closes,
and if I don't find the money,
I'm out of a job anyway.
Oh, I get it.
At least this way, you get to
leave on the winning side.
- We leave on the winning side.
- Who says I'm gonna do that?
What happened to, "you think
I'm staying if you leave"?
Yeah, that was before I knew
you were gonna screw over
Sidwell.
- Amy, I...
- No, he may be
a dick sometimes,
but he's the reason you're here.
You think I want this?
I have to make a choice between
the promise I made
to Walter Gillis
and what I owe Jonathan.
Mike, Walter Gillis
doesn't give a shit
about that promise anymore.
Yeah, but I do,
and so do all the people
that work for him.
So you're gonna do it.
I don't know.
But I do know that I keep
having to do shity things
just to win this thing,
but I'm gonna go make up
for one of them right now.
I'm sorry I didn't do
what you asked me to do.
I should have evaluated
your ideas.
You should have,
but I should have remembered
that you don't always do
what people expect of you.
You mean what people
tell me to do.
I chose the nicer version.
Well, I, um...
I finished what I should
have done in the first place.
- And?
- And let's go through them.
- What are you doing here?
- Waiting for you.
I figured if I tried
to go upstairs,
you'd have me killed.
Oh, is that a joke,
'cause I'm not laughing.
Louis, I didn't say it
right the first time.
I want to say it again.
I'm sorry.
You think "I'm sorry"
makes up for what you did?
No, but I'm hoping
that we can move past it
and be friends again.
Well, the only problem
with that is,
is that you and I both know
that you're only here
because I took away
your sugar daddy,
and now you want me
to take it easy on you.
Louis, if you don't want to
accept my apology, that's fine,
but I'm not here
from a position of weakness.
I'm here from
a position of strength.
Bullshit. Where'd you get money?
You don't have any friends
out there.
No, but Harvey has enemies.
What's that supposed to mean?
You told me
these guys hold grudges.
I just found a guy
with one against Harvey.
You son of a bitch.
You didn't come here
to apologize.
You came here
to rub it in my face.
Oh, and I bet you just
can't wait to tell Harvey
that I'm the one
who gave you the idea.
Louis, I wasn't even
gonna tell you
how I got the idea at all.
I'm still not gonna tell Harvey.
Because you want me to owe you?
Because I'm not
as much of an asshole
as you think I am.
- What about a buyout?
- Never gonna happen.
He's got a golden parachute.
Well, then I've got two people
on the board.
I can force a vote.
You do that,
it triggers a stock split.
His shares double
in voting power.
Yours don't.
I mean, that's all five.
None of them work.
No, they don't.
So when you told me
you should have
evaluated my ideas first,
you weren't saying
that they were good.
I was saying
I wasn't doing my job.
Which was to let me
figure out for myself
that my ideas weren't good.
I chose the nicer version.
Logan, there are plenty
of other companies out there.
None that we're gonna find
in time
for my board meeting tomorrow.
- So push it.
- I can't.
I didn't call it.
- And I thought...
- Yeah, I know.
That I only even arranged it
to spend time with you?
You really didn't.
No, and now they're gonna
ask me tomorrow
how Gillis is going,
and I'm gonna have to tell them
we might lose,
and then they're gonna ask me
what else I have,
and I'm gonna have to
tell them nothing.
Or maybe you won't.
I told you,
I'm not in that business.
Then convince the board
that you should be.
Okay.
Go back to your office.
Get your files.
Like you said,
I don't always do
what people expect me to do.
Louis, can I talk to you
for a minute?
Of course.
I heard about what you did
with Gianopolous.
Good job.
I appreciate that, Harvey.
I do.
Um...
But it doesn't matter.
You know,
he went somewhere else.
I know.
He went to Forstman.
I just wanted to tell you
you did a good job anyway.
See, that's the thing.
I didn't.
What are you talking about?
Mike got the idea from me.
What?
How?
When I cut him off
from Gianopolous,
I stuck it in his face,
and I told him that
people hold grudges, and I...
He must have known
your history with Forstman,
and that's why he went to him,
so...
I'm sorry.
God damn it, Louis.
I don't want to keep
being mad at you,
but you keep doing
the same shit.
But, see, this wasn't me
being duped.
No, it was you
letting your emotions
lead you into
doing something stupid.
Again.
You just had to
stick it in his face.
You know what?
I'm done.
It's not fair, you know.
I'm emotional. You're cold.
You're loved,
and I'm hated.
Louis, if I was so cold,
I wouldn't have come here
in the first place.
What are you doing?
Pouring us a drink.
Cahill took the deal.
All seven cases
are officially dead.
Jessica, I'm sorry that I didn't
come clean with you before.
Me too.
Lying to you
was a business decision,
and it was wrong,
but I want you to know
that I would never lie to you,
man to woman.
I appreciate that.
We have a problem.
I just got off the phone
with Richard Coleman.
Last week, Sean Cahill asked him
if I'd ever crossed any lines
in his presence.
Son of a bitch.
He doesn't want our clients
to leave us.
He wants them
to cough up dirt on me.
At least none of them did,
or we'd be in trouble right now.
- How do you want to handle it?
- Let's talk about it tomorrow.
Right now, I've got
something else to do.
Shit.
They wouldn't turn on Harvey.
Cahill wanted us
to drop those cases anyway,
and I just did him a big favor.
You couldn't have known that.
It was my job to know that.
Hey, Mike?
- Yeah.
- Harvey Specter's here to...
Harvey, what can I do for you?
I wanted to thank you
for the recordings.
Is that why you came
all the way down here?
I came to tell you I think
you're making a big mistake
getting into bed with Forstman.
I knew it.
Mike, you don't know this guy.
You could have thanked me
for those recordings days ago,
but instead you picked
the exact day
that I find a new investor
to show up
with your thank-you
and your friendly advice.
This isn't some move.
- You only make moves.
- Mike.
Hey, tell me right now
that you wouldn't do
the same thing
if you were in my position.
I was.
And I did.
What?
You think our grudge
is about some car?
What the hell
are you talking about?
When I was younger,
I made a shady deal with him,
and I paid for it.
Who says that I'm making-
If you haven't, you will,
because Forstman
doesn't throw money around
without getting something
in return.
He's gonna get money in return.
Money is third on his list.
The first two
are getting back at people
and getting control of people.
Maybe you should have
thought of that
before you had Louis
cut me off from Gianopolous,
because now I have
no other choice!
You always have a choice.
Here's to turning around
Piedmont Avionics.
What?
Nothing.
What time is it?
Too late for you
to change your mind.
Logan, the board
is going to be wowed.
Well, I wish I had
your confidence.
You are not short
in the confidence department.
Oh, you don't have to
pay me compliments.
I meant it as an insult.
You know, if this law thing
doesn't work out...
Then I could have a career
in venture capital?
No, I was gonna say
you could be my assistant.
Hilarious.
Seriously, Rachel, I...
I couldn't have done it
without you.
Yes, you could have.
It just wouldn't have been
as good.
Humility.
Another thing I love about you.
Logan, I should go.
Rachel, I...
Um...
Good luck tomorrow.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man