Previously on Suits...
I want you to go back
over your work
with a fine-tooth comb.
We're as protected as we can be.
Every partner at this firm
goes over their work
if I say so.
I'm not every goddamn partner.
I made a deal with Forstman.
This has got to be
the most genius thing
you have ever done
in your entire, wonderful life.
Forstman's insisting
that I run the money
through Switzerland
and the Caymans.
Louis, that's illegal.
You didn't see the look
on Harvey's face
when he found out
that I was the one
who saved the day,
and I am not gonna see
the look on his face
when he finds out that I didn't.
There isn't enough money
in the world
for me to ever trust you again.
- Listen to me.
- No, you listen to me!
You're fired.
- No, I can't.
- Rachel. Rachel.
What the hell is this?
A job offer.
I am going to tell Mike
what happened.
If you do this,
you will be risking
your whole life with Mike.
I'm risking it if I don't.
♪ ♪
I heard.
How?
Amy.
Why would she...
So that you wouldn't have to.
Here.
Shit.
I didn't even think
about what would happen to her.
Mike, you don't have
to think about anyone
except for you right now.
I don't want to think about me.
All I've done is let everyone
down, including you.
You have not let me down.
You don't even know
what I've done.
Whatever it is,
it can't be as bad as...
As I think?
Rachel, I lost my job.
I lost the takeover.
I lost Walter Gillis
his company.
I cut a deal to sell out the man
who gave me a chance
in the first place.
And to top it all off,
the guy who made me
do that called me his guy
and then offered me a job.
So what does that make me?
It makes you a human being.
♪ ♪
I don't know what to do.
I don't either.
But we don't have to do
anything tonight.
Louis, you need to calm down.
I broke the law.
Please keep your voice down.
Why? Let any man judge me.
So says the good book.
- No, it doesn't.
- You know what?
I think I know
what the goddamn good book says.
Listen to me.
You did what you had to do.
Oh, really?
Well, that's not what you said
when you found out.
You said,
"Louis, that's illegal."
Because I was trying to get
you not to go through with it.
But you made a decision.
I understand why.
And now that it's done,
I'm not going to let you
beat yourself up about it.
Yeah, well, you may not,
but what do you think Harvey
and Jessica are going to do
when they find out?
Louis, you have been a hero
again and again.
And if the one time
they actually treat you like one
you crossed a little line
to get there,
that doesn't make you horrible.
It makes you Harvey.
You know what?
You're absolutely right.
And as of this second,
I'm going to start acting
like the hero that I am.
Hey, jerk-off.
Who do I have to blow
to get some more nuts?
It turned out he knew
all about the crop reports.
You know what I did?
I nailed him on six counts
of mail fraud.
Did you tell them the one
about how you got your head
stuck up Eric Woodall's ass?
Excuse me for a second.
What the hell
are you doing here?
You think you're the only person
who can have someone followed?
You have no right.
Oh, I have every right.
I just didn't need
to hire someone
'cause it turns out you come to
the same shithole every night,
telling the same stories
to the same people
because you have no place
else to go.
If you're thinking
you can bait me
into taking a swing at you,
you might be right.
Why don't you take a swing
at this?
Oh, you're trying
to bribe me now.
That's a certified letter
outlining everything
that's happened
since you started targeting me,
every bullshit move you've made.
It's not bullshit.
It's an ongoing investigation.
And it's turned up bullshit,
which I've outlined
for Judge Hopkins.
Everything
from targeting my clients
to having me followed.
So now you have ten days
to dispute
my accounting of events,
and when they're done,
I expect to never see you again.
You don't know me that well.
Sean, any time
you want to put the badge down
and fight me man-to-man,
you know where to find me.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ Suits 4x07 ♪ We're Done
Original Air Date on July 30, 2014
♪ the greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man.
How's the job hunting going?
What do you want, Forstman?
Oh, now that you don't
want my money, it's Forstman?
No mister?
What happened to the obsequious
little shit
who approached me in a coffee
shop with his hand out?
He realized that you
don't deserve any respect.
I don't need your respect.
I need an answer
on my job offer.
Thought I was pretty clear.
Your mouth said one thing.
Let's see what your eyes
have to say.
A million dollars.
Is this a joke?
It's your signing bonus.
Are you ready
to come work for me now?
Thought I was
an obsequious little shit.
You are, but so was I
when I was your age,
and look what happened to me.
You could make it ten million,
Charles.
I don't want your money.
I'm not gonna make it
ten million.
The offer is one,
and that's where it's standing.
You have a day.
If you decide
not to take my offer,
I will know
you're not only an asshole.
You're a fool.
Let's go.
Jessica.
To what do I owe the honor?
What can I do for you?
Louis, I am coming to you
because the question
isn't what you can do for me,
but what can I do for you?
Harvey and I were very impressed
by what you did
with Charles Forstman.
I'm impressed
that you understand
how impressive it was.
And since we couldn't figure out
how best to show our gratitude,
I'm here to ask you
what you would like.
I'm sorry.
You want to give me... a reward.
- Anything I want?
- All you have to do is ask...
Pearson, Specter, Litt.
- Excuse me?
- I think I was clear.
I want my name on the door.
It can go third.
Louis, named partner isn't
something I can just hand out.
But you just said
I saved the day.
You just said you saved the day.
I said we wanted
to show our gratitude.
By telling me
I get to choose whatever I want,
except for the one thing
I really want.
Maybe I should have been
more clear.
Maybe you should have.
I mean, you're a goddamn lawyer,
after all.
Louis,
then let me be clear right now.
I am giving you an opportunity
to accept a well-deserved
thank-you with grace.
You can either take it,
or you can turn it
into a personal snub
and ruin all the goodwill
that you've just earned
with me and Harvey.
The choice is yours.
- Can I get back to you on that?
- I'm sorry. What?
Can I get back to you on that?
That's all I can hope for,
Louis.
Hey.
So I just wanted
to run through your schedule
for the rest of the week.
Mm, go ahead.
You've got Ellis at 4:00 today,
McKinney at 10:00 tomorrow,
Chamberlain at 2:00,
and when should I pencil you in
to go see Mike?
- See him for what?
- To be a friend.
Donna, as far as he's concerned,
I sold him out
to win the takeover.
I am the last person
he wants to see right now.
And I would agree with all that,
except for the fact
that Mike got fired.
What?
When? Last night.
And I wasn't gonna tell you
because you should be
hearing it from him,
but men are idiots,
and they would rather be
alone and miserable
than ever run the risk
of being accused
of needing someone.
He has Rachel.
Who is the one person
Mike believes
will stand by him
no matter what,
which makes her the one person
he won't believe
when she says
he didn't completely fail.
How important
is the meeting with Ellis?
He says it's urgent.
Tell him I have to reschedule.
That's weird. I already did.
Rachel or Donna?
Who told you to check up on me?
You don't think
I'd do that on my own?
No, I don't.
Well, I wouldn't have
because I didn't think
you'd need it.
Then I found out you got fired.
So what?
People lose their jobs
every single day.
Yeah, not people like you.
Something's going on.
Why'd you get fired?
You mean other than the fact
that I picked a fight
I couldn't win?
I don't care how it turned out.
You went 15 rounds
on your first shot.
No way Jonathan Sidwell
lets you go after that.
It was Forstman, wasn't it?
I only got his money
if I agreed to cut Sidwell
out of the deal.
And Sidwell found out.
He didn't just find out.
Forstman told him.
That son of a bitch.
Yeah, there's more.
That son of a bitch
has offered me a job.
Mike, you can't do it,
and you know it.
What choice do I have?
I was an investment banker
for ten minutes,
and I blew the only deal
I'm ever gonna get near.
Well, that sounds exactly
like the kind of bullshit.
Forstman tells people
to wrap them around his finger.
- Doesn't mean it's not true.
- Yes, it does.
I could get you
five interviews before tomorrow.
And how are you going
to do that?
By making
five goddamn phone calls.
And what are you gonna say
when they answer?
You gonna tell them
I was a Harvard-educated lawyer
working for you?
Because you do that,
I might as well go back
to being a fraud.
What if I can get Jessica
to take you back?
What if you could bring
my parents back to life?
Because both those things
have about the same chance
of happening.
- Mike, I'm trying to help you.
- And I appreciate that.
But I only have two references,
Harvey,
you, who has to lie for me,
and Jonathan,
who wants to kill me.
- Mike.
- Harvey, it's enough.
As much as you want to help me,
you have no idea what it is
to have been a fraud
and have to start all over.
I don't.
But someone else does.
Well, well.
If it isn't employee
number 7611053.
You still remember that.
I lied on my resume.
I never lied about having a head
for numbers.
I never said how sorry I was
for what happened to you.
You don't need to be sorry,
Mike.
The truth is,
I should be thanking you.
What?
You know what I do now?
Statistical analysis
for fantasy baseball.
That's awesome.
You don't know the half of it.
My old, better job,
I sat in my office,
crunched my numbers,
made a lot more money,
barely knew the name
of one person on my floor.
Now my best friends
are people I work with.
Well, why'd you call me?
The last time I saw you,
you had no idea
what you were gonna do
with the rest of your life.
You had
to completely start over,
and it looks like you did.
I guess I... want to know how.
Start by starting.
What does that mean?
It means, for six months,
I threw myself
a giant pity party,
wondered how the hell
I was gonna get out
of the mess I was in.
And then one day
I said, "enough's enough."
And instead of asking questions,
I started looking for answers.
And you found fantasy baseball.
No, I found out
that how much money you make
is not the most important thing
in the world.
Who you spend it with,
every day, is.
Thanks, Stan. I appreciate it.
Whoa, Mike.
Why exactly is it
you need to start over?
That's a long story.
I have time.
Another day, Stan.
- You wanted to see me?
- Yes.
Clear your schedule tonight.
Done. Why?
Jessica offered me
anything I want
as a reward for my heroism,
and we're gonna figure out
what that is.
What's to figure out?
Named partner.
No, not that. Anything but that.
What do you mean,
"anything but that?"
There isn't anything but that.
Oh, you think
I didn't ask for it?
The words were out of my mouth
faster than Esther
when she was 13.
Louis, I don't care
about your slutty sister.
You deserve named partner.
And I don't care
that you don't care
because it's not gonna happen.
Now, we were given a chance
to take the high road,
and that's exactly
what we're gonna do.
If I were ever going to be
attracted to you,
now would be the time.
Instead I'll prepare a list
of demands befitting a hero.
Good.
And don't ever talk about being
attracted to me again.
It weirds me out.
The answer's no.
You don't even know
what I'm here for.
I know what you're not here for.
To tell me after a long night
of soul-searching,
you've decided to give me
full control
of Gillis Industries.
You're right. I'm not.
But I am here to give you
full control of this.
This isn't public information.
It will be in 24 hours.
So it's legal to give it to you.
And it gives me a 24-hour edge
if I decide to act
on this information.
Which, as you can see
from that filing,
would be
a very profitable thing to do.
And all I have to do in return
is use your law firm?
I don't care
what law firm you use.
I just want you to have
Mike Ross
run point on the deal.
Then we're back
where we started,
and you can get the hell
out of my office.
Jonathan, I know what he did,
but he thought he had no choice.
When a person
thinks he has no choice
is when you see
his true character.
You think you have no choice
other than to be vindictive
right now.
This isn't vindictive.
It's common sense.
And where I come from,
you don't give the fox
another run at the henhouse.
You wouldn't have even had
a shot at the henhouse
if it wasn't
for him getting you out
from under Tony Gianopolous.
And I repaid him for that
by giving him his first shot
at investment banking.
And where I come from,
the way you really repay someone
is by giving them
a second goddamn shot.
Then go the hell back
to where you came from.
And, hey,
if you think he's so great,
take him back there with you.
- Louis, you have a minute?
- Not really.
I'm in the middle of some
very important gift-choosing.
What?
Yeah, wouldn't you like to know?
But you never will
because a person only gets gifts
when they fix the mistakes
that Jeff Malone's made.
Actually, Louis,
that's why I'm here.
I wanted to thank you
for catching that error
on the Wexler stock.
You want to thank me?
Yes, Louis, I do.
Look, I know you don't trust me,
but you got us out of a jam,
and I'm here to thank you,
man-to-man.
Bullshit.
You're here to kiss my ass
because you found out
that I'm now above you
in the pecking order.
Louis, I don't care
about the pecking order,
and all I found out is that
you fixed this thing for Harvey,
and I am here to thank you.
I'm not talking about Harvey,
and you know it.
- No, Louis.
- Don't play dumb with me.
I'm talking
about Jessica Pearson,
the woman whose ass
you've really been kissing,
the very same woman
who came to me
and asked me to check your work.
Yeah, uh-huh.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have some Llipizzaner stallions
to look at.
You had Louis Litt
check my work?
I was wondering
when we might get into this.
Well, the wondering is over
because it's now.
And if you were going to do
something like that,
you should have discussed it
with me first
before going behind my back.
I did discuss it with you,
and you stood right there
and said your work was perfect
and I should trust you.
You see,
that's the problem right there.
You don't trust me.
And now you're just rubbing
my mistake in my face.
If the goal
was to rub it in your face,
I would have done that already,
and we wouldn't be having
this conversation.
In that case, maybe
we should keep our conversations
on a professional level
for a while.
You're the one
who wanted to do both.
And maybe I was wrong.
I never said I didn't trust you.
I said I didn't trust
your work on Wexler.
That's the difference
between us, Jessica.
You see, when I say, "trust me,"
I mean trust the man
who works for you
and the man that's with you.
You wanted to see me?
You don't seem in a good mood.
I'm not.
We can talk about it later.
I walked all the way down here.
We can talk about it now.
I was just gonna ask
how Louis' talk went.
Bullshit.
That is not an "I have to come
talk to you" conversation.
I want to bring Mike back.
That is not a conversation
I ever want to have.
Jessica...
Harvey, I haven't slept better
since his last night,
except for every night since,
and I'm not going back.
In case
you really were wondering,
Louis took his thank-you
like a dick.
And if that's all,
I'm going home.
Hey.
Are you cooking? Mmm.
I make one thing,
and I make it awesome.
Mike, every single guy
thinks that his spaghetti sau...
Oh, my God. That's amazing.
Not every single guy
was raised by his grandmother.
Now you sit down, shut up,
and tell me about your day.
What got you
in such a good mood?
Oh, you know, nothing.
Just spent the afternoon
figuring out what I'm gonna do
with my life.
Well, that sounds
like quite the afternoon.
What did you figure out?
Well, I figured out I don't want
to take the job with Forstman,
and I don't want to be
an investment banker.
So what do you want to be?
I don't know.
But I know
I want to be with you.
- What are you saying?
- I want to start over.
I don't understand.
Rachel, when I met you,
I had nothing in my life
except what came
from being a fraud.
And now I have nothing in it
except being with you,
and I wouldn't go back
even if I could because...
Mike...
I don't care
what I do for a living.
I mean, I'll figure it out,
but as long as I have you,
I have everything.
Rachel?
What...
I didn't mean to make you cry.
I meant to make you feel better.
Hey, hey,
everything's going to be okay.
- No, it's not.
- Rachel, what's wrong?
I'm sorry. I just need a minute.
- Rachel.
- I just need a minute.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
I'm right here. You can tell me.
What's going on? I can't.
Rachel, stop. Yes you can.
Hey, hey. No, you don't-
I don't deserve you.
- What are you talking about?
Rachel, hey...
Logan and I kissed.
What?
We were just talking,
and then he...
He what?
Mike, please.
I am so sorry.
Mike, no, please.
Please, it didn't mean anything.
Wait.
I'm...
This is how you handle losing?
I'm not here
about Gillis Industries.
Ooh, you gonna fight me?
You stay the hell away
from Rachel.
Well, that's up to her.
But if she does come back here,
it won't be to tell me
to stay away.
Ah!
I don't know what she told you.
But she let it go on
a long time.
And she didn't just like it.
She loved it.
You told him.
I don't even know where he is.
He's at Harvey's.
How do you know?
Where did you go?
Forstman?
Logan.
Gillis.
Rachel.
Get the hell in here.
I never should have told him.
Rachel,
there's no use thinking that.
What if he doesn't forgive me?
You don't know that he won't.
You don't know that he will.
And you're the one that said,
"this will bore a hole
in his head."
And you're the one who said
you had to find a way
to trust him with the truth.
He walked out. I can't just...
Stay here tonight?
Of course you can.
I'm not going back there.
I'm not saying you have to.
I'm saying
you need to calm down.
Would you calm down
after someone
stuck it in your face like that?
I would if I knew he was just
trying to get in my head.
How the hell do you know
that's all it is?
Because that piece of shit
did it to you before,
and I let him
because I'm his lawyer,
but I'm not gonna let him
do it to you now.
Yeah, well, he got in my head.
He put the image in there,
and now I can't get it out.
Mike...
Look, I need to know
if it's true.
And what good
is gonna come of that?
I just need to know.
Then there's only one way
to find out.
But you're not gonna find out
tonight.
Here.
Mike.
Oh, my God, I was so worr...
Oh, my God, your face.
What happened?
You know what happened.
You went to see Logan.
I want you to tell me
exactly what happened
between you and him.
Okay, why don't we just
go home right now,
and we can talk
about all of it there?
You're gonna tell me
what happened right here.
Mike, I...
I need to know
that I can trust you,
because you said
that it didn't mean anything,
but he said...
- Mike, please.
- Did it mean something or not?
It meant something
when it happened, but now...
Okay, look. Okay.
I made a huge mistake,
but you just asked
if you could trust me...
Trust you?
You didn't tell me about this
for a week,
and then when you finally did,
you lied.
I didn't lie.
You walked out before I could
tell you the whole story.
The whole story?
There's no way you were going
to tell me that whole story.
- Mike, please.
- He said that you loved it!
And when I said
that it didn't matter
what I'd do next
because I have you?
I was wrong
because we're done.
Ohhhh, it is busy.
Okay, listen, Rachel.
When you are done can you just...
Holy shit, are you?
No, I'm not.
So help me, if Harvey
mistreated you, I will...
It wasn't Harvey, Louis.
It's Mike.
That son of a bitch.
Where is he?
Because I'll...
It wasn't him. It was me.
Rachel.
Look, I know
that he hurt you with Sheila,
but I love him,
and I lost him.
And I don't really know
what to do.
Oh, come on, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
listen to me right now, okay?
Whatever I may think of Mike,
I have no doubt
that he loves you.
And when two people
love each other,
no problem is insurmountable.
That's bullshit.
And you of all people know it.
What?
You and Sheila loved each other,
and you still broke up,
even though neither of you
had done anything wrong.
That's different.
Did you hear me?
I did something wrong.
And now he doesn't trust me,
and I can't make him
trust me or forgive me.
So it doesn't matter
how much I love him, okay?
Becau...
Okay, all right, listen.
Rachel, you have so much
going for you.
It's gonna be okay.
And what good is any of it
if I don't have the one person
I want to share it with?
Logan, what are you doing here?
You told Mike after you
explicitly told me not to.
I don't have
to explain myself to you.
- Really?
- I didn't mean for it...
It doesn't matter what you did
or didn't mean to happen.
It happened,
and I know why it did.
What are you talk...
You told him
because deep down inside,
you want to be with me,
and you knew this
would make it happen.
That is bullshit.
Really?
Because that is exactly
what you said to me
when I told Allison about us.
That has nothing
to do with this.
Rachel.
And since
you obviously came here
to find out where it is
we stand,
let me tell you.
There is no us.
There will never be an us.
And no matter what happens
between me and Mike,
this is the last time
that you and I are ever gonna
have a conversation again.
- You're my lawyer.
- Not anymore, Logan.
So whatever real or fake meeting
you have with Harvey,
you can go to it now,
but I won't be in it
or any other meeting
you have here in the future
because we're done.
Louis, glad you're here.
I just got off the phone
with Charles Forstman.
He wants to cross the "T"s,
dot the "I"s,
and be done with this deal,
and so do I.
Oh, believe me, Jessica.
Nobody wants to be done
with that man more than me.
I'm actually heading over there
in an hour,
but before I do,
I just wanted to tell you
that I finally figured out
what I want as my reward.
And what is that?
I want to amend my contract
to allow for telecommuting
whenever I deem appropriate
and a month's more vacation
every year
to be used at my discretion.
Anything else?
I want it in writing,
and I want my partnership
protected
for as long
as this situation persists.
Okay.
Before I give you
what you're asking...
Jessica, you said I could have
whatever I want.
You're not gonna
talk me out of this.
I'm not trying
to talk you out of anything.
I just want to say that the fact
that named partner
isn't happening now
doesn't mean it never will,
and I'd hate to see you
throw in the towel
because you've lost faith.
Yeah, well, the only thing
I'm throwing
is my hat in the ring
for Sheila's heart.
I don't understand.
I love her.
And I miss her.
And I want to try
to win her back,
and I need these things
to make that happen.
Then you have them.
- Rachel, are you okay?
- I don't know.
- Where are you going?
I just can't be here,
and I can't be at home.
I can't be anywhere.
Go see him.
I don't even know where he is.
Yes, you do.
I did see him.
He came here,
and everything went to shit.
And I tried to explain,
and he wouldn't listen.
And then he said
we're just done.
- Rachel.
- I'm sorry, Donna.
If it's about Mike, I'm busy.
Harvey, I know about
your issues with infidelity,
but...
Donna, stop right there.
No, I'm not gonna stop
because you need to go talk
to Mike about Rachel.
- Need.
- Yes, need.
Listen to me because I'm only
gonna say this once.
What she did
is between the two of them,
and I'm not gonna get
in the middle of it
one way or another,
but if I did,
it sure as shit
wouldn't be to defend her.
Harvey, your lack
of emotional awareness
never ceases to amaze me.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm not asking you
to do this for Rachel.
I'm asking you
to do this for Mike.
Like I said, I'm busy.
May I?
Since when do you
need permission?
To come in, I don't.
No, you don't.
And I'll come back when you're
in a more receptive mood.
What exactly
am I being receptive to?
You are not just any partner
in this firm.
You are the man
I am involved with,
and I need to take that
into consideration from now on.
You sound like you're
saying that as damage control.
I'm saying it because I mean it.
Then why does it still sound
like you're talking
to your employee?
Because it's hard for me
to say
that I don't want to lose you
over some stupid work bullshit.
Now, that's
what I'm talkin' about.
So you just wanted to make it
hard for me.
I just wanted
to hear you say it.
It being hard for you is on you.
So we're good.
Oh, yeah. We're good.
All right.
Jessica, one more thing.
If you don't want to lose me
over some stupid work bullshit,
then please don't do
stupid work bullshit.
You're fired.
"Simple term condition,"
blah-blah, blah-blah.
Yeah, it's all there.
You just need to sign
by the arrows.
Mm-hmm.
Walk me through this one
more time.
It says Sanders international
agrees to pay you
the aforementioned amount.
Through a Swiss account
or the Caymans?
Both, per your instructions.
Now are we done?
You went to a lot of trouble
to shelter some money for me.
Because you forced me to.
Which got me to wondering.
What's to keep you from walking
out of here,
growing a conscience,
and telling someone
about our little arrangement?
Because if I do, I'll be
admitting to my own guilt,
which you damn well know.
Right, but what exactly
are you guilty of?
What is this?
That's your fee
for putting this deal together.
I don't want a fee.
That's exactly
why you're gonna take it.
Son of a bitch.
You didn't bring me here
for you to sign on the arrows.
You brought me here for me
to sign on the arrows.
Yep.
And I don't give a shit
what you do with the money
after it goes into your account,
but it's going in there.
I won't.
It's up to you.
Now you can either close
this deal
or go back
to writing in your diary
about what a loser
Harvey Specter thinks you are.
Sign it, pal.
♪ ♪
Mike, what are you doing here?
What are you doing here?
You know what? Doesn't matter.
I'm here to take a job.
Wait. What?
No, you can't do that.
- What do you care?
- Mike, listen to me.
I know I'm mad at you
about Sheila,
but I don't care
about that right now.
You cannot take a job
with that man.
I don't have
any other options, Louis.
And I'm in this position
because you paid that man
greenmail
to walk away from my deal
in the first place.
Believe me, I wish I hadn't.
What the hell
is that supposed to mean?
- Mike...
- You know what?
Doesn't matter.
None of it matters.
This is about Rachel, isn't it?
She told me she hurt you.
Believe me, I understand,
but you cannot do this
because of that.
This is a job, Louis, all right?
I'm not robbing a bank.
It's not a job!
It's a decision,
and I'm not gonna let you
make it.
Yeah?
What are you gonna do about it?
Anything I have to.
You wanted to see me?
I thought you wanted to see me.
I wanted to see you both.
Louis.
Is this about implementing
your request with Sheila?
It's about retracting
my request with Sheila.
What happened? I thought...
Nothing happened.
I hired Mike Ross
back at the firm.
What?
If Sheila and I are meant to be,
we'll make that work,
but Mike was gonna do something
that I could not let him do.
So I'm using my reward on him.
- Okay, Lewis, I...
- It's a great choice.
I'm proud of you.
Why don't you give me a minute
with Jessica
and see if we can't get him
an office?
Thank you, Harvey.
Thank you both.
Is that it?
I'd still like to be able
to take Rosh Hashanah off
if that's okay.
I think we can work
something out.
- No way.
- Jessica.
Mike Ross is not coming back
to this firm.
You heard Louis.
He already gave him the job.
He can un-give him the job.
It's too late for that,
and you know it.
Well, it damn sure didn't help
when you jumped on in there
and told him
it was a great choice.
It was a great choice,
and if I hadn't jumped in
and let you speak your mind,
you know
what he would have heard?
Something's wrong
with Mike Ross.
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do, and so do you.
This is Louis
we're talking about.
And you rejected
his first request.
Because it was unreasonable.
And the only way
you're gonna convince him
that this is unreasonable
is to tell him why.
Harvey...
Jessica, the only way
to make him take that offer back
is to force him to do it
because he's gonna ask you why
again and again.
And no matter what you say,
he's gonna know
you're full of shit.
And then how long do you think
it's gonna take him
to remember that last year,
he wondered if Mike
even went to Harvard.
You could at least pretend
to hide how happy you are.
I may be happy about it,
but you know I'm right.
And the truth is,
I never should have let him go
in the first place.
You look a lot better
than the last time I saw you.
Well, didn't you hear?
I got a new job.
Oh, I heard.
What're you getting at there,
Harvey?
What am I getting at?
Louis hires you.
You don't run it by me.
You don't even tell me
it's happening.
All I am anymore to you
is a clean set of sheets.
Speaking of which, you might
want to up the thread count.
And run it by you?
You were practically begging me
to come back yesterday.
I didn't beg shit.
I posited a theory.
We both knew
it was never gonna happen.
I was just trying to make you
feel better.
I guess it took Louis
to do what you couldn't do.
Hire an unqualified fraud?
I did that already.
Seriously, Mike,
it's good to have things
back to normal.
Yeah. Normal.
Mike, I'm gonna say
something to you
that I have never told
you before.
I admire what you have
with Rachel.
- Harvey...
- No, let me finish.
It's real.
It's hard to come by,
and all you have to do
to keep it
is forgive her.
So if you want to stay
here tonight, by all means,
but I think you should go home.
Where are you going?
I have to take care of something
I should have days ago.
Harvey. You wanted to see me?
Yes.
I wanted you to take a look
at a draft of the paperwork
to wrap up your deal.
Why would you...
Because I wanted to let you know
how things are gonna be
moving forward.
You're gonna sign these papers
at 8:00 a.m. tomorrow,
and at 8:01,
you're gone.
Harvey.
Look, I don't give a shit
how much business
you give my firm.
I never want to see you again.
You're really gonna drop me?
You're damn right I am.
And if you go to Jessica
to try to overrule me,
the next time, it won't be Mike
you get in a fight with.
It'll be me.
♪ ♪
You're home.
I am.
Why aren't you at work?
Because I spent
the whole day moving
from one place to another,
and I just had to talk to you.
How'd you know I'd be here?
I didn't.
I just went to Harvey's.
Yeah.
Not there anymore.
Are you back here?
No.
No, I'm going to stay
somewhere for a while.
Mike...
Rachel,
whatever you're going to say,
now is not the time to say it.
If you want there to be
a chance for us...
At all,
just go back out a little longer
and let me get my things
together.
One more thing.
I'm coming back to work
tomorrow.
If you can't accept that,
then whatever you were going
to say to me
won't matter.
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man