Mike Ross never went
to law school.
I knew it,
and I hired him anyway.
I still can't stay, Harvey.
I know.
I just want to stop lying
to the people I love.
This makes it look like
Forstman's payment
never went to
any offshore accounts.
That's forgery.
Which is less of a crime
than what you did.
I had no choice.
Bullshit, you had no choice.
You could've said no at
any goddamn point along the way.
One thing is for sure:
When all this is over,
I'm gonna fire the shit
out of you.
I went to Robert Zane,
and I asked him
to give Louis a job.
You want to see if I can break
my partnership agreement.
If you can't do that,
what the hell good are you?
Louis won't be going to Zane,
and neither will you.
I'm here to ask you
to take Louis anyway.
And why would I do that?
If you do, I'll owe you one.
Mike Ross doesn't forget
anything.
See, the reason
he didn't recognize this
is because he didn't go
to Harvard.
You've been lying to me
since the day Mike Ross arrived.
I am your friend, Louis.
No, you're not.
And don't you ever say that
to me again.
You might as well spit it out.
You asked me what I wanted
once before, and I told you,
and then you told me
that I couldn't have it.
Pearson...
Specter...
Litt.
♪
Want to tell me
what was so important
I had to get back here?
He knows.
I know what you're thinking.
Why didn't Donna tell you?
I'll tell you why.
Because as my first official act
as name as name partner,
I told her not to.
What?
You heard me.
You can look at her
as long as you want.
She can't help you.
Because my name's going up there
first thing tomorrow.
No, it isn't.
Yes, it is.
But it won't be tomorrow.
I'm not waiting
just so you can...
Louis, I have to sell this
to the senior partners.
I can't just slap your name
up there one morning.
You did it for him.
I didn't resign the week before.
- I don't care.
- Louis.
That's enough.
This is going to take time,
and while it does, you're going
to keep this to yourself.
Bullshit.
You're just trying to buy time
so you can get out of this.
I'm not trying to buy anything.
We have an agreement,
and this is for your own good.
Well, for your own good,
you better remember what I'll do
if this takes too long.
Please tell me
you had no other choice.
You know damn well I didn't.
No, I don't.
That's because
you didn't see him.
All he's ever thought about
since the day he was born
was getting this.
So if I have to choose
between giving it to him
and going to jail...
He really threatened that?
He didn't just threaten it.
He was going to do it.
And what are we going to do?
We're going to take it.
We give him this,
it is never gonna end.
Harvey, before you say
another word to me,
I want you to think
about the fact
that I just ate
a big bowl of shit
because you brought that kid
into my house.
And I had to take it,
so you're going to take it.
Harvey.
You don't need to say it.
Yeah, I do.
Louis came looking for you,
and I didn't know what to do.
He was gonna call Sheila
and tell her everything.
I'd never seen him
like that before.
Donna, this is not on you.
Yes, it is.
He pressed me, and I broke.
It doesn't matter,
because he already knew.
How can you know that?
Because I know Louis,
and I know you.
And he couldn't have broken you
unless he knew
the truth already.
So this is not your fault,
and I never want to hear you
say that again.
I should've at least warned you
before you got here.
All that would have done
was antagonize him even more
because he would've known
you did it.
You did everything
you could've done.
Okay.
We have to tell Mike.
No, we don't. Not now.
Harvey.
Look, I'll tell him
in the morning.
We just had a huge win,
and I am not in the mood
to ruin his night.
Louis.
What are you doing here?
They didn't tell you.
Tell me what?
Jessica made me name partner.
But, uh...
But? But?
But what?
I resigned in shame?
Well, that's all changed,
and it's all because of you.
Remember this?
No, you don't,
because you can't remember
something you never knew.
Cool to the end.
Well, it doesn't matter,
because Donna told me.
And Harvey.
And Jessica.
When I told them
that I knew you were a fraud,
did they run from you
like you were the plague.
What do you want?
I already got
what I wanted from you.
- Name partner.
- You must want something else.
Otherwise, you wouldn't be here.
See, that's what
I love about you, Mike.
Almost always a step ahead.
What I want from you
is to know that you're dead
at my law firm.
You can't fire me.
Why would I fire you
when I can break you?
You see, I'm going to bury you
under a mountain of shit so big
you're going to be begging me
to take it off.
And all you have to do
is say two simple words...
The same two words
that you let me say
to Harvey and Jessica.
"I resign."
Louis.
- What are you doing here?
- Leaving.
That way I don't have to look at
either one of you two liars.
Oh, my God, he knows.
He doesn't just know.
He's a name partner.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ All right
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ Suits 4x11 ♪ Enough Is Enough
Original Air Date on January 28, 2015
♪ The greenback boogie
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man.
- You know.
- Yeah, I know.
And a little heads up
would've been nice.
I wanted to give you the night.
Well, the night
kind of got blown up
when Louis showed up
at my apartment
and said he was gonna break me.
What do you want from me, Mike?
I want to know how you let him
become name partner.
Would you rather we let him go
to the police?
I don't believe that Louis
would actually go to the police.
He would because Jessica said
he would.
So if you're here to say
that we can figure
some way out of it,
that's not going to happen.
He knows, and it's done.
Did you hear what I said?
Louis came to my apartment
filled with rage,
and he told me he was making it
his personal mission
to break me.
Then you make it your mission
not to let him.
Harvey, he's name partner.
Did I ever tell you
the story about the gym?
I'm not really in the mood
for a story right now.
Then you're going to hear it
anyway.
When I was a kid,
my father put me in boxing camp.
Middle of summer, 90 degrees.
Every day after sparring
in that,
they'd make you do 100 laps
and 50 pull-ups.
They'd push you
until you either threw up
or passed out or both.
Anyone could leave at any point.
All you had to do was quit.
And let me guess,
you didn't quit.
I quit every goddamn day.
I just never said it out loud.
Because no way
was I gonna give them
the satisfaction of breaking me.
So I guess it's time for me
to drop down and give Louis 20.
I think it's gonna be
a little more than 20, buddy.
I see you noticed
I scraped your little
associate title away.
You scraped it away?
Yeah, just like
I'm gonna scrape you away,
starting with these.
Oh, Louis, go ahead.
Give me all of the shittiest
cases that you can find,
but I'm telling you,
it's not gonna break me.
You overestimate yourself.
Did you think when I said
I was going to bury you in shit,
I meant legal work?
No, no, no.
You're not a lawyer,
which means
you must be a paralegal,
and that's exactly the kind
of work you're gonna be doing.
Louis, you can't do this.
Everyone out there
thinks of me as a lawyer.
And two days ago,
they thought of me
as someone who used to
work here.
Look at us now.
Oh, and if you're thinking
of crying to Harvey.
That would be a major mistake,
because this is
between you and me.
What are you doing here?
I'm here because
I know you're angry
and you're feeling betrayed,
but I am not gonna let you
throw our friendship away.
I can't throw away something
that never existed
in the first place.
- Louis...
- Donna, we're not friends.
We were never friends, because
it was all based on a lie.
So you think my giving you this
and every other nice thing
that I ever did for you
was just to keep you from
finding out about Mike?
No, I don't.
But I do think
if you had the chance
to take back
all those nice things you did
in exchange for me never finding
out about your little secret,
you'd do it in a heartbeat.
You want a chance
to tell me the truth?
Go ahead.
Tell me the truth right now.
And that answers my question.
You know what, Louis?
It was a bullshit question
designed to do nothing
but make me feel like shit.
Mission accomplished.
And now I'm gonna tell you
what I told Mike.
- You're dead to me.
- Okay.
You want to hate me? Hate me.
You want to hate Mike?
Hate Mike.
But everybody at this firm
can't be dead to you,
because sooner or later,
you're going to need someone.
Thank you, Donna,
but that someone
isn't going to be you.
Donna said you wanted to see me.
No, I didn't want to see you,
I needed to see you.
I know you're under
a lot of stress,
but that was a one-time thing.
I don't need you to do that
to me.
Louis has already done it.
What are you talking about?
Look at this.
He's buried me
in paralegal work.
Okay, that's bullshit.
He can't treat you like that.
Rachel, I don't care
how he treats me, all right?
I can take it
until he gets over this.
But look at these deadlines.
There's no way I can get
all of this work done
on time without your help.
I will do whatever you need,
but, Mike,
he is not going to get over it
until you make him get over it.
- Rachel, please...
- Mike.
The day after what happened
in here happened,
I shut you out.
But then, a week later,
you came to my door,
and you said you weren't gonna
let me go without a fight.
That is not the same.
I wanted you
to fall in love with me.
I was already in love with you,
and you knew it.
Yeah, well,
Louis is a lot of things,
but he's not in love with me.
He used to be.
You just have to
make him remember that.
Okay, the first thing
we need to do
is finish all of this work.
Okay.
Unless, of course,
that offer still stands.
I don't recall making an offer.
You did say whatever I need.
That's not what I meant.
And then you said never
take no for an answer, so...
Lock the doors.
- Are you serious...
- Take yes for an answer.
I'm locking the door.
Louis, you sounded urgent
on the phone.
What's going on?
I'll tell you what's going on.
I'm back at Pearson Specter.
What?
I don't understand.
Let me explain it to you.
I just became name partner.
Louis, this is amazing.
I'm so happy for you.
Okay, well, you can keep
being happy for me,
but you better start
being happy for you,
because I'm bringing you back.
What? I... oh.
Katrina Amanda Bennett,
will you be my associate?
Louis Marlowe Litt,
I will be your associate.
Again.
You've just made me
the happiest attorney on earth.
When do we consummate our new
preexisting relationship?
As soon as my new position
is official.
- Wait, why isn't it official?
- I can't tell you that.
Louis, I think I've more than
proven you can trust me.
Oh, are you kidding me?
You're the only one I can trust.
It's not that. It's just...
Okay, Louis,
you don't need to tell me.
But if you won't tell me,
and they won't tell the world,
something's wrong.
Katrina, I know what I'm doing.
And Jessica knows
what she's doing,
which is playing you for a fool.
Harvey, I was just gonna
call you.
I'll save you the trouble.
We're bringing Louis Litt
back to the firm.
That doesn't matter.
Because that call was
to tell you
I'm hiring him, and you owe me.
Bullshit.
You calling me a liar?
I'm not calling you anything,
but you are calling
Sylvia out there a liar.
Oh, no, no,
Sylvia wouldn't tell you shit.
Wrong.
One compliment about her hair,
and she told me you gave Louis
the bad news an hour ago.
See you around, Robert.
Harvey, one more thing.
You do still owe me that favor.
What kind of math are you doing?
The kind of math
that says Jessica Pearson
hiring Louis Litt back
adds up to shady.
If that's all you've got,
you can collect your favor
when the clock strikes
kiss my ass,
because partners leave firms
and come back all the time.
Maybe, but they don't come back
with their name on the wall.
Ah, I'm guessing he wasn't
supposed to tell me that.
But he did, and Louis Litt
is not name partner material,
which means he must have
something on you.
So unless you want me
going around town
flapping my big mouth
that something isn't right
in your kitchen, you're gonna
make good on that favor.
Sylvia didn't slip up at all,
did she?
No, she didn't.
You have your girl Friday;
I have mine.
But you can still tell her
how nice her hair looks
on the way out.
I'll be in touch.
Oh, you're tapping out already?
I thought you'd have
a lot more backbone than that.
I'm not tapping out.
I finished all of the work...
Which I expected to be done
an hour ago.
Come on, Louis, you didn't
expect it to be done at all.
Just like
you didn't expect this.
What the hell is that?
It's a gift certificate.
What, are you trying
to bribe me now?
It's not a bribe,
it's a reminder.
Look, the gift certificate is
from Peter's Steak House,
the place that you and I saved
together.
And after we saved it,
you told me that
we had something in common.
Yeah, I don't give a shit.
Yes, you do,
because what we had in common
was a love of the law.
You told me that
when you asked me
to be your associate, Louis,
and I am still the same person.
And if I found out a woman
I had something in common with
was actually a man,
I wouldn't keep seeing her.
Okay, what I did is not at all
the same thing.
No, it's worse.
You say you love the law
so much,
but every single case
you've ever touched is tainted.
So you get exposed,
Peter's gets bulldozed.
It wouldn't even be there
to get bulldozed
if you and I hadn't
worked together.
All right, genius.
You want to work together?
You love the law so much?
You're gonna memorize
every case that I've ever done.
Louis.
No, get to work,
and use that magnificent
memory of yours
for something more than
bullshitting
your way through life.
We have a problem.
Unless it's urgent,
I don't have the time.
Louis is telling people.
What people?
For starters, Robert Zane.
Why the hell is Louis even
talking to Robert Zane?
I asked him to hire Louis
after we took back VersaLife.
And you didn't think to tell me
that after last night?
I was handling it.
From what I can tell,
you handled it like shit.
So this is my fault?
Well, it sure as hell
isn't mine.
You know what, Jessica,
I'm not the one
who wanted to fire Louis,
and I'm not the one who wanted
to deny him clients.
I did that because of
his performance as an attorney.
You antagonized him for years
for your own pleasure.
Tell yourself whatever you want.
You handed out
your share of abuse.
Tell yourself whatever you want.
You're the one who hired a fraud
and gave Louis leverage.
And I told you
Louis would get worse,
and you said I had to take it.
Well, I don't care whose fault
it is,
he is getting worse,
and I'm not gonna take it.
Oh, yes, you are.
You're going to take it,
and you're gonna do it
with a smile on your face
until I say otherwise.
And what the hell
are you gonna do?
I'm going to clean up this mess
once and for all.
What do you mean, you don't have
diamond-encrusted
business cards?
Fine, what about
the embossed ivory?
Okay, great, well, how much
would 10,000 of those run me?
Money's no object.
What, are you crazy?
I'm not paying that much.
Unless it comes
with a reach-around.
Which, by the way,
I'm still not paying that much.
Elite Printing, my ass.
I give you
one simple instruction...
To keep your mouth shut...
And you couldn't even do that.
Um, okay, did you make
an appointment with Norma?
- What?
- To see me.
Did you check
with my secretary, Norma?
Cut the shit, Louis.
I'm not in the mood.
Well, get in the mood,
because I hold all the cards.
And those cards are getting you
your name on the wall,
but you need
to keep this to yourself.
Why?
So you can figure out a way
to screw me?
I gave you my word.
Well, no disrespect, Jessica,
but your word means shit.
So if you want me
to stop telling people,
you better start
telling people yourself.
I told you, in good time.
And I just told you
I don't give a shit.
So I suggest you call a meeting
with the senior partners.
Those meetings are on Thursdays.
Well, consider today Thursday.
I told you, I have yet
to figure out how to sell it.
You want to sell it?
I'll tell you how to sell it.
You and Harvey do it together,
you do it like you mean it.
And you do it now.
Got it? Good.
I'm sure you've all heard rumors
about why we called
this meeting,
but that's because it's hard
to keep good news quiet.
We'll be making this official
later this week
but we're here to announce
our newest name partner,
Louis Litt.
Thank you, Jessica.
Harvey.
Some of you may be wondering
how this happened.
There's a simple explanation,
and all it requires is for me
to admit something.
I made a mistake.
I never should have accepted
Louis's resignation,
because not only is he
a billing machine
and a damn good attorney,
he has personally gotten me
out of more than one jam,
and there's no one
I'd rather have my name next to
than my friend Louis Litt.
Thank you, Harvey.
Even though it's "not official,"
I already feel like
my name's been up there
as long as yours.
And I definitely feel like
it's gonna be up there
for a long, long time.
A lot of good that did.
Leave it to Louis to take
his big moment like a dick.
Harvey, calm down.
Calm down?
I just did exactly
what he wanted,
and he acted like a dick,
and he's not gonna stop.
He's not gonna stop because
you didn't do what he wanted.
Jessica, I just got up there
and kissed his ass
in front of
the entire partnership
and pretended to like it.
Exactly.
Pretended.
Oh, you want me
to actually like it?
I want you to make him
feel accepted.
Jessica.
Harvey, what Louis wants
is to be accepted.
And like it or not, the person
he wants that from
the most is you.
So you're gonna go to him,
you're gonna make nice,
and that's how we're gonna
put all of this to bed.
You want to tell me
what the hell that was?
If you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna let Jessica handle
this conversation.
I have to go kill myself.
Jeff, I can't do this right now.
Should I make an appointment?
Because the partners may have
bought that fairy tale
about Louis's triumphant return,
but they don't know what I know.
What exactly is that?
That Louis committed a crime,
and then he resigned
five seconds
before you were
about to fire him.
And now he's not only back,
he's name partner.
I reconsidered,
which, as managing partner,
I am entitled to do.
And as someone with a brain,
I'm entitled
to come to the conclusion
that Louis has something on you.
Jeff, you said you didn't
want me to lie to you anymore,
and I'm trying like hell not to.
And that's the same thing
as lying to me.
No, it's not.
Oh, you are one hell of
a lawyer.
So are you,
which is why you're here.
So I'll come clean.
I can't tell you the truth
about this,
and that's as honest as
I can be with you right now.
Can you handle that?
I can handle it for now.
But I won't handle it forever.
Louis, what are you doing here?
I noticed you haven't
congratulated me yet,
so I wanted to give you
a chance to make up for it.
Right, congratulations.
We're all so happy for you.
Is that what you wanted?
Seemed a little disingenuous.
Then let me be clear.
I don't mean a word of it.
You really want to talk that way
to a new name partner?
I'm talking to you that way
because you threatened to throw
the man that I love in jail
to become that name partner.
So, you know what, Louis,
I'm sorry
that I didn't bake you a cake.
That's too bad.
You didn't do anything for me,
but I got something for you.
Doc review.
Filings to be done
in triplicate.
Paralegal work,
since you like doing it so much.
You know I don't like doing it
at all.
You helped your boyfriend
with his work.
You didn't think
I'd figure that out?
You know what? I don't care.
You have no authority over me.
I'm Harvey's associate.
Yeah, but I run the associates.
Therefore, I run you.
I know what you're doing.
But do you know
what you're doing?
Not only do you live
with a fraud,
you're just like him...
Pretending to be a lawyer
when you're not.
I'm not pretending
to be anything.
I am in law school.
Are you really gonna make it
through?
You could barely handle
the LSATs.
You couldn't get into Harvard.
As a matter of fact,
your boyfriend may be a fraud,
but he's a better lawyer
than you'll ever be.
You have no idea what kind of
lawyer I'm gonna be.
Don't I?
You learned from
the best liars around, Rachel:
Harvey, Mike,
your father.
Yeah, I know exactly the kind of
lawyer you're gonna be.
But until that day,
this kind of work
is all you're good for.
So you like marinated meat?
Oh, yum.
Okay, wait,
but which one do you make?
Kansas City or Memphis style?
Oh, hell, when it comes to ribs,
I make 'em
every which way I can.
I am now officially starving.
- Harvey.
- Please have a seat.
Don't let my law firm get in
the way of your coffee klatch.
Oh, now, now,
don't blame Donna here.
I told her you and I had
some unfinished business.
Already?
What, did you pick something
out of your generic favor file?
I've never done anything generic
in my life.
This favor is tailor-made
for you.
It's very specific
and very personal.
We're in a little dispute
with another firm.
I need you to get them
to back off of it.
Why can't you do it yourself?
'Cause I don't know the lawyer
on the other side.
You do. Good luck.
What the hell
is he talking about?
- It's Scottie.
- Aw, shit.
I know.
Scottie doesn't do favors
like this,
and I don't have any leverage
on her.
Yeah, you do.
You're just not gonna
like using it.
Hey, there you are.
Look, I just finished memorizing
all of Louis's cases,
and I had an idea
I wanted to run by...
Rachel, what happened?
Nothing happened.
What did Louis do?
It's nothing.
He found out that I helped you,
and now he's giving me
paralegal work,
and I was a little upset,
but now I'm okay.
You weren't just a little upset.
You were crying,
and a little paralegal work
wouldn't do that.
It is not important.
And you know what?
I had it coming.
You had it coming?
What are you...
Rachel, what did he do?
Mike, I was the one that
told you to make up with him.
- Rachel.
- I helped you with the work.
- What did he do?
- And you know what?
I lied to him
as much as you did.
What did he do?
It's not what he did,
it's what he said.
What did he say?
Mike, I'm a big girl,
and I can take care of Louis.
This isn't about you,
this is about me and him,
and I'm gonna make him
remember that.
You piece of shit.
You said this was
between me and you.
It is between me and you.
No, it stopped being
between me and you
the second you went to Rachel.
You put her between us
the second you went to her
to help you.
God, are you insane?
Rachel has never been
anything but kind to you.
I can't even count
the amount of times
that she defended you.
And now, she tries to help me
just a little bit,
and you rip her to pieces.
No, that's not the help
I'm talking about, fraud.
Then what the hell
are you talking about?
You went to her to help you
lie to me about who you are,
and like the good little lackey
that she is,
she came to me
and lied to my face.
She did it to protect me, Louis.
Well, good for you,
but when I found out about it,
I felt like shit
for the 180th time.
So I just went to her
and did the same thing.
You know, Louis,
I've just been memorizing
all of your old arguments.
I was actually gonna try
and come in here
and use one of them
to change your mind about me.
- It won't work.
- Oh, I know.
Because while I am the same
person that I was before,
you're not.
You're right.
I'm not the same person.
I used to be a man of my word,
but you people taught me
that doesn't mean a thing.
So when I told you
it was between me and you,
I lied.
I found your weak spot,
and you know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna keep hammering on her
until you break.
Jessica.
Please, if it can wait,
I've had a long day,
and I need to go home.
Too bad.
You're staying here
and drafting Louis Litt's
new partnership agreement.
So now you're piling on too now?
I'm not piling on.
I am giving you this
because it's non-billable work
and the only reason
it exists is because of you.
This again?
Excuse me?
You heard me.
I've seen this movie before.
And the reason
it keeps rerunning
is because every time
I think I'm done with you,
you and your dirty little secret
rear your ugly heads.
You know what, Jessica?
I have had it up to here
with you saying that this is
my dirty little secret.
You could have fired me when
you found out, and you didn't.
No, you decided to keep me
around
because you were more concerned
with beating Daniel Hardman
and keeping your power.
And then you kept me around
because you didn't want to
lose Harvey.
And then you wanted to use
my secret to beat Harvey,
and then again
and again and again.
So please, Jessica,
why don't you tell me,
when the hell does this become
your dirty little secret?
This seat taken?
Hi.
Hey.
Since your message
was so cryptic,
I'm assuming
this is about business.
I need a favor.
Hey, Scottie.
How are you?
How have you been
since you left?
I heard that
you took some time off.
Where did you land?
I need you to settle your case
against Robert Zane.
And why would I do that?
Because I owe him one.
Harvey, I'm just getting
back on my feet at a new firm.
This case is winnable.
The firm knows that it is
because I told them it is.
I settle, I look like shit.
I know that,
but you came to me once
to take it easy on you
with Folsom Foods...
Because you said if I was ever
in trouble personally...
I am in trouble personally.
What the hell is personal
about Robert Zane?
You don't do this for me,
Zane's going to put it together
about Mike Ross.
Scottie.
You selfish son of a bitch.
You said you told me that
because you didn't want to keep
lying to the people you love.
I didn't want to.
And now you come to me
trading on the fact
that I know to get you
out of a jam
for doing something
stupid and selfish
that drove a wedge between us
before we ever even
had a chance.
I told you the truth.
After it was too late.
Scottie.
I loved you.
I loved you,
and you let some stupid secret
that I would never tell anyone
come between us because
you couldn't trust me with it.
You're right, Scottie.
I don't have a leg to stand on.
But if you don't do this for me,
I am in trouble.
I'm going to recommend
we settle with Robert Zane.
Thank you.
But to be clear,
you get to ask me this once.
And I never want to hear
the name Mike Ross again.
Scottie...
Once.
You wanted it to be official.
There it is, Louis.
It's official.
So that's it?
People are just gonna walk in
here tomorrow morning
like it's any other day
and see it or maybe not see it?
What were you expecting?
A ceremony and a brass band?
We don't do that.
Well, I'm name partner,
and I say we do now.
Excuse me?
You heard me.
I want pomp and circumstance
in the form of an unveiling.
I'm going home, Louis.
I'm not spending
the rest of the night
emailing invitations
to an unveiling.
You're going home?
Well, then I'll send them out
myself.
Because tomorrow...
This is happening.
4:00 p.m. sharp.
I have a meeting at 4:00.
Then reschedule it.
You don't want me to reschedule.
What you want is
to know you've earned that.
I have earned it,
but I want you to know it.
Okay, here it is.
You got your name up there
by finding leverage
and using it to strong-arm me
into doing something
that I never would have done.
See, I knew you...
Let me finish.
It was a stone-cold move,
and it's exactly what Harvey
would have done.
Now, if that doesn't tell you
that you've earned it,
then I don't know what will.
You still want me to reschedule
my meeting?
Yes, I do.
Fine. I'll be there.
You and Harvey.
Of course, Louis.
We're your partners.
Jesus, you look like shit.
What's going on?
Between drafting Louis's
partnership agreement
for Jessica and Louis's
never-ending onslaught,
I didn't get any sleep.
Well, splash some water
on your face,
'cause we have to go to
his debutante ball
and look like we give a shit.
No. I'm not going.
What do you mean
you're not going?
Now is not the time
to poke the bear.
It's too late.
The bear is an asshole,
and he's not just taking it out
on me anymore.
- He's taking it out on Rachel.
- What?
Yeah, he made it clear
that he found the weak spot
that's going to get to me,
and he's gonna keep
pressing it and pressing it
until I can't take it anymore.
Mike, you are not ringing
that bell.
You're damn right
I'm not ringing that bell.
But if I have to go raise
a glass to that son of a bitch,
I'm gonna end up
smashing it over his head.
Come with me.
What are you going to do?
Enough is enough.
Harvey.
You're just in time.
Jessica's on her way down
with the partnership agreement.
You here to be my witness?
He's here to keep me
from ripping your face off.
Oh, I see.
Now that big brother's here...
Okay, that's enough.
Louis, you got everything
you wanted,
and you are done
taking it out on him,
because no matter what you do,
I'm not letting him quit.
- Then I'll just fire him.
- You can't.
I can, and I will,
because Jessica would rather
he be fired
than you all go to jail.
No one's going to jail.
See? She knows what's what.
I sign the agreement, he's done,
and then I bring Katrina back
as my associate.
And that's not going to happen.
What are you talking about?
Louis, I'm afraid you've made
your last dictate to me
as name partner.
I'm not gonna let you
take this away from me.
I'm not taking anything away
from you.
You are still name partner.
Right after you sign this.
I added a little something extra
after you finished drafting it.
This says I'm co-conspirator
to hiring a fraud.
You are.
You became one
the second you used him
to get your name on the door.
I know I'm not a real lawyer,
but that sounds like
he is to me.
I am a real lawyer.
He is.
I'm not signing it.
Louis, here's the thing.
I told you not to tell anybody
about this,
and then you went and
you shouted it to Robert Zane,
and then you made me
tell the partners.
And the capper is,
there are about a hundred people
waiting to greet you
after the unveiling
you arranged,
which won't happen
if you don't sign that.
I could still go to the police.
Yeah, you could, but you won't.
'Cause you used
that little secret
to get where you are right now.
It was the only bullet
in your chamber,
and I am taking your gun away.
You set me up.
You set yourself up,
just like you did
with Charles Forstman.
And what I learned from him was,
once you get something
that you want,
you will do whatever it takes
to keep it.
So why don't you go ahead
and sign
so we can get out
to your goddamn party.
You know, it's funny.
We've never had a ceremony
when we've changed names before,
but Louis Litt had the audacity
to convene us all here today.
And as it turns out,
his first decision
as name partner is brilliant,
because a ceremony like this
gives us a chance
to reevaluate where we've been
and where we're going.
Perhaps you had a disagreement
with a colleague,
or there's some other issue
that's been on your mind.
The point is, with a new name
comes a new beginning.
For me, I'm hoping
we can see this as a chance
to wipe the slate clean.
With that said,
here's to our newest
name partner, Louis Litt.
Nice speech.
Let's hope it takes.
It's got a better chance
of taking
now that you made him sign
the agreement.
That it does.
Speaking of which,
when exactly did you know
you were gonna do that?
Oh, um, about 15 seconds
after Donna told me he knew.
And you didn't feel the need
to bring me in on that plan?
I felt the exact opposite.
What are you talking about?
Harvey, Louis wanted
to see you suffer.
If I had told you,
you would have had to fake it,
and you're a shitty actor.
Excuse me, but I can act.
No, everybody thinks
they can act, Harvey.
The fact of the matter is, well,
you're just a pretty face.
Oh, you think I'm pretty?
Pretty stupid.
I can't believe
it's actually up there.
This firm is changing names
more than Prince.
Who?
You're kidding, right?
Purple Rain.
Raspberry Beret.
I'm kidding.
I almost had to reevaluate
our entire relationship.
Mm-hmm, after you were gonna go
and beat Louis up for me?
I doubt that.
Mike, thank you.
It just seemed right.
After all, you stood up
to Louis for me.
Mm-hmm, and I almost
got pummeled for it.
That took guts.
And that's why I love you.
I love you too.
I wanted to tell you
that you were right.
I started this whole thing
by hiring Mike.
It's my fault.
Thank you.
But I've been on board
long enough,
and it's time
I accepted the fact
that it's my secret too.
So where do we go from here?
We fight like
hell to protect it.
No cake?
What are you doing here,
Jessica?
I know you're tired of waiting
for an explanation,
so I'm here to give you one.
You've given me explanations
before.
I want the truth.
Are you ready for the truth?
Because it's not pretty.
There's only one way
to find out.
It seems like forever ago,
but it wasn't that long ago
at all.
Daniel Hardman embezzled money
from the firm,
and I covered it up.
Now, make no mistake,
I found about it,
I confronted him,
and I eventually made him
pay it all back.
But I did cover it up.
From the partners,
from the police, from everyone.
I even adjusted our books
to hide the crime.
And being a bloodhound
about these things,
Louis found out
and used it
as leverage to come back.
As name partner.
Why couldn't you trust me
with that before?
Because I didn't know
how you'd react,
and I didn't want to risk losing
everything I had.
Jessica,
your secret is safe with me.
You're late.
But I come bearing gifts.
Huh.
That doesn't look like cannoli.
It's better than cannoli, Dad.
It's the résumé
of your new associate.
If this is Harvey's way of
trying to make up
for the fact
that I didn't hire Louis...
This isn't from Harvey.
It's from me.
And you're going to do this
for me,
and I am not going to owe you
a thing.
This is what they're
teaching you at Columbia?
Because that's not how
favors work.
I know how favors work.
You do this, and then you want
something from me someday.
But by then
you're going to understand
that right now
I'm the one doing you a favor,
because Katrina Bennett
is an amazing lawyer.
I was wrong about you.
You're not like your mother.
You're like your father.
Come on.
- Oh, that's good.
- That was a good one.
That was a good one.
Sounds just like me, baby girl.
I had you fooled, huh?
You did.
Now let me show you
how a lawyer cooks.
What do you want?
I just thought you'd want this.
The associates saved it for you.
No, they didn't.
You saved it for me
because you want to pretend
to be my friend again.
Louis, didn't you hear
Jessica's speech?
This is our chance
wipe the slate clean.
I did hear her speech,
and I know that she sent you
here to say that to me.
No one sent me here.
I'm here
because I want to be here.
You see, that's sweet.
But how can I ever believe
a word you say?
I want to know
if you ever thought once
to tell me the truth about Mike.
No, I didn't.
Of course you didn't.
- Because we're not friends.
- You're wrong.
We are friends,
but my professional loyalty
to Harvey comes above that,
which is why
I never told anyone...
Jessica, Rachel, anyone.
So put yourself in my position
and ask yourself,
what you would have done?
I want you to tell me
something else.
Yes. Anything.
You ever sleep with Harvey?
Wait. What?
It's not
a professional question.
It's a personal question.
Can you put our so-called
friendship high enough
to answer that one honestly?
Louis...
Because it's the only thing
I can think of
to know if I can even begin
to trust you again.
Once.
That's my way of wiping
the slate clean.
You can accept it or not.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man