Previously on Suits...
You really know him.
I really do.
- Never.
- No.
Why not?
Because you can never go back.
Forstman's insisting
that I run the money
through Switzerland
and the Caymans
before it comes out
on the other side.
You're obligated to report it.
I didn't, and I'm not going to.
What are you talking about?
Rachel, hey. Logan and I kissed.
Mike, no. Please.
When I said that it
didn't matter what I do next
because I have you,
I was wrong because we're done.
That's your fee
for putting this deal
together. You son of a bitch.
You didn't bring me here
for you to sign on the arrows.
You brought me here for me
to sign on the arrows.
Yep.
You cannot take a job
with that man.
What are you gonna do about it?
I hired Mike Ross
back at the firm.
- What?
- You're really gonna drop me?
You're damn right I am.
I never want to see you again.
- Are you back here?
- No, no.
I'm... stay somewhere for a while.
Mike-
Rachel,
whatever you're gonna say,
now is not the time to say it.
I'm coming back
to work tomorrow.
If you can't accept that,
then whatever you were gonna
say to me won't matter.
Thought you might need this.
Thank you.
So, the way I see it,
you've got three options.
You can wear what you
were wearing last night,
you can go back to your place
and change,
or you can grab anything
you want from my closet.
Nothing? I thought for sure
you would leap at the chance...
Mike's coming back to work
today.
I know.
- What am I gonna do?
- You're gonna do
what you've been doing
since the day Mike left.
You're gonna walk into Harvey's
office with your head held high,
and you're gonna do your job.
- Mike's job.
- Rachel...
I don't know how to be
near him without being near him.
I'll tell you how.
Give him space.
I don't want to give him space.
I want to run to him
and hold him and tell him
that I love him.
I know, but, Rachel,
if you try to pull him
towards you right now,
all you're gonna
do is push him away.
Trust me. Let things be.
They'll turn out the way
they're supposed to.
You don't know that.
I do know that.
Okay.
Rachel, I'm gonna tell you
something I've never told you.
I slept with Harvey.
Oh, my God.
But you told me that...
I know what I told you.
It was once,
and I never would have done it
if we were still
working together.
But then,
he left the D.A.'s office,
and... it happened.
And then, the next time
I saw him,
he wanted me to come with him
to the firm,
and I did, and that was that.
Would you have wanted
a relationship with him?
I would have wanted to try,
but he wasn't ready.
And if I had pushed him
to be ready,
I would be sitting here
talking to somebody else
about somebody I used to work
with a long time ago.
What are you saying?
I'm saying everything turned
out the way it was supposed to.
But you said the reason
that you two never... is
because you can never go back.
I lied.
Oh, I'd let you go,
but I was here first.
Words to live by
by Harvey Specter,
the most selfish man
in the world.
Don't mind if I do.
Wait a second.
What are you
doing here so early?
I always get in this early.
You never get in this early,
and I know that for a fact
because this is the time
I get in every single day.
You should sleep in once
in a while.
It's good for you. Trust me.
I do it every single day.
It just so
happens that this morning,
I have work to do.
What work?
The Schmoolkinsberg brief.
The Schmoolkinsberg brief?
That's what you're going with?
It's not gonna write itself.
I'm taking your name
off the wall.
Seriously, I'm here
for the Tokyo markets.
Name one Tokyo market.
- The Nikkei.
- Name another.
Honda, Toyota, Kia.
Kia's Korean.
Yeah, but they're
in the same time zone.
Where it is currently dinner.
I'm a tired of this inquisition.
This is exactly
why I don't come in this early.
And the reason that you're
here this early this morning
is because it's
Mike Ross' first day back.
Is it?
Louis,
why are you here so early?
I am taking
this Forstman document,
and I am burying it
in the bowels of these files.
And then,
I am putting these files
deep in the bowels
of our storage.
Louis, please stop saying
bowels.
Katrina, I don't have time
to give a shit about bowels,
'cause after this,
we are starting fresh.
And I don't want to hear about
Gillis Industries, Sean Cahill,
Charles Forstman ever again.
Well, look who it is,
Bonnie and Clyde.
Just the people I wanted to see.
What do you want, Sean?
To serve you with this.
What the hell is that?
He wants all files relating to
the Gillis Industries takeover.
Oh, I don't want the files.
I'm taking them. Bullshit.
We have 60 days
to fight that or comply.
You want to tell him
or should I?
It's not a subpoena, Harvey.
It's a search warrant.
So you're gonna give me
all the files,
or you're gonna head downtown
with these two fine gentlemen.
Okay, Sean.
Have it your way.
You're going to take that hall.
You're going to run
into what appears
to be the mummified remains
of a legal secretary.
- Her name is Norma.
- Mm-hmm.
She's gonna limp you
up to the 60th floor
where you will find
30 years worth of files
that haven't been sorted
since the Reagan Administration.
Or is it the 56th floor?
It could be the 35th floor
for all I know.
The point is,
while you're trying
to find the Ark of the Covenant,
we'll be downtown in front of
a judge blocking this bullshit.
You think the threat
of you getting to a judge
before I find what I want
is gonna get me to leave?
Then stay,
but who do you think's gonna
get the job done faster?
You and those two windbreakers
or Bonnie and Clyde.
Welcome home, sailor.
You were out to sea a long time.
I was, but now I'm back.
And this place
hasn't changed a bit.
Maybe it has.
Is this a new Spinner's album?
No, and you know it's not new.
You and Harvey joked about it.
I could have sworn
that was a different one.
Said the man
with the photographic memory.
Okay, that doesn't mean
I've seen every album...
You have no idea
where to go, do you?
- Not a clue.
- Come with me.
Donna, I went to the bullpen.
Some guy with a soul patch
was sitting at my desk.
That's because
it's not your desk anymore,
and you're not cool enough
to pull off a soul patch.
I dispute that.
Are you even capable
of growing a soul patch?
I had a goatee
my sophomore year of never.
Look, it's not your desk anymore
because you're on the other side
of the bullpen now.
Which other side?
The other side. Like,
not the side that you were on.
Towards the door
or away from the door?
Which door are you talking
about?
Which door are you
talking about?
You know what?
Just shut up and keep walking.
You're not here five minutes,
and you're already a pain
in my ass.
This is the other side
of the bullpen.
- Are you serious?
- I know.
I fought it tooth and nail.
I mean, if it were up to me,
you'd be setting up shop
in the file room.
You did this, didn't you?
Well, I didn't not do it.
Thanks, Donna.
It's good to have you back,
Mike.
Well, some of us have work
to do,
and of course, by "some of us,"
I mean you.
As soon as word got out
that you were coming back,
the partners started
taking numbers
to give the boy wonder
their work.
- Thanks, Donna.
- You already thanked me.
Not for that.
For not mentioning Rachel.
- Mike...
- Come on.
You expect me to believe
you don't know what's going on?
I know enough to know
that it's between you and her.
Shit.
Look who's back.
Shit, look who's still here.
Somebody had to pick up
your slack
while you were shiting the bed
on Wall Street.
Which is why it's good to be
back here where there's a shity
lawyer like you
to make me look good.
It's good to see you.
Thanks, Katrina.
Don't thank me. Thank Louis.
Oh, I did when he hired me back.
I'm sure you did, and I'm sure
he would never tell you this,
but I wanted you to know what he
gave up to bring you back here.
- What are you talking about?
- Jessica gave Louis one wish
when he closed Forstman,
and he had a whole plan
to manage his work schedule
so he could try
to reignite things with Sheila.
And he gave all that up
because he cared more about you
than he did about himself.
- I didn't know that.
- Well, like I said,
I thought you should.
Welcome back.
I have court in ten minutes.
Now, what are you three doing
in front of my face?
We're here because he showed
up at our offices this morning
with a search warrant.
A search warrant,
I'm sorry to say,
you have no authority to stop.
Yes, you do
because he deliberately
went outside your authority
to get it.
- What?
- Your Honor,
I went to a different judge
because my office
tried to reach you,
but you were unavailable.
Check with your clerk.
There's a record of the call.
Did you make it
from Judge Franklin's house?
Because he's the one who signed
the warrant at 8:30 last night.
The same judge you play golf
with every Thursday.
And Barack Obama plays
basketball with Eric Holder.
Let's arrest everybody.
I'm not interested in everybody.
I'm interested in
why you went around me.
Because I needed a warrant
last night
to stop them from destroying
evidence this morning.
And the day someone's guilty
until proven innocent
is the day that argument
holds an ounce of water.
Better get your glass, Harvey.
That day's coming
sooner than you think.
Well, it's not today.
I'm revoking your search warrant
until we can have
a full hearing.
- Your Honor...
- Now, that's enough.
If you want to go rummaging
around in a law firm's files,
you better come to me
with more than innuendo.
I better get going.
I have to look up
the word "innuendo,"
if you know what I mean.
Harvey, I'm telling you, that
man is not going to stop coming.
I'm going to suggest
something radical here.
And what is that?
We could just give him
what he wants.
The fact is
we've got nothing to hide.
Harvey, I don't care
that we have nothing to hide.
A police officer
follows a car long enough,
he's gonna find
a busted taillight.
And even if he doesn't,
he's gonna bust it himself.
Well, what are you
suggesting we do?
I don't know,
but this whole witch hunt
is about Cahill thinking
you colluded with Mike Ross.
So now that he's back,
why don't you collude
with that fraud
and get us the hell out of this?
See you got yourself an office.
Yeah, it's not as nice
as the one I had, but...
It's still a step up.
You mean because it's smaller
or because the view is worse?
I mean
because it's my old office.
You're shiting me.
Look in the top left drawer.
- You're serious.
- I am.
Donna said she did this.
She had the idea
to give you an office.
It was my idea
to give you this office.
And it just
happened to be empty.
Something like that.
Right.
It's good to have you back
where you belong.
Okay, enough fun.
Sean Cahill's trying
to go through every file
we have on the takeover. You in?
I sure as hell
don't want to do an amicus brief
for Paul Porter. Good.
Then figure out a way
to keep Cahill
from getting his hands
on our documents,
and do it fast
because we don't have much time.
Harvey, have you considered
the fact that he's been
going after us for collusion,
and we didn't collude?
What are you getting at?
Why don't we just give
him all the files?
We have nothing to hide,
and fighting him makes it
look like we do.
That's what I said to Jessica.
You know what she said to me?
"A cop follows a car
long enough,
"he's gonna find
a busted taillight.
And even if he doesn't,
he's gonna bust it himself."
Speaking of Jessica,
you never told me how she felt
about me coming back.
Find a way to beat Cahill,
and then ask me that again.
You just had to get
to him first, didn't you?
What, did you give him a lock
of your hair?
What are you talking about,
Louis?
You think I didn't notice
you conveniently put Henderson
in my old office so you
can give Mike your old office?
For your information,
Louis, Henderson
begged for your old office
because he thinks
you're the best attorney
that's ever walked the face
of this earth.
Oh, bull... really?
Absolutely.
So you're not just saying
that to butter me up
so I'll let this go?
Hand to God,
or as Henderson would say,
"hand to Louis." Okay, then.
Just as long as you're not
trying to pull one over on me.
That Henderson is going places.
Don't move.
What are you doing?
Taking a mental picture
of this moment.
Louis, that's not a mental...
Mike Ross, the prodigal son,
returns.
- Thanks.
- You're very welcome.
And Louis, I want to thank
you again for bringing me back.
I'm never gonna forget it.
And if there is every anything
that I can do to repay you...
Mike, please.
Don't insult me.
You do not owe me,
and if you really care about me,
you will never mention
repaying me with a favor again.
- Really appreciate it, Louis.
- Good.
Now, I need you to drop
whatever it is you're doing...
Oh, Louis,
I can't drop what I'm doing.
Harvey just asked me to...
What do you mean you
can't drop what you're doing?
I just brought you back here.
You owe me.
You just told me
never to mention that again.
What, do you think I meant that?
I said that because that's
what people say.
Now, what you say is,
"screw what Harvey
asked me to do.
"I don't give a shit about him.
I only give a shit about you,
Louis."
Louis, this isn't
just for Harvey.
It's for the firm, okay?
Sean Cahill... Bullshit.
That's just the kind of thing
that Harvey...
did you just... did you just...
did you just say, "Sean Cahill"?
Yeah. He's trying to get access
to our files
on the Gillis takeover.
Why didn't you
say that in the first place?
We need to fight
this son of a bitch
with the full force
of the law, Mike.
- That's what I was doing.
- Then, do it.
You don't have time
to work on this case.
I need to bring it to Katrina.
- Louis, are you okay?
- No, I am not okay.
Mike, this is an attack
on our firm,
and an attack against one of us
is an attack against all of us.
Get the hell to work.
We're in trouble.
Sean Cahill is trying
to get the Gillis files.
Louis, you buried that document.
You don't understand.
The SEC is gonna have
these files forever,
and eventually,
they're gonna see the money
went in one place
and came out the other,
and I'm the person who did it.
What do you need me to do?
I want you to cover up
my tracks as best you can.
And what are you going to do?
I'm going to try to fix it
so the goddamn thing
never happened
in the first place.
What are you doing here?
I didn't think we had
any further business to discuss.
We don't. We just have a problem
with the business we just did.
Are you here to shake me down
for more money?
I'm here to give it all back.
- Louis, I told you...
- No, just listen to me, okay.
The SEC... they're trying
to get access to our files.
That happens, they see that
your payout was routed offshore
and you didn't pay taxes on it.
They'll see
I haven't paid taxes.
I have until the third quarter
of two years from now
to report that income,
and if I need to, I will.
Are you crazy?
They're not idiots.
Nobody has money wired through
a Swiss bank and the Caymans
if they're planning
on reporting it to the IRS.
That's not proof of anything,
and the only thing
they'll definitely find if they
get a look at those files
is that you embezzled money.
So get out of my office.
Listen to me, goddamn it.
We need to undo this deal.
I tell you what, Louis.
Have a seat.
You want peace of mind?
Draw up the same paperwork
we already signed.
Only this time, have Harvey
sign it instead of you.
What?
You're the one
who said you'd go to the ends
of the earth to stick it to him.
Taking his client is one thing.
Framing him for a felony?
That's another.
It's your call.
Use your name,
replace it with his,
I don't give a shit.
But the deal
is staying in place.
I heard they hired
a new hotshot attorney,
but they never said
how handsome he was.
Look, Rachel,
I'm really swamped right now.
Too swamped to even
stop by and say, "hello"?
Saying hello is just
gonna lead to saying a lot more,
and now is not the time
to have it out.
Well, I'm not here
to have it out with you.
I am here to work with you
on fighting off Sean Cahill.
I don't need any help.
But you just
said you were swamped.
Because I'm trying to avoid
having a conversation with you,
which, obviously, isn't working.
Well, Mike,
I am Harvey's associate now.
So you working a case with him,
you're working it with me.
He didn't say anything
to me about it.
Well, he said it to me.
Why do you think I'm here?
I don't care what he said.
It's not a good idea.
What isn't? For us to even be
in the same room together?
Not right now. No.
You're the one
who chose to come back here.
So?
So you don't get
to act disappointed
that I work here too.
Rachel. Listen to me.
I told you that I needed space.
What do you call
staying in a hotel?
Based on this conversation,
I call it a smart move.
Okay, Mike, I'm sorry.
Where are you going?
Get some air.
Wow.
They hire you back after helping
them break the law,
and this is
what they give you for lunch?
You wouldn't ask that if you'd
ever had one of these bagels.
Maybe not,
but let me ask you this.
You remember that game show
called Let's Make a Deal?
Not interested.
You haven't heard
what's in it for you.
I don't need to hear
what's in it for me because I
know what's in it for you.
You're a smart kid.
I see why they wanted you back.
I'm gonna get back
to my bagel, which is gonna
taste so much better
when I'm not looking at you.
All right, before you gobble
that up, think about this.
Sooner or later,
I'm gonna get those files,
but there's nothing to stop you
from giving them to me
all on your own.
If you do that,
any of those files
that say "Mike Ross,"
I'll replace with "anonymous
former employee."
That would be tempting, Sean,
if I actually had something
to hide.
Oh, I do have
one more question, though.
Is Harvey footing the bill?
What?
For your room at the Soho Grand.
That's where you're staying,
right?
You should try the Cobb salad.
It's out of this world.
Guess who just got propositioned
by a striking blonde?
Please tell me
it was Kate Upton.
Isn't she a little young
for you?
Last night, she told me
I was the perfect age.
To be her father.
When are you gonna understand
they all want a daddy, Mike?
You want to talk about Cahill
or just
keep bragging about things
that never actually happened.
- What did Cahill want?
- It's not what we wanted.
It's what he gave me.
Well, let's have it.
Son of a bitch
knew I was staying at a hotel.
- What are you getting at?
- Didn't you say
he sidestepped Judge Hopkins
to get a search warrant
for our files?
You're thinking
he went around Hopkins
to get authorization
to follow us?
I'm thinking he never
got authorization at all.
Then we need to get a list
of the SEC's requests
for surveillance by tomorrow.
I have a friend at justice.
Since when?
Okay, I don't,
but I thought it sounded cool.
Mike, this is serious.
We need that list,
and we need it by tomorrow.
On it.
Good new, Louis.
I not only misfiled
and misdated that document,
I added in 10,000 others
that look just like it.
That thing is as buried
as it's ever going to be.
What the hell difference
does it make?
It's all for nothing.
- What happened with Forstman?
- What do you think?
He didn't go for it.
No, something else happened
because you wouldn't
be this upset
if he just turned you down.
He wouldn't undo anything,
but he is willing to let me pin
the whole thing on Harvey.
How could you even do that?
Oh, I don't know.
Make up a new document,
forge his signature.
Doesn't matter 'cause
I'm not gonna do it.
- Louis...
- Katrina, enough.
You did good work,
but the truth is, if we
have to turn over those files,
they find that transaction.
I'm gonna end up in prison.
Then you and I better
figure out a way to make sure
Harvey wins that motion.
Okay.
Don't you have a funny way
of giving someone space. What?
Not only did you do exactly
what we talked about not doing
but you lied, and you
used Harvey's name to do it.
- I am sorry.
- No, sorry's not good enough.
This is the second time we've
had this conversation recently,
and I want to know why the hell
we're having it again.
I didn't mean to lie.
I just... I went to Mike to talk...
That's my point.
You couldn't even make it
through one day?
I thought that I could.
And then, I saw
him sitting there, and I just...
Rachel, just because
something's hard to do
doesn't mean
that you can't do it.
Okay. I shouldn't have
brought Harvey into it,
but I am not going to apologize
for talking to Mike
because he and I aren't the same
as you and Harvey.
Excuse me?
- That didn't come out that I...
- I did not tell you
that for you to just
throw it back in my face.
I didn't mean
to throw it in your face.
I respect that you let things
take their natural course,
but I want to make things work
with Mike,
and the only way I know how
to do that is to fight for him.
Fight for him all you want,
but don't lie about Harvey
ever again.
You missing it in here already?
Just passing through.
- I lied to you.
- I know you lied to me...
Not that.
Harvey never assigned me
to your case.
I did it
because you left our home,
and you came here.
And all I can think every time
I look at you is how sorry I am.
And the reason
I want you to leave me alone
is all I can think
when I look at you is him.
Then why did you come back?
I was drowning,
and Louis threw me a lifeline.
I'm your lifeline, too.
A lifeline? You're the one
that threw me overboard.
- Mike...
- And why did it have to be him?
I don't need you to keep
telling me that you're sorry
or to be charming
or anything else.
I just need to get that image
out of my head.
- Did you get it?
- No.
A little heads
up would have been nice.
I don't exactly
have a backup plan.
- Well, good thing I do.
- What are you talking about?
It doesn't matter whether we
have proof of our theory or not.
It just matters whether or not
our theory is true.
You typed up a fake list.
Exactly. Brilliant.
It would have
been a little more brilliant
if you didn't get here
at the last second.
It wouldn't work if it doesn't
look real, and that takes time.
Okay, just give it to me.
I got it.
Oh, well, well.
If it isn't the wonder twins.
Form of "douche bag."
Shape of "got you by the balls."
No, no, no, no.
It's got to be an animal.
I don't care what it has to be.
What that is,
is every surveillance request
from the SEC
in the last three months.
Mike, why don't you tell him
what's on there?
Oh, he knows what's on there
and what's not on there,
which would be me and you.
Wait a second,
doesn't that make any evidence
he's planning on using today
inadmissible?
I believe it would.
Save yourself
the embarrassment, Sean.
Withdraw your request
for a warrant, a subpoena,
or anything.
All right.
Let's get this thing going.
What are you two doing
at his table?
You want to tell him
or should we?
Your Honor, I am formally
withdrawing my request
to go through their files.
Then, why are we all here?
Because I want it to be
on the record
that Logan Sanders requests
the release
of all communications
between these two gentlemen
on his behalf.
- What?
- You heard me.
Your Honor, how do we know
that signature isn't fabricated?
Go ahead.
Give Mr. Sanders a call.
He'll tell you it's true.
Because unlike you,
he was more than happy
to sign the request
in exchange for immunity.
Pending verification
of this signature,
you are to give him everything
he asks for immediately.
Your Honor.
I told you I'd get those files
sooner or later.
Guess it's gonna be sooner.
What's that?
It's 50 different ways we can
stop Sean Cahill in his tracks.
- Why did you...
- I told you.
An attack on one of us
is an attack on all of us.
Harvey is my brother, and if
Cahill's coming after him,
he is coming after me.
Louis, it doesn't matter.
There's nothing
we can do about it.
What do you mean there's
nothing we can do about it?
Logan Sanders cut a deal
with Cahill.
We have to release
all communications
between me and Harvey on Gillis.
Just between you and Harvey?
That's it?
None of the Forstman stuff?
That's it.
Thank God. We're in the clear.
Louis, one second ago, you
said that an attack on Harvey
was an attack on you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And you just said there's
nothing we can do about it.
But that doesn't make
it a good thing.
- Doesn't it?
- What are you...
Mike, did you
collude with Harvey or not?
- Of course I didn't.
- That's exactly my point,
so as far as I'm concerned,
this matter is done.
Guess what this is?
Louis, I was never really
a Star Trek fan.
It's the resting heart rate
of a happy man.
It's over?
We're sending them files,
but we're not sending
them our files.
I don't understand.
Logan Sanders signed a deal,
blah, blah, blah.
They're not getting
the Forstman document.
And that's the end?
- That's the end.
- Congratulations, Louis.
Thank you, Katrina.
You know what,
why don't take the rest
of the day off and check out
that Mummenschanz retrospective
I've been telling you about.
Thank you, Louis,
though I may do something else.
Suit yourself,
but I'm telling you right now.
It's a game changer.
They...
Am I to understand
Logan Sanders waived privilege?
- Yeah, it's his right.
- Goddamn it, Harvey.
You never should have cut
that man loose as a client.
Well, I cut him loose because
I knew he was the kind of person
who would do what he just did.
Bullshit. You cut him loose
because you knew Mike Ross
was coming back here.
Well, you're damn right I did.
I'm not gonna apologize for it.
You should have
discussed it with me first.
Well, it's easier to ask
for forgiveness than permission.
Forgiveness?
You just said you're not
going to apologize for it.
You know what? I'm not because
I don't want to hear a lecture
on the amount of billings
his company brought in.
You mean the $20 million
going back over two decades.
I don't give a shit
if it's $100 million.
You want to have it
out over which clients we keep,
I'm happy to.
But in this case, I made a call,
and you're either gonna back
me or you're not.
We need to stop fighting.
Excuse me?
- We're not fighting.
- Yes, we are.
I'm not talking about you two.
Then what the hell
are you talking about?
Cahill.
You want us to give in?
No. I'm saying
he wants all the files,
let's give him all the files.
Rachel, what are you doing here?
I told you needed some time.
And then you told me that you
needed to get that image
out of your head.
Which is why I need-
No. No, it isn't
because you'll never completely
get it out of your head.
- Tess.
- Yes, Tess.
And my image isn't made up,
and it wasn't of two people
kissing.
But I got over it
without getting rid of it
because forgiveness
doesn't work that way.
You knew how I felt about him.
You knew what it would do to me,
and you did it anyway.
And I told you I made a mistake.
What do you want from me,
Rachel?
I want you to decide
if you love me
more than you hate what I did.
And if you don't,
then I want you to tell me
that it's over.
And if you do,
then I want you to come home.
- Afternoon, Sean.
- Well, you're in a good mood
for a man who keeps getting
his ass kicked.
Well, at a certain point,
you get tired of fighting.
Well, I wouldn't know,
but after this,
we can grab a beer,
and you can tell me
what it's like to be a loser.
Your Honor.
Mr. Specter,
you better be here
to hand over your clients files.
I'm here to do more than that.
We're handing
over all of the files
in the Gillis Industries
takeover,
but I want the court to catalog
every piece of paper
in there so Sean doesn't "find
one" that was never there
in the first place.
Isn't this what you were
arguing against from day one?
We changed our minds
because we have nothing to hide.
No, no. This is a ploy.
He's trying to get me on record
stating that we have everything,
and if I find nothing,
he's gonna file
malicious prosecution charges.
Actually, Sean, I'm filing
those charges right now.
And when you don't find anything
in the contents
of everything you ever asked
for, this bullshit
search becomes Exhibit A.
Your Honor, he has no basis
to file that action.
I can't stop the man
from giving you
exactly what you were in here
asking me for two days ago.
Now, are you gonna proceed under
threat the malicious prosecution
or not?
What's the matter, Sean?
Afraid you won't find anything?
Just give me the files.
You wanted to see me?
I wanted to give credit
where credit is due.
Cahill went for it.
Yes,
and when he finds nothing,
we'll be done with him.
Good job.
Thank you.
And thank you
for taking me back,
especially since I know
you didn't want to.
Would you have wanted
to if you were me?
I did just come up
with that fix.
A fix for Cahill coming after
you for colluding with Harvey?
A problem I never would have had
if I'd never met you.
Why'd you call me down here?
I want to know
why the hell you came back.
You know, it's funny. If you'd
asked me that this morning,
I would have said because I had
no place else to go.
I didn't ask you this morning.
I'm asking you now.
Then it doesn't matter
why I came back.
What matters is that I'm staying
because this is where I belong.
Hey, just the person
I was looking for.
- You heard?
- I heard that I just
booked a plane ticket
to Boston to surprise Sheila,
and I need you to cover
the McBain hearing tomorrow.
Louis, the McBain hearing
is the least of our worries.
What do you mean?
Harvey went to court
this morning and agreed to hand
over every single document
on the Gillis takeover,
including Forstman.
What? Why would...
Because he thinks
we have nothing to hide.
Shit.
Then it's only a matter of time
before I'm marched
out of here in handcuffs.
I'm not gonna
let it come to that.
Oh, how the hell
are you gonna stop it?
By replacing one document
with another.
I am not framing Harvey.
This isn't framing Harvey.
It's freeing you.
What are you talking about?
This makes it look
like Forstman's payment never
went to any offshore accounts
and that you never took a piece
of it.
No, that's forgery.
Which is less of a crime
than what you did.
I didn't ask you to do this.
Then don't use it,
but you're the one who said that
if we give them those files,
it's only a matter of time.
Louis, Cahill's looking for dirt
on Harvey and Mike,
not you and Forstman.
He won't even give this
a second glance.
But if he does,
it puts Harvey in jeopardy,
and I might as well frame him
just like Forstman wanted me to.
Then you have a decision
to make because they're turning
everything over
first thing tomorrow.
Louis, is everything okay?
Yeah, everything's fine, Mike.
Donna?
What can I do for you, Harvey?
Everything taken care of
for the file transfer tomorrow?
It was taken care of 20
minutes before you asked for it.
Great. Here's Howard, Miller,
and Klein.
I'd like to get a jump
on these right now.
Oh, it's late, Harvey.
We've had a long day.
Maybe we can just... come on.
We can order from that shity
Thai place you love.
Knock this out in two hours.
- Is that an order or a request?
- What are you...
I have a date tonight, Harvey,
so unless you think we're gonna
lose Howard, Miller, or Klein,
I'm leaving.
Have a good night.
Thanks, Harvey.
Don't forget to use
protection...
Stop right there.
Oh, so when I go out
with someone,
you can give me all the shit
in the world, but when you do...
Yep. That's exactly
how it works.
Get used to it.
What's wrong with you? You
look like you just saw a ghost.
I feel like I did.
I think we have a problem.
What do you mean?
We just took step number one
to finally putting
this Cahill bullshit behind us.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
I don't think it is behind us.
- What?
- I don't know what Louis did,
but I think
he did something wrong.
What are you talking about?
When he came to me yesterday,
he was chomping at the bit
to help fight Cahill.
That's Louis.
He'd take a bullet for
this firm, you know that.
Then why did he immediately
change his tune after I told him
that Logan was only
releasing our communications?
He seemed relieved?
He seemed ecstatic,
and before that, he was pissed
that I was working on your stuff
until he found out
it was to fight Cahill.
What exactly are you
thinking he might have done?
I don't know exactly,
but I think he cut some sort
of deal with Forstman.
He did cut a deal with Forstman.
I'm talking about
an illegal deal.
Mike, I know Forstman's a snake,
but this is Louis
you're talking about.
I know, but you weren't there
when he made me that offer.
I'd never seen him like that.
He was desperate to keep me
from working for "that man."
- Mike...
- And then on top of that,
I found out what he gave up
to get me back here.
Sheila.
But why would he care about us
handling over everything
if he didn't care about
the communications between us?
Because if he did make
a dirty deal with Forstman,
it wouldn't have been
in those documents.
It would have been
in the other documents.
The documents
we just told the court
we're happy to turn over.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna find out
what the hell Louis did.
Go home, Mike.
There's nothing
you can do tonight.
I made a huge mistake.