Previously on Suits...
I have a list here
of the signing bonuses
of the top three associates
who have come into this firm.
An advance plus my salary
will cover my tuition.
Those numbers don't add up.
Summer associates
work as lawyers,
and I can do the same.
It's an offer letter.
We're investment bankers.
Our job blows yours
out of the water.
Harvey, Stephanie Liston
just called me.
She said they just brought Mike
in for questioning.
You're a dirty lawyer,
and now you're on my radar.
I'm tired of putting the
people I care about in jeopardy.
I called Jonathan Sidwell
this afternoon.
I took the job.
Mike Ross never went
to law school.
I knew it,
and I hired him anyway.
I still can't stay, Harvey.
I'm sorry.
Give me permission to go.
Going to work or school?
Both.
Think you have time
for some of this?
Maybe if you will loan me
your limo.
Hmm.
I'm sure
we can work something out.
Mm-hmm.
Thought you were
getting dressed.
I did get dressed.
Then you got undressed.
I got a little hot.
Yes.
You did.
Come to think of it, it is
getting a little warm in here.
Good. Thank you.
Mr. Gillis.
Mike Ross. Nice to meet you.
You should know
I'm only doing this
as a courtesy
to Jonathan Sidwell.
But I'll tell you right now,
the answer is no.
- Good.
- Why good?
Because a yes
is always so much better
when it starts as a no.
You're a confident young man,
but I know what my
distribution centers are worth.
You know
what they're worth to you.
This is what they're worth
to me.
This is bigger than I expected.
I've heard that before.
Okay, fun time's over.
I'm not interested in selling
to someone
who I don't know
where they're coming from.
Let me tell you
where I'm coming from.
I do my homework.
These centers are a beacon
to every predator out there
that you haven't laid
the groundwork
to get out of the DVD business.
Sounds to me
like where you're coming from
is trying to scare me.
No, no,
I'm not trying to scare you.
I'm trying to help you.
They're circling,
and you know it.
You don't do this,
you might as well send out
an invitation
asking for a hostile takeover.
This number can't be real.
- It is.
- Then what the hell
are you gonna do
with my distribution centers?
I'll be happy to tell you that
five seconds after I buy them.
Walter, I know you want
your people to be okay,
and I give you my word
they will be.
But these centers...
have become a headache.
And you need cash for when
those predators come knocking.
Let them knock.
I'm not answering the door.
No, you're not hearing me.
If you don't raise enough money,
they're coming in
whether you answer that door
or not.
The offer's good
for another hour.
You are not
my hair-gelled partner in crime.
I haven't used hair gel
since ninth grade.
I was trying to avoid
the frizzy look.
Where is he?
Donna said that he had
a morning meeting
outside of the office.
And where is Donna?
Right here.
I prefer to appear
at the exact moment I'm needed.
I wish I could say the same
for Harvey.
- Oh, well, Harvey has a very...
- Save it.
She may have been born
yesterday,
but I know that morning meeting
doesn't mean "morning meeting."
Everyone knows that.
It's just not my place
to say it.
Not mine either.
He did it yesterday too.
When he resurfaces,
tell Specter
Pearson wants to see him.
I used mousse in high school.
It was the '90s. Was it?
I heard that.
Did you bring me lunch?
Chen Dynasty.
How many egg rolls are in here?
- Two.
- You closed Gillis.
No, I killed Gillis.
Well, I hope you told them
no mushrooms in the lo mein.
- You never told me that.
- I didn't think I had to.
Aren't you supposed to be
the one taking care of me?
Ugh, how am I
supposed to do that
when there are mushrooms
in my lo mein?
Why do I keep you around again?
Deal memo
on Friedman Technologies,
engagement letter
signed by Stillman,
and, oh, two front-row tickets
to Daft Punk
for you and Rachel tonight.
But why do I keep you around?
Mike, Sidwell's in there
waiting for you.
Be careful, okay?
He's not in a good mood.
It's okay. You know why?
'Cause I killed it with Gillis.
Hey, Amy. Yeah?
Eat the mushrooms.
They're good for you.
Screw you.
- Morning.
- Where have you been?
Oh, you know,
just getting Walter Gillis
to sell us
all of his distribution centers.
Oh.
- What the hell are you doing?
- What's it look like I'm doing?
I'm sending a message.
We're not a convent.
We're in business to make money.
And this deal does that.
You did this deal
to retain those people's jobs.
- And to make us 30%.
- We're a hedge fund.
If we don't make 50%,
we might as well buy time-shares
and hope for the best.
That's bullshit.
This deal is solid.
No, what's bullshit is you've
been here for three months.
All you've done is hit singles,
and I need a goddamn home run.
- Jonathan, listen.
- I don't want to hear it.
I want you to get
your head out of your ass.
Stop trying
to save people's jobs,
and start making us
some real money.
Or go back to being a lawyer.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Suits 4x01 ♪ One-Two-Three Go...
Original Air Date on June 11, 2014
♪ all right
♪ all that time imagine this ♪
♪ The greenback boogie
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man.
I heard you wanted to see me.
That was three hours ago.
If you knew what I was doing
three hours ago,
I don't think
you would've wanted to see me.
I know what you were doing
three hours ago.
Well, then, you should have
come on over.
Maybe you should try having
some morning meetings yourself.
Don't you worry
about my mornings.
What you need to worry about
is Logan Sanders.
What?
He drive one of his father's
subsidiaries into bankruptcy?
The opposite.
Boy got his shit together.
Max is retiring,
and Logan's taking over.
Let me guess.
He wants a meeting.
He's got one.
With you, tomorrow morning,
10:00 a.m.
Great. Push it a week.
Harvey, this kid considers
himself a young lion.
He's gonna want
to make his mark,
and the easiest way
for him to do that
is to change lawyers.
Maybe, but the last thing
a lion wants
is to have his dinner handed
to him on a silver platter.
You're gonna give him a hunt.
Did you think of that
all on your own?
I'm extra sharp.
I haven't worked
a minute all morning.
See, that's funny, 'cause
I was late from all the sex.
Get the hell out of my office.
♪ Bow chicka bow bow
Look what the cat dragged in.
And you're wearing a vest.
Here it comes.
Here what comes? Mazel tov.
Congratulations
on your special day.
- That's a good one.
- Harvey, leave him alone.
He looks better than you do.
- Thank you, Donna.
- You're welcome.
Oh, and Mr. Peanut called,
and he said he'd be happy
to lend you his top hat.
- Are you two finished?
- I could go all day.
I think the vest has had enough.
Yeah.
So you come all the way
down here just to let me know
that you were right
about Walter Gillis?
I came all the way over here
to tell you
I am done playing
in the kiddie pool.
- I'm listening.
- I'm going after a whale.
I think I'm in love.
Let's go to war.
That's the thing.
We're not going to war.
Mike, the second
whoever it is finds out
that you've got 5%
of their company,
we're going to war
whether you like it or not.
They're not gonna find
that out because I don't own 5%.
Do I need to give you
a tutorial on the procedure?
You start by buying shares.
I know what
the procedure is, Harvey.
Well, how many shares
have you bought?
- None.
- This phrase,
"I know what the procedure is,"
I don't think it means
what you think it means.
Well, as inconceivable
as it might be to you, Harvey,
I'm actually
not going in hostile.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking
about approaching someone
to buy their company
in order to keep it alive,
instead of selling it for parts.
You're offering someone
hugs and rainbows.
I'm offering someone
the chance to survive
and banking
that they'll take that chance
rather than give up.
You don't have the money,
do you?
No, I don't.
But even if I did,
I wouldn't use it.
Well,
welcome to what every person
who doesn't have money
has ever said.
Oh, I get it.
You think this is the meeting
where you make fun of my idea.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
This is the meeting
where you realize
that my idea is happening
whether you like it or not.
Where's the fun in that meeting?
Oh, the fun?
It's all right over here
on this side of the table.
Hey, I'll give you a chance
to get acquainted
with the new reality.
I'll be in my office.
Get back to me
by the end of the day.
Wow.
Looks like our baby boy's
all growns up.
Hey, tell me, sweetheart,
you guys validate parking?
Oh, yeah, sure thing.
I've got it right here.
And how many hours
is that good for?
What's it matter?
We're just gonna charge it
back to you anyway.
You know my secretary is,
like, so much younger
did he say "fitter"?
What did you find out?
- Woodall's resurfacing.
- Me too. When?
- Next week.
- Me too. Where?
- S.E.C.
- Me too. Title?
- Supervisor.
- Director.
Me too. I just threw that in
to make sure
you weren't yes-man-ing me.
Talk to me.
I found out the name of the man.
Woodall's sending after us.
Jeff Malone.
Jeff Malone is a beast.
Well, the only way
to beat a beast
is with a bigger beast.
I need to get in there
before everyone else
and let Harvey and Jessica know
that I had the foresight
to look for it,
the cunning to find it,
and the balls to stop it.
Then you take on Malone.
Next stop: Name partner.
- Pearson Specter Litt.
- Okay, you know what?
Just let's not count
our chickens before they hatch.
But just for shits and giggles,
say it one more time.
Leave out Specter.
Donna, I got Paul Porter's
annual restructuring proposal.
Can you file it
under "I don't give a shit"?
What about Mike?
You want me to have Rachel
prepare a dog and pony show
for him?
- That won't be necessary.
- Why not?
Harvey, I need to talk
to you right now
about something very important.
Harvey, why won't it
be necessary?
'Cause you don't beg
the girl to go out with you.
You wait.
She'll call. That's not even-
Excuse me. Hold on a second.
Um, what if they don't call?
They always call.
Well, what about people
who aren't you?
- You mean you?
- Yeah, of course I do.
If they don't call,
then they don't call.
But once they smell
your desperation,
they won't respect you,
and you'll never get
what you want anyway.
I'm sorry, did you want
to talk to me about something?
It can wait.
Come to think of it,
tell Rachel
when she's back from school
she can have
the rest of the day off.
Harvey.
You do that, you might as well
send Mike a telegram that says,
"I'm not putting any thought
into your idea."
Yeah, might as well.
Okay, are you sure that's how
you want to play this?
Didn't I just answer that?
You did, but this isn't about
whether or not Mike calls back.
This is about you
not letting Mike call the shots.
I let him call the shots,
all he's gonna do
is shoot himself in the foot.
Maybe.
But if this was anybody
other than Mike,
you wouldn't be acting
like this.
Bullshit. I don't let
Tony Gianopolous push me around.
You think I'm gonna let
Mike Ross?
No, of course you don't let
Tony push you around,
but I've never seen you
mock one of his ideas.
Yeah, because his ideas
aren't ridiculous.
This is Mike's first big idea.
And I just told you,
his first big idea sucks.
And if you use Rachel
to deliver that message,
this is gonna end badly.
Okay, thanks, mom, but I think
I'm gonna keep playing ball
in the house.
Okay, act like a child
who doesn't want to be told
what to do, but Mike's a client,
and you need to start
treating him like one.
Donna, the next time
I need help figuring out
how to treat a client,
I'll let you know.
Okay, great.
Harvey, what can I do for you?
There's a Jeff Malone
waiting in the conference room
wanting to see both of us.
Any idea who he is?
I've run into him before.
He's a hotshot at the S.E.C.
- What do you think he wants?
- Let's go find out.
Ms. Pearson.
You must be Harvey Specter.
I'm Jeff Malone.
I know who you are.
My question is,
why are you here?
- You seem hostile.
- You investigate
publicly traded companies.
We're not publicly traded.
No, but your clients are.
Hence his question
and our hostility.
- Our?
- We tend to stick together
when an uninvited guest
interrupts our dinner.
Well, I didn't bring any wine,
but when I go,
I hope you'll be happy
that I dropped by.
Yeah, I doubt that.
So why don't you tell us
which client you're here for
and be on your way?
All of them.
Since when does the S.E.C.
go around intimidating law firms
by going after their clients?
They don't, but they will
when Eric Woodall starts there
next week.
He comes at our clients
after what he did,
this time, he won't get fired,
he'll end up in jail.
Except it won't be Woodall
who's coming.
It'll be him.
Exactly.
Listen, I'm gonna be getting
a vaguely worded assignment
with a not-so-vague agenda
of getting up
your clients' asses
with the full power
of the S.E.C.
And when they ask why...
And they always ask why...
I'm gonna be expected
to tell them
that it's because
they're clients of your firm.
Why are you telling us this?
Because he doesn't want
to work for Woodall.
He wants to work here.
I've always heard
how good you were.
It's nice to see it's true.
Anyway, here's the thing.
I'm really tired
of being a public servant,
and more importantly,
I've always thought
that Eric Woodall was a, um...
Oh, shit,
I'll just go ahead and say it.
He's a dick.
Finally, something
we can agree on.
Seems to me the only thing
left for us to agree on, Harvey,
is my starting salary.
I'm just kidding.
I'm sure
all your new senior partners
get paid the same.
Before you start picking out
floor patterns
for your new office,
I'd like to discuss this
with my partner first.
I'd expect nothing less.
Oh, uh, just one more thing.
I haven't been formally given
this assignment yet,
so I have no conflict.
But in one more week I will,
which means this offer
will be gone.
Is that a threat?
I would never threaten someone
that I want to be
in business with, Jessica.
It's just the truth.
I like him.
How did it go with Harvey?
Didn't.
What do you mean "it didn't"?
You're the only man here
who can take on Jeff Malone.
How could he not see that?
I didn't bring it up.
Louis, winter is coming.
I know,
and I'm the night's watch.
But right now
we need to be patient.
Patience
is not your strong suit.
Well, today it is.
Because if there's one thing
that I've always known,
it's that you do not call
the pretty girl.
You wait for her to call you.
Louis, I'm seeing someone.
I'm happy for you,
though I have no idea why
you're saying that right now.
Katrina, trust me.
They're gonna find out
about Jeff Malone soon enough
'cause he's gonna come calling.
And when he does, they're gonna
come right over to me.
Like him all you want.
I'm not hiring him.
- Why not?
- Why do you think?
Because you don't like
making decisions
staring down the barrel
of a shotgun.
Jessica Pearson.
Nice to meet you.
Jessica, the man walked in here
and offered to fight for us.
If it's not him,
who's it gonna be?
The guy in the office next door.
Louis?
Harvey, Louis knows
everything there is to know
about the S.E.C.
He's damn good, and you know it.
This guy isn't damn good.
He's a killer.
And he's a prosecutor.
We need a defender.
If I'm in a dark alley,
I'd take the killer
over the defender
seven days a week.
And Eric Woodall's gonna put us
in a dark alley.
Louis is a known quantity.
And right now Jeff Malone's
biggest selling point
is telling us
that Woodall is coming.
Louis sure as hell didn't,
which means
he either didn't know
or he wasn't man enough
to come in here
and take the job for himself.
Harvey, do you know why
I don't like being strong-armed
into decisions?
Because I'll never be able
to trust the person who did it.
Then figure out a way
to get someone as good
or hire this guy
and come to terms with it.
Because if it's Louis
against Malone
in a street fight,
I'm picking that dude.
Oh, thank you.
Hey, how'd your meeting go
with the mysterious
Harvey Specter?
Being a dick
doesn't make him mysterious.
Well, then I guess
you're an open book.
You know, I was gonna give you
those Daft Punk tickets,
but now after that,
I think I'll give them to Edna.
Okay, first of all, Edna
was 63 when Daft Punk was born.
Really? With that skin?
You know what, I worked hard
to get you those things.
Why aren't you going?
I dropped the hammer on Harvey,
which means Rachel's
gonna be working all night.
Hey, what are you doing here?
Donna texted me
when I was at Columbia...
Mmhmm.
And told me that Harvey gave me
the rest of the day off
because I'm kicking ass.
He's giving you
the rest of the day off?
Mmhmm, so I figured
we could celebrate over dinner
before the concert.
What, are you jealous 'cause
he never did that for you?
Um, no. That's great.
You pick a place.
I'll meet you there.
I got to set up some meetings
for tomorrow first.
What about the little owl?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Mike, what are you doing here?
You delivered a message,
so now I'm delivering one.
Pearson Specter
is formally in review.
What did you just say to me?
You want my business,
you're gonna have to earn it.
- I have earned it.
- By shit-ing on my plan?
You don't have a plan.
You're running into a wall.
It's not my job
to crash into it with you.
Crash into it?
You didn't even ask me
who I'm going after.
I didn't have to
because it doesn't matter.
But go ahead. Who is it?
Gillis industries.
That's not a whale.
That's a monster.
A man like Walter Gillis isn't
gonna listen to a guy like you
offering to save him
with sunshine and rainbows.
That's exactly
what you said to me
before I got him to sell me
his distribution centers.
Congratulations.
You got to walk his dog.
That doesn't mean he's gonna
let you marry his daughter.
Listen to me.
You want to be my guy?
You stop telling me
why I can't do this,
and you start figuring out
how I can.
I already told you how you can.
You get some money,
start buying some shares,
and you walk in there
with a club
and the balls to use it
if you have to.
Harvey, when I told you
my plan's happening
whether you like it or not,
I meant it.
I'm interviewing law firms
tomorrow.
You show up with a better
attitude and another move,
or you just lost a client.
You want talk about it?
Talk about what?
About whatever's going on
with you and Harvey.
Why does everybody think
that I was born yesterday?
I tell you that he gives me
the rest of the day off work,
you vanish until dinner,
and then you're pissed off
for the rest of the night,
so it doesn't take
a rocket scientist.
Clearly.
I meant "I love you."
Mmhmm, nice recovery.
Doesn't get you
out of answering my question.
You really want to know?
I'll tell you.
Harvey was Michael Jordan.
Now it's Lebron's time,
and he can't take it.
That's a pretty big accusation
to make.
Well, there's more
to the story than you know.
- What?
- Right, so come on.
I said I didn't want to get
between you two.
What?
Let's just say
that you kicking ass for him
isn't the reason
you got the day off.
I thought
you had law school today.
I do right after this.
He told you.
Did you think he wouldn't?
Look, if you want to send
a message to Mike,
go right ahead.
If you want me to send
a message to Mike,
tell me when and where, but...
Please don't ever use me
like that again.
You're right.
I'm what now?
I shouldn't have done that.
I'm sorry.
Is it April fools' day?
No, but don't ever
let it be said
that I can't admit
when I'm wrong.
Then I will stop saying that.
Didn't you say
you have class today?
I'm on my way.
What was that all about?
Just some administrative stuff.
Administrative stuff.
You and Rachel.
I don't want to talk about it.
You mean about how everything
I said would happen happened,
and now you realize I was right
the whole time?
No one likes a gloater, Donna.
Well, then I guess
the Harvey Specter University
of gloating
is gonna have to shut down.
I can still give lectures
on the weekend.
You want to hear it?
You were right.
Call Ray.
I'm gonna go let Mike know
I'm his lawyer.
You're gonna push
a meeting with me?
Harvey, Logan Sanders
is here to see you.
First of all, I don't appreciate
you stomping into my office
with an attitude.
Yeah, well, I don't appreciate
being put off,
especially when I know
that you never pushed a meeting
with my father.
Your father
never went to Jessica
to set a meeting with me.
Then I assume that next time
I call you directly,
you'll pick up the phone.
Logan, let me give you
the ABCs of me.
I don't take meetings.
I set them.
And my respect isn't demanded.
It's earned.
That's only two things.
What's "C"?
"C" is for people who show me
they know "A" and "B."
Well, since we're quoting
Jerry Maguire,
all I want is for you
to show me the money.
You just took step number one
towards earning my respect.
And I dig that about you. Great.
Would it be too much trouble for
me to discuss my business now?
Well, I was gonna move on
to Crimson Tide,
but, yeah, go ahead.
Knock yourself out.
You ever hear of a family
called the Winwards?
No. Should I?
In 1950, they were worth
the equivalent
of a billion dollars.
By 1988, one of them owned
a couple of dry cleaners.
And it didn't happen
because they squandered it.
It happened
because they stayed a dinosaur.
You don't want to become
a dinosaur.
No.
I like to think of myself
as a shark.
Keep moving forward or die.
You're talking hostile takeover.
You think I'd be here
if I wasn't?
You just took step number two
towards earning my respect.
What's the company?
Gillis Industries,
and I already own 4.9%.
Logan, we have to end
this conversation right now.
What are you talking about?
I thought I just earned
your respect.
You did, but we have a conflict.
What do you mean,
you have a conflict?
I mean we have a conflict.
What are you gonna do about it?
I'm gonna go and resolve it.
Well, you better do it fast,
because I am in on this.
And that means you're either
with me or against me.
That includes all $1 billion
of my business.
Hey. Prunie?
- What is that?
- It's a prune smoothie.
I invented it myself.
Rain check.
Louis, guess who
stopped by yesterday
for an impromptu meeting
with Jessica and Harvey.
Please tell me
it was Dick Cheney.
Why would you want it
to be Dick Cheney?
Why wouldn't I want it
to be Iron Dick?
Holy shit, I think I know
who you were talking about.
I think you do too.
Is it a certain S.E.C. beast
whose name happens to rhyme
with schmeff schmalone?
Schmess it is,
and schmess it does.
Well, schmuck me.
Louis, we have a problem.
What's the problem?
As if I didn't know.
I just got out of a meeting
with Logan Sanders.
Logan Sanders?
This isn't about... about what?
Then-never mind.
What's the problem?
He wants to go
after the same company
that Mike pitched me first.
So what's the problem?
Mike brought it to you first.
You're obligated
to stick with him.
The problem is Mike formally
put us in review.
Holy shit.
That's why you're coming to me.
You're gonna lose Mike,
and you want to know
if there's any way around it?
- Is there?
- No, Harvey.
I'm sorry, but you're
gonna have to drop Mike.
- What happened with Harvey?
- Nothing.
He had an emergency with Mike.
Fine, but don't you think now
is the time to act for yourself?
No, we have a good plan,
and we're sticking to it.
They're stewing on Malone,
and the more they stew...
The more leverage we have.
Name partner.
And as I've said,
all we need to do is be patient.
Well, patience may be
one of your virtues,
but it is not one of mine.
I didn't want to jinx it.
You didn't.
Katrina, this is
one of the sweetest things
anyone's ever done for me.
I want to make sure
you don't waste your opportunity
to get this.
I promise I won't.
What are you doing here?
We shouldn't be seen together.
You had no problem walking
into my place of business.
Why should I have a problem
walking into yours?
Because unless you're here
to tell me that I have the job,
then you're putting
my position here in jeopardy.
How do you think I felt
when I found the man
that I'm sleeping with
standing in my conference room?
Jessica, will you please
lower your voice?
Not only that,
but you stood there
with a shit-eating grin
on your face
and tried to strong-arm me
into giving you a job.
Are you as turned on
as I am right now?
You're not funny.
Why didn't you come to me first
with this?
Because if I had come to you
with this first,
you would have thought I was
trading on our relationship.
- Aren't you?
- No.
And if we weren't together,
I would have gone
to both of you, all right?
So I went to both of you.
Now it may not
have been perfect, but...
There was no perfect way
of doing it,
unless I hadn't done it.
Now that sounds
pretty perfect to me.
What are you so afraid of?
Do I have to draw you a picture?
I'm not the one
that made up the saying
"you don't shit where you eat."
Am I the shit or the food in
this little painting of yours?
Because if we're just a fling,
then what difference
does it make
whether I work with you or not?
I didn't say we're just a fling.
Then if there really
is a chance for us,
then why not go for both?
Because I've seen what happens
when things go south
between partners,
and I'm not willing to put
my business in jeopardy.
Your business.
Yes, my business.
The one that I have fought
tooth and nail to keep together,
the same business that
you strolled into with a shotgun
and said, "marry me,
or I'll start shooting."
Jess, if you want me
to apologize
for the way that I asked,
then I will.
But I don't ask for things
that I don't want.
And what I want is to work
at Pearson Specter
and to keep seeing you.
Those two things
are not both gonna happen.
Then I guess you have to decide
what's more important to you...
What we have or what you have.
Hey, Mike.
There's another prospect here
to see you,
but he's late,
and his tie's too fat.
Should I let him in?
You tell her to say
all that garbage?
He didn't need to,
Johnnie fat tie.
Yeah, I guess I have time
for one more meeting.
- Mike, I need to talk to you.
- Although, I'm sorry, sir.
You've missed the pastries.
I can call you some up.
Listen to me.
I came down here
because I wanted to tell you
if you want to run
through this wall,
I'm ready to run through it
with you.
Good.
But I can't.
What?
What I can do is tell you
I'm ready
to run through another one.
What the hell
are you talking about?
- We have a conflict.
- Bullshit.
Who is it? It's not bullshit.
Then who is it?
You know I can't tell you that.
No, what I know
is that it's very convenient
that you suddenly
have a conflict
the day after you tell me
that my idea isn't good enough.
I don't find it convenient
at all,
but you put us in review,
and now I have to go
with the other client.
I put you in review because
you refused to get on board.
And I just told you,
I want to run
through another wall with you,
and we still can
if you drop this.
And why should I be the one
to drop it?
Because they're not going to,
and I have to stick with them.
And I'm telling you,
you're gonna lose.
What, because
you're on the other side?
Because their plan is better.
Says
the professional bullshit-er
who has a brand-new vested
interest in me bowing out.
I'm gonna let that go.
But if you don't let this go,
I can't represent you
on anything until it's over.
Then I guess we're done here.
You cook?
You come home to this
in your kitchen,
and that's what you're going
to ask me?
Well, I was gonna ask you
how the hell you got
into my apartment,
but I knew
you weren't gonna tell me.
Do you remember when you told me
I should think about taking
some morning meetings?
I can't say that
it's never crossed my mind,
but you really think
it's a good idea...
Jeff Malone.
Well, he's not my type.
You gotta be kidding me.
Why didn't you tell me
yesterday?
Because I wasn't gonna
hire him yesterday,
so it was none of your business.
But today I might, so now it is.
And you want to know
how I feel about it.
You're my partner.
Well, I already told you
how I feel about hiring him.
This doesn't change that.
Good to know.
Seems like something else
is on your mind.
He doesn't
just want to work together.
He wants us
to keep seeing each other.
And you don't want to risk
the one to have the other.
No. I don't.
I've been there.
I know.
Then you need to figure out
which is more important.
I guess I do.
So you two have, um...
Yes.
So he's seen you naked?
That's usually
how these things work.
Are you picturing me naked
right now?
Maybe.
Yes.
Go wash your hands.
Don't spend too much time
in that bathroom.
Let me get this straight.
You come to me
with a killer idea,
and all of a sudden
you don't want to do it anymore
'cause you lost your BFF?
I don't want to do it because
it's not a killer idea anymore.
- Why the hell not?
- Because Harvey has a conflict,
which means somebody already
has a dog in the fight.
- Who gives a shit?
- I do.
'Cause whoever it is
is already buying shares.
You didn't come in here
to give up.
You came in here
to get my money.
You're damn right I did.
I give you my money,
now I have downside.
Jonathan, look.
You said you wanted a home run.
You gotta pull out
your checkbook,
'cause I can't compete
without it.
- You could yesterday.
- Now it's today.
And you're still going in there
another banker in a suit,
hoping he'll trust you
based on nothing.
I've got more than nothing.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Trust me.
I did my homework.
Batter up.
What are you doing here?
I said I'd tell you
what we were gonna do
with your centers
five seconds after we closed.
When did we close?
About three seconds ago.
I guess we better hurry.
All right, what's going
to happen to my employees?
We're going to sell
your distribution centers
to a pharmaceutical company
as distribution centers.
They use your workers.
They hit the ground running.
Win-win.
You're a man of your word.
But that's not why you're here.
No, it isn't.
I'm not interested
in selling my business.
I know that, because I know why
you've thrown your whole life
into this company
and why you chose the movie
business in the first place.
What's your point?
Phillip.
Your son.
You loved watching movies
together.
That's why you started
this company
and why you won't let go
of what it's become
for any amount of money.
How do you know that?
I told you.
I do my homework.
You lost him,
and you needed an outlet,
and that's what this company
is to you now...
Your family.
I told you, I'm not selling.
And I told you,
they're coming after you
whether you like it or not.
And the difference
between me and them
is they want to tear
your company apart,
and I want to keep it together.
You don't have the resources
to do that.
Yes.
I do.
As of an hour ago,
I started investing.
So by this time next week,
I will own 4.9%.
I didn't have to tell you that.
And that's supposed
to make me trust you?
I lost both of my parents
when I was 11 years old,
so I know a little something
about needing family.
Walter...
I can't guarantee you we'll win,
but I can guarantee you
that I will never sell you out.
All right, I'm in.
Listen, Zane,
I want that goddamn filing
on my desk nine seconds ago,
or you can forget
you ever worked here.
Now excuse me.
I've got to go be a dick
to someone.
Sit down.
Is this about you and Mike?
Listen to me...
This is gonna be a street fight,
and there's only gonna be
one man standing when it's over.
So I'm only gonna
ask you this once.
You don't need to.
I don't want out. I want in.
And when I said, "you want me
to send a message to Mike?"
I meant it.
I was just gonna ask
if you were comfortable
getting me coffee
in the mornings.
I'm serious.
I didn't back down
from a fight with my dad,
and I'm not going to back down
from one with Mike.
Good.
Now, I actually am
gonna get coffee.
Great.
One sugar, a splash of cream,
and don't skimp on the hazelnut.
Too soon.
Instead of failing
to be charming,
why don't you do
something useful and get moving
on drawing up a tender offer
for Logan Sanders?
Logan? No, you mean Max Sanders.
I keep forgetting that you're
in law school half the time.
Max is retired.
It's Logan's show now.
You wanted to see me?
We need to move up our timeline.
Well, I'm buying shares
as fast as I can.
I'm talking
about a tender offer.
The plan is shock and awe.
If we rush a tender offer,
we won't have enough leverage
to force people to vote with us.
It's fine to have shock and awe
when you're the only one
in the game,
but Walter Gillis
knows we're coming,
and he got himself an ally.
How do you know that?
Because I do.
Your conflict... who is it?
- I can't talk about it.
- Well, when the hell can you?
In another hour.
You have it for me?
Harvey, you know you can still
get out of this if you want to.
Mike's not gonna sign that thing
if you tell him not to.
It's too late for that.
Oh, my God.
Hey, just the woman
I wanted to see.
Donna, would you happen to have
the measurements
to Hardman's old office?
Louis, get out of my way.
Whoa. What's going on, Donna?
What's going on?
That bullshit Harvey told you
about waiting
for the girl to call,
it's bullshit.
He waited,
and now it's too late.
Change of plans.
Cancel anything you have.
We're staying here all night.
What for?
The S.E.C.'s coming,
Jessica's hiring one person
to fight 'em,
and first thing tomorrow,
we need to convince her
that person's me.
Hey.
I see you have the movies.
Mmhmm.
I guess that means
you've decided
which relationship
you want us to have.
I have.
But it's not
what you might think.
If you still want the job,
it starts tomorrow.
I do.
Then tonight is our last night.
We'll see if you still
think that in four hours.
Oh, you want to go three times?
Oh, I was including
one of the movies.
- No.
Finally got yourself an office.
Maybe you forgot,
but I had an office before.
I just gave it back.
I remember,
as a show of loyalty.
Yeah, well, that was then.
This is now.
What you got there, Harvey?
You think you could meet
with Walter Gillis
and I wouldn't find out?
No, I knew you'd find out.
I just didn't care.
Then maybe you won't mind
signing this.
Let me guess.
You want me to waive
the conflict that you still have
after hearing my plan first.
I sure didn't come here
to see your shit-y office.
Aren't you supposed to be nice
to the person
you need something from?
They're still coming
whether you sign it or not.
If I don't sign it,
they won't be coming with you.
True.
Of course, if you don't sign it,
it may cause some people to say
you're afraid of me.
And by "some people," I mean me.
Of course, if I sign it
just because you said that,
then it might cause some people
to say you baited me.
But I knew you were coming
the second I went to see
Walter Gillis,
so...
I went ahead
and signed one for you.
- I guess it's on.
- I guess it is.
You think we need to lay out
some ground rules?
Rules? In a knife fight?
I guess somebody ought to yell,
"one, two, three, go."
One, two, three, go.
You know, usually
when someone gets a new office,
you're supposed to bring them
something, right?
Like an orchid or something?
No?
Nothing?
You signed the waiver,
didn't you?
You know I did.
Not gonna back down from Harvey.
Mm.
And I suppose you got Gillis
on board with your plan?
I wouldn't have needed
to sign the waiver if I didn't.
Hey.
Hey, it's gonna be okay.
This thing
between me and Harvey...
It doesn't have to affect us.
We won't let it.
I didn't know that Logan Sanders
took over his father's company
until today.
What does that have to do
with anything?
- He's Harvey's client.
- Yeah, so?
Do you remember
when I told you that I...
That I once had an affair
with a married man?
It was him.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man