- Jeff.
- Jessica, you were right.
We either need to have both,
or it's not going to work.
Effective immediately,
I'm tendering my resignation.
Forstman
doesn't throw money around
without getting something
in return.
He's gonna get money in return.
Money is third on his list.
The first two are
getting back at people
and getting control of people.
You son of a bitch,
you didn't bring me here
for you to sign on the arrows.
You brought me here
for me to sign on the arrows.
Yep.
After Woodall lost his job,
Forstman got him installed
at the SEC.
Where's the proof?
In Eric Woodall's bank accounts.
This is ridiculous.
I'm your boss.
Gentlemen, give me a minute.
You're forcing me to turn you in
for what you did 12 years ago.
You're not gonna do that.
Because you did it too, pal.
Anyone else
ever loses faith in me,
it doesn't matter.
With you, it's different.
I should go.
Why?
You know I love you, Donna.
♪ ♪
To Harvey.
To Harvey. Cheers.
♪ ♪
Jay, can I get a Macallan 18?
You know, usually when someone
wins their first trial,
they at least pretend
to finish the drink
their fellow ADAs bought them.
I'm sorry, do we...
Know each other? Not yet.
But today's your lucky day.
And why is that?
Because it's the day
you get to meet Donna.
And let me guess. You're Donna.
Oh, you have no idea
how Donna I am.
- Well, Donna, I'm Harvey...
- Harvey Specter.
You really think
I'd be talking to you
if I didn't know who you were?
And how exactly
do you know about me?
I know about everybody.
What I don't know is
why this is the first case
you ever took to trial.
Because it was
a white-collar crime,
not some drug dealer
on a corner,
which makes it
the kind of case...
That puts your name
in the paper.
You're not just a pretty face,
are you?
No, I'm not.
So maybe you should
buy me a drink,
and we can continue
this conversation in the corner.
Jay?
♪ ♪
Sean, what are you doing
in my building
in the middle of the night?
I thought we were done
with you following me.
I'm not following you.
I'm waiting for you.
I need your help.
You need my help,
or the SEC needs my help?
We both do.
But at the moment,
I care more about me
than I do about the SEC.
I can't find the money.
What do you mean
you can't find the money?
What the hell have you been
doing for the last three months?
Looking for the money.
Then look harder,
because Woodall isn't
in the charity business.
Forstman buys people,
and we handed them to you
on a silver platter.
And I stuck my neck out for you,
and I accused my friend
of being on the take.
Now, if I can't follow through
with that, Eric Woodall walks.
Charles Forstman walks.
Well, what makes you think
I can find the money
when you couldn't?
I don't know if you can or not,
but they're gonna shut me down
in five days,
and I need all the help
I can get.
Okay, enough about me.
Let's talk about you.
Ooh, my favorite subject.
- You know what I think?
- Hmm?
I think your favorite subject
didn't come up to me
just to find out
why I went to trial.
You want something.
I sure do.
And I think I might be ready
to give it to you.
It's not sex.
Then never mind.
Wow, you're gonna be
that honest about it.
Saves time.
Well, in that case,
I want to move to your desk.
And why is that?
Because it's no secret
that in a few years,
you're going back to Gordon,
Schmidt, and Van Dyke.
And let me guess, you want to
come with me when I do.
No, I don't.
Then why?
Because I'm gonna be an actress,
and I want somebody
who understands
that there's more to life
than just the DA's office.
And that I can give my all
to them
but still step out
for the occasional audition.
So you're stepping out
on me already?
Yes, but the important thing is,
I'm telling you about it
in advance.
Macallan 36.
I didn't order a Macallan 36.
It's from the gentleman
over there.
Okay, I don't know who that is,
but I'm telling you right now,
he is bad news.
You look different.
I will take that
as a compliment.
I meant I wasn't expecting
to see you like that...
I-I know what you meant.
What you really meant is that
you weren't expecting
to see me at all.
Excuse me?
Oh, come on, Harvey.
Ever since Mike came back
to the firm,
I've basically been
nonexistent to you.
What's going on?
Cahill can't find the money.
What do you mean
he can't find the money?
What's he been doing
this whole time?
- Yeah, that's what I said.
- And what did he say?
He said he's in trouble
and he needs our help.
And I'm gonna tell you
what I couldn't tell him.
He can't find the money
because he's been looking
in the wrong place.
So where's the right place?
I don't know exactly.
But somewhere, there's a person
Eric Woodall cares about,
and that's where the money went.
And why can't we tell
Cahill that?
Because I don't know him to know
how I know it.
- How do you know it?
- Because I know.
You want a chance to exist?
Figure out a way
to get this done.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ Suits 4x16 ♪ Not Just a Pretty Face
Original Air Date on March 4, 2015
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ ♪
Louis, I got your note,
and I know that Norma's
still out,
but I really
don't have time to...
Norma's dead.
What?
She died this morning
taking care of her sister.
Oh, Louis, I'm so sorry.
You don't need to fake it,
Donna.
I'm not faking it.
She was a sweet woman.
She was a frickin' battle-ax
is what she was.
There wasn't a day that went by
that I didn't want to rip out
one of her varicose veins
and strangle her with it.
Okay, I don't think
you're in touch
with how you're really feeling
right now.
How I'm feeling
is that she left me high and dry
just like she always did.
You expect her to keep working?
Look at this.
It's her entire estate
laid out on paper.
She couldn't manage my calendar,
but this crap fest she plans
within an inch of her life.
And you want me to make sure
these things
are bequeathed properly?
You can stuff them in
a giant piñata for all I care.
I have to go find
the perfect urn
to throw her ashes
off the top of the building.
She requested that?
No, she wanted them
to be in here with me,
but like hell I'm gonna do that.
Okay, Louis, I will
take care of this for you,
but you're not throwing
her ashes anywhere without me.
Okay, fine.
Do you want me to smooth things
over with Harvey for you?
No.
Harvey will be just fine
on his own.
I know who you are,
and I'm not interested.
Just 'cause I got
a bad reputation?
Because I'm not accepting
a drink
for putting your rival
behind bars.
You got the wrong idea, pal.
I didn't buy you that
for putting my enemy away.
I bought you that
for how you put my enemy away.
Okay, you got me.
What are you talking about?
You.
You've got something special.
And I want people
with something special
working for me.
Why exactly would I want
to work for you?
I can think of
a million reasons,
'cause that's the signing bonus
I'm gonna give you,
and that's a hell of
a lot more money
than you're ever gonna make
as a lawyer.
And what if I told you
I don't practice law
to make money?
Then I'd ask you,
what do you practice it for?
To bend people to my will.
Then bend people to your will
for me
and make a lot of money
on top of it.
Well, here's the thing,
Mr. Forstman.
Not that
it's any of your business,
but I'll be making 1/2 million
a year in no time.
1/2 million a year is dick.
My gardener makes that.
Then go offer your gardener
a job,
because I'm not interested.
Just so you know, if you change
your mind and come back to me,
it's not gonna be
the same conversation.
Thanks for the drink.
Good luck, Mr. Forstman.
Okay.
What are you doing?
What do you think I'm doing?
If Forstman gave the money
to someone Woodall's close to,
we need to start
by compiling a family tree.
I meant why aren't you
at school today?
Because I'm gonna prove
to Harvey that I exist.
Okay.
Now that you mention it,
what was that last night?
Ever since you came back,
it's like you and Harvey
speak this secret language,
and I'm not a part of it.
Rachel, come on.
We have history.
I'm not talking about history.
I'm talking about respect.
Okay, you don't know
what you're talking about
if you think
Harvey doesn't respect you.
Are you gonna tell me
that last night
he didn't give you a look
that said,
"You don't need to tell her
the full story
because she doesn't need
to know"?
Rachel, he didn't give me
that look
because he doesn't respect you.
He gave me that look
because he's ashamed.
What are you talking about?
Let's just say that
I'm not the only one
that Charles Forstman duped.
- Harvey got taken by Forstman?
- Yes.
And he only told me
because he had to
when we were in the middle
of that takeover battle.
That's why Harvey's so slow
to care about anybody.
Forstman used somebody
he cared about.
Holy shit.
I never even thought about that.
Who do you think it was?
I don't know,
but I have a pretty good guess.
Well, what do you think?
I think this place is a dump,
and I'm busy,
so why don't you tell me
why we're here?
I want to open
a restaurant here.
Marcus, there's already
And it isn't working.
Which is why they're gonna
lose their lease.
Take a look.
I've got a chef.
I've got a liquor license.
I've got renovation plans.
I have everything I need.
Except the money.
I need $150,000.
- Are you crazy?
- Come on, Harvey.
This is my dream.
I know I can make this work.
And I'm not saying you can't,
but I don't have
that kind of money.
What are you talking about?
You're the big-time lawyer who
just got his name in the paper.
My name in the paper
doesn't pay me extra money.
I make $50,000 a year.
And you said you were gonna be
a corporate lawyer.
Yeah, and when I am,
I can help you, but right now...
I don't give a shit
about right now.
I give a shit about when
you were supposed to be
my big brother, but instead,
what did you do?
I know what I did.
Then you know
I can never get a loan
for as long as I live.
Marcus, when are you gonna
take responsibility
for your own shit?
What the hell does it look like
I'm trying to do?
I came to you first because
I know you'd want me to,
but if you don't come through,
I'm gonna go to Mom.
You don't mean Mom.
You mean him.
And you're not taking
a nickel from that man.
Taking his money
isn't gonna make
what he did to Dad any worse.
That's bullshit,
and you know it,
and I'm not gonna let you do it.
Hey, Harvey.
How the hell
are you gonna stop me?
Am I crazy,
or is that the same dress
you were wearing
the last time I saw you?
You must be crazy,
because I don't wear
the same dress ever.
Then you must spend a fortune
on wardrobe.
But I have to say,
it's worth it.
I suddenly get the feeling
this isn't just a drop-by.
I want to move up our timeline.
Harvey, we have a deal.
I put myself on the line
for you,
and our deal
is not going to change.
I could just pay you
the money back and move on.
And if you could do that,
you wouldn't be here
asking to come back.
How much money
did Marcus lose this time?
He didn't lose anything.
He wants to start a restaurant.
He doesn't want to start shit.
He owes somebody something.
You don't know that.
He's turned his life around.
What I know is,
he has a problem,
and he's looking
to get money from you.
And you're not gonna get it
from me.
Then I'll get it somewhere else.
And what's that
supposed to mean?
I got a job offer
from Charles Forstman.
Look at me.
I don't care
what he's offering you.
Don't take it.
Because he's got
a bad reputation?
You think I don't know that?
I think there are
a lot of things
you think you know
that you don't.
What I know is,
you're either gonna help me
or Charles Forstman is.
It's up to you.
Harvey, I can't make you
listen to me,
but what I'm not going to do
is let you come here
and leverage me
with some bullshit offer
from a shady banker,
so do what you're gonna do.
But don't say I didn't warn you.
You can buy all the Wonder Bread
you want, Eric,
but you can't take it with you
to prison.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to remind you
that once they find the money,
it's all gonna come
tumbling down.
Well, they're not gonna
find the money,
'cause there is no money.
Not in your accounts,
but I know what Cahill doesn't.
Forstman gave it to somebody
you care about,
and if I tell him that,
it'll be too late.
I know what you're trying to do.
You're trying to bait me
into moving the body.
We both know you're not
dumb enough to do that.
I'm here to get you
to cut a deal
and turn Forstman in.
You don't have the authority
to cut a deal.
No, but I can get Cahill to
after you hire me
to represent you.
You mean hire the fox
to watch the henhouse?
Not a chance.
Eric, they're closing in,
and when they do,
you're gonna want to call me.
So why don't you take my card?
This is ridiculous.
Woodall's got 30 people
it could be,
or it could be none of them.
I know that,
but this is our job.
No, our job is to help Harvey
get Forstman.
If you're thinking
what I think you're thinking...
I am, and you are too.
Rachel, we are never
gonna get Harvey
to go after Forstman
for what they did 12 years ago.
Why, because of his brother?
Yes, because of his brother,
or because he's ashamed.
Either way, he knows
it's a possibility.
He doesn't need me
to tell him about it.
No, he just doesn't need me
- Rachel...
- This is not about that.
Look, I can't tell him
because I'm not supposed
to know, but you can.
And I just told you,
he doesn't want to hear it.
And when has that ever
stopped you before?
- This is different.
- Why?
Because he's ashamed.
Then he's not thinking right,
and he needs your help
more than ever.
Then we're both telling him.
Mike, I don't need the credit.
No, this isn't about credit.
This is about us.
He can't tell me something
and expect me not to tell you.
You wanted to see me?
Yes.
Where have you been all day?
Why? Is there something
you want to talk about?
Yeah, where you've been.
Sean Cahill was at my door
last night...
Harvey, Norma passed away.
I've been helping Louis.
Norma died?
That's terrible.
I thought
you couldn't stand her.
I couldn't, but I assume
Louis loved her, so...
- Do what you need to do.
- Oh.
Because she was his secretary,
he must have loved her.
- That's not what I meant.
- But it is what you said.
Okay, Donna. What's wrong?
How about we start with the fact
that I have been wondering
for the last ten hours
if you're going to acknowledge
what happened last night.
But you're you,
so of course you're not.
I'm not gonna acknowledge it
because nothing happened
last night.
Why?
And don't tell me I know why.
Because it would have been
a mistake, and you know it.
What I know is
something happened,
and you ran away, but not before
you told me you loved me.
I did that because I wanted
to make you feel better.
What did you just say to me?
That's not what I meant.
I didn't say that...
Because you pity me?
Yeah, you did.
No, I said it
because I love you,
and I wanted you to know it.
Love me how?
- Why does that have to...
- Love me how?
That's what I thought.
You either can't answer
or you won't,
which is bullshit,
because obviously,
you don't just look at me
this way.
You're capable of looking at me
that way,
but you don't want to let
those worlds collide
because you're afraid
to risk anything.
Because we have everything.
No, Harvey. You have everything.
So you're saying
you want everything?
I don't know, Harvey,
but what I do know is
I don't want your pity.
♪ ♪
What are you doing here?
Nobody finds out where I live.
I do.
Hold on a second.
Let me turn this off.
You got to be kidding me.
You're watching Wall Street?
A monthly ritual
to remind myself.
Of what?
Of what a pussy Gordon Gekko is.
Now, you want to tell me
what changed your mind?
I decided I wanted the money.
And you turned me down,
so now you're gonna tell me
why you want the money.
My brother needs $150,000
for a restaurant.
Hmm.
Now we're getting somewhere.
Let's have it.
Okay, you want it?
Here it is.
It's not just a restaurant.
It's a second chance.
Marcus has a gambling problem,
and I gave it to him.
Mm-hmm.
And you think
this is his way out?
I know it is.
Hmm.
We're not a good fit,
'cause restaurants fail,
and when this one does,
you'll leave.
So you might as well leave
right now.
Then how about we bet on it?
You're gonna gamble on something
to get your brother
out of a gambling problem?
- I didn't say I had a problem.
- I think maybe you do.
When you always win,
it's not a problem.
I think I might like you, pal.
Louis.
I got your message.
What's going on?
What's going on is,
they're trying to screw me,
and I need you to be bad cop.
What?
Have you made a decision, sir?
No, I haven't made a decision,
you shyster dealer of death.
Okay, I think maybe
we're gonna need another minute.
No, we don't.
I don't need another minute
to see
that this looks like a pot
from Home Depot,
this looks like a lamp
from Motel 6,
and this looks like
a goddamn howitzer shell.
You are lucky that I don't take
this mockery
of a final resting place
and shove it up your ass.
- Louis, that's enough.
- No, it's not enough.
I've been handling this bullshit
for two days
for a woman who's supposed to be
handling things for me.
Louis, this isn't about the urn.
Oh, please don't give me
that touchy-feely shit.
And why the hell
are you not being bad cop?
Because that's not
what's needed.
Oh, bullshit
it's not what's needed.
- Louis.
- You don't care about me.
You never cared about me.
All you care about
is yourself...
and your stupid sister
and your Hummel figurines
and your Murder, She Wrote
reruns.
Louis, I'm not Norma.
She's gone...
and it's gonna be okay.
She was a battle-ax!
But she was my battle-ax.
I know. I know.
Oh, she didn't just leave me
high and dry.
She left me for good.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
Both of you?
We both work for you.
Which is why we're both here
to say
maybe it's time
we explore other options.
You got to be kidding me.
You spent two days on this,
and you're ready
to throw in the towel?
We've spent two
of our five days on it,
and we still don't have a name,
so we think
it's time to consider...
What?
Going after Forstman
for whatever he did to you
12 years ago.
- You told her?
- Yes, I did.
Because like I said,
we both work for you.
Which means
we both want to help.
You think I haven't wondered
how to go after Forstman
100 times
in the last dozen years?
Then why don't you?
Because I'm not the only one
at risk.
You mean your brother.
Yes, I do.
And I'm not gonna bring him
into this,
because he didn't do
anything wrong.
Harvey, I'm not saying...
Did you hear me?
He doesn't just have a gun
to my head, okay?
He's got one to my brother's.
And how many times
have you told me
that when someone has
a gun to your head,
you figure a different way out?
This is Charles Forstman.
- There is no other way out.
- Harvey, there's...
I gave you a job to do.
Now do your goddamn job.
Well, that was a bust.
- We had to try.
- Did we?
I told you he'd be pissed off,
and he was.
Yeah, and you also told me
he needed to hear things
that he didn't want to hear.
Okay, well, now all he heard is,
not only can't he trust me,
he can't trust you either.
That's not what he heard,
and you know it.
What he heard was that
you're the closest person
in the world to me,
I am never gonna
keep things from you,
and I'm not the only one
in his corner.
I'm the closest person
in the world to you.
Of course you are.
How can you even...
I'm not questioning it.
I'm the closest person
in the world to you,
and I wouldn't be
on your family tree.
You're talking about Woodall.
Yes, I'm talking about Woodall.
Woodall's married.
We checked his wife. Nothing.
That's the thing.
We're not married.
Okay, I really don't think this
is the time to bring that up.
I'm being serious.
We've exhausted every person
that's related to him.
Maybe it's time
we found someone who isn't.
- That's genius.
- Thank you.
Now I really don't understand
why Harvey doesn't respect you.
It's too soon.
It's too soon for that joke.
Too soon.
I can have any one?
Take your pick.
It doesn't matter,
'cause you're gonna lose.
That's funny.
I look at it like
I'm gonna win twice.
I get to drive a badass car,
and I get to kick your ass.
Cocky. I like that.
A guy like you,
I'm surprised you could stand
working for Cameron Dennis
in the first place.
- What do you mean?
- He doesn't like cocky.
Take, for instance,
what's-his-name... DuPont?
What's he up for? Tax evasion?
- Insider trading.
- Yeah, whatever.
The point is, after
what you did the other day,
why aren't you leading that?
Because this is Cameron's case.
If I were him, it'd be yours.
Harvey, you are his star player,
and he's not even putting you
in the game.
And on top of that,
he didn't have the balls
to announce whether
he's going after DuPont or not.
Don't you worry
about Cameron Dennis.
DuPont's gonna get
what's coming to him.
That's exactly what
I wanted to hear.
What are you talking about?
Well, you're loyal to the guy
you work for.
I like that.
So you were just
talking shit about him
to see if I'd jump on board?
And you didn't...
which is why
we don't have to race anymore.
You're saying I got the job?
I'm saying welcome to the team.
Well, that's all
well and good, Charles,
but we're still racing.
We sure as hell are.
We just have to find
something else to bet on.
Hey, Sean. Good to see you.
Don't give me that shit.
Did you confront Eric Woodall
yesterday morning
at his supermarket?
I ran into him by accident.
I like the produce there.
I'm not in the mood, Harvey.
Did you approach the subject
of an SEC investigation
with the express purpose
of intimidating him?
I approached him
with the express purpose
of hiring me as his lawyer.
Why the hell would you do that?
You're supposed to be
helping me.
And if he's willing to
admit what he did,
that is helping you.
And instead, he's claiming that
I sent you there
to intimidate him.
Then I guess
that's the way it's breaking.
What the hell
are you talking about?
He's either gonna buy
what I'm selling
or cover his tracks.
And if he covers his tracks,
you need to be there.
Are you asking me to follow him?
No, I'm telling you
to follow him.
I can't do that.
I don't have authorization.
Didn't stop you following me.
Enough.
He's filing charges
of harassment against me.
We do this, nothing sticks.
Then we might not get him,
because I have nothing.
Well, let me give you
a little extra motivation.
Remember,
Woodall knows all about
Louis Litt's
little Forstman transgression.
So if he gets exonerated,
who do you think's gonna be
the first person he goes after?
So, instead of going to Jersey
for your produce,
go get me something I can use.
You're having a drink
by yourself?
What's going on?
What's going on is,
I just finished having them
scrape Jeff's name off his door.
So why don't you tell me
why you're here, Harvey?
Cahill's having trouble
getting evidence
against Forstman and Woodall.
I'm aware of that.
Then you should also be aware
that if Woodall keeps his job,
he's likely to go after Louis.
I could've done that math,
and so could you, so...
I might be able to
help them get Forstman...
on something else.
Does this have something to do
with when he offered you
that job 12 years ago?
Yes.
I told you that man was trouble.
And I told you
I wouldn't abandon Marcus
and you were wrong about him.
So this has something to do
with Marcus.
Yes, it does.
Well, if you are asking me
to choose
between your brother and Louis,
you know who I'm choosing.
I'm not asking you to do that.
Then what are you asking?
I want your help
to get my mind right.
Here's the thing, Harvey.
Jeff's gone,
and he's gone
because of the choices I made.
So I'm not sure if I can
help you get your mind right,
'cause right now...
mine's not right.
Hang on a sec.
Hey.
You didn't come down here
just to give me my start date.
I came down here to tell you
I think
you have something special,
and I'd love nothing more
than to have you on my desk,
but I'm leaving the DA's office.
Does this have something to do
with that Forstman guy
buying you a drink
the other night?
I thought you didn't know
who he was.
Well, I looked him up
because I thought
I was gonna be working for you.
And I'm telling you, he's shady.
Because he's got
a bad reputation?
I don't care
what his reputation is.
You don't know this about me
yet, but I know people...
usually better
than they know themselves.
And the same way
I know you are a good person,
I can tell you that man
is rotten to the core.
You're just trying
to get me to stay
so you can work at my desk.
Listen to me.
I don't care whether
I work on your desk or not.
You're making a mistake
if you take a job with that man.
Then I guess
I'm making a mistake,
because I already did.
It was nice knowing you, Donna.
So you're keeping her here
after all.
Yeah, I couldn't throw her
off the roof
after you got me to cry.
I'm glad.
Donna, I can't thank you enough
for what you did.
Oh, you're welcome, Louis.
The truth is, I needed this
more than you know.
Well, I get it.
You needed a distraction
after everything
you just went through.
Uh, yeah. Something like that.
Truth is,
I could use a distraction
myself.
Well, there is one thing
that you still need to do.
You need to start thinking
about a new secretary.
Donna, I know
I've asked you this before,
but we're so much closer now
than we were then, and...
Louis, I work for Harvey.
You know
I can't be your secretary.
But we have this bond...
you and I.
Shakespeare, the gun club.
We've always spoken the same
language, and you know it.
Louis, I can't.
I get it.
We're better as friends.
Hey.
How about I set up
a little farewell for Norma
as my last official act
as your interim secretary?
Thank you, Donna.
Are you sure
we've got the right address?
I'm positive.
I'll be right back.
Can I help you?
Uh, yes, is there
a Mary Ann McGrath here?
Who can I say is asking?
We're with Pearson Specter Litt.
We'd like to speak with her
in regards to an ongoing case.
I'm afraid
that won't be possible.
You just said she was here.
I don't understand...
Mary Ann has
advanced Alzheimer's.
But she's 55.
It's early onset, and hers is
particularly aggressive.
I'm sorry.
Can I ask how long
she's been a patient?
We're not supposed to
disclose any...
Please. It's really important.
She was moved her
about a year and a half ago.
And before that?
I don't really know,
but I don't think
she was getting the best care.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
My mother's 55.
You know, and if she's only here
because Forstman pays for it...
I know.
Harvey wants us to find
the person Woodall's close to.
That's all we can do.
Well, "all we can do"
is gonna send her back
to some horrible facility.
- We don't exactly know that.
- Yes, we do.
Rachel, it's terrible.
I don't like it
any more than you do,
but it's not up to us.
I know.
It just sucks.
You goddamn liar.
Oh, don't be mad.
Yeah, Conchita tells everybody
I'm not home.
You know what I'm talking about.
DuPont Investments
dropped through the floor today,
and you sold short
based on something
that I told you in confidence.
I don't recall you telling me
anything at all.
You son of a bitch.
You made over $100 million
on that trade.
Yeah, I did.
Welcome to the real world, pal.
My real world doesn't involve
befriending young attorneys
to get inside information.
Maybe you're not the right man
for me after all.
You think I still want
to work for you after this?
You wanted competition
and money.
You got the competition.
Here's your money.
You can shove that $1 million
up your ass,
because I'm not only
not taking your job,
I'm gonna prosecute you.
Then you might as well
add your name to the indictment
since you've already
shared in the profits.
What are you talking about?
Take a look at this check.
It's not $1 million.
It's 850,000.
Bet you can guess where
the other $150,000 went.
What did you do?
You know what I did.
Marcus had nothing to do
with this.
He wouldn't have had you said
yes right away.
But you didn't.
We're giving you the money back.
You're gonna break
his little heart.
He thinks that money
came from you.
And you snatch cash out
of an addicted gambler's hands,
take away his dream,
only one way that story ends.
So you can either
pout about it...
or you can embrace it and
prove to everyone I was right
when I said I saw
something special in you.
Someday the shoe's gonna be
on the other foot, Charles.
Words spoken by every loser
I've ever met.
See you around, pal.
It's Woodall's first wife.
Her name's Mary Ann.
They grew up together.
They got married
when they were 21
and had it annulled
six months later.
And what's the money for?
- She has Alzheimer's.
- Don't tell me.
He moved her
to a high-end facility
and pays
for round-the-clock care.
And the problem is,
we called the company
that handles the billing, and...
And everything's in cash
up front,
probably paid five years
in advance.
And Mary Ann couldn't tell you
because she doesn't speak.
Which mean we don't have
any proof.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna go get us some proof.
You did this?
Mike and I both did.
Then why isn't he here?
You know why.
Because it was more you
than him.
You did a good job, Rachel.
Shopping, renting videos.
You must be going stir-crazy.
That's all right.
My suspension
is about to expire.
Yeah, I wouldn't count on it.
We found Mary Ann.
I'm told she's doing well
at the new facility...
You know,
the one Forstman's paying for.
You son of a bitch.
I'm not here to exploit
your tragedy, Eric.
I'm here to tell you it's over.
Well, if this were over,
you'd be with Sean Cahill
right now,
which means you're still looking
for me to cut a deal.
I'm looking for you
to turn on Forstman.
You accost me
for the second time
in three days
and throw Mary Ann's name around
like a bargaining chip,
and you think
I'm gonna help you?
Drop dead.
Eric, please.
The reason I knew to look
for someone that you cared about
was that Forstman did
the same thing to me.
He finds your weakness
and presses down
until you don't have
the will to stand up to him.
With you, it was an ex-wife
with Alzheimer's.
With me...
it was a little brother
addicted to gambling.
I don't care.
You don't have proof,
and you're not gonna get it
in the next 24 hours.
You're right. I don't.
But here's the thing.
Cahill may have a deadline,
but I don't,
and I don't care
how long it takes,
because I'm gonna find
that proof
if you don't turn on Forstman.
A lot of you don't know this,
but the truth is, I hated Norma.
I hated her clogs,
her mustache,
her stupid seasonal sweaters.
But the thing
I hated most about her
was her favorite story
about how Abe Vigoda asked her
to marry him in 1975.
I mean, we get it.
You were hot.
You turned him down,
and it was the biggest regret
of your life.
And like everything
you ever said,
I couldn't stand it at the time.
But now that you're gone,
I understand what you meant.
Don't let the moment pass.
Don't let the people you love
walk by you
without letting them know
how you feel about them,
because life slips by,
and then it's over.
And I'm not gonna let
another minute pass me by
without letting you know
how much you mean to me.
I love you, Norma.
Thank you, Louis.
That was a lovely ceremony.
That was beautiful, Louis.
I couldn't have done it
without you.
- Oh, that's not true.
- Yeah, it is.
I couldn't even see how I felt
without you showing me.
And the truth is, Donna,
you know me better
than I know myself.
Like I said, Harvey has no idea
how lucky he is to have you.
♪ ♪
Looking for the money
I supposedly gave Eric Woodall?
You want to save me the trouble
and just admit what you did?
Now, where would be the fun
in that?
Fine. Keep playing your games,
but this time,
you're gonna lose.
Why, because you think
you convinced Woodall
to give me up?
Yeah, he came to see me.
Said you tried to get him
to turn me in.
What I said was,
you're an arrogant bastard
who's spent his life
manipulating people.
And you're the loser who
only cares about competition.
Not my fault you can't beat me.
I can this time.
Oh, I don't think so, pal,
because...
he turns on me, I turn on you.
If you're talking about
12 years ago, let me remind you.
We were both part of that deal.
Yes, we were.
All three of us were...
You, me, and your brother.
You leave my brother
out of this.
Not a chance.
And you don't leave
this Woodall thing alone,
by the time I'm done,
all anybody will know
about 12 years ago
is you gave me a tip
and made sure your little
brother profited from it.
I didn't give you shit.
You tricked me into giving you
inside information
and then blackmailed me
by giving Marcus money
he didn't even know was dirty.
That may be the truth,
but they're never gonna
hear it from me.
I'm afraid they just did.
Hi, Charles.
Sean Cahill. Nice to meet you.
Who the hell are you?
I'm the guy from the SEC
that isn't in your pocket.
I asked Sean to follow Woodall.
Couldn't. No authorization.
But I had no problem
getting authorization
to follow you.
Which is how I knew
when to turn this on.
You're wearing a goddamn wire?
For someone whose favorite movie
is Wall Street,
that's got to be
pretty embarrassing.
Son of a bitch.
You may have gotten the better
of me 12 years ago, Charles,
but this time, you didn't.
So remember what it feels like,
because I know I will.
Harvey, this isn't over.
Words spoken by every loser
I've ever met.
See you around, pal.
Two for two.
He didn't touch my balls.
Black, two sugars,
splash of vanilla.
How do you know
that's how I take my coffee?
The same way I know
you're not taking that job.
You know I'm not taking that job
because I came into work today.
No, Mr. Specter.
I knew you weren't taking
that job
the second you walked away
from me the other night.
I told you I know people better
than they know themselves.
Well, what did you do with Tina?
Oh, I had Big Bertha
reassign her.
- To who?
- Do you really care?
- Not a bit.
- Good.
Here's the deal.
I will take a bullet for you.
And I don't mean that literally.
But what you do for me is,
when I need something,
you give it to me.
It's not just a one-way street.
Will you also do some actual
secretarial work?
Take a look at what I did with
your calendar there, hotshot.
Holy shit.
When'd you get that done?
I told you I'm not like
every other secretary.
I'm Donna.
Then let's get to work.
But for the record, I don't take
vanilla with my coffee.
You will after you taste that.
Oh, my God, this is awesome.
When will they learn?
Perfect timing.
And what are we celebrating?
Our win.
"Our win."
- I like the sound of that.
- Me too.
Where were you?
I'll get into that in a minute.
I want to talk to you
for a second.
What is it?
Rachel, you know I told you
I loved you
from the second I met you.
Well, you loved my pencil skirt.
I loved your face.
♪ ♪
You're the most amazing woman
I have ever met,
and you're not just beautiful,
but you're sweet
and caring and kind
and brilliant and tenacious.
Mike, are...
Are you doing
what I think you're doing?
I called your father today.
And then I went to get
Grammy's ring cleaned.
Oh, my...
I don't want to go 40 years
wondering why I didn't do this
one day sooner.
Rachel Elizabeth Zane...
I love you...
and I always will.
You're my whole life.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
- Yes?
- Yes.
Oh, my God.
All right, here...
Oh.
Oh, my God.
It's beautiful.
She wore it every day
for almost 60 years.
So will I.
What's up, dickhead?
What's up, loser?
Hey, Harvey.
Good to hear from you.
What's going on?
Everything okay?
Yeah, everything's okay.
I just haven't talked to you
in a while
and wanted to see
how you were doing.
I'm great. Katie's good.
The kids are good.
Everything's good.
Great.
That's exactly what
I wanted to hear.
You sure
there's nothing going on?
Nothing.
Like I said, I just haven't
talked to you in a while,
and I miss you.
I miss you too, Harvey, but
unless you got something else,
I've got to go.
The kids are in the bath.
Nothing else.
Love you, Harvey.
I love you too.
- Hey.
Listen, I was thinking about
what you said,
about me pitying you.
And I don't.
Nothing could be further
from the truth.
I think you're one of
the most amazing women
I've ever met,
and just because I don't...
- I'm leaving you, Harvey.
- What?
This isn't working
for me anymore.
Donna, I know
how you're feeling,
but you just went
through something huge,
with being on trial, and, uh...
you need to give it time.
You can't just quit.
I'm not quitting.
I'm going to work for Louis.
Donna.
Donna, please.
I love you, Harvey.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man