Professor Gerard, I came
to ask for a favor.
The answer's no.
Which is why I brought this.
You know.
And you talk a big game,
but you're just as human
as everyone else,
you smug son of a bitch.
Louis.
- What are you doing here?
- Leaving.
That way, I don't have to look
at either one of you two liars.
Oh, my God. He knows.
He doesn't just know.
He's a name partner.
She came to me
and lied to my face.
She did it to protect me.
I'm gonna keep hammering on her
until you break.
With a new name
comes a new beginning.
Here's to our newest
name partner,
Louis Litt.
Louis has something on you.
Daniel Hardman embezzled
money from the firm,
and I covered it up.
Why couldn't you trust me
with this before?
Because I didn't know
how you'd react.
Jessica, your secret
is safe with me.
♪ ♪
I thought we were done
with rooftop conversations.
Some things require privacy.
I haven't heard you say that
since the midnight coup
of Schmidt, Gordon,
and Van Dyke.
You done?
It wasn't a joke.
Well, neither is this.
I told Jeff Malone
I helped cover up
Daniel Hardman's embezzlement.
Why the hell would you
open that time capsule?
Because he knew the explanation
we gave the partners about
Louis was bullshit,
and I had to tell him something.
You could've told him
it was none of his business.
Harvey, I didn't bring you here
to get relationship advice.
I brought you here
to tell you what I did
in case it ever came up.
No, you didn't.
You brought me here because now
you have to get Louis
to back you,
and you knew you'd be mad at me
when I told you what
you didn't want to hear.
You're right.
I don't want to hear it.
How do you think it's gonna go
when I tell Louis he holds
the fate of my relationship
in his hands?
How do you think it's gonna go
the first time Malone
brings up Louis' blackmail?
I don't care.
Well, I'll tell you
how it's gonna go.
Louis is gonna look back
with his beady little eyes
and say, "Embezzlement?"
That's not how I got
my name on the wall."
And the shit's gonna
hit the fan anyway.
You know what?
You can be a real
son of a bitch.
Yeah, but instead
of being pissed at me,
why don't you take
a look in the mirror?
Because we held out
an olive branch,
and after Louis hears this,
he's gonna take that branch
and beat the shit
out of us with it.
Louis.
Professor Gerard?
What are you doing here?
I've got a small legal matter
to attend to.
Well, is it anything
I can help you with?
Actually, I'm here
to speak with Harvey.
Ah, ah, I understand.
You're looking
for a name partner.
Well, you can't quite
see it from here,
but if you walk back
about ten feet,
take a gander to your left,
you'll see I've gotten
a little recognition...
I appreciate that,
but as I said,
I'm here to speak with Harvey.
So are we gonna talk about
that little welcome speech
that Jessica made for Louis?
We don't have to talk about it
because Louis isn't
going to accept it.
Why not?
Because it'll be
a cold day in hell
when he can accept being
Maverick to my Iceman.
Don't... don't you mean
Iceman to your Maverick?
No, I don't.
You actually want to be
Iceman over Maverick?
- Who got the trophy?
- Who's the better pilot?
- The one who got the trophy.
- Wrong.
Because in the end,
Maverick saved Iceman,
and if he hadn't, trophy boy
would be sitting
on the bottom
of the Indian Ocean right now.
- Where he'd still be the man.
- According to you.
According to me is the only
"according to" that matters.
Here we go.
Maybe, but according to me,
Viper was the real hero
of that film.
What?
You think I'm too old
to know Top Gun?
What I think is,
you have no business
being in my office.
Are we gonna do this
in front of your associate?
We don't have to do anything
in front of anybody.
You just have to go.
Harvey...
I need a lawyer.
Louis' office is down the hall.
I don't want Louis.
- I want you.
- That's funny.
The last time you saw me,
you told me I wasn't fit
to practice law
in your ivory tower.
What I told you was,
is that you'll sacrifice
ethics for wins,
and right now
I'm not in my ivory tower,
and I need a win.
I knew it.
You're just like everybody else.
The ends don't justify the means
until it's your ass on the line.
Do you think I like
asking you for help?
I think this Liberty Rail thing
must have you by the balls.
So you know.
I know after their
train derailed,
you were appointed to assess
the victims'
compensation formula,
and I know after you did,
some of those victims
hired a lawyer
and opened an investigation.
Then you also know
they found nothing.
Then the question is,
why are you here?
The TSA found $25,000
in my luggage
the day I announced I was
changing the formula.
So now you're being accused
of accepting a bribe.
Which I did not do.
Well, good luck proving
that, Professor,
because it won't be
with my help.
I was wrong about you,
Mr. Specter.
I never thought that you
wouldn't represent somebody
just because you
didn't like them.
Well, you're wrong again.
I don't like you,
but I'm not representing you
because you did something shady,
and I'm not screwing over
crash victims
for the likes of you.
You know I didn't do this.
What I know is
you showed yourself in.
You can show yourself out.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ Suits 4x12 ♪ Respect Original
Air Date on February 4, 2015
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man.
Hey, I didn't want
to say anything
in front of Gerard,
but has it occurred to you
that you're an idiot
if you don't take this case?
Last year, you were
shitting yourself
he'd find out about you,
and now you think
we should work with him?
No, I wasn't worried
he'd find out.
I was worried about Louis.
Gerard didn't bat
an eye at me back then,
and he didn't just now.
But we get him out of this
and he ever does
find out about me,
he's gonna owe us.
Mike, that man is never
gonna compromise his ethics
just because we got him
out of a jam.
Never gonna compromise
his ethics?
You just said he took a bribe.
So what does that
have to do with anything?
It has everything
to do with everything
because you don't
think he did it.
- So what?
That means you're not
turning him down
because you think he's shady.
You're...
You're turning him down
because you have
a Henry Gerard-sized chip
on your shoulder.
I do not have a chip
on my shoulder.
You sure sound like you do,
which makes you
worse than an idiot.
It makes you a jackass.
- Excuse me?
- You heard me.
You know that he divided
that money fairly,
which means that you're just...
I don't care what it means,
and I don't need
a lecture from you.
Apparently you do,
because you're about
to screw over
a bunch of innocent people
just to stick it to some guy
who hurt your feelings.
That's not something
I ever thought
I'd be saying to you.
Well, look who it is,
the woman who put me
in my place.
What now?
You want me to sign
a piece of paper
admitting that I was the man
on the grassy knoll?
I meant what I said
at the ceremony, Louis.
You mean the ceremony
that you only had
in order to trick me?
I had it because
you demanded it,
but I'm not here
to talk about that.
I'm here to talk
about Jeff Malone.
What about him?
You may be aware
that he and I are...
Fifty Shades of Grey? I'm aware.
I'm gonna let that go
because you may
also not be aware
that I had to lie to him.
He doesn't know
about Mike, does he?
No.
But he does know
you committed a crime
and that you resigned
and now your name
is up on the wall.
What'd you tell him?
I told him you found out
that I covered up
Daniel Hardman's embezzlement
and that you used it
to strong-arm me.
And now you want me to protect
another one of your secrets.
It's the same secret, Louis,
and you have just as much
invested in it as I do.
No, I don't,
because I don't care
if your relationship
with Jeff survives or not.
What do you want, Louis?
I want something for
continuing to cover your ass.
You got something.
You got your name on the wall.
Now I want the respect
that comes with it.
Meaning?
I want one of Harvey's clients.
Which one?
That's between me and Harvey.
♪ ♪
Okay.
I agreed to meet.
I hope it's not just
so you can tell me more
about what a horrible
person I am.
I came here to tell you
that I changed my mind.
So you admitted to yourself
that I didn't do this?
I've admitted to myself
that you came to me
because this case
needs rule-bending,
and you're gonna tell me
why right now.
The money.
Yes, the money.
If you weren't bribed,
where the hell did you
get that $25,000 from?
You know where it came from.
It's the same thing
you tried to use
to blackmail me last year.
Let me get this straight.
You have an explanation
for the money
that would get you
out of this whole thing.
But I can't use it.
Where are you going?
To get you out of this.
Welcome to the real world,
Professor.
♪ ♪
I need you to find out
everything you can
on Garrett Brady.
Absolutely. Who's Garrett Brady?
The guy on the other side
of Gerard's suit.
Wait a second.
Does this mean
you took his case?
You know that means
I took his case,
and I don't want to hear
any gloating.
Gloating? No, no, no, no, no.
I'm not... I'm not gloating.
I'm merely recognizing
the fact that you
completely changed your mind
based entirely on what I said.
- Which is gloating.
- "Po-tay-to," "po-tah-to."
But as long as you're
gonna think of it that way,
I might as well point out
that since you listened
to my lecture,
maybe you should start
calling me Professor.
I'm gonna start
calling you unemployed
if you don't figure out a way
around using Gerard's alibi.
Wait, we can't say where
the money came from?
No, we can't, because
he was playing backroom poker,
and if that comes out,
Harvard fires him.
Are you kidding me?
He's an ethics professor,
and he's breaking the law?
Where the hell do you think
my chip comes from?
Well, if we can't use his alibi,
how are we supposed
to get him out of this?
I don't know, Professor,
but you're the one
who wanted us to take this case,
so why don't you use
that big brain of yours
and find a solution?
You're giving me Henry Gerard.
What?
I saw him. I want him.
You got him. He's mine.
That's not the way
it works, Louis.
I'm afraid you'll have
to find yourself
another boyfriend.
Oh, this is exactly
how it works.
You talked to Jessica,
didn't you?
Sure did, and she used me
to cover her ass,
so I get one
of your clients in return.
You want one of my clients,
we can talk about that,
but Gerard's staying with me.
Oh, please, don't pretend
like you actually care
about him.
He can't even stand you.
Louis, I just offered
to consider giving you
one of my clients,
so I suggest you let Gerard go.
No, I'm not letting anything go,
because it doesn't make
any sense.
Not only can't he stand you.
He doesn't respect you
because he's got things...
What did you just say to me?
I said he doesn't respect you.
Well, you know what?
He definitely
doesn't respect you,
because when he told me
he needed a lawyer,
I tried to send him your way,
and his exact words were,
"I don't want Louis.
I want you."
Fine.
Then I'll just take
another one of your clients.
- You're not taking a thing.
- You just said that I could...
Look, I don't give a shit
what I just said, okay?
My clients are my clients.
And you don't get
out of my office
in the next three seconds,
something's gonna happen
between you and me,
and I guarantee
it won't end with you
keeping all of your teeth.
No.
Just turn around and walk
right back out that door.
- Harvey.
- Did you hear what I said?
I did, but apparently,
you didn't hear
what Jessica said
about wiping the slate clean.
And apparently, you didn't
hear what I said,
because I just told Louis
he could have one of my clients.
And three seconds later,
you told him he couldn't.
Yeah, because I realized
that I'm paying
for Jessica's mistake.
No, Harvey, you were willing
to pay for her mistake
right up until Louis said
Gerard doesn't respect you.
Oh, that has nothing
to do with it.
You can lie to yourself
all you want,
but I'm not gonna
let you bullshit me.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Henry Gerard is the one
person you respect
who never respected you,
and Louis touched that nerve.
And I told you that
has nothing to do with it.
You really think that?
I don't think it. I know it.
Then you know what, Harvey?
You're no different than Louis,
because you have a chance
to help us all move on,
and you are blowing it off
out of pettiness,
which is exactly
what Louis would do.
What do you want from me, Donna?
I want you to be a grown-up
and do what you said you'd do
in the first place.
You got something?
Yeah, we've been
overlooking the obvious.
Yeah, I'm not in the mood
for 20 questions.
Give it to me.
Unless you're traveling
internationally
and don't report it,
carrying cash on board a plane
isn't a crime.
Great, except for the fact
that Gerard's not being
charged with smuggling.
He's being sued.
Right, but my point is,
how did Garrett Brady
even find that out?
Well, he found out
because Gerard
was detained by the TSA.
Who talked to him
for five minutes
and then sent him on his way.
Those searches aren't a matter
of public record.
- Exactly.
- Holy shit.
Brady bribed the TSA.
Which isn't only illegal.
It makes that report
totally inadmissible.
You figured this out
on your own?
Well, I would've done it faster,
but I had to order some sushi.
"Would've done it faster."
That's what you said
your first week here,
except it was pizza
instead of sushi.
Yeah, I'm growing.
You mean Rachel
taught you how to eat.
Like I said, I'm growing.
Hey, Donna, I'm a little
busy at the moment.
Too busy to take on this?
What's that?
Just the first client
that Jessica gave Harvey
when he made name partner.
Harvey said he wouldn't
let me have any of his clients.
No. He said he would.
But then instead
of taking him up on it,
you went ahead
and shit on his feelings.
Please.
Harvey doesn't have feelings.
That's not true,
and you know it.
And you of all people
should know that a person
can overreact when they're hurt.
If you're referring to me,
I do not overreact when...
Okay, whatever you say,
Fatty-Baldy.
Okay, get the hell
out of my office and...
Fine, you have a small,
legitimate point.
I really hurt his feelings?
Yeah, you really did.
But then he realized
he was overreacting
and that this was
a chance for us all
to get back to where we were.
You swear that is
the first client
that Jessica gave him
after me made name partner?
I swear.
Leave me the file.
You two go ahead.
I haven't decided yet.
Actually, we're not here
for the falafel.
We're here to introduce
ourselves.
Mike Ross.
Harvey Specter.
We represent Henry Gerard.
Ah.
Well, in that case,
let me buy you two lunch,
because I'm about to come
into an unexpected windfall.
Well, I guess
that's your thing...
Paying people off.
I hope the TSA got more
than some shitty falafel.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm talking about this.
Oh. Bribery?
Ironic, isn't it?
You suing Professor Gerard
for accepting a bribe
when you're the one
paying off federal employees.
Allegedly paying, Counselor.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
You don't want to slander me.
- So you admit it.
- I don't admit a thing.
Your client sold out victims
of a train derailment.
He's going to pay.
You may not be willing
to admit anything here,
but you'll have to
in front of the judge.
Because I've drafted subpoenas
for every TSA employee
on duty that night.
Drop the case, Mr. Brady.
Are you threatening me?
No, we're informing you.
Well, let me inform you.
In case you forgot,
the TSA falls
under the Department
of Homeland Security,
which makes this
a national security issue.
This has nothing to do
with national security,
and you know it.
All I know is
the government found
a large sum of cash
on a passenger.
Now, how they came to know that,
how they proceeded
to investigate that,
or what they did
with that information
is the government's business.
And that's what
you're going with?
That's not what I'm going with.
That's what they're
going to go with.
So you can call up as many
TSA agents as you like,
but they're not gonna be
saying a thing.
And you can buy
your own damn falafel.
I need Cutie Pie Cosmetics.
You want to try that again?
I have a meeting
with Joan Walsh tonight,
and I need her files.
Joan is Harvey's client.
- Not anymore.
- Since when?
Since it doesn't matter,
because I'm name partner,
which means when I say
I need something,
your response should either be,
"How high?"
or "Can I have another?"
Fine.
There are a few things
that you should know...
You see, what I know is
your boss seems to think
all it takes
to impress Joan Walsh
is getting Donna to make
a fancy dinner reservation,
but I'm going to impress her
with so much legal domination
that by the end of the night,
all she's gonna be able
to say is,
"Harvey Specter who?"
- Okay, that's a mistake...
- A mistake?
Oh, I get it.
You're trying to impress me
with your legal domination
to prove that you're not
just a paralegal
but an associate.
No, Louis. I'm...
See, I don't care
what you call yourself.
So unless you did
such a shitty job,
the files are unreadable,
hand 'em over to me right now.
That's more like it.
What's this?
I know you have to work tonight,
but you also need to eat.
I wouldn't call this
just eating.
Well, you deserve better
than paper plates.
I don't mind paper plates.
Oh, I know you don't.
I just said you deserve better.
Is that ropa vieja?
Hmm.
I made it myself.
Which means you got it
at the Cuban place
that I love on 40th and Lex.
By myself.
What did I do to deserve this?
I don't know.
I'm just...
feeling closer.
Because I confided in you.
Because the walls
are coming down,
and I can feel it.
What did I do to deserve you?
Mm, well, we can talk about that
over this delicious meal
that I made all by myself.
♪ ♪
To us.
And then I said, "Helen",
"that's no Pomeranian.
"That's a Pomimo.
You've been had."
Oh-ho-ho, that is hilarious.
Really, dogs, they are...
They are so fascinating.
Do you have many dogs, Louis?
Hell, no.
Building regulations...
It's a clusterf-f-f...
I've been fighting them
for years.
- Oh, that's horrible.
- Yes.
As is what's going on
with your stock.
Oh, Louis, we're having dinner.
- Put that away.
- No, no, no.
But I just thought you'd
be interested to know
that we could skyrocket
the share price...
Right now what I'm interested in
is having another Manhattan
and hearing what's
on the dessert list.
Oh, you don't need a list.
Get the crème brûlée.
Now, this stock issue, I have...
Fax the papers to my office,
and I'll review them
when I get home.
When you get home?
What the f-f...
What the hell did we come
to dinner for, then?
For this.
What this?
This.
Okay.
I don't know how Harvey handled
these quarterly reviews, but I...
Oh, Harvey...
was magnificent.
Truth be told,
I was a little disappointed
when I heard that
you'd be handling this
instead of him,
but I haven't seen
your cha-cha yet,
so the jury's still out.
- That was a lawyer joke.
- Yep. Got it.
Yep.
Listen, Joan,
I think you're
gonna be really glad
that it was me here tonight,
because I already sent
a letter to your board.
- You did what?
- And I...
I notified them of this.
That's what...
What I'm trying to tell you.
Why the hell
would you do something
so patently stupid?
Stupid?
Hey, I didn't become
name partner being stupid.
Didn't you?
Two members of my board
are about to reach
their term limits.
At least one is being circled
by Glamour Cosmetics.
You have just notified
that person of a product
that I've had in R & D
for years,
and now they can trade
information
for a seat on the board
of my biggest competitor.
Joan, I didn't know...
Tell me, Mr. Litt,
did you actually graduate
from law school,
or did you just buy your way
onto the letterhead?
Yeah, you better put
that bag down,
because we're staying all night.
Didn't go well with Joan,
did it?
No, it didn't, because
you sandbagged me.
I didn't sandbag you.
Well, then what do you call
not telling me
that Glamour was circling
her board members?
I tried to tell you,
but you couldn't hear me
through all of your rage.
What I'm not hearing
is the sound of you
putting your bag down,
because the board members
are meeting tomorrow afternoon,
and I only have until then
to fix this.
And you want me to help you?
You're the associate
on this case, aren't you?
- So now I'm an associate?
- Hey, you know what?
Now is not the time
to get into it.
No, now is exactly the time
to get into it,
because you have taken
every opportunity possible
to make me feel like
I am nothing,
and now, even though
you want something,
you're still treating me
like I'm nothing.
I'm treating you like
every other associate.
That is bullshit,
and you know what?
Even if it were true,
you didn't used to
treat me that way.
I didn't used to know you
lied to me on a daily basis.
Louis, it would serve you right
if I take my bag
and leave you here
and go home to the man
that I love.
So you're not gonna help.
No, I'm gonna help you,
but not because you deserve it.
I'll do it because I am
an associate,
and I am a professional,
which means I am capable
of putting the personal aside
in order to do my job.
And one of those, please.
Just what I was in the mood for.
Ah, you're getting a bagel.
That means you kicked ass.
Which I did.
You called up the TSA,
busted up their
national security defense?
No, I used their defense.
Gerard's gonna testify
under seal
because it's a matter
of national security.
And the judge bought that?
What's not to buy?
The TSA made
the argument for us.
And what did Brady say?
That's the best part about it.
He doesn't even know it.
It's a matter
of national security.
We testify under seal,
the judge realizes that Gerard
is a degenerate gambler...
But a fair mediator.
The case gets dismissed,
and Garrett Brady
and Harvard Law
never know it happened.
You thought of all
of that on your own?
You think you're the only
one who can come up
with an intelligent solution?
You are 1 for 400
in the time
we've worked together.
Okay, smart guy, since
I did your job for you,
you're gonna do my job for me.
You want me to prep Gerard
because you don't
want to sit in a room
and listen to him talk
for two hours.
I didn't want to 15 years ago,
and I don't want to now.
We only get one shot at this,
and his testimony
better be rock solid.
Thanks.
Oh, yeah, sure, help yourself!
Dick.
I see you haven't slept.
I have a lot of work
that needs attending to.
I bet you do, considering
the phone call
I got from Joan Walsh
this morning.
She called you?
She wanted to know what
the other name partners
were going to do about the one
that screwed the pooch.
Oh, come on, that is not fair.
I didn't have all
the information...
You had enough information
to make a deal
to get her from Harvey,
and part of that deal was
you backing me with Jeff.
Oh, so that's why you're here.
You don't trust
I'm still gonna do it?
Because you haven't done it yet,
and you have a history
of making poor decisions
when things aren't
going your way.
The only poor decision
I've made is agreeing
to cover for you
in the first place.
You didn't think that
was such a bad idea
when you were using it
to get what you wanted.
And now you're threatening
to take that thing away.
Louis, you want to keep Joan,
that's on you,
but I held up my end
of the bargain.
You better hold up yours.
I just want to go over it
one more time, Professor.
How much money was in that pot?
I'm tried of going over it.
Why do we have to keep replaying
every moment of this game?
Because your entire case
depends on it.
My case depends on the fact
that I won that money gambling,
not whether I won it
with a flush.
Your case depends on
the judge believing you,
and if he finds any holes
in your testimony, then we...
I gave you the names of
everyone I knew at that game.
But none of those men were
there when you won that money.
I can't help it if I didn't
get the name of the guy I beat.
Which is why your story
needs to be rock solid.
Okay.
Go ahead.
So I ask you again, Professor,
how much money
was in the final pot?
Roughly $12,000.
And you won that hand.
As I said before, I won,
and then I cashed out.
And what did you have again?
A queen-high flush.
And who did you beat?
I told you,
I didn't get his name.
Okay, so what did he have?
Two pair, queens over sixes.
Wait a second.
You said before that
the man next to you
folded with two queens up,
and now this guy has two queens,
and you had a queen-high flush?
I said that the man next to me
folded with two kings.
No, you didn't.
You heard me wrong.
No, I didn't.
Is this part of prepping me,
or are you accusing me
of something?
I'm trying to get
your story to line up.
- My story does line up.
- Not to me, it doesn't.
Look, young man, if you're
gonna sit over there
and call me a liar...
I'm not calling you a liar,
but if you say tomorrow
what you said today,
we're gonna be
in a lot of trouble,
because where I come from,
there are only
four queens in a deck.
I said two kings,
and I'm gonna say that
again tomorrow.
So you do your job,
and I'm gonna do mine.
He's lying.
What are you talking about?
Gerard's story about
winning all that money
playing poker is bullshit.
All right, slow down.
What the hell happened?
I did the math,
and the hands don't add up.
What do you mean
you did the math?
I mean first he said that he
drew a queen on fourth street,
and then when I pressed
him about it, he...
Wait a second.
This conclusion is based
on him recalling hands
under cross-examination?
Harvey, I got kicked out
of Atlantic City
for counting cards.
- I know this shit.
- It doesn't mean he's lying.
I got a little experience
with that too,
and I'm telling you, he was.
- Or maybe he's tired.
- Or maybe I'm right.
Or maybe you don't know what
the hell you're talking about.
- Why are you defending him?
- Because you asked me to.
Look, Harvey,
I'm not saying that
he took a bribe.
I'm just saying that he didn't
get that money playing poker.
Well, unless he admitted that,
he's testifying tomorrow.
Since when do you stick
your head in the sand?
- Did he admit it?
- No, he didn't.
But he screwed up the details,
and he shouldn't have,
because people who are telling
the truth get it right.
And you know it.
What's that?
Jacks full of fours.
I can see that, but why...
Why is it staring you
in the face?
It's what I threw down
the last time I won a huge hand.
It was six weeks ago,
and I can remember every hand
that every player
at that table had.
Now, if you won money
the other night,
you'd remember it too.
I do remember,
and as I explained
to your associate...
Yeah, stop bullshitting me.
Where the hell did that
money really come from?
'Cause if you don't
tell me the truth,
I'm canceling
that hearing right now.
It came...
from a student of mine.
For what?
In exchange
for changing his grade.
Jesus Christ. For $25,000?
He was going to fail my class,
and that would've stopped him
from getting an offer from...
You goddamn hypocrite.
You preach about ethics,
and you do this?
This is about ethics.
And you don't have
any idea why I did it.
I don't care why you did it.
I care about what
you're making me do,
because I am not
suborning perjury.
Well, you tell me that you've
never done anything worse.
I knew it.
You would do it
for someone else...
but not for me.
You know what, Professor?
There's a small part of me
that actually thought
that you came to me because
you thought I'm the best,
but you just think I'll do
whatever it takes to win.
Isn't that what
makes you the best?
Get someone else
to do your dirty work,
because I'm not
suborning perjury.
What are you doing?
Getting my blood flowing.
I've been sitting here
all night,
and restless leg syndrome
kills 14 people every hour.
I don't think that's accurate.
I don't care what you think.
What do you have?
I found a way to fix
things with Joan.
Okay, you're arguing
anything in R & D
is the intellectual property
of the person
who suggested the product?
Until such time that
the results become public.
Which they did the second
I sent the board that letter.
Except board members are subject
to the nondisclosure agreement.
Well, the board members
haven't signed
a nondisclosure agreement.
Yet.
What's to stop them
from refusing?
Nothing, but if they do,
then the noncompete kicks in.
Preventing them from revealing
the contents of my letter
under threat of prosecution.
Specifically
corporate espionage.
Oh, my God.
You got this idea from...
- Our bylaws.
- My bylaws.
Rachel, holy shit, this is...
acceptable.
I think the word you're
looking for is "awesome."
Well, the word I'm saying
is, "Get out",
because I have a meeting
to prepare for."
You know what, Louis?
I have been working all night.
And this gets your ass
out of a major sling,
so instead of dismissing me,
you should be asking me
to come with you.
Excuse me, Miss Professional.
You wanted me to treat you
like every other associate.
- Now I am.
- By acting as if I did nothing?
No, by acknowledging
you did acceptable work.
Letting you come with me
is something
that I would only do for you
if we were friends,
which we are not.
You canceled the hearing.
You were right.
He was lying.
I'm sorry.
You know, I knew
he was a hypocrite
after I found out
about the gambling.
I never thought
he'd sell out Harvard.
What are you talking about?
He did take the bribe,
but it had nothing to do
with the accident victims.
He did it to change
someone's grade.
Why would he do that?
What difference does it make?
Either way, he was gonna
let me suborn perjury.
It makes a difference because
we still have to win this case.
Oh, I don't give a shit
about winning this case.
I've never heard you say
anything like that before.
You... you care
about winning every case,
every game, every argument.
Did you hear me?
He was gonna let me
suborn perjury.
And so would
every client you have
if they thought
they'd get away with it.
He's not every client.
No, he's the one you hated
in the first place.
- I didn't hate him.
- Harvey, what is going on here?
I thought he was better than us.
I sat in that class
and listened to him talk
about what kind
of lawyers we should be,
and I always let him down
because I knew
that wasn't the kind
of lawyer that wins.
And I wanted to win.
So I'd argue with him,
and he'd look down on me.
And now instead of you
letting him down,
he let you down.
He turned out to be
no better than any of us.
So then let's make him
better than us.
Miss Walsh.
You are not on my schedule
today.
Ah, ah, Miss Walsh,
please take a look at this.
What is it?
It's a chance
to make things right.
Ha.
You cannot call
board members employees
based on them having access
to an expense account.
Not just an expense account.
They have corporate cards
and standing offices,
which, as defined
by section 14.2
of the Internal Revenue Code,
makes them employees.
Well, Mr. Litt,
seems I won't be demanding
a new point person after all.
I'm glad to hear that.
Are you?
Of course I am.
You're my first client
as name partner.
You're very important to me.
Well, I suppose
we'll find out the truth
when someone else
makes name partner.
What are you talking about?
I'm not an idiot.
I know that no one in your firm
wants to deal with me.
That's not true.
In fact, I fought for you.
You may have thought
you were fighting for me,
but I know that Jessica
dumped me on Harvey,
and it seems that the second
you made name partner,
Harvey did the same thing
to you.
Oh, you didn't know that,
did you?
Then maybe we were
meant for each other,
since we're both
left out of the club.
You betrayed me.
You make this big speech
about repairing our friendship,
and all it was was more words.
What are you talking about?
You convinced me to take Joan,
while conveniently
leaving out the fact
you're doing Harvey a favor.
That's not why I did it, Louis.
Well, just tell me right now,
can he stand her?
No, but he was gonna keep her
because you...
Hurt his precious feelings.
I know.
I felt so awful about that.
You know what, Louis?
You should.
And while you're at it,
you should feel pretty awful
about being a dick to me
right now.
You lied to me again.
No, Louis.
I fought for you... again.
No.
You made Joan sound important.
"The first client
that Jessica gave Harvey
when he made name partner."
She is important, Louis,
but you can't see that
because you didn't
want a client.
You just wanted to take
something away from Harvey.
What I want is respect.
Then get out of your own way
and get on the goddamn team.
You mean the team that kept
Mike's secret from me?
No, Louis!
I mean the team that
protected its own,
because that's what teams do.
And, you know, I shouldn't
even be telling you this
because she wasn't going to,
but if you need
a little bit more evidence
of what we do for each other,
then take a look at Rachel,
because she got Katrina a job.
- What?
- That's right.
Your former associate,
and you've been treating
Rachel like shit.
So, if you're done
yelling at me,
then I suggest you go fix
one of the thousand things
that you have screwed up lately,
because the rest of us,
we are done fighting for you.
Mr. Ross.
Ah, you must be Ian.
And, please,
don't call me Mr. Ross.
- Mike is fine.
- Ah, sure.
Hey, thanks for your call, Mike.
Pearson Specter is a great firm.
Ah, well, you're
a great candidate.
I'm a little curious why
you're still interviewing.
I heard you had
a solid offer at Skadden.
I do, but Skadden Arps
is no Pearson Specter.
Are you sure it's not
because you're worried
they'll find out that you failed.
Professor Gerard's
legal ethics class?
- What?
- Oh, shit.
You don't know.
He hasn't changed your grade,
but he still has your $25,000.
Who the hell are you?
I'm exactly who I said I was.
The only thing I left out
is that Professor Gerard
is my client.
Well, he can't be
in trouble for this.
I'd know.
He's not.
He's being accused
of accepting a bribe
while conducting
a federal mediation
because of this.
That's not my problem.
It's your problem now,
which is why you're
gonna sign this.
What is that?
It's a sworn affidavit
stating the money that
you paid Gerard is a loan.
Well, what happens to my grade?
It stays the same
because Henry Gerard
doesn't take money
to change grades.
That's bullshit. We had a deal.
Yeah, well, consider this your
first lesson in the real world.
Deals change.
I don't care what world it is.
I'm not signing anything.
That's too bad,
because the truth will come out.
And this way,
you're failing a class
instead of getting thrown
out of school
for bribing a professor.
It's up to you, Ian.
You want an F,
or do you want to not have
a legal career at all?
So I sign this, and the
bribery allegations are gone?
And no one ever knows a thing.
But I still have to pay
Ian back the money.
That's the way loans work.
You say that like
I am a monster.
I say it like it's true.
You know...
you never let me tell you
what the money was for.
You didn't listen to me
when I told you I don't care.
Who's the monster now?
I don't care
because you always said
the circumstances don't matter.
Well, do you care
that after Mike grilled me,
I was so impressed with him
that I wonder why
I'd forgotten him.
So I looked through
my old records,
just to see how he did,
but I couldn't find
any record of him
ever being in my class.
Just like they're not
gonna find any record
of you accepting a bribe
from a student.
You saying we're even?
I'm saying you got
a two-for-one,
because they're also
not gonna find any record
of you gambling last year.
That's why you came to see me
back then, isn't it?
You didn't want anyone
to find out about him.
I'm not gonna tell you
why I came
to see you last year, Henry,
because the circumstances
don't matter.
You really did pay
attention in my class.
A lot more than you think.
I'm sorry I let you down,
Mr. Specter.
Professor...
Don't worry about
paying back that loan.
I got it.
♪ ♪
Louis...
what can I do for you?
The question isn't what
you can do for me, Jeff,
but it's a matter
of what you're gonna do,
which is cut the bullshit
right now.
- What?
- You heard me.
I know Jessica told you
about Hardman.
Yeah, she did tell me,
and I have refrained
from coming to see you
about blackmailing her
out of courtesy.
Courtesy?
You haven't so much as
wished me a congratulations.
You want me to kiss
the ring, Louis,
after what you did?
You're damn right I do,
because I don't care
how it got up there.
My name is on that wall.
And if I had a crowbar handy...
I would pry it off.
Well, Jeff, you don't.
So the question you got
to ask yourself is,
"Do you want to stick
with the team?"
Because my name
is up there to stay
whether you like it or not.
♪ ♪
Hey.
Thanks for meeting me.
What's going on?
I wanted to thank you
for making me take Gerard.
What happened?
What makes you think
something happened?
Because I know you,
and I know you don't have
moments of self-reflection,
let alone have a drink
with someone
to tell them about it
unless something happened.
You know what?
Something did happen.
I dealt with some shit,
and I'm trying
to thank you for it
because it turned out
to be a good thing.
I think the word you're
looking for is "closure."
That's your word.
The word I'm looking for is,
"You're welcome, Harvey.
That's nice of you to say."
Thanks, Harvey.
Good.
Now listen to me.
For a minute there, I thought
you were gonna tell me
that he knows.
What?
Maybe I'm crazy,
but when I was prepping him,
for a second, he looked at me,
and I thought,
"He's suspicious."
And then you called,
and after everything
that's happened already, I...
It's fine, Mike.
He doesn't know.
♪ ♪